{
    "name": "JPDB 50K",
    "cards": [
  {
    "question": "贖い",
    "answer": "あがない",
    "meaning": "atonement, redemption, compensation"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄り目",
    "answer": "よりめ",
    "meaning": "crossed eyes, convergent strabismus"
  },
  {
    "question": "補塡",
    "answer": "ほてん",
    "meaning": "compensating, making up for, supplementation"
  },
  {
    "question": "抜糸",
    "answer": "ばっし",
    "meaning": "removal of stitches, removal of sutures"
  },
  {
    "question": "拍子木",
    "answer": "ひょうしぎ",
    "meaning": "wooden clappers"
  },
  {
    "question": "偶像崇拝",
    "answer": "ぐうぞうすうはい",
    "meaning": "idolatry, idol worship"
  },
  {
    "question": "捥ぐ",
    "answer": "もぐ",
    "meaning": "to pluck (usually from a tree), to pick (e.g. apples)"
  },
  {
    "question": "慕わしい",
    "answer": "したわしい",
    "meaning": "dear, beloved"
  },
  {
    "question": "後足",
    "answer": "あとあし",
    "meaning": "hind legs, rear legs"
  },
  {
    "question": "不審火",
    "answer": "ふしんび",
    "meaning": "fire under suspicious circumstances, arson"
  },
  {
    "question": "兄弟弟子",
    "answer": "きょうだいでし",
    "meaning": "fellow pupil (apprentice)"
  },
  {
    "question": "同一性",
    "answer": "どういつせい",
    "meaning": "identity"
  },
  {
    "question": "乱撃",
    "answer": "らんげき",
    "meaning": "random shooting"
  },
  {
    "question": "映写",
    "answer": "えいしゃ",
    "meaning": "projection"
  },
  {
    "question": "平らか",
    "answer": "たいらか",
    "meaning": "level, just, peaceful"
  },
  {
    "question": "価",
    "answer": "あたい,か",
    "meaning": "price, cost, value, worth, merit, valence, valency"
  },
  {
    "question": "灌漑",
    "answer": "かんがい",
    "meaning": "irrigation"
  },
  {
    "question": "二輪車",
    "answer": "にりんしゃ",
    "meaning": "two-wheeled vehicle (bicycle, motorcycle, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "配置転換",
    "answer": "はいちてんかん",
    "meaning": "reshuffling, job rotation"
  },
  {
    "question": "自然的",
    "answer": "しぜんてき",
    "meaning": "natural"
  },
  {
    "question": "巷間",
    "answer": "こうかん",
    "meaning": "on the street, around town, the world, the public"
  },
  {
    "question": "急拵え",
    "answer": "きゅうごしらえ",
    "meaning": "hastily made, improvised preparation"
  },
  {
    "question": "合算",
    "answer": "がっさん",
    "meaning": "adding up, totalling, totaling"
  },
  {
    "question": "立方",
    "answer": "たちかた,りっぽう",
    "meaning": "way of standing, dancer (in a Japanese dance performance), cube"
  },
  {
    "question": "飾り切り",
    "answer": "かざりぎり",
    "meaning": "cutting ingredients into decorative shapes (e.g. vegetables)"
  },
  {
    "question": "航空写真",
    "answer": "こうくうしゃしん",
    "meaning": "aerial photograph"
  },
  {
    "question": "滾々",
    "answer": "こんこん",
    "meaning": "copious (flowing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "枠外",
    "answer": "わくがい",
    "meaning": "(beyond the) limits, scope, boundary"
  },
  {
    "question": "過渡期",
    "answer": "かとき",
    "meaning": "transition period"
  },
  {
    "question": "手向かう",
    "answer": "てむかう",
    "meaning": "to resist"
  },
  {
    "question": "文明開化",
    "answer": "ぶんめいかいか",
    "meaning": "civilization and enlightenment, Japan's Westernization movement during the Meiji era (Westernisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑費",
    "answer": "ざっぴ",
    "meaning": "miscellaneous expenses"
  },
  {
    "question": "俗世間",
    "answer": "ぞくせけん",
    "meaning": "this world, earthly world, secular society, ordinary world, everyday life, workaday world"
  },
  {
    "question": "乱高下",
    "answer": "らんこうげ",
    "meaning": "violent fluctuation"
  },
  {
    "question": "弛み",
    "answer": "ゆるみ,たるみ,たゆみ",
    "meaning": "slack, looseness, play, slackening, sagginess, flabbiness (skin, etc.), dullness, letdown, depressio"
  },
  {
    "question": "良妻賢母",
    "answer": "りょうさいけんぼ",
    "meaning": "good wife and wise mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "盤台",
    "answer": "ばんだい",
    "meaning": "oval tub or tray used in fish shops"
  },
  {
    "question": "箏",
    "answer": "こと,そう",
    "meaning": "koto (13-stringed Japanese zither), stringed instrument, zheng (Chinese zither), guzheng"
  },
  {
    "question": "後漢",
    "answer": "ごかん,こうかん",
    "meaning": "Later Han dynasty (China, 25-220 CE), Eastern Han dynasty, Later Han dynasty (China, 947-950 CE)"
  },
  {
    "question": "教派",
    "answer": "きょうは",
    "meaning": "sect, denomination"
  },
  {
    "question": "泰山",
    "answer": "たいざん",
    "meaning": "large mountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "大僧正",
    "answer": "だいそうじょう",
    "meaning": "high priest"
  },
  {
    "question": "薬研",
    "answer": "やげん",
    "meaning": "druggist's mortar"
  },
  {
    "question": "潜望鏡",
    "answer": "せんぼうきょう",
    "meaning": "periscope"
  },
  {
    "question": "出羽",
    "answer": "でわ,いでわ",
    "meaning": "Dewa (former province located in present-day Yamagata and Akita prefectures)"
  },
  {
    "question": "美感",
    "answer": "びかん",
    "meaning": "sense of beauty, aesthetic sense"
  },
  {
    "question": "目白",
    "answer": "めじろ",
    "meaning": "white-eye family of birds (Zosteropidae), Japanese white-eye (Zosterops japonicus)"
  },
  {
    "question": "元号",
    "answer": "げんごう",
    "meaning": "name of an imperial era (e.g. Heisei, Shōwa), Japanese era name"
  },
  {
    "question": "潰滅",
    "answer": "かいめつ",
    "meaning": "destruction, annihilation, devastation, catastrophe"
  },
  {
    "question": "歯科",
    "answer": "しか",
    "meaning": "dentistry"
  },
  {
    "question": "滋賀",
    "answer": "しが",
    "meaning": "Shiga (prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "伝言板",
    "answer": "でんごんばん",
    "meaning": "message board"
  },
  {
    "question": "画板",
    "answer": "がばん",
    "meaning": "drawing board, drafting board"
  },
  {
    "question": "組曲",
    "answer": "くみきょく",
    "meaning": "suite"
  },
  {
    "question": "比翼",
    "answer": "ひよく",
    "meaning": "wings abreast, single garment made to look double"
  },
  {
    "question": "御願い",
    "answer": "おねがい",
    "meaning": "request, favour (to ask), wish, please"
  },
  {
    "question": "遺構",
    "answer": "いこう",
    "meaning": "(archaeological) remains, remnants (of ancient structures), ancient foundation"
  },
  {
    "question": "専業主夫",
    "answer": "せんぎょうしゅふ",
    "meaning": "full-time househusband, stay-at-home dad"
  },
  {
    "question": "火攻め",
    "answer": "ひぜめ",
    "meaning": "attacking with fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "振動数",
    "answer": "しんどうすう",
    "meaning": "frequency"
  },
  {
    "question": "分娩",
    "answer": "ぶんべん",
    "meaning": "childbirth, delivery, confinement"
  },
  {
    "question": "詩作",
    "answer": "しさく",
    "meaning": "composition of a poem"
  },
  {
    "question": "城跡",
    "answer": "しろあと,じょうせき,じょうし",
    "meaning": "castle site, ruins of a castle"
  },
  {
    "question": "衆愚",
    "answer": "しゅうぐ",
    "meaning": "the vulgar masses"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍役",
    "answer": "ぐんえき,ぐんやく",
    "meaning": "military service"
  },
  {
    "question": "策動",
    "answer": "さくどう",
    "meaning": "maneuvers, manoeuvers, machinations, scheming"
  },
  {
    "question": "人間国宝",
    "answer": "にんげんこくほう",
    "meaning": "living national treasure"
  },
  {
    "question": "察",
    "answer": "さつ",
    "meaning": "cops, police"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿り",
    "answer": "やどり",
    "meaning": "lodging, abode, shelter"
  },
  {
    "question": "濁音",
    "answer": "だくおん",
    "meaning": "voiced consonant in Japanese"
  },
  {
    "question": "不妊",
    "answer": "ふにん",
    "meaning": "infertility, sterility, barrenness"
  },
  {
    "question": "綿花",
    "answer": "めんか",
    "meaning": "raw cotton, cotton wool"
  },
  {
    "question": "名も無い",
    "answer": "なもない",
    "meaning": "unknown, obscure, insignificant"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗君",
    "answer": "あんくん",
    "meaning": "foolish ruler"
  },
  {
    "question": "営々",
    "answer": "えいえい",
    "meaning": "hard, unceasing"
  },
  {
    "question": "品出し",
    "answer": "しなだし",
    "meaning": "stocking shelves, stock person, stocking person"
  },
  {
    "question": "金型",
    "answer": "かながた,かねがた",
    "meaning": "die, (metal) mold, mould"
  },
  {
    "question": "急使",
    "answer": "きゅうし",
    "meaning": "express messenger"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓄財",
    "answer": "ちくざい",
    "meaning": "amassing of wealth"
  },
  {
    "question": "派出所",
    "answer": "はしゅつじょ,はしゅつしょ",
    "meaning": "branch office, police box, local police station"
  },
  {
    "question": "精神医学",
    "answer": "せいしんいがく",
    "meaning": "psychiatry"
  },
  {
    "question": "夕涼み",
    "answer": "ゆうすずみ",
    "meaning": "evening cool, cool of the evening"
  },
  {
    "question": "積分",
    "answer": "せきぶん",
    "meaning": "integration, integral"
  },
  {
    "question": "航空券",
    "answer": "こうくうけん",
    "meaning": "airline ticket, plane ticket, air ticket"
  },
  {
    "question": "基礎研究",
    "answer": "きそけんきゅう",
    "meaning": "basic research"
  },
  {
    "question": "飲み友達",
    "answer": "のみともだち",
    "meaning": "drinking buddy"
  },
  {
    "question": "掘り抜く",
    "answer": "ほりぬく",
    "meaning": "to dig through, to drill into, to excavate"
  },
  {
    "question": "経年",
    "answer": "けいねん",
    "meaning": "passing of years, lapse of time, aging, ageing"
  },
  {
    "question": "住所録",
    "answer": "じゅうしょろく",
    "meaning": "address book, list of addresses, mailing list"
  },
  {
    "question": "口語",
    "answer": "こうご",
    "meaning": "spoken language, colloquial speech, (modern) spoken Japanese, written style based on (modern) spoken"
  },
  {
    "question": "少年法",
    "answer": "しょうねんほう",
    "meaning": "Juvenile Act"
  },
  {
    "question": "互換性",
    "answer": "ごかんせい",
    "meaning": "compatibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "守秘",
    "answer": "しゅひ",
    "meaning": "keeping a secret, secrecy, confidentiality"
  },
  {
    "question": "締り",
    "answer": "しまり",
    "meaning": "closing, shutting, firmness, tightness, discipline, control"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄明り",
    "answer": "うすあかり",
    "meaning": "dim light, faint light, half-light of early morning, twilight"
  },
  {
    "question": "遇う",
    "answer": "あしらう,あう",
    "meaning": "to treat, to handle, to deal with, to arrange, to decorate, to dress, to garnish, to meet, to encoun"
  },
  {
    "question": "坐する",
    "answer": "ざする",
    "meaning": "to sit, to squat, to be implicated"
  },
  {
    "question": "芝刈り",
    "answer": "しばかり",
    "meaning": "lawn mowing"
  },
  {
    "question": "燻り出す",
    "answer": "いぶりだす",
    "meaning": "to smoke animal out of its den"
  },
  {
    "question": "出入国",
    "answer": "しゅつにゅうこく",
    "meaning": "emigration and immigration"
  },
  {
    "question": "海抜",
    "answer": "かいばつ",
    "meaning": "height above sea level"
  },
  {
    "question": "二元論",
    "answer": "にげんろん",
    "meaning": "dualism"
  },
  {
    "question": "因業",
    "answer": "いんごう",
    "meaning": "heartless, cruel, causes and actions, results of actions in previous life"
  },
  {
    "question": "国際条約",
    "answer": "こくさいじょうやく",
    "meaning": "international treaty"
  },
  {
    "question": "防水加工",
    "answer": "ぼうすいかこう",
    "meaning": "waterproof finish"
  },
  {
    "question": "汗水",
    "answer": "あせみず",
    "meaning": "profuse sweat"
  },
  {
    "question": "毛並",
    "answer": "けなみ",
    "meaning": "coat (of hair or fur), lie of (dog's) hair, type, sort, lineage, breeding"
  },
  {
    "question": "口火",
    "answer": "くちび",
    "meaning": "fuse, pilot light, cause (of a war, argument, revolt, etc.), origin, trigger"
  },
  {
    "question": "当て推量",
    "answer": "あてずいりょう",
    "meaning": "conjecture, guesswork"
  },
  {
    "question": "湧かす",
    "answer": "わかす",
    "meaning": "to breed (e.g. maggots), to let breed"
  },
  {
    "question": "揚州",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "町会",
    "answer": "ちょうかい",
    "meaning": "town council"
  },
  {
    "question": "縦坑",
    "answer": "たてこう",
    "meaning": "shaft (e.g. in a mine), pit"
  },
  {
    "question": "霊場",
    "answer": "れいじょう",
    "meaning": "sacred ground"
  },
  {
    "question": "虫籠",
    "answer": "むしかご",
    "meaning": "insect cage"
  },
  {
    "question": "随員",
    "answer": "ずいいん",
    "meaning": "member of an entourage or retinue or party, attendant"
  },
  {
    "question": "賊徒",
    "answer": "ぞくと",
    "meaning": "rebels, bandit, robber, traitors"
  },
  {
    "question": "検査官",
    "answer": "けんさかん,けんしょうかん",
    "meaning": "inspector, examiner, auditor"
  },
  {
    "question": "独語",
    "answer": "どくご",
    "meaning": "monologue, soliloquy, German (language)"
  },
  {
    "question": "革帯",
    "answer": "かわおび",
    "meaning": "leather belt"
  },
  {
    "question": "外地",
    "answer": "がいち",
    "meaning": "overseas territories, outlying areas"
  },
  {
    "question": "禁酒法",
    "answer": "きんしゅほう",
    "meaning": "Prohibition Law"
  },
  {
    "question": "複座",
    "answer": "ふくざ",
    "meaning": "two-seater (e.g. aircraft)"
  },
  {
    "question": "血刀",
    "answer": "ちがたな",
    "meaning": "bloody sword (blade)"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀灰色",
    "answer": "ぎんかいしょく",
    "meaning": "silver gray, silver grey"
  },
  {
    "question": "芥川賞",
    "answer": "あくたがわしょう",
    "meaning": "Akutagawa Prize (literary award)"
  },
  {
    "question": "永世",
    "answer": "えいせい",
    "meaning": "eternity, perpetuity, immortality, permanence"
  },
  {
    "question": "身代り",
    "answer": "みがわり",
    "meaning": "substitution (for someone else), substitute, stand-in, scapegoat, sacrifice"
  },
  {
    "question": "人声",
    "answer": "ひとごえ",
    "meaning": "human voice, cry"
  },
  {
    "question": "自発",
    "answer": "じはつ",
    "meaning": "spontaneity, spontaneous passive"
  },
  {
    "question": "某月",
    "answer": "ぼうげつ",
    "meaning": "a certain month"
  },
  {
    "question": "岩手",
    "answer": "いわて",
    "meaning": "Iwate (prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "四重奏",
    "answer": "しじゅうそう",
    "meaning": "instrumental quartet"
  },
  {
    "question": "失陥",
    "answer": "しっかん",
    "meaning": "surrender, fall"
  },
  {
    "question": "頽廃",
    "answer": "たいはい",
    "meaning": "degeneration, decadence, deterioration, laxness, corruption"
  },
  {
    "question": "妖怪変化",
    "answer": "ようかいへんげ",
    "meaning": "(animal making a) monstrous apparition"
  },
  {
    "question": "巧者",
    "answer": "こうしゃ",
    "meaning": "cleverness, skill, tact, clever person (in a particular field), skillful person (skilful)"
  },
  {
    "question": "只々",
    "answer": "ただただ",
    "meaning": "absolutely, only"
  },
  {
    "question": "打率",
    "answer": "だりつ",
    "meaning": "batting average"
  },
  {
    "question": "板塀",
    "answer": "いたべい",
    "meaning": "wooden fence, board fence"
  },
  {
    "question": "汚臭",
    "answer": "おしゅう",
    "meaning": "foul smell"
  },
  {
    "question": "打鍵",
    "answer": "だけん",
    "meaning": "keystroke"
  },
  {
    "question": "縫い取り",
    "answer": "ぬいとり",
    "meaning": "embroidery"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓑",
    "answer": "みの",
    "meaning": "straw raincoat"
  },
  {
    "question": "麒麟児",
    "answer": "きりんじ",
    "meaning": "child prodigy, wonder child"
  },
  {
    "question": "動議",
    "answer": "どうぎ",
    "meaning": "motion (i.e. proposal to a committee, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "気抜け",
    "answer": "きぬけ",
    "meaning": "dispiritedness, dejection, languor, lethargy, apathy, becoming flat (e.g. beer, carbonated drinks),"
  },
  {
    "question": "天日",
    "answer": "てんぴ,てんじつ",
    "meaning": "the sun, sunlight, heat of the sun"
  },
  {
    "question": "受取",
    "answer": "うけとり",
    "meaning": "receiving, receipt"
  },
  {
    "question": "熱傷",
    "answer": "ねっしょう",
    "meaning": "burn"
  },
  {
    "question": "体側",
    "answer": "たいそく",
    "meaning": "side of a body"
  },
  {
    "question": "御無沙汰",
    "answer": "ごぶさた",
    "meaning": "not writing or contacting for a while, neglecting (failing) to write (call, visit, etc.), long silen"
  },
  {
    "question": "御破算",
    "answer": "ごはさん,ごわさん",
    "meaning": "starting afresh, going back to square one, abandoning (e.g. a plan), calling off, clearing an abacus"
  },
  {
    "question": "注意報",
    "answer": "ちゅういほう",
    "meaning": "warning (e.g. for a storm), advisory"
  },
  {
    "question": "尊崇",
    "answer": "そんすう",
    "meaning": "reverence, veneration"
  },
  {
    "question": "議決",
    "answer": "ぎけつ",
    "meaning": "resolution, decision, vote"
  },
  {
    "question": "挙る",
    "answer": "こぞる",
    "meaning": "to assemble everything together, to do something as a group"
  },
  {
    "question": "第三国",
    "answer": "だいさんごく",
    "meaning": "a third country"
  },
  {
    "question": "粛然",
    "answer": "しゅくぜん",
    "meaning": "silent, quiet, solemn, softly, quietly, solemnly"
  },
  {
    "question": "海鳴り",
    "answer": "うみなり",
    "meaning": "oceanic noise, rumbling of the sea, mistpouffer"
  },
  {
    "question": "乞い",
    "answer": "こい",
    "meaning": "request, entreaty"
  },
  {
    "question": "序文",
    "answer": "じょぶん",
    "meaning": "preface, foreword, introduction"
  },
  {
    "question": "問題意識",
    "answer": "もんだいいしき",
    "meaning": "awareness of the issues, (having a) critical mind, concerns"
  },
  {
    "question": "微分",
    "answer": "びぶん",
    "meaning": "differentiation, differential, derivative"
  },
  {
    "question": "差支える",
    "answer": "さしつかえる",
    "meaning": "to interfere (with), to hinder, to be hindered (from doing), to become impeded, to have difficulty,"
  },
  {
    "question": "辛党",
    "answer": "からとう",
    "meaning": "drinker, person fond of alcohol (as opposed to sweets), person fond of spicy food"
  },
  {
    "question": "逆用",
    "answer": "ぎゃくよう",
    "meaning": "abuse, misuse, taking advantage of"
  },
  {
    "question": "水煙",
    "answer": "みずけむり,すいえん",
    "meaning": "mist over a body of water, spray, suien, four decorative metal plates joined at right angles forming"
  },
  {
    "question": "腱鞘炎",
    "answer": "けんしょうえん",
    "meaning": "inflammation of a tendon (sheath), tendonitis, tendinitis, tenosynovitis, tenovaginitis, tendovagini"
  },
  {
    "question": "心得違い",
    "answer": "こころえちがい",
    "meaning": "imprudence, misbehavior, misbehaviour, misunderstanding"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄焼き",
    "answer": "うすやき",
    "meaning": "frying or baking something thin (e.g. thin omelette)"
  },
  {
    "question": "埋蔵",
    "answer": "まいぞう",
    "meaning": "burying in the ground, having underground deposits"
  },
  {
    "question": "芥子粒",
    "answer": "けしつぶ",
    "meaning": "poppy seed, pinhead-like, small as ants"
  },
  {
    "question": "青年期",
    "answer": "せいねんき",
    "meaning": "adolescence"
  },
  {
    "question": "半ギレ",
    "answer": "はんギレ",
    "meaning": "looking furious, looking like one's about to blow their top"
  },
  {
    "question": "代休",
    "answer": "だいきゅう",
    "meaning": "compensatory holiday (for working on a day off), time in lieu"
  },
  {
    "question": "空き室",
    "answer": "あきしつ",
    "meaning": "vacant or unoccupied room"
  },
  {
    "question": "三つ折り",
    "answer": "みつおり",
    "meaning": "threefold, folded in three"
  },
  {
    "question": "悋気",
    "answer": "りんき",
    "meaning": "jealousy"
  },
  {
    "question": "肝を潰す",
    "answer": "きもをつぶす",
    "meaning": "to be frightened out of one's wits, to be amazed, to be astounded, to be stunned"
  },
  {
    "question": "船便",
    "answer": "ふなびん,せんびん",
    "meaning": "surface mail (ship), sea mail, ferry service, steamer service"
  },
  {
    "question": "優れ物",
    "answer": "すぐれもの",
    "meaning": "exceptional item, extraordinary product"
  },
  {
    "question": "義理人情",
    "answer": "ぎりにんじょう",
    "meaning": "duty and humanity, (a sense of) moral obligation and humane feelings"
  },
  {
    "question": "四角四面",
    "answer": "しかくしめん",
    "meaning": "square, formal, prim, stuffy"
  },
  {
    "question": "里心",
    "answer": "さとごころ",
    "meaning": "homesickness, nostalgia"
  },
  {
    "question": "総立ち",
    "answer": "そうだち",
    "meaning": "standing in a group, standing up in unison"
  },
  {
    "question": "煮崩れ",
    "answer": "にくずれ",
    "meaning": "falling apart while cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "陰気臭い",
    "answer": "いんきくさい",
    "meaning": "dismal, gloomy"
  },
  {
    "question": "油っこい",
    "answer": "あぶらっこい",
    "meaning": "greasy, fatty, oily"
  },
  {
    "question": "笑い物",
    "answer": "わらいもの",
    "meaning": "laughingstock, butt of ridicule"
  },
  {
    "question": "心血",
    "answer": "しんけつ",
    "meaning": "heart and soul, all one's heart, putting all one's energy into something"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾日",
    "answer": "いくにち,いくか",
    "meaning": "(for) how many days, what day (of the month)"
  },
  {
    "question": "尚早",
    "answer": "しょうそう",
    "meaning": "prematurity"
  },
  {
    "question": "画数",
    "answer": "かくすう",
    "meaning": "stroke count"
  },
  {
    "question": "一汗",
    "answer": "ひとあせ",
    "meaning": "doing a job, riding and sweating up a horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "自筆",
    "answer": "じひつ",
    "meaning": "one's own handwriting, autograph, holograph"
  },
  {
    "question": "花盛り",
    "answer": "はなざかり",
    "meaning": "flowers in full bloom, time of year in which flowers are in full bloom, the age at which someone (es"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒙古",
    "answer": "もうこ",
    "meaning": "Mongolia"
  },
  {
    "question": "古河",
    "answer": "ふるかわ",
    "meaning": "old river"
  },
  {
    "question": "早瀬",
    "answer": "はやせ",
    "meaning": "swift current, rapids"
  },
  {
    "question": "聖櫃",
    "answer": "せいひつ",
    "meaning": "Ark of the Covenant (Judaism), tabernacle (Catholicism)"
  },
  {
    "question": "親征",
    "answer": "しんせい",
    "meaning": "military expedition led in person by the emperor"
  },
  {
    "question": "重砲",
    "answer": "じゅうほう",
    "meaning": "heavy artillery"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗物",
    "answer": "のりもの",
    "meaning": "vehicle, conveyance, transport, ride (playground, fair, carnival), playground facility"
  },
  {
    "question": "天下布武",
    "answer": "てんかふぶ",
    "meaning": "unify the nation by force, spread military force under the heavens"
  },
  {
    "question": "督促",
    "answer": "とくそく",
    "meaning": "urge, demand, importunity"
  },
  {
    "question": "誓願",
    "answer": "せいがん",
    "meaning": "(religious) vow, prayer (for something by making a vow)"
  },
  {
    "question": "手代",
    "answer": "てだい",
    "meaning": "sales clerk"
  },
  {
    "question": "横町",
    "answer": "よこちょう",
    "meaning": "bystreet, side street, back street, alley, lane"
  },
  {
    "question": "屈曲",
    "answer": "くっきょく",
    "meaning": "crookedness, bending, indentation, curvature, flexion"
  },
  {
    "question": "北極海",
    "answer": "ほっきょくかい",
    "meaning": "Arctic Ocean"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼き鏝",
    "answer": "やきごて",
    "meaning": "soldering iron, hot iron, brand, mark, stigma"
  },
  {
    "question": "写経",
    "answer": "しゃきょう",
    "meaning": "hand-copied sutras, copying of a sutra"
  },
  {
    "question": "肥後",
    "answer": "ひご",
    "meaning": "Higo (former province located in present-day Kumamoto Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "千億",
    "answer": "せんおく",
    "meaning": "100,000,000,000, hundred billion, many"
  },
  {
    "question": "国技",
    "answer": "こくぎ",
    "meaning": "national sport (e.g. sumo)"
  },
  {
    "question": "流離う",
    "answer": "さすらう",
    "meaning": "to wander, to roam"
  },
  {
    "question": "下履き",
    "answer": "したばき",
    "meaning": "outdoor shoes"
  },
  {
    "question": "別売り",
    "answer": "べつうり",
    "meaning": "selling separately, not being included in the price"
  },
  {
    "question": "万夫不当",
    "answer": "ばんぷふとう",
    "meaning": "being a match for thousands, being a mighty warrior (combatant)"
  },
  {
    "question": "脳腫瘍",
    "answer": "のうしゅよう",
    "meaning": "brain tumor, brain tumour"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜の蝶",
    "answer": "よるのちょう",
    "meaning": "hostess (at a bar, cabaret, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "激甚",
    "answer": "げきじん",
    "meaning": "intenseness, violence, severity, vehemence, keenness"
  },
  {
    "question": "捨石",
    "answer": "すていし",
    "meaning": "ornamental garden stone (seemingly placed randomly to give the garden a more natural appearance), ga"
  },
  {
    "question": "就航",
    "answer": "しゅうこう",
    "meaning": "entering service (on a route; of a plane or ship), going into commission, being in service"
  },
  {
    "question": "記憶媒体",
    "answer": "きおくばいたい",
    "meaning": "storage medium, recording medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸洗い",
    "answer": "まるあらい",
    "meaning": "washing a kimono (or futon, etc.) without taking it apart, laundering whole"
  },
  {
    "question": "訓辞",
    "answer": "くんじ",
    "meaning": "admonitory speech (e.g. to students), words of admonition"
  },
  {
    "question": "初等教育",
    "answer": "しょとうきょういく",
    "meaning": "elementary education"
  },
  {
    "question": "小猿",
    "answer": "こざる",
    "meaning": "baby monkey, small monkey"
  },
  {
    "question": "酒蒸し",
    "answer": "さかむし",
    "meaning": "seafood seasoned with salt and sake then steamed"
  },
  {
    "question": "霜柱",
    "answer": "しもばしら",
    "meaning": "frost columns, ice needles"
  },
  {
    "question": "押し込み",
    "answer": "おしこみ",
    "meaning": "burglary, burglar, closet"
  },
  {
    "question": "水墨画",
    "answer": "すいぼくが",
    "meaning": "India-ink painting"
  },
  {
    "question": "月経",
    "answer": "げっけい",
    "meaning": "menstruation, menstrual period"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会構造",
    "answer": "しゃかいこうぞう",
    "meaning": "social structure"
  },
  {
    "question": "神秘主義",
    "answer": "しんぴしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "mysticism"
  },
  {
    "question": "地方紙",
    "answer": "ちほうし",
    "meaning": "local newspaper"
  },
  {
    "question": "明太",
    "answer": "メンタイ,めんたい",
    "meaning": "walleye pollack (Theragra chalcogramma), Alaska pollack, walleye pollack roe (generally served salte"
  },
  {
    "question": "変ずる",
    "answer": "へんずる",
    "meaning": "to change into, to be transformed, to be transfigured, to transform, to alter, to convert"
  },
  {
    "question": "多生",
    "answer": "たしょう",
    "meaning": "metempsychosis, saving the lives of many"
  },
  {
    "question": "左脳",
    "answer": "さのう",
    "meaning": "left brain"
  },
  {
    "question": "湿",
    "answer": "しつ",
    "meaning": "moisture, humidity, dampness, scabies, sarcoptic mange, the itch"
  },
  {
    "question": "早世",
    "answer": "そうせい",
    "meaning": "dying young, early death"
  },
  {
    "question": "女声",
    "answer": "じょせい",
    "meaning": "female voice"
  },
  {
    "question": "尻叩き",
    "answer": "しりたたき",
    "meaning": "spanking, traditional ceremony where the newly-wed wife, upon entering her new home, is hit on the r"
  },
  {
    "question": "歌謡",
    "answer": "かよう",
    "meaning": "song, ballad"
  },
  {
    "question": "潮目",
    "answer": "しおめ",
    "meaning": "junction line between two sea currents, line where two ocean currents meet, course of things, turnin"
  },
  {
    "question": "三段論法",
    "answer": "さんだんろんぽう",
    "meaning": "syllogism"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱サラ",
    "answer": "だつサラ,だっサラ",
    "meaning": "setting oneself free from the life of a white-collar worker, quitting a job as a salaryman and launc"
  },
  {
    "question": "原産地",
    "answer": "げんさんち",
    "meaning": "place of origin (of a plant or animal species, etc.), natural habitat, original home, place of origi"
  },
  {
    "question": "一面的",
    "answer": "いちめんてき",
    "meaning": "one-sided"
  },
  {
    "question": "年の暮れ",
    "answer": "としのくれ",
    "meaning": "year end"
  },
  {
    "question": "二重生活",
    "answer": "にじゅうせいかつ",
    "meaning": "double life"
  },
  {
    "question": "同国",
    "answer": "どうこく",
    "meaning": "the same country, the same province, the said country"
  },
  {
    "question": "大気汚染",
    "answer": "たいきおせん",
    "meaning": "air pollution"
  },
  {
    "question": "末日",
    "answer": "まつじつ",
    "meaning": "last day (of a month)"
  },
  {
    "question": "ボール紙",
    "answer": "ボールがみ",
    "meaning": "cardboard, pasteboard"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓋付き",
    "answer": "ふたつき",
    "meaning": "lidded, covered, container with a lid"
  },
  {
    "question": "誇大",
    "answer": "こだい",
    "meaning": "exaggeration, hyperbole"
  },
  {
    "question": "一畳",
    "answer": "いちじょう",
    "meaning": "one mat"
  },
  {
    "question": "全館",
    "answer": "ぜんかん",
    "meaning": "entire building"
  },
  {
    "question": "パイプ役",
    "answer": "パイプやく",
    "meaning": "mediator"
  },
  {
    "question": "中間報告",
    "answer": "ちゅうかんほうこく",
    "meaning": "interim report"
  },
  {
    "question": "全編",
    "answer": "ぜんぺん",
    "meaning": "whole book (volume), complete episode"
  },
  {
    "question": "空かす",
    "answer": "すかす",
    "meaning": "to feel hungry, to get hungry"
  },
  {
    "question": "出来具合",
    "answer": "できぐあい",
    "meaning": "result, effect, performance, success"
  },
  {
    "question": "親思い",
    "answer": "おやおもい",
    "meaning": "love or affection for one's parents"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤備え",
    "answer": "あかぞなえ",
    "meaning": "troops outfitted with red armor (Sengoku and Edo periods)"
  },
  {
    "question": "天童",
    "answer": "てんどう",
    "meaning": "cherub, gods disguised as children, children parading as cherubs"
  },
  {
    "question": "安保",
    "answer": "あんぽ",
    "meaning": "security (e.g. national security), US-Japan Security Treaty, campaign against the Japan-U.S. Securit"
  },
  {
    "question": "参事官",
    "answer": "さんじかん",
    "meaning": "councillor, councilor"
  },
  {
    "question": "神座",
    "answer": "しんざ",
    "meaning": "place where there is a god or spirit, place containing the sacred object of a shrine"
  },
  {
    "question": "落陽",
    "answer": "らくよう",
    "meaning": "setting sun"
  },
  {
    "question": "倭",
    "answer": "わ,やまと",
    "meaning": "Japan, Japanese-style, (ancient) Japan, Yamato (former province located in present-day Nara Prefectu"
  },
  {
    "question": "少年団",
    "answer": "しょうねんだん",
    "meaning": "Boy Scouts"
  },
  {
    "question": "奥羽",
    "answer": "おうう",
    "meaning": "Ōu (the two former provinces of Mutsu and Dewa), Tōhoku"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎮め",
    "answer": "しずめ",
    "meaning": "controlling, suppressing, quelling"
  },
  {
    "question": "先駆",
    "answer": "せんく",
    "meaning": "forerunner, precursor, pioneer, leader, outrider, outriding"
  },
  {
    "question": "鹿毛",
    "answer": "かげ",
    "meaning": "fawn colour, fawn-colored horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "僚艦",
    "answer": "りょうかん",
    "meaning": "consort ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "電算",
    "answer": "でんさん,でんそろ",
    "meaning": "computer, electronic calculator combined with a soroban"
  },
  {
    "question": "凶手",
    "answer": "きょうしゅ",
    "meaning": "assassin"
  },
  {
    "question": "点心",
    "answer": "てんしん,てんじん",
    "meaning": "Zen monk's early morning meal, refreshment, cakes, simple Chinese food, dim sum"
  },
  {
    "question": "髄液",
    "answer": "ずいえき",
    "meaning": "cerebrospinal fluid"
  },
  {
    "question": "楽舞",
    "answer": "がくぶ",
    "meaning": "singing and dancing, song and dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "調練",
    "answer": "ちょうれん",
    "meaning": "military drill, training"
  },
  {
    "question": "巨艦",
    "answer": "きょかん",
    "meaning": "large warship"
  },
  {
    "question": "雲母",
    "answer": "うんも,うんぼ,きらら",
    "meaning": "mica, isinglass"
  },
  {
    "question": "帰艦",
    "answer": "きかん",
    "meaning": "returning to one's (war)ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "受動",
    "answer": "じゅどう",
    "meaning": "passivity"
  },
  {
    "question": "撃砕",
    "answer": "げきさい",
    "meaning": "pulverising"
  },
  {
    "question": "働き蟻",
    "answer": "はたらきあり",
    "meaning": "worker ant, hard worker"
  },
  {
    "question": "拡大鏡",
    "answer": "かくだいきょう",
    "meaning": "magnifying glass, magnifier, loupe"
  },
  {
    "question": "出願",
    "answer": "しゅつがん",
    "meaning": "application"
  },
  {
    "question": "纏め役",
    "answer": "まとめやく",
    "meaning": "mediator, peacemaker, troubleshooter, manager"
  },
  {
    "question": "囮捜査",
    "answer": "おとりそうさ",
    "meaning": "sting operation, undercover investigation"
  },
  {
    "question": "土塁",
    "answer": "どるい",
    "meaning": "earthen walls (of fortification), earthwork, embankment"
  },
  {
    "question": "西遊",
    "answer": "せいゆう,さいゆう",
    "meaning": "westward trip, trip to the West"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨傘",
    "answer": "あまがさ",
    "meaning": "umbrella"
  },
  {
    "question": "世話人",
    "answer": "せわにん,せわびと",
    "meaning": "sponsor, manager, go-between, mediator, agent, caretaker"
  },
  {
    "question": "水爆",
    "answer": "すいばく",
    "meaning": "hydrogen bomb"
  },
  {
    "question": "諸元",
    "answer": "しょげん",
    "meaning": "various factors or elements"
  },
  {
    "question": "枕木",
    "answer": "まくらぎ",
    "meaning": "sleeper, railroad tie"
  },
  {
    "question": "放校",
    "answer": "ほうこう",
    "meaning": "expulsion from school"
  },
  {
    "question": "日勤",
    "answer": "にっきん",
    "meaning": "day shift"
  },
  {
    "question": "特務機関",
    "answer": "とくむきかん",
    "meaning": "secret military agency, secret service"
  },
  {
    "question": "保険医",
    "answer": "ほけんい",
    "meaning": "insurance doctor"
  },
  {
    "question": "暑気",
    "answer": "しょき,あつけ",
    "meaning": "summer heat, hot weather, heatstroke"
  },
  {
    "question": "無酸素",
    "answer": "むさんそ",
    "meaning": "without oxygen, anaerobic, anoxia, hypoxia"
  },
  {
    "question": "割かし",
    "answer": "わりかし",
    "meaning": "comparatively, quite, rather"
  },
  {
    "question": "旅情",
    "answer": "りょじょう",
    "meaning": "one's mood while traveling (travelling)"
  },
  {
    "question": "高解像度",
    "answer": "こうかいぞうど",
    "meaning": "high resolution"
  },
  {
    "question": "籤",
    "answer": "くじ,ひご,せん",
    "meaning": "lottery, lot, raffle, draw, thin strip of bamboo, slip (of paper), tag (usu. bamboo, wood, ivory, et"
  },
  {
    "question": "朝立ち",
    "answer": "あさだち",
    "meaning": "erection when waking in the morning, nocturnal penile tumescence, morning glory, morning wood, early"
  },
  {
    "question": "後ろ楯",
    "answer": "うしろだて",
    "meaning": "backing, support, backer, supporter, patron, sponsor, shield that protects one's back"
  },
  {
    "question": "突き回す",
    "answer": "つつきまわす",
    "meaning": "to poke around"
  },
  {
    "question": "火の用心",
    "answer": "ひのようじん",
    "meaning": "be careful about fire, watch out for fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "二女",
    "answer": "にじょ",
    "meaning": "second daughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "毒杯",
    "answer": "どくはい",
    "meaning": "cup of poisoned alcohol"
  },
  {
    "question": "平和条約",
    "answer": "へいわじょうやく",
    "meaning": "peace treaty"
  },
  {
    "question": "碌",
    "answer": "ろく",
    "meaning": "satisfactory, decent, good, proper, worthy"
  },
  {
    "question": "漏電",
    "answer": "ろうでん",
    "meaning": "short circuit, leakage (of electricity), electrical fault"
  },
  {
    "question": "壊乱",
    "answer": "かいらん",
    "meaning": "corruption (of order, customs, etc.), to fall apart (organization, system, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕掛",
    "answer": "しかけ",
    "meaning": "device, contrivance, mechanism, gadget, trick, trap, calculated manipulation, gambit, (small) scale,"
  },
  {
    "question": "仰向ける",
    "answer": "あおむける",
    "meaning": "to turn up (one's face)"
  },
  {
    "question": "奸",
    "answer": "かん",
    "meaning": "cunning and wickedness, cunning and wicked person"
  },
  {
    "question": "環状線",
    "answer": "かんじょうせん",
    "meaning": "loop line, (transportation) belt line"
  },
  {
    "question": "女運",
    "answer": "おんなうん",
    "meaning": "luck with women"
  },
  {
    "question": "草々",
    "answer": "そうそう",
    "meaning": "hurry, rush, flurry, simple, brief, quick, rough, crude, careless, inadequate, yours sincerely, your"
  },
  {
    "question": "練り物",
    "answer": "ねりもの",
    "meaning": "paste products (incl. sweets, fish paste, etc.), parade float, procession"
  },
  {
    "question": "打ち手",
    "answer": "うちて",
    "meaning": "shooter, drummer (taiko, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "玉露",
    "answer": "ぎょくろ",
    "meaning": "high-quality green tea, jewel-like dewdrop"
  },
  {
    "question": "写真写り",
    "answer": "しゃしんうつり",
    "meaning": "photogenicity"
  },
  {
    "question": "照り輝く",
    "answer": "てりかがやく",
    "meaning": "to shine brilliantly"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗誦",
    "answer": "あんしょう,あんじゅ",
    "meaning": "recitation, reciting from memory"
  },
  {
    "question": "睦む",
    "answer": "むつむ",
    "meaning": "to be harmonious, to get on well, to be intimate or close"
  },
  {
    "question": "簿記",
    "answer": "ぼき",
    "meaning": "journalization (accounts), journalisation, bookkeeping"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑食性",
    "answer": "ざっしょくせい",
    "meaning": "omnivorousness, polyphagia, omnivorous, polyphagous"
  },
  {
    "question": "些少",
    "answer": "さしょう",
    "meaning": "trifling, little, few, slight"
  },
  {
    "question": "腰紐",
    "answer": "こしひも",
    "meaning": "cord tied around the waist of a kimono before an obi is tied"
  },
  {
    "question": "使い込み",
    "answer": "つかいこみ",
    "meaning": "embezzlement"
  },
  {
    "question": "接ぎ穂",
    "answer": "つぎほ,つぎぼ",
    "meaning": "scion, cion, (horticultural) graft, opportunity to continue a conversation"
  },
  {
    "question": "叙情",
    "answer": "じょじょう",
    "meaning": "lyricism, description of one's feelings"
  },
  {
    "question": "零細企業",
    "answer": "れいさいきぎょう",
    "meaning": "small business, micro-enterprise, microenterprise"
  },
  {
    "question": "渦巻",
    "answer": "うずまき",
    "meaning": "whirlpool, eddy, coil"
  },
  {
    "question": "呆け",
    "answer": "ぼけ",
    "meaning": "fool, idiot, dotage, senility, dementia, touched in the head (from), out of it (from), feeling slugg"
  },
  {
    "question": "乳離れ",
    "answer": "ちちばなれ,ちばなれ",
    "meaning": "weaning"
  },
  {
    "question": "家族計画",
    "answer": "かぞくけいかく",
    "meaning": "family planning"
  },
  {
    "question": "一極集中",
    "answer": "いっきょくしゅうちゅう",
    "meaning": "heavy concentration, overconcentration"
  },
  {
    "question": "体系的",
    "answer": "たいけいてき",
    "meaning": "systematic"
  },
  {
    "question": "没交渉",
    "answer": "ぼっこうしょう,ぼつこうしょう",
    "meaning": "lack of relation (to), independence (of)"
  },
  {
    "question": "狡賢い",
    "answer": "ずるがしこい",
    "meaning": "devious, cunning, sly, crafty"
  },
  {
    "question": "苦り切る",
    "answer": "にがりきる",
    "meaning": "to look sour (disgusted)"
  },
  {
    "question": "釈然",
    "answer": "しゃくぜん,せきぜん",
    "meaning": "fully satisfied (with an explanation, apology, etc.), happy, cleared of doubt"
  },
  {
    "question": "滑り込み",
    "answer": "すべりこみ",
    "meaning": "sliding, being just in time"
  },
  {
    "question": "天象儀",
    "answer": "てんしょうぎ",
    "meaning": "planetarium"
  },
  {
    "question": "協商",
    "answer": "きょうしょう",
    "meaning": "negotiation, agreement"
  },
  {
    "question": "敷島",
    "answer": "しきしま",
    "meaning": "Yamato (province), Japan, the art of classical Japanese poetry"
  },
  {
    "question": "貂",
    "answer": "てん",
    "meaning": "Japanese marten (Martes melampus), marten (any arboreal weasel-like mammal of genus Martes)"
  },
  {
    "question": "獣医師",
    "answer": "じゅういし",
    "meaning": "veterinarian, veterinary surgeon, vet"
  },
  {
    "question": "着順",
    "answer": "ちゃくじゅん",
    "meaning": "order of arrival"
  },
  {
    "question": "花木",
    "answer": "かぼく",
    "meaning": "flowers and trees, flowering trees"
  },
  {
    "question": "改易",
    "answer": "かいえき",
    "meaning": "change of rank"
  },
  {
    "question": "三強",
    "answer": "さんきょう",
    "meaning": "top three"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤軍",
    "answer": "せきぐん",
    "meaning": "Red Army (Soviet Union, 1918-1946), Workers' and Peasants' Red Army"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄河",
    "answer": "こうが",
    "meaning": "Yellow river (in China)"
  },
  {
    "question": "連理",
    "answer": "れんり",
    "meaning": "trees with entwined branches, intimate male and female relationship"
  },
  {
    "question": "就役",
    "answer": "しゅうえき",
    "meaning": "placed in commission, entering servitude"
  },
  {
    "question": "坤",
    "answer": "こん,ひつじさる",
    "meaning": "kun (one of the trigrams of the I Ching: earth, southwest), southwest"
  },
  {
    "question": "仮設住宅",
    "answer": "かせつじゅうたく",
    "meaning": "temporary dwelling, temporary housing"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛行甲板",
    "answer": "ひこうかんぱん",
    "meaning": "flight deck"
  },
  {
    "question": "土瓶",
    "answer": "どびん",
    "meaning": "earthenware teapot"
  },
  {
    "question": "遺失",
    "answer": "いしつ",
    "meaning": "loss"
  },
  {
    "question": "峡",
    "answer": "かい",
    "meaning": "gorge, ravine"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇岩",
    "answer": "きがん",
    "meaning": "strangely shaped rocks, massive rock of unusual shape"
  },
  {
    "question": "屯所",
    "answer": "とんしょ",
    "meaning": "post, quarters, military station, police station"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗機",
    "answer": "じょうき",
    "meaning": "airplane (manned by ...), boarding (an airplane)"
  },
  {
    "question": "超克",
    "answer": "ちょうこく",
    "meaning": "overcoming, conquering, surmounting, getting over"
  },
  {
    "question": "狩衣",
    "answer": "かりぎぬ,かりごろも",
    "meaning": "kariginu (informal clothes worn by the nobility from the Heian period onwards), (during the Edo peri"
  },
  {
    "question": "風力発電",
    "answer": "ふうりょくはつでん",
    "meaning": "wind power generation"
  },
  {
    "question": "耐圧",
    "answer": "たいあつ",
    "meaning": "pressure-resistant"
  },
  {
    "question": "釣り師",
    "answer": "つりし",
    "meaning": "angler, Internet troll"
  },
  {
    "question": "止む無く",
    "answer": "やむなく",
    "meaning": "out of necessity, with no other option, perforce, unavoidably, reluctantly, unwillingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "日舞",
    "answer": "にちぶ",
    "meaning": "traditional Japanese dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "焦熱地獄",
    "answer": "しょうねつじごく",
    "meaning": "burning hell, inferno"
  },
  {
    "question": "一打ち",
    "answer": "ひとうち",
    "meaning": "stroke, blow"
  },
  {
    "question": "天竺",
    "answer": "てんじく",
    "meaning": "India, cotton sheeting, foreign, imported, ultra-spicy, extra hot"
  },
  {
    "question": "外相",
    "answer": "がいしょう",
    "meaning": "Foreign Minister"
  },
  {
    "question": "行路",
    "answer": "こうろ,ゆきみち",
    "meaning": "one's course, one's path, one's road, route (when going somewhere), way (to get somewhere)"
  },
  {
    "question": "砂岩",
    "answer": "さがん,しゃがん",
    "meaning": "sandstone"
  },
  {
    "question": "耐火性",
    "answer": "たいかせい",
    "meaning": "fire resistance"
  },
  {
    "question": "福笑い",
    "answer": "ふくわらい",
    "meaning": "game like 'pin the tail on the donkey'"
  },
  {
    "question": "農法",
    "answer": "のうほう",
    "meaning": "farming methods"
  },
  {
    "question": "一篇",
    "answer": "いっぺん",
    "meaning": "piece (e.g. poetry), poem, essay, book, story"
  },
  {
    "question": "激走",
    "answer": "げきそう",
    "meaning": "flat-out run, driving at full speed"
  },
  {
    "question": "美々しい",
    "answer": "びびしい",
    "meaning": "beautiful"
  },
  {
    "question": "商材",
    "answer": "しょうざい",
    "meaning": "product, commodity, merchandise"
  },
  {
    "question": "不渡り",
    "answer": "ふわたり",
    "meaning": "non-payment, dishonouring (bill), dishonoring (bill), bouncing (cheque, check)"
  },
  {
    "question": "古物商",
    "answer": "こぶつしょう",
    "meaning": "antiques business, curio dealer, secondhand dealer"
  },
  {
    "question": "明細書",
    "answer": "めいさいしょ",
    "meaning": "detailed statement, detailed account, minute description, specifications, list of particulars"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪法",
    "answer": "あくほう",
    "meaning": "bad law, evil ways, evil way of doing things"
  },
  {
    "question": "利得",
    "answer": "りとく",
    "meaning": "gain, profit, benefit, amplification"
  },
  {
    "question": "女子大学",
    "answer": "じょしだいがく",
    "meaning": "women's college"
  },
  {
    "question": "恐懼",
    "answer": "きょうく",
    "meaning": "being struck with awe"
  },
  {
    "question": "盗み撮り",
    "answer": "ぬすみどり",
    "meaning": "taking pictures secretly, taking a sneak shot"
  },
  {
    "question": "水死",
    "answer": "すいし",
    "meaning": "death by drowning"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り回す",
    "answer": "とりまわす",
    "meaning": "to deal with effectively, to handle (well), to manage, to pass around (a plate of food, etc.) after"
  },
  {
    "question": "気を吐く",
    "answer": "きをはく",
    "meaning": "to make a good showing"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨樋",
    "answer": "あまどい",
    "meaning": "drainspout, rain gutter"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒砂糖",
    "answer": "くろざとう",
    "meaning": "(unrefined) brown sugar, muscovado"
  },
  {
    "question": "男部屋",
    "answer": "おとこべや",
    "meaning": "room for menservants"
  },
  {
    "question": "当たり屋",
    "answer": "あたりや",
    "meaning": "lucky person, someone who made a lot of money (e.g. gambling or on the stock market), skilled batter"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒胡椒",
    "answer": "くろこしょう",
    "meaning": "black pepper (Piper nigrum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "枯れ尾花",
    "answer": "かれおばな",
    "meaning": "withered silver grass"
  },
  {
    "question": "万有引力",
    "answer": "ばんゆういんりょく",
    "meaning": "universal gravitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "魂消る",
    "answer": "たまげる,たまぎる",
    "meaning": "to be astonished, to be flabbergasted, to be startled, to be amazed, to be appalled"
  },
  {
    "question": "悔む",
    "answer": "くやむ",
    "meaning": "to mourn, to lament, to be sorry, to regret, to repent"
  },
  {
    "question": "割烹",
    "answer": "かっぽう",
    "meaning": "cooking (esp. Japanese style), cuisine, (Japanese) restaurant"
  },
  {
    "question": "心弱い",
    "answer": "こころよわい",
    "meaning": "tenderhearted, faint of heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "麻疹",
    "answer": "はしか,ましん",
    "meaning": "measles"
  },
  {
    "question": "印璽",
    "answer": "いんじ",
    "meaning": "imperial seal"
  },
  {
    "question": "雪中",
    "answer": "せっちゅう",
    "meaning": "in the snow"
  },
  {
    "question": "右脳",
    "answer": "うのう",
    "meaning": "right brain"
  },
  {
    "question": "脅し取る",
    "answer": "おどしとる",
    "meaning": "to extort (money), to blackmail"
  },
  {
    "question": "摩擦係数",
    "answer": "まさつけいすう",
    "meaning": "coefficient of friction"
  },
  {
    "question": "進行形",
    "answer": "しんこうけい",
    "meaning": "progressive form, in progress (e.g. of a project)"
  },
  {
    "question": "侘びる",
    "answer": "わびる",
    "meaning": "to be worried, to be grieved, to pine for"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷却期間",
    "answer": "れいきゃくきかん",
    "meaning": "cooling-off period"
  },
  {
    "question": "射落とす",
    "answer": "いおとす",
    "meaning": "to shoot down, to win, to gain"
  },
  {
    "question": "新機軸",
    "answer": "しんきじく",
    "meaning": "innovation, new departure, milestone, breakthrough"
  },
  {
    "question": "満了",
    "answer": "まんりょう",
    "meaning": "expiration, termination"
  },
  {
    "question": "黙読",
    "answer": "もくどく",
    "meaning": "reading silently"
  },
  {
    "question": "野晒し",
    "answer": "のざらし",
    "meaning": "weather-beaten"
  },
  {
    "question": "勘気",
    "answer": "かんき",
    "meaning": "disfavor, disfavour, disinheritance"
  },
  {
    "question": "肉離れ",
    "answer": "にくばなれ",
    "meaning": "pulled or torn muscle"
  },
  {
    "question": "昔風",
    "answer": "むかしふう",
    "meaning": "old fashioned"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑言",
    "answer": "ぞうごん",
    "meaning": "foul language, abuse"
  },
  {
    "question": "銘じる",
    "answer": "めいじる",
    "meaning": "to stamp, to engrave, to inscribe"
  },
  {
    "question": "食塩",
    "answer": "しょくえん",
    "meaning": "table salt"
  },
  {
    "question": "反語",
    "answer": "はんご",
    "meaning": "irony, rhetorical question"
  },
  {
    "question": "早上がり",
    "answer": "はやあがり",
    "meaning": "finishing early (e.g. work, a game), entering elementary school a year earlier than others"
  },
  {
    "question": "投げ売り",
    "answer": "なげうり",
    "meaning": "bargain (sacrifice) sale, selling at a loss, dumping"
  },
  {
    "question": "白肌",
    "answer": "しらはだ",
    "meaning": "white-coloured skin, vitiligo, leucoderma, leukoderma"
  },
  {
    "question": "折り込み",
    "answer": "おりこみ",
    "meaning": "insert (in a magazine, newspaper, etc.), foldout, insertion"
  },
  {
    "question": "色付け",
    "answer": "いろづけ,いろつけ",
    "meaning": "coloring, colouring, adding color, adding colour"
  },
  {
    "question": "具体",
    "answer": "ぐたい",
    "meaning": "concrete, tangible, material"
  },
  {
    "question": "下方修正",
    "answer": "かほうしゅうせい",
    "meaning": "downward adjustment, downward revision"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨量",
    "answer": "うりょう",
    "meaning": "(amount of) rainfall"
  },
  {
    "question": "伝統工芸",
    "answer": "でんとうこうげい",
    "meaning": "traditional craft, traditional handicrafts"
  },
  {
    "question": "失職",
    "answer": "しっしょく",
    "meaning": "losing one's job"
  },
  {
    "question": "足蹴",
    "answer": "あしげ",
    "meaning": "kick, treating (someone) poorly"
  },
  {
    "question": "送別",
    "answer": "そうべつ",
    "meaning": "farewell, send-off"
  },
  {
    "question": "切れ口",
    "answer": "きれくち",
    "meaning": "cut end, section, opening, slit"
  },
  {
    "question": "上を下へ",
    "answer": "うえをしたへ",
    "meaning": "confused, chaotic, jumbled, upside-down"
  },
  {
    "question": "終夜",
    "answer": "しゅうや,よもすがら",
    "meaning": "all night"
  },
  {
    "question": "浮名",
    "answer": "うきな",
    "meaning": "rumour (of a love affair), rumor, romance, scandal, bad reputation"
  },
  {
    "question": "岩倉",
    "answer": "やぐら",
    "meaning": "caves dug as tombs in and around Kamakura during the Kamakura and Muromachi periods"
  },
  {
    "question": "極楽鳥",
    "answer": "ごくらくちょう",
    "meaning": "bird of paradise (Paradisaeidae family)"
  },
  {
    "question": "御苑",
    "answer": "ぎょえん",
    "meaning": "imperial garden"
  },
  {
    "question": "撃剣",
    "answer": "げきけん,げっけん",
    "meaning": "fencing, kendo"
  },
  {
    "question": "築山",
    "answer": "つきやま",
    "meaning": "artificial hill (in a garden)"
  },
  {
    "question": "高座",
    "answer": "こうざ",
    "meaning": "platform, stage, upper seat, pulpit"
  },
  {
    "question": "信任投票",
    "answer": "しんにんとうひょう",
    "meaning": "vote of confidence"
  },
  {
    "question": "青果",
    "answer": "せいか",
    "meaning": "fruit(s) and vegetables, produce"
  },
  {
    "question": "天球儀",
    "answer": "てんきゅうぎ",
    "meaning": "celestial globe, armillary sphere"
  },
  {
    "question": "邀撃",
    "answer": "ようげき",
    "meaning": "interception, counter-attack"
  },
  {
    "question": "更衣",
    "answer": "ころもがえ,こうい,きさらぎ",
    "meaning": "seasonal change of clothing, changing one's dress for the season, renovation, facelift, redesign, re"
  },
  {
    "question": "学士",
    "answer": "がくし",
    "meaning": "university graduate, bachelor, bachelor's degree"
  },
  {
    "question": "級長",
    "answer": "きゅうちょう",
    "meaning": "head of class, monitor"
  },
  {
    "question": "内懐",
    "answer": "うちぶところ",
    "meaning": "inside pocket, bosom, real intention"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍縮",
    "answer": "ぐんしゅく",
    "meaning": "reduction of armaments, disarmament"
  },
  {
    "question": "芸妓",
    "answer": "げいぎ,げいこ",
    "meaning": "geisha"
  },
  {
    "question": "大納言",
    "answer": "だいなごん",
    "meaning": "chief councillor of state, chief councilor of state, large-grained variety of adzuki bean"
  },
  {
    "question": "紅葉狩り",
    "answer": "もみじがり",
    "meaning": "autumn-leaf viewing, fall-leaf viewing"
  },
  {
    "question": "古地図",
    "answer": "こちず",
    "meaning": "old map, antique map"
  },
  {
    "question": "右大臣",
    "answer": "うだいじん",
    "meaning": "Minister of the Right (official in Nara and Heian periods)"
  },
  {
    "question": "美術商",
    "answer": "びじゅつしょう",
    "meaning": "art dealer, fine art(s) shop"
  },
  {
    "question": "肝腎",
    "answer": "かんじん",
    "meaning": "essential, important, crucial, vital, main"
  },
  {
    "question": "力攻め",
    "answer": "ちからぜめ",
    "meaning": "disregarding strategy and using brute force"
  },
  {
    "question": "野球拳",
    "answer": "やきゅうけん",
    "meaning": "yakyūken, strip version of rock, paper, scissors (similar to strip poker)"
  },
  {
    "question": "移乗",
    "answer": "いじょう",
    "meaning": "transferring (to another ship, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "美質",
    "answer": "びしつ",
    "meaning": "virtue, good qualities"
  },
  {
    "question": "無道",
    "answer": "むどう,ぶどう,ぶとう",
    "meaning": "inhuman, immoral, unreasonable, outrageous, wicked"
  },
  {
    "question": "同体",
    "answer": "どうたい",
    "meaning": "as one flesh or body, simultaneously"
  },
  {
    "question": "牡牛",
    "answer": "おうし",
    "meaning": "bull, ox, steer"
  },
  {
    "question": "入校",
    "answer": "にゅうこう",
    "meaning": "matriculation"
  },
  {
    "question": "猟場",
    "answer": "りょうば",
    "meaning": "hunting grounds"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒眼",
    "answer": "くろめ",
    "meaning": "pupil and (dark) iris of the eye"
  },
  {
    "question": "浮き袋",
    "answer": "うきぶくろ",
    "meaning": "swimming belt, swimming float, life buoy, life jacket, swim bladder, air bladder"
  },
  {
    "question": "舷",
    "answer": "ふなばた,ふなべり,げん",
    "meaning": "side of a boat, gunwale"
  },
  {
    "question": "要諦",
    "answer": "ようてい",
    "meaning": "important point"
  },
  {
    "question": "障子紙",
    "answer": "しょうじがみ",
    "meaning": "shoji paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "秋祭り",
    "answer": "あきまつり",
    "meaning": "autumn festival, fall festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "村役場",
    "answer": "むらやくば",
    "meaning": "village office, local administration office in a village"
  },
  {
    "question": "干潮",
    "answer": "かんちょう,ひしお",
    "meaning": "low tide, low water, ebb"
  },
  {
    "question": "宵の明星",
    "answer": "よいのみょうじょう",
    "meaning": "evening star, Vesper, Hesperus, Venus in the evening sky"
  },
  {
    "question": "大威張り",
    "answer": "おおいばり",
    "meaning": "bragging, showing off, pride"
  },
  {
    "question": "練炭",
    "answer": "れんたん",
    "meaning": "briquette (charcoal or coal)"
  },
  {
    "question": "缶切り",
    "answer": "かんきり",
    "meaning": "can opener"
  },
  {
    "question": "偏光",
    "answer": "へんこう",
    "meaning": "polarized light, polarised light, polarization, polarisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "御大",
    "answer": "おんたい",
    "meaning": "boss, governor, headman"
  },
  {
    "question": "巨星",
    "answer": "きょせい",
    "meaning": "giant star, great person, giant, superstar, big-shot"
  },
  {
    "question": "靴磨き",
    "answer": "くつみがき",
    "meaning": "shoeshine, shoe polishing"
  },
  {
    "question": "量子論",
    "answer": "りょうしろん",
    "meaning": "quantum theory"
  },
  {
    "question": "男子高",
    "answer": "だんしこう",
    "meaning": "boys' high school"
  },
  {
    "question": "練兵",
    "answer": "れんぺい",
    "meaning": "military drill"
  },
  {
    "question": "赦",
    "answer": "しゃ",
    "meaning": "pardon, amnesty"
  },
  {
    "question": "香味",
    "answer": "こうみ",
    "meaning": "smell and taste, flavour, flavor"
  },
  {
    "question": "五十音",
    "answer": "ごじゅうおん",
    "meaning": "the Japanese syllabary"
  },
  {
    "question": "麺棒",
    "answer": "めんぼう",
    "meaning": "rolling pin"
  },
  {
    "question": "白毛",
    "answer": "しろげ",
    "meaning": "white (horse coat color)"
  },
  {
    "question": "本鈴",
    "answer": "ほんれい",
    "meaning": "bell signalling that work, class, etc. has formally begun"
  },
  {
    "question": "控訴",
    "answer": "こうそ",
    "meaning": "appeal to a higher court, intermediate appeal"
  },
  {
    "question": "投げ縄",
    "answer": "なげなわ",
    "meaning": "lasso, lariat"
  },
  {
    "question": "提",
    "answer": "ひさげ",
    "meaning": "ceremonial sake decanter with a spout and semicircular handle"
  },
  {
    "question": "後れる",
    "answer": "おくれる",
    "meaning": "to be late, to be delayed, to fall behind schedule, to be overdue, to fall behind (in a race, one's"
  },
  {
    "question": "退陣",
    "answer": "たいじん",
    "meaning": "resignation, stepping down, retirement, retreat, decamping, withdrawal"
  },
  {
    "question": "巻き貝",
    "answer": "まきがい",
    "meaning": "snail, spiral shell"
  },
  {
    "question": "気付け薬",
    "answer": "きつけぐすり",
    "meaning": "restorative, smelling salts"
  },
  {
    "question": "邦画",
    "answer": "ほうが",
    "meaning": "Japanese film, Japanese painting"
  },
  {
    "question": "痩ける",
    "answer": "こける",
    "meaning": "to become hollow (with age, illness, etc.), to be scrawny, to be thin"
  },
  {
    "question": "自己啓発",
    "answer": "じこけいはつ",
    "meaning": "self-development, self-enlightenment"
  },
  {
    "question": "防塵",
    "answer": "ぼうじん",
    "meaning": "protection against dust, dust-proof, dust-tight"
  },
  {
    "question": "猪武者",
    "answer": "いのししむしゃ",
    "meaning": "daredevil, foolhardy warrior, hotspur"
  },
  {
    "question": "外資",
    "answer": "がいし",
    "meaning": "foreign capital (e.g. in a company), foreign investment"
  },
  {
    "question": "欠番",
    "answer": "けつばん",
    "meaning": "missing number"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝訴",
    "answer": "しょうそ",
    "meaning": "winning a (legal) case, victory (in a legal case)"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち方",
    "answer": "たちかた",
    "meaning": "way of standing, dancer (in a Japanese dance performance)"
  },
  {
    "question": "顕在",
    "answer": "けんざい",
    "meaning": "being actual (as opposed to hidden or latent), being apparent, being obvious, being tangible, being"
  },
  {
    "question": "学問的",
    "answer": "がくもんてき",
    "meaning": "scholarly"
  },
  {
    "question": "月の出",
    "answer": "つきので",
    "meaning": "moonrise, rise of the Moon"
  },
  {
    "question": "児童虐待",
    "answer": "じどうぎゃくたい",
    "meaning": "child abuse"
  },
  {
    "question": "飲み仲間",
    "answer": "のみなかま",
    "meaning": "drinking companion"
  },
  {
    "question": "公称",
    "answer": "こうしょう",
    "meaning": "public name, announcing publicly, nominal"
  },
  {
    "question": "少しく",
    "answer": "すこしく",
    "meaning": "a little, somewhat"
  },
  {
    "question": "作り付け",
    "answer": "つくりつけ",
    "meaning": "built-in, fixed, attached"
  },
  {
    "question": "苦る",
    "answer": "にがる",
    "meaning": "to feel bitter, to scowl"
  },
  {
    "question": "訪う",
    "answer": "とう,おとなう",
    "meaning": "to ask, to inquire, to blame (someone) for, to accuse of, to pursue (question of responsibility), to"
  },
  {
    "question": "返し技",
    "answer": "かえしわざ",
    "meaning": "counterattack (kendo, judo, etc.), reversal technique"
  },
  {
    "question": "分母",
    "answer": "ぶんぼ",
    "meaning": "denominator"
  },
  {
    "question": "政治学",
    "answer": "せいじがく",
    "meaning": "political science"
  },
  {
    "question": "無理筋",
    "answer": "むりすじ",
    "meaning": "unreasonable idea, illogical plan, illogical move (in shogi or go)"
  },
  {
    "question": "隠然",
    "answer": "いんぜん",
    "meaning": "latent, hidden, secret, behind the scenes"
  },
  {
    "question": "完全燃焼",
    "answer": "かんぜんねんしょう",
    "meaning": "perfect combustion"
  },
  {
    "question": "悖る",
    "answer": "もとる",
    "meaning": "to go against, to act contrary to, to run counter to, to deviate from"
  },
  {
    "question": "天王山",
    "answer": "てんのうざん",
    "meaning": "strategic point, crucial time, watershed, crunch"
  },
  {
    "question": "明解",
    "answer": "めいかい",
    "meaning": "clear explanation"
  },
  {
    "question": "直毛",
    "answer": "ちょくもう",
    "meaning": "straight hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "競り勝つ",
    "answer": "せりかつ",
    "meaning": "to win after tough bidding"
  },
  {
    "question": "和え物",
    "answer": "あえもの",
    "meaning": "chopped fish, shellfish or vegetables, dressed with (miso or other) sauce"
  },
  {
    "question": "背任",
    "answer": "はいにん",
    "meaning": "breach of trust, malfeasance, malpractice, misappropriation"
  },
  {
    "question": "好例",
    "answer": "こうれい",
    "meaning": "good example"
  },
  {
    "question": "それ見ろ",
    "answer": "それみろ",
    "meaning": "well, look at that"
  },
  {
    "question": "誘い合う",
    "answer": "さそいあう",
    "meaning": "to ask each other"
  },
  {
    "question": "大器晩成",
    "answer": "たいきばんせい",
    "meaning": "great talents mature late"
  },
  {
    "question": "知能犯",
    "answer": "ちのうはん",
    "meaning": "intellectual crime, white-collar crime, intellectual criminal, smart criminal"
  },
  {
    "question": "一皮",
    "answer": "ひとかわ",
    "meaning": "unmasking"
  },
  {
    "question": "凍り",
    "answer": "こおり",
    "meaning": "ice, shaved ice (usually served with flavored simple syrup)"
  },
  {
    "question": "成立つ",
    "answer": "なりたつ",
    "meaning": "to consist of, to be made up of, to be composed of, to be concluded (e.g. of an agreement), to hold"
  },
  {
    "question": "釣師",
    "answer": "つりし",
    "meaning": "angler, Internet troll"
  },
  {
    "question": "簀",
    "answer": "す,さく",
    "meaning": "mat (made of pieces of split bamboo or reeds tied together)"
  },
  {
    "question": "弱視",
    "answer": "じゃくし",
    "meaning": "amblyopia, weak sight"
  },
  {
    "question": "阿波",
    "answer": "あわ",
    "meaning": "Awa (former province located in present-day Tokushima Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "聖殿",
    "answer": "せいでん",
    "meaning": "sacred shrine, sanctuary"
  },
  {
    "question": "空自",
    "answer": "くうじ",
    "meaning": "Air Self-Defense Force, ASDF"
  },
  {
    "question": "淡路",
    "answer": "あわじ",
    "meaning": "Awaji (former province located on Awaji Island in present-day Hyōgo Prefecture), Awaji (island)"
  },
  {
    "question": "渓",
    "answer": "たに",
    "meaning": "valley"
  },
  {
    "question": "打ち消し",
    "answer": "うちけし",
    "meaning": "negation, denial, negative"
  },
  {
    "question": "土塀",
    "answer": "どべい",
    "meaning": "mud wall, earthen wall, plaster wall"
  },
  {
    "question": "轢殺",
    "answer": "れきさつ",
    "meaning": "killing by running over with a car or train"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨垂れ",
    "answer": "あまだれ",
    "meaning": "raindrops (dripping from eaves, branches, etc.), exclamation point, exclamation mark"
  },
  {
    "question": "祝典",
    "answer": "しゅくてん",
    "meaning": "celebration"
  },
  {
    "question": "弾帯",
    "answer": "だんたい",
    "meaning": "bandolier, bandoleer, ammo belt, driving band (of a shell or bullet), rotating band"
  },
  {
    "question": "ケ月",
    "answer": "かげつ",
    "meaning": "months (period of)"
  },
  {
    "question": "春画",
    "answer": "しゅんが",
    "meaning": "shunga, erotic or pornographic woodblock prints"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎮守",
    "answer": "ちんじゅ",
    "meaning": "local Shinto deity, tutelary god"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤十字",
    "answer": "せきじゅうじ",
    "meaning": "Red Cross"
  },
  {
    "question": "情弱",
    "answer": "じょうじゃく",
    "meaning": "person with limited access to information (via the Internet, television, etc.), person who is inept"
  },
  {
    "question": "前橋",
    "answer": "まえばし",
    "meaning": "Maebashi (city in Gunma)"
  },
  {
    "question": "製鉄所",
    "answer": "せいてつじょ,せいてつしょ",
    "meaning": "ironworks, steelworks"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀賞",
    "answer": "ぎんしょう",
    "meaning": "silver (second-place) prize"
  },
  {
    "question": "味噌漬け",
    "answer": "みそづけ",
    "meaning": "meat or fish or vegetables preserved in miso"
  },
  {
    "question": "大鳥",
    "answer": "おおとり",
    "meaning": "large bird, peng (in Chinese mythology, giant bird said to transform from a fish), fenghuang (Chines"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会秩序",
    "answer": "しゃかいちつじょ",
    "meaning": "(maintain, observe) social (public) order"
  },
  {
    "question": "声帯模写",
    "answer": "せいたいもしゃ",
    "meaning": "vocal mimicry"
  },
  {
    "question": "詩吟",
    "answer": "しぎん",
    "meaning": "reciting Chinese poems"
  },
  {
    "question": "水炊き",
    "answer": "みずたき,みずだき",
    "meaning": "food (esp. chicken and vegetables) boiled in plain water (or sometimes dashi, etc.) and served with"
  },
  {
    "question": "直言",
    "answer": "ちょくげん,ただごと,ただこと",
    "meaning": "plain speaking, plain speech, direct speech"
  },
  {
    "question": "青虫",
    "answer": "あおむし",
    "meaning": "cabbageworm (caterpillar of the cabbage white butterfly)"
  },
  {
    "question": "仮借",
    "answer": "かしゃく,かしゃ",
    "meaning": "pardon, extenuation, excuse, borrowing, borrowing a kanji with the same pronunciation to write a sim"
  },
  {
    "question": "半纏",
    "answer": "はんてん",
    "meaning": "traditional short winter coat resembling a haori without gussets, livery coat"
  },
  {
    "question": "糞便",
    "answer": "ふんべん",
    "meaning": "feces"
  },
  {
    "question": "筆を折る",
    "answer": "ふでをおる",
    "meaning": "to break off writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "釣り鐘",
    "answer": "つりがね",
    "meaning": "temple bell, hanging bell, funeral bell"
  },
  {
    "question": "綽名",
    "answer": "あだな",
    "meaning": "nickname"
  },
  {
    "question": "美尻",
    "answer": "びしり",
    "meaning": "beautiful buttocks"
  },
  {
    "question": "寸評",
    "answer": "すんぴょう",
    "meaning": "brief review, brief comment"
  },
  {
    "question": "減殺",
    "answer": "げんさい,げんさつ",
    "meaning": "lessening, diminishing, reducing"
  },
  {
    "question": "深傷",
    "answer": "ふかで",
    "meaning": "severe wound, serious wound, gash"
  },
  {
    "question": "電気椅子",
    "answer": "でんきいす",
    "meaning": "electric chair"
  },
  {
    "question": "渡し船",
    "answer": "わたしぶね",
    "meaning": "ferry, ferryboat"
  },
  {
    "question": "留守居",
    "answer": "るすい",
    "meaning": "house-sitting, house-sitter, caretaker or keeper (official post in the Edo era)"
  },
  {
    "question": "軌",
    "answer": "き",
    "meaning": "rut, wheel track, distance between two wheels, gauge"
  },
  {
    "question": "釣鐘",
    "answer": "つりがね",
    "meaning": "temple bell, hanging bell, funeral bell"
  },
  {
    "question": "平面図",
    "answer": "へいめんず",
    "meaning": "ground plan, plane figure"
  },
  {
    "question": "信用金庫",
    "answer": "しんようきんこ",
    "meaning": "credit union"
  },
  {
    "question": "贈収賄",
    "answer": "ぞうしゅうわい",
    "meaning": "bribery, corruption"
  },
  {
    "question": "顰",
    "answer": "ひそみ,ひん",
    "meaning": "knitted brows, frown"
  },
  {
    "question": "貸家",
    "answer": "かしや,かしいえ",
    "meaning": "house for rent"
  },
  {
    "question": "縄目",
    "answer": "なわめ",
    "meaning": "knot (in rope, etc.), bonds, fetters, arrest, rope impressions (on the surface of pottery)"
  },
  {
    "question": "手拭き",
    "answer": "てふき",
    "meaning": "(hand) towel, handkerchief, paper tissue, napkin, serviette"
  },
  {
    "question": "科捜研",
    "answer": "かそうけん",
    "meaning": "forensic researcher, crime scene investigator"
  },
  {
    "question": "吸い口",
    "answer": "すいくち",
    "meaning": "mouthpiece, cigarette holder, cigarette filter (tip), fragrant garnish (for soup)"
  },
  {
    "question": "血栓",
    "answer": "けっせん",
    "meaning": "thrombus, blood clot"
  },
  {
    "question": "肩叩き",
    "answer": "かたたたき",
    "meaning": "shoulder massage (performed by tapotement), tap on the shoulder (request to resign)"
  },
  {
    "question": "金融業",
    "answer": "きんゆうぎょう",
    "meaning": "finance business, moneylending business"
  },
  {
    "question": "社員食堂",
    "answer": "しゃいんしょくどう",
    "meaning": "staff canteen"
  },
  {
    "question": "虚仮威し",
    "answer": "こけおどし",
    "meaning": "empty threat, bluff, paper tiger"
  },
  {
    "question": "卦",
    "answer": "け",
    "meaning": "divination sign"
  },
  {
    "question": "一神教",
    "answer": "いっしんきょう",
    "meaning": "monotheism"
  },
  {
    "question": "太極拳",
    "answer": "たいきょくけん",
    "meaning": "grand ultimate fist, Tai Chi Chuan"
  },
  {
    "question": "独り寝",
    "answer": "ひとりね",
    "meaning": "sleeping alone"
  },
  {
    "question": "小料理屋",
    "answer": "こりょうりや",
    "meaning": "small restaurant, eating house"
  },
  {
    "question": "謙る",
    "answer": "へりくだる",
    "meaning": "to deprecate oneself and praise the listener, to abase oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "替え歌",
    "answer": "かえうた",
    "meaning": "parody (of a song), new lyrics to an old melody, song parody"
  },
  {
    "question": "荒ぶる神",
    "answer": "あらぶるかみ",
    "meaning": "malevolent god"
  },
  {
    "question": "免責",
    "answer": "めんせき",
    "meaning": "exemption from responsibility, disclaimer"
  },
  {
    "question": "抜き足",
    "answer": "ぬきあし",
    "meaning": "stealthy footsteps"
  },
  {
    "question": "段落",
    "answer": "だんらく",
    "meaning": "paragraph, end, stopping place, conclusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "外光",
    "answer": "がいこう",
    "meaning": "light from outside, natural light"
  },
  {
    "question": "剝げる",
    "answer": "はげる,へげる",
    "meaning": "to come off, to be worn off, to fade, to discolor, to discolour, to peel off"
  },
  {
    "question": "来航",
    "answer": "らいこう",
    "meaning": "arrival of ships, arrival by ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "転出",
    "answer": "てんしゅつ",
    "meaning": "moving out, transfer"
  },
  {
    "question": "空返事",
    "answer": "そらへんじ,からへんじ",
    "meaning": "absentminded response"
  },
  {
    "question": "六法全書",
    "answer": "ろっぽうぜんしょ",
    "meaning": "compendium of laws, statute books, complete book of the Six Codes"
  },
  {
    "question": "付記",
    "answer": "ふき",
    "meaning": "addition, appendix, note, supplement"
  },
  {
    "question": "独身貴族",
    "answer": "どくしんきぞく",
    "meaning": "unmarried person living affluently"
  },
  {
    "question": "非常線",
    "answer": "ひじょうせん",
    "meaning": "cordon"
  },
  {
    "question": "満額",
    "answer": "まんがく",
    "meaning": "full amount"
  },
  {
    "question": "名刺入れ",
    "answer": "めいしいれ",
    "meaning": "(business) card case"
  },
  {
    "question": "値崩れ",
    "answer": "ねくずれ",
    "meaning": "price collapse"
  },
  {
    "question": "打撲傷",
    "answer": "だぼくしょう",
    "meaning": "bruise, contusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "巴投げ",
    "answer": "ともえなげ",
    "meaning": "overhead throw in judo"
  },
  {
    "question": "法定",
    "answer": "ほうてい",
    "meaning": "legal, designated by law"
  },
  {
    "question": "切り貼り",
    "answer": "きりばり",
    "meaning": "patching (up), cutting a part and pasting a new one (e.g. a shoji door), cut and paste"
  },
  {
    "question": "適時",
    "answer": "てきじ",
    "meaning": "timely, opportune"
  },
  {
    "question": "部外",
    "answer": "ぶがい",
    "meaning": "outside the department"
  },
  {
    "question": "大酒",
    "answer": "おおざけ",
    "meaning": "heavy drinking"
  },
  {
    "question": "窃盗罪",
    "answer": "せっとうざい",
    "meaning": "(crime of) theft, (crime of) stealing, larceny"
  },
  {
    "question": "糊付け",
    "answer": "のりづけ,のりつけ",
    "meaning": "starching (e.g. clothes), pasting, gluing (e.g. paper, a letter)"
  },
  {
    "question": "韻を踏む",
    "answer": "いんをふむ",
    "meaning": "to rhyme (with)"
  },
  {
    "question": "前人",
    "answer": "ぜんじん",
    "meaning": "predecessor, people of former times"
  },
  {
    "question": "向学心",
    "answer": "こうがくしん",
    "meaning": "love of learning, desire for learning, passion for knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "粗略",
    "answer": "そりゃく",
    "meaning": "coarse, crude, rough"
  },
  {
    "question": "専有",
    "answer": "せんゆう",
    "meaning": "exclusive possession, sole ownership, monopoly"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼び返す",
    "answer": "よびかえす",
    "meaning": "to call back, to recall"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤蟻",
    "answer": "あかあり",
    "meaning": "red ant"
  },
  {
    "question": "天壌",
    "answer": "てんじょう",
    "meaning": "heaven and earth"
  },
  {
    "question": "六国",
    "answer": "りっこく,ろっこく,りくこく",
    "meaning": "the Six Kingdoms (of China's Warring States period: Qi, Chu, Yan, Han, Wei and Zhao), the six tree-d"
  },
  {
    "question": "天色",
    "answer": "てんしょく",
    "meaning": "weather, sky colour, sky color"
  },
  {
    "question": "槍騎兵",
    "answer": "そうきへい",
    "meaning": "lancer"
  },
  {
    "question": "北辰",
    "answer": "ほくしん",
    "meaning": "North-Star"
  },
  {
    "question": "中納言",
    "answer": "ちゅうなごん,なかのものもうすつかさ,すけのものもうすつかさ",
    "meaning": "medium-ranked councillor in the Department of State"
  },
  {
    "question": "対潜",
    "answer": "たいせん",
    "meaning": "antisubmarine"
  },
  {
    "question": "御伽",
    "answer": "おとぎ",
    "meaning": "attending (upon), keeping another company"
  },
  {
    "question": "三蔵",
    "answer": "さんぞう",
    "meaning": "three branches of Buddhist sutras"
  },
  {
    "question": "脚気",
    "answer": "かっけ",
    "meaning": "beriberi"
  },
  {
    "question": "対バン",
    "answer": "たいバン",
    "meaning": "battle of the bands"
  },
  {
    "question": "召集令状",
    "answer": "しょうしゅうれいじょう",
    "meaning": "draft papers, callup notice"
  },
  {
    "question": "休載",
    "answer": "きゅうさい",
    "meaning": "suspending publication (of serialized content in newspapers, magazines, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "気脈",
    "answer": "きみゃく",
    "meaning": "tacit understanding, connection (of thoughts), collusion, blood vessel"
  },
  {
    "question": "不壊",
    "answer": "ふえ",
    "meaning": "indestructibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "連環",
    "answer": "れんかん",
    "meaning": "links, chain, shackle, linking"
  },
  {
    "question": "燭",
    "answer": "ともしび,しょく",
    "meaning": "light, lamp, torch, obsolete unit of luminous intensity (approx. 1.0067 candela)"
  },
  {
    "question": "素姓",
    "answer": "すじょう,すぞう",
    "meaning": "birth, lineage, parentage, origin, identity, background, history, past, provenance"
  },
  {
    "question": "朝議",
    "answer": "ちょうぎ",
    "meaning": "court council, privy council"
  },
  {
    "question": "結線",
    "answer": "けっせん",
    "meaning": "hard wiring"
  },
  {
    "question": "ヤミ金",
    "answer": "ヤミきん",
    "meaning": "black-market lending, illegal loan"
  },
  {
    "question": "讃",
    "answer": "さん",
    "meaning": "praise, tribute, inscription (on a painting)"
  },
  {
    "question": "米粉",
    "answer": "こめこ,べいふん,ビーフン",
    "meaning": "rice flour, rice vermicelli, rice noodles"
  },
  {
    "question": "撓る",
    "answer": "しなる,しわる",
    "meaning": "to bend, to warp, to yield, to be supple (e.g. bamboo, body), to be flexible, to be pliant"
  },
  {
    "question": "停職",
    "answer": "ていしょく",
    "meaning": "suspension from office"
  },
  {
    "question": "法螺貝",
    "answer": "ほらがい",
    "meaning": "conch (esp. Charonia tritonis), trumpet shell"
  },
  {
    "question": "箱船",
    "answer": "はこぶね",
    "meaning": "ark (i.e. Noah's)"
  },
  {
    "question": "一寸法師",
    "answer": "いっすんぼうし",
    "meaning": "dwarf, midget, elf, Tom Thumb, Jack Sprat, Issun-bōshi (Japanese fairytale)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鞣す",
    "answer": "なめす",
    "meaning": "to tan (leather, hide, etc.), to dress"
  },
  {
    "question": "通信衛星",
    "answer": "つうしんえいせい",
    "meaning": "communication satellite, Broadcast Satellite, BS"
  },
  {
    "question": "雌牛",
    "answer": "めうし,めうじ",
    "meaning": "cow, heifer"
  },
  {
    "question": "鋳鉄",
    "answer": "ちゅうてつ",
    "meaning": "cast iron"
  },
  {
    "question": "冬期",
    "answer": "とうき",
    "meaning": "winter, wintertime, winter term"
  },
  {
    "question": "積る",
    "answer": "つもる",
    "meaning": "to pile up, to accumulate, to estimate"
  },
  {
    "question": "脊柱",
    "answer": "せきちゅう",
    "meaning": "spinal column"
  },
  {
    "question": "無農薬",
    "answer": "むのうやく",
    "meaning": "pesticide-free, non-chemical, organic"
  },
  {
    "question": "源平",
    "answer": "げんぺい",
    "meaning": "Genji and Heike clans, two opposing sides"
  },
  {
    "question": "農閑期",
    "answer": "のうかんき",
    "meaning": "slack season for farmers, leisure season for farmers"
  },
  {
    "question": "年若",
    "answer": "としわか",
    "meaning": "young, youthful"
  },
  {
    "question": "権現",
    "answer": "ごんげん",
    "meaning": "manifestation of a Buddha (or bodhisattva, etc.) in the form of a Shinto kami"
  },
  {
    "question": "傀儡政権",
    "answer": "かいらいせいけん",
    "meaning": "puppet government (regime)"
  },
  {
    "question": "障害者",
    "answer": "しょうがいしゃ",
    "meaning": "disabled person, handicapped person, person with a (physical or mental) disability"
  },
  {
    "question": "変移",
    "answer": "へんい",
    "meaning": "change, alteration, transmutation, mutation"
  },
  {
    "question": "氷砂糖",
    "answer": "こおりざとう",
    "meaning": "rock candy, sugar candy, crystallized sugar, sugar crystals"
  },
  {
    "question": "精励",
    "answer": "せいれい",
    "meaning": "diligence, industry, assiduity, hard work"
  },
  {
    "question": "英才",
    "answer": "えいさい",
    "meaning": "genius, brilliance, unusual talent, gifted person, person of unusual talent"
  },
  {
    "question": "豊胸",
    "answer": "ほうきょう",
    "meaning": "full breasts, ample breasts, breast enlargement"
  },
  {
    "question": "現代語",
    "answer": "げんだいご",
    "meaning": "modern language, contemporary language, living language, modern Japanese, Japanese as spoken since t"
  },
  {
    "question": "符牒",
    "answer": "ふちょう",
    "meaning": "symbol, sign, mark, (secret) price mark, secret language, code, cipher, argot, password"
  },
  {
    "question": "妥当性",
    "answer": "だとうせい",
    "meaning": "validity, verification, propriety"
  },
  {
    "question": "植栽",
    "answer": "しょくさい",
    "meaning": "raising trees and plants"
  },
  {
    "question": "天動説",
    "answer": "てんどうせつ",
    "meaning": "Ptolemaic theory, geocentric model, geocentrism"
  },
  {
    "question": "曲射",
    "answer": "きょくしゃ",
    "meaning": "high-angle fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "共同出資",
    "answer": "きょうどうしゅっし",
    "meaning": "joint investment"
  },
  {
    "question": "天井画",
    "answer": "てんじょうが",
    "meaning": "decorative ceiling painting"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒙",
    "answer": "もう",
    "meaning": "ignorance, covering, concealing, Mongolia"
  },
  {
    "question": "年商",
    "answer": "ねんしょう",
    "meaning": "yearly (annual) turnover"
  },
  {
    "question": "擡げる",
    "answer": "もたげる",
    "meaning": "to raise (one's head)"
  },
  {
    "question": "表われる",
    "answer": "あらわれる",
    "meaning": "to appear, to come in sight, to become visible, to come out, to embody, to materialize, to materiali"
  },
  {
    "question": "欠航",
    "answer": "けっこう",
    "meaning": "cancellation (of a flight or sea voyage)"
  },
  {
    "question": "別ける",
    "answer": "わける",
    "meaning": "to divide (into), to split (into), to part, to separate, to divide up, to classify, to sort out, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "広大無辺",
    "answer": "こうだいむへん",
    "meaning": "boundless, infinite, vast"
  },
  {
    "question": "同好",
    "answer": "どうこう",
    "meaning": "similar tastes"
  },
  {
    "question": "細腰",
    "answer": "さいよう,ほそごし",
    "meaning": "slender hips, slim waist"
  },
  {
    "question": "阿漕",
    "answer": "あこぎ",
    "meaning": "greed, cruelty, insistent, insistence"
  },
  {
    "question": "排気量",
    "answer": "はいきりょう",
    "meaning": "(engine) displacement"
  },
  {
    "question": "闇ルート",
    "answer": "やみルート",
    "meaning": "black-market channels, illegal channels"
  },
  {
    "question": "非業",
    "answer": "ひごう",
    "meaning": "unnatural or untimely (death)"
  },
  {
    "question": "骨折り",
    "answer": "ほねおり",
    "meaning": "pains, efforts, trouble, labor, labour, services"
  },
  {
    "question": "柄物",
    "answer": "がらもの",
    "meaning": "patterned cloth"
  },
  {
    "question": "猪口才",
    "answer": "ちょこざい",
    "meaning": "impertinent, impudent, saucy, cheeky"
  },
  {
    "question": "木石",
    "answer": "ぼくせき",
    "meaning": "trees and stones, unfeeling person"
  },
  {
    "question": "労しい",
    "answer": "いたわしい",
    "meaning": "heartrending, pitiful, saddening, pathetic, heart-breaking"
  },
  {
    "question": "内の者",
    "answer": "うちのもの",
    "meaning": "member of one's 'in group' (e.g. one's family, employees, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "門外",
    "answer": "もんがい",
    "meaning": "outside a gate, beyond one's area of expertise"
  },
  {
    "question": "雄視",
    "answer": "ゆうし",
    "meaning": "overwhelming, overpowering, prevailing"
  },
  {
    "question": "痛し痒し",
    "answer": "いたしかゆし",
    "meaning": "delicate situation, choice of two evils, mixed blessing"
  },
  {
    "question": "一稼ぎ",
    "answer": "ひとかせぎ",
    "meaning": "job, gain"
  },
  {
    "question": "尾鰭",
    "answer": "おひれ,おびれ",
    "meaning": "tail and fins, embellishment (of a story, rumor, etc.), exaggeration, caudal fin, tail fin"
  },
  {
    "question": "俗語",
    "answer": "ぞくご",
    "meaning": "colloquialism, colloquial language, slang"
  },
  {
    "question": "話し言葉",
    "answer": "はなしことば",
    "meaning": "spoken language, colloquial expression"
  },
  {
    "question": "立て膝",
    "answer": "たてひざ",
    "meaning": "sitting with one knee drawn up"
  },
  {
    "question": "胃炎",
    "answer": "いえん",
    "meaning": "gastritis, gastric catarrh"
  },
  {
    "question": "記憶容量",
    "answer": "きおくようりょう",
    "meaning": "storage capacity, memory capacity"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒み",
    "answer": "くろみ",
    "meaning": "black tinge, black colour, black color, black part, dark spot"
  },
  {
    "question": "必見",
    "answer": "ひっけん",
    "meaning": "must-see, not to be missed, a must"
  },
  {
    "question": "話が付く",
    "answer": "はなしがつく",
    "meaning": "to come to an agreement"
  },
  {
    "question": "抗菌",
    "answer": "こうきん",
    "meaning": "antibacterial, antimicrobial"
  },
  {
    "question": "出来す",
    "answer": "でかす",
    "meaning": "to do, to commit, to accomplish, to achieve"
  },
  {
    "question": "侃々諤々",
    "answer": "かんかんがくがく",
    "meaning": "outspoken, arguing (heatedly) what one believes in, insisting on something without restraint"
  },
  {
    "question": "瘧",
    "answer": "おこり,わらわやみ,えやみ",
    "meaning": "ague, intermittent fever, the shakes, malarial fever (old name), infectious disease, plague, epidemi"
  },
  {
    "question": "論う",
    "answer": "あげつらう",
    "meaning": "to discuss, to find fault with, to criticize, to criticise"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち腐れ",
    "answer": "もちぐされ",
    "meaning": "unused possession"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち駒",
    "answer": "もちごま",
    "meaning": "captured piece that can be reused, person or object held in reserve, available means"
  },
  {
    "question": "肩肘",
    "answer": "かたひじ",
    "meaning": "shoulders and elbows"
  },
  {
    "question": "行人",
    "answer": "こうじん",
    "meaning": "passer-by, traveler, traveller"
  },
  {
    "question": "尾長",
    "answer": "おなが",
    "meaning": "azure-winged magpie (Cyanopica cyana), long-tailed"
  },
  {
    "question": "勅許",
    "answer": "ちょっきょ",
    "meaning": "imperial sanction, royal charter, chartered (e.g. chartered accountant)"
  },
  {
    "question": "天目",
    "answer": "てんもく",
    "meaning": "tenmoku, ceramics (esp. tea bowls) with a dark glaze that resembles oil spotting, tenmoku tea-bowl,"
  },
  {
    "question": "市松",
    "answer": "いちまつ",
    "meaning": "check (pattern), ichimatsu doll"
  },
  {
    "question": "加持",
    "answer": "かじ",
    "meaning": "faith-healing, incantation"
  },
  {
    "question": "延暦",
    "answer": "えんりゃく",
    "meaning": "Enryaku era (782.8.19-806.5.18)"
  },
  {
    "question": "天真",
    "answer": "てんしん",
    "meaning": "naivete"
  },
  {
    "question": "会計監査",
    "answer": "かいけいかんさ",
    "meaning": "audit, auditing"
  },
  {
    "question": "総支配人",
    "answer": "そうしはいにん",
    "meaning": "general manager"
  },
  {
    "question": "四囲",
    "answer": "しい",
    "meaning": "surroundings, circumference"
  },
  {
    "question": "外力",
    "answer": "がいりょく",
    "meaning": "external force"
  },
  {
    "question": "中性子",
    "answer": "ちゅうせいし",
    "meaning": "neutron"
  },
  {
    "question": "月蝕",
    "answer": "げっしょく",
    "meaning": "lunar eclipse"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛤",
    "answer": "はまぐり,かえる",
    "meaning": "common orient clam (Meretrix lusoria), frog"
  },
  {
    "question": "上皇",
    "answer": "じょうこう",
    "meaning": "retired emperor, ex-emperor, former emperor, emperor emeritus"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄甲",
    "answer": "てっこう",
    "meaning": "iron armor (armour), iron helmet"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄白い",
    "answer": "うすじろい",
    "meaning": "whitish"
  },
  {
    "question": "驚倒",
    "answer": "きょうとう",
    "meaning": "being very surprised, being utterly astonished, being shocked"
  },
  {
    "question": "大元帥",
    "answer": "だいげんすい",
    "meaning": "commander-in-chief, generalissimo"
  },
  {
    "question": "掠奪",
    "answer": "りゃくだつ",
    "meaning": "pillage, plunder, looting, robbery"
  },
  {
    "question": "学則",
    "answer": "がくそく",
    "meaning": "school regulations"
  },
  {
    "question": "切札",
    "answer": "きりふだ",
    "meaning": "trump card, ace up one's sleeve, secret weapon"
  },
  {
    "question": "校閲",
    "answer": "こうえつ",
    "meaning": "revision, proofreading"
  },
  {
    "question": "薬袋",
    "answer": "やくたい",
    "meaning": "prescription bag, pharmacy bag, small bottle for carrying gunpowder"
  },
  {
    "question": "癌細胞",
    "answer": "がんさいぼう",
    "meaning": "cancer cell"
  },
  {
    "question": "街頭演説",
    "answer": "がいとうえんぜつ",
    "meaning": "street oratory, soapbox speech"
  },
  {
    "question": "馬刺し",
    "answer": "ばさし",
    "meaning": "horse-meat sashimi"
  },
  {
    "question": "球威",
    "answer": "きゅうい",
    "meaning": "(pitcher's) stuff"
  },
  {
    "question": "大筒",
    "answer": "おおづつ",
    "meaning": "cannon"
  },
  {
    "question": "外苑",
    "answer": "がいえん",
    "meaning": "outer garden"
  },
  {
    "question": "落花生",
    "answer": "らっかせい",
    "meaning": "peanut (Arachis hypogaea), groundnut"
  },
  {
    "question": "視聴覚",
    "answer": "しちょうかく",
    "meaning": "senses of seeing and hearing, audiovisual"
  },
  {
    "question": "当確",
    "answer": "とうかく",
    "meaning": "projected to win, sure to be elected, home free"
  },
  {
    "question": "現着",
    "answer": "げんちゃく",
    "meaning": "arrival on location (esp. used in transport industries, police, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "意味深長",
    "answer": "いみしんちょう",
    "meaning": "with profound (often hidden) meaning, pregnant with significance, meaningful, suggestive, interestin"
  },
  {
    "question": "婉然",
    "answer": "えんぜん",
    "meaning": "graceful, beautiful"
  },
  {
    "question": "生菓子",
    "answer": "なまがし",
    "meaning": "fresh Japanese sweets (usu. containing red bean paste), fresh Western sweets (usu. containing cream"
  },
  {
    "question": "波飛沫",
    "answer": "なみしぶき",
    "meaning": "sea spray, spindrift"
  },
  {
    "question": "闘魂",
    "answer": "とうこん",
    "meaning": "fighting spirit"
  },
  {
    "question": "粉チーズ",
    "answer": "こなチーズ",
    "meaning": "powdered cheese, cheese powder"
  },
  {
    "question": "同心円",
    "answer": "どうしんえん",
    "meaning": "concentric circles"
  },
  {
    "question": "埼",
    "answer": "さき",
    "meaning": "small peninsula, cape, promontory, headland"
  },
  {
    "question": "大腿",
    "answer": "だいたい",
    "meaning": "thigh"
  },
  {
    "question": "弾除け",
    "answer": "たまよけ",
    "meaning": "bulletproof, protection (or charm) against bullets"
  },
  {
    "question": "教育課程",
    "answer": "きょういくかてい",
    "meaning": "curriculum"
  },
  {
    "question": "送致",
    "answer": "そうち",
    "meaning": "sending, forwarding"
  },
  {
    "question": "閉所",
    "answer": "へいしょ",
    "meaning": "confined place, closing (an institution, office, clinic, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "紺地",
    "answer": "こんじ",
    "meaning": "dark blue ground, dark blue cloth"
  },
  {
    "question": "季語",
    "answer": "きご",
    "meaning": "seasonal word (in haiku)"
  },
  {
    "question": "皆々",
    "answer": "みなみな",
    "meaning": "all, everyone, everybody, everything"
  },
  {
    "question": "恩給",
    "answer": "おんきゅう",
    "meaning": "pension (esp. public servant's), a lord giving a land holding to a vassal"
  },
  {
    "question": "神経症",
    "answer": "しんけいしょう",
    "meaning": "nervous disorder, neurosis"
  },
  {
    "question": "泥土",
    "answer": "でいど",
    "meaning": "mud"
  },
  {
    "question": "洒脱",
    "answer": "しゃだつ",
    "meaning": "sophisticated, refined, witty, urbane, unconstrained"
  },
  {
    "question": "本機",
    "answer": "ほんき",
    "meaning": "this device, this plane"
  },
  {
    "question": "土踏まず",
    "answer": "つちふまず",
    "meaning": "arch of the foot, plantar arch"
  },
  {
    "question": "日本舞踊",
    "answer": "にほんぶよう",
    "meaning": "traditional Japanese dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "大仕掛け",
    "answer": "おおじかけ",
    "meaning": "large-scale"
  },
  {
    "question": "自任",
    "answer": "じにん",
    "meaning": "regarding oneself (as), fancying oneself (as), seeing oneself (as), considering oneself (to be), pre"
  },
  {
    "question": "話し好き",
    "answer": "はなしずき",
    "meaning": "talkative person, gossip"
  },
  {
    "question": "御茶",
    "answer": "おちゃ",
    "meaning": "tea (usu. green), tea break (at work), tea ceremony"
  },
  {
    "question": "没後",
    "answer": "ぼつご",
    "meaning": "after death, posthumously"
  },
  {
    "question": "万年雪",
    "answer": "まんねんゆき",
    "meaning": "perpetual snow"
  },
  {
    "question": "劇画",
    "answer": "げきが",
    "meaning": "comic strip with dramatic story"
  },
  {
    "question": "仏門",
    "answer": "ぶつもん",
    "meaning": "Buddhism, priesthood"
  },
  {
    "question": "雛形",
    "answer": "ひながた",
    "meaning": "model, miniature, pattern, sample, specimen, prescribed form"
  },
  {
    "question": "重る",
    "answer": "おもる",
    "meaning": "to get heavy, to worsen (of illness), to grow serious"
  },
  {
    "question": "押し頂く",
    "answer": "おしいただく",
    "meaning": "to accept an object and hold it reverently over one's head"
  },
  {
    "question": "異才",
    "answer": "いさい",
    "meaning": "genius, prodigy, (person of) great talent, remarkable person"
  },
  {
    "question": "勃興",
    "answer": "ぼっこう",
    "meaning": "sudden rise to power, sudden rise in prosperity"
  },
  {
    "question": "筋立て",
    "answer": "すじだて",
    "meaning": "plot (of a story)"
  },
  {
    "question": "精根",
    "answer": "せいこん",
    "meaning": "energy, vitality, mental determination"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝違える",
    "answer": "ねちがえる",
    "meaning": "to get a crick in one's neck (while sleeping)"
  },
  {
    "question": "虫干し",
    "answer": "むしぼし",
    "meaning": "airing of clothes, hanging scrolls, etc. (to prevent damage from insects and mould)"
  },
  {
    "question": "引止める",
    "answer": "ひきとめる",
    "meaning": "to detain, to check, to restrain"
  },
  {
    "question": "流行語",
    "answer": "りゅうこうご",
    "meaning": "buzzword, vogue word, popular phrase"
  },
  {
    "question": "渋味",
    "answer": "しぶみ",
    "meaning": "astringency, tartness, austere elegance, elegant simplicity, subdued style, quiet taste, refinement"
  },
  {
    "question": "多趣味",
    "answer": "たしゅみ",
    "meaning": "having various interests, wide range of interests"
  },
  {
    "question": "謗り",
    "answer": "そしり",
    "meaning": "censure, criticism, blame, disparagement, vilification"
  },
  {
    "question": "心憎い",
    "answer": "こころにくい",
    "meaning": "refined, admirable, superb"
  },
  {
    "question": "両袖",
    "answer": "りょうそで",
    "meaning": "both sleeves"
  },
  {
    "question": "煮え湯",
    "answer": "にえゆ",
    "meaning": "boiling water"
  },
  {
    "question": "ぼろ儲け",
    "answer": "ぼろもうけ",
    "meaning": "easy money, easy gain, making a killing"
  },
  {
    "question": "見方",
    "answer": "みかた",
    "meaning": "viewpoint, point of view, way of understanding, way of appreciating, how to look at something (e.g."
  },
  {
    "question": "ずれ込む",
    "answer": "ずれこむ",
    "meaning": "to drag on, to be delayed"
  },
  {
    "question": "両輪",
    "answer": "りょうりん",
    "meaning": "two wheels"
  },
  {
    "question": "雅兄",
    "answer": "がけい",
    "meaning": "you"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒円",
    "answer": "くろまる",
    "meaning": "black spot, black dot, bull's-eye, middle dot, interpunct"
  },
  {
    "question": "朽葉",
    "answer": "くちば",
    "meaning": "decayed leaves, russet, tawny, yellow-brown"
  },
  {
    "question": "定跡",
    "answer": "じょうせき",
    "meaning": "standard move"
  },
  {
    "question": "大悟",
    "answer": "たいご,だいご",
    "meaning": "enlightenment, great wisdom"
  },
  {
    "question": "花祭り",
    "answer": "はなまつり",
    "meaning": "Buddha's birthday festival (April 8th), Vesak"
  },
  {
    "question": "動輪",
    "answer": "どうりん",
    "meaning": "driving wheel"
  },
  {
    "question": "救命艇",
    "answer": "きゅうめいてい",
    "meaning": "lifeboat"
  },
  {
    "question": "大統領府",
    "answer": "だいとうりょうふ",
    "meaning": "Executive Office of the President (USA, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "西部戦線",
    "answer": "せいぶせんせん",
    "meaning": "the Western Front"
  },
  {
    "question": "交流戦",
    "answer": "こうりゅうせん",
    "meaning": "exhibition game, friendly match, friendly, interleague game between the Central and Pacific baseball"
  },
  {
    "question": "休廷",
    "answer": "きゅうてい",
    "meaning": "court recess"
  },
  {
    "question": "債券",
    "answer": "さいけん",
    "meaning": "bond, debenture"
  },
  {
    "question": "回天",
    "answer": "かいてん",
    "meaning": "changing the world, turning the tide, torpedo modified as a suicide weapon (used in WWII)"
  },
  {
    "question": "太閤",
    "answer": "たいこう",
    "meaning": "taikō (esp. Toyotomi Hideyoshi), title for a regent, later for the grand chancellor, also for the fa"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄",
    "answer": "すすき,うす",
    "meaning": "Japanese pampas grass (Miscanthus sinensis), maiden silvergrass, zebra grass, light (e.g. colour, co"
  },
  {
    "question": "穀倉",
    "answer": "こくそう,こくぐら",
    "meaning": "granary"
  },
  {
    "question": "代替物",
    "answer": "だいたいぶつ",
    "meaning": "substitute article"
  },
  {
    "question": "一等兵",
    "answer": "いっとうへい",
    "meaning": "private (e-2) (US)"
  },
  {
    "question": "防衛庁",
    "answer": "ぼうえいちょう",
    "meaning": "Japan Defense Agency (became Ministry of Defense in January 2007)"
  },
  {
    "question": "実業団",
    "answer": "じつぎょうだん",
    "meaning": "corporate (e.g. sports team), business organization, business corporation"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻眼鏡",
    "answer": "はなめがね",
    "meaning": "pince-nez glasses, pince-nez, nose glasses, Groucho glasses"
  },
  {
    "question": "仮令",
    "answer": "たとえ,たとい",
    "meaning": "even if, no matter (what), if, though, although, supposing, supposing that, -ever"
  },
  {
    "question": "閨房",
    "answer": "けいぼう",
    "meaning": "bedroom, (woman's) bedchamber, pillow talk"
  },
  {
    "question": "女店員",
    "answer": "じょてんいん",
    "meaning": "saleswoman, shopgirl"
  },
  {
    "question": "秩父",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "金気",
    "answer": "かなけ",
    "meaning": "metallic taste, taste of iron"
  },
  {
    "question": "勇戦",
    "answer": "ゆうせん",
    "meaning": "brave fight, desperate fight"
  },
  {
    "question": "釘抜き",
    "answer": "くぎぬき",
    "meaning": "pincers, nail puller"
  },
  {
    "question": "丁字路",
    "answer": "ていじろ",
    "meaning": "T junction"
  },
  {
    "question": "内見",
    "answer": "ないけん",
    "meaning": "preview, private viewing"
  },
  {
    "question": "主審",
    "answer": "しゅしん",
    "meaning": "chief umpire, referee (soccer, boxing, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "南北戦争",
    "answer": "なんぼくせんそう",
    "meaning": "(US) Civil War"
  },
  {
    "question": "仏間",
    "answer": "ぶつま",
    "meaning": "Buddhist family chapel, altar room"
  },
  {
    "question": "家族風呂",
    "answer": "かぞくぶろ",
    "meaning": "family bath (in a ryokan, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "伊勢海老",
    "answer": "いせえび",
    "meaning": "spiny lobster (esp. Japanese spiny lobster, Panulirus japonicus)"
  },
  {
    "question": "後書き",
    "answer": "あとがき",
    "meaning": "afterword, postscript"
  },
  {
    "question": "幅跳び",
    "answer": "はばとび",
    "meaning": "long jump, broad jump"
  },
  {
    "question": "佳作",
    "answer": "かさく",
    "meaning": "good piece of work, honourable mention (honorable)"
  },
  {
    "question": "政体",
    "answer": "せいたい",
    "meaning": "form of government, system of government, polity"
  },
  {
    "question": "土偶",
    "answer": "どぐう",
    "meaning": "earthen figure, clay figure, dogū, clay figurines from the late Jōmon period"
  },
  {
    "question": "遮断機",
    "answer": "しゃだんき",
    "meaning": "railway crossing gate"
  },
  {
    "question": "啓発",
    "answer": "けいはつ",
    "meaning": "enlightenment, development, edification, public awareness, illumination, education, inspiration"
  },
  {
    "question": "民主制",
    "answer": "みんしゅせい",
    "meaning": "democracy, democratic system of government"
  },
  {
    "question": "御付き",
    "answer": "おつき",
    "meaning": "retainer, attendant, escort"
  },
  {
    "question": "皴",
    "answer": "しわ,しゅん",
    "meaning": "wrinkle, crease, ripple"
  },
  {
    "question": "創傷",
    "answer": "そうしょう",
    "meaning": "wound"
  },
  {
    "question": "徒然",
    "answer": "つれづれ,とぜん",
    "meaning": "tedium, boredom, ennui"
  },
  {
    "question": "無期",
    "answer": "むき",
    "meaning": "indefinite, unlimited, life imprisonment"
  },
  {
    "question": "今上",
    "answer": "きんじょう",
    "meaning": "His Majesty the Emperor, the present emperor, the reigning emperor"
  },
  {
    "question": "薬包",
    "answer": "やくほう",
    "meaning": "chartula, cartridge"
  },
  {
    "question": "長編小説",
    "answer": "ちょうへんしょうせつ",
    "meaning": "full-length novel"
  },
  {
    "question": "千羽鶴",
    "answer": "せんばづる",
    "meaning": "(string of) many (traditionally 1000) paper cranes"
  },
  {
    "question": "農協",
    "answer": "のうきょう",
    "meaning": "agricultural cooperative"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛇の目",
    "answer": "じゃのめ",
    "meaning": "bull's-eye (pattern), double ring (pattern), umbrella with bull's-eye pattern"
  },
  {
    "question": "国風",
    "answer": "こくふう,くにぶり",
    "meaning": "national customs and manners, provincial song or ballad, waka (classical Japanese poetry, as opposed"
  },
  {
    "question": "釣り具",
    "answer": "つりぐ",
    "meaning": "fishing gear, fishing tackle"
  },
  {
    "question": "焚書",
    "answer": "ふんしょ",
    "meaning": "book burning"
  },
  {
    "question": "呈示",
    "answer": "ていし,ていじ",
    "meaning": "exhibition"
  },
  {
    "question": "地質学",
    "answer": "ちしつがく",
    "meaning": "geology"
  },
  {
    "question": "禁足",
    "answer": "きんそく",
    "meaning": "confinement"
  },
  {
    "question": "好漢",
    "answer": "こうかん",
    "meaning": "fine fellow"
  },
  {
    "question": "中背",
    "answer": "ちゅうぜい",
    "meaning": "average height"
  },
  {
    "question": "部材",
    "answer": "ぶざい",
    "meaning": "component, part, material, member"
  },
  {
    "question": "排便",
    "answer": "はいべん",
    "meaning": "defecation"
  },
  {
    "question": "情報化",
    "answer": "じょうほうか",
    "meaning": "computerization, computerisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "差し足",
    "answer": "さしあし",
    "meaning": "stealthy steps, spurt to overtake a leading horse just before the finish line"
  },
  {
    "question": "手水",
    "answer": "てみず,ちょうず",
    "meaning": "water for washing or moistening one's hands"
  },
  {
    "question": "零下",
    "answer": "れいか",
    "meaning": "below zero, sub-zero"
  },
  {
    "question": "母数",
    "answer": "ぼすう",
    "meaning": "(statistical) parameter"
  },
  {
    "question": "地磁気",
    "answer": "ちじき",
    "meaning": "geomagnetism, terrestrial magnetism"
  },
  {
    "question": "決す",
    "answer": "けっす",
    "meaning": "to decide, to determine"
  },
  {
    "question": "組体操",
    "answer": "くみたいそう",
    "meaning": "coordinated group gymnastics (in which teams form pyramids or other shapes)"
  },
  {
    "question": "脳卒中",
    "answer": "のうそっちゅう",
    "meaning": "stroke, cerebral haemorrhage, cerebral hemorrhage"
  },
  {
    "question": "忘る",
    "answer": "わする",
    "meaning": "to lose something"
  },
  {
    "question": "体脂肪率",
    "answer": "たいしぼうりつ",
    "meaning": "body fat percentage"
  },
  {
    "question": "流動食",
    "answer": "りゅうどうしょく",
    "meaning": "liquid food (diet)"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち合う",
    "answer": "もちあう",
    "meaning": "to balance, to counterpoise, to remain unchanged, to share (e.g. the expense), to bear (part of)"
  },
  {
    "question": "金満",
    "answer": "きんまん",
    "meaning": "being rich, having plenty of money, wallowing in money"
  },
  {
    "question": "詣でる",
    "answer": "もうでる",
    "meaning": "to make a pilgrimage"
  },
  {
    "question": "床上",
    "answer": "ゆかうえ",
    "meaning": "on a floor, above floor level"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷酒",
    "answer": "ひやざけ,れいしゅ",
    "meaning": "cold sake"
  },
  {
    "question": "自然保護",
    "answer": "しぜんほご",
    "meaning": "nature conservation"
  },
  {
    "question": "手を拱く",
    "answer": "てをこまねく,てをこまぬく",
    "meaning": "to fold one's arms, to stand and watch (without interfering)"
  },
  {
    "question": "古典文学",
    "answer": "こてんぶんがく",
    "meaning": "classical literature"
  },
  {
    "question": "色情狂",
    "answer": "しきじょうきょう",
    "meaning": "sex mania"
  },
  {
    "question": "水撒き",
    "answer": "みずまき",
    "meaning": "watering, sprinkling"
  },
  {
    "question": "荷下ろし",
    "answer": "におろし",
    "meaning": "unloading (cargo, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "宗教戦争",
    "answer": "しゅうきょうせんそう",
    "meaning": "religious war"
  },
  {
    "question": "系図",
    "answer": "けいず",
    "meaning": "family tree, pedigree, genealogy"
  },
  {
    "question": "未来像",
    "answer": "みらいぞう",
    "meaning": "vision of the future"
  },
  {
    "question": "信賞必罰",
    "answer": "しんしょうひつばつ",
    "meaning": "sure punishment or reward"
  },
  {
    "question": "陰謀説",
    "answer": "いんぼうせつ",
    "meaning": "conspiracy theory"
  },
  {
    "question": "置き傘",
    "answer": "おきがさ",
    "meaning": "spare umbrella kept (at work) in the event of a sudden shower"
  },
  {
    "question": "青草",
    "answer": "あおくさ,せいそう",
    "meaning": "green grass"
  },
  {
    "question": "鍋物",
    "answer": "なべもの",
    "meaning": "stew, food cooked in a pot"
  },
  {
    "question": "動ずる",
    "answer": "どうずる",
    "meaning": "to be perturbed, to be agitated"
  },
  {
    "question": "洒落っ気",
    "answer": "しゃれっけ",
    "meaning": "fashion-consciousness, desire to be stylish, humor, humour, wit"
  },
  {
    "question": "盲従",
    "answer": "もうじゅう",
    "meaning": "blind obedience"
  },
  {
    "question": "錆付く",
    "answer": "さびつく",
    "meaning": "to become rusted together, to become rusted shut, to rust, to become (completely) rusty, to be cover"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽挙妄動",
    "answer": "けいきょもうどう",
    "meaning": "rash and blind act"
  },
  {
    "question": "慮外者",
    "answer": "りょがいもの",
    "meaning": "rude person, insolent person"
  },
  {
    "question": "理想型",
    "answer": "りそうけい",
    "meaning": "ideal type"
  },
  {
    "question": "乱暴狼藉",
    "answer": "らんぼうろうぜき",
    "meaning": "running amok (amuck), committing an outrage, rampageous behavior"
  },
  {
    "question": "深爪",
    "answer": "ふかづめ",
    "meaning": "cutting a fingernail (or toenail) to the quick, cutting a nail too close, deep-set nail, deep-set pa"
  },
  {
    "question": "北緯",
    "answer": "ほくい",
    "meaning": "north latitude"
  },
  {
    "question": "併記",
    "answer": "へいき",
    "meaning": "writing side by side"
  },
  {
    "question": "直観的",
    "answer": "ちょっかんてき",
    "meaning": "intuitive"
  },
  {
    "question": "売り言葉",
    "answer": "うりことば",
    "meaning": "inflammatory words"
  },
  {
    "question": "毀損",
    "answer": "きそん",
    "meaning": "damage, injury, defamation, harm"
  },
  {
    "question": "紙質",
    "answer": "ししつ",
    "meaning": "paper quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "年波",
    "answer": "としなみ",
    "meaning": "old age, oncoming age"
  },
  {
    "question": "上り調子",
    "answer": "のぼりちょうし,のぼりぢょうし",
    "meaning": "rise, improvement, uptrend"
  },
  {
    "question": "引く手",
    "answer": "ひくて",
    "meaning": "admirer, inducer"
  },
  {
    "question": "枚挙",
    "answer": "まいきょ",
    "meaning": "enumeration"
  },
  {
    "question": "一昨",
    "answer": "いっさく",
    "meaning": "one previous"
  },
  {
    "question": "波旬",
    "answer": "はじゅん",
    "meaning": "killer demon, demon who strives to destroy all goodness"
  },
  {
    "question": "敦賀",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "赤髭",
    "answer": "あかひげ",
    "meaning": "red beard, person with a red beard, Westerner, Ryukyu robin (Erithacus komadori)"
  },
  {
    "question": "賦役",
    "answer": "ふえき,ぶやく",
    "meaning": "slave labour, slave labor, compulsory service, forced labour, forced labor, exacted service"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀鈴",
    "answer": "ぎんれい",
    "meaning": "silver bell"
  },
  {
    "question": "鴛鴦",
    "answer": "おしどり,えんおう,おし",
    "meaning": "mandarin duck"
  },
  {
    "question": "新開",
    "answer": "しんかい",
    "meaning": "opening (of uncultivated land)"
  },
  {
    "question": "西ドイツ",
    "answer": "にしドイツ",
    "meaning": "West Germany (1949-1990), Federal Republic of Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "妓楼",
    "answer": "ぎろう",
    "meaning": "brothel"
  },
  {
    "question": "書写",
    "answer": "しょしゃ",
    "meaning": "transcription, copying, handwriting (as a school subject), penmanship"
  },
  {
    "question": "不知",
    "answer": "ふち,しらず",
    "meaning": "being unknown, not knowing, ignorance, foolishness, not having, unaffected by, aside, I don't know a"
  },
  {
    "question": "刑部",
    "answer": "けいぶ",
    "meaning": "Ministry of Justice (Tang-dynasty China)"
  },
  {
    "question": "貢",
    "answer": "こう",
    "meaning": "tribute"
  },
  {
    "question": "島人",
    "answer": "とうじん",
    "meaning": "islanders"
  },
  {
    "question": "薬種",
    "answer": "やくしゅ",
    "meaning": "drugs, ingredients (for Chinese medicine)"
  },
  {
    "question": "枢軸",
    "answer": "すうじく",
    "meaning": "axle, pivot"
  },
  {
    "question": "皹",
    "answer": "ひび,あかぎれ",
    "meaning": "crack, fissure, rift, split, chaps, skin fissure"
  },
  {
    "question": "大垣",
    "answer": "おおがき",
    "meaning": "roofed mud wall around a villa or temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "恥垢",
    "answer": "ちこう",
    "meaning": "smegma"
  },
  {
    "question": "確り",
    "answer": "しっかり",
    "meaning": "tightly (holding on), firmly, securely, strongly (built), solidly, sturdily, steadily, properly, wel"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄金律",
    "answer": "おうごんりつ",
    "meaning": "The Golden Rule ('do unto others as you would have them do unto you')"
  },
  {
    "question": "納車",
    "answer": "のうしゃ",
    "meaning": "delivery of a vehicle (to its new owner)"
  },
  {
    "question": "会則",
    "answer": "かいそく",
    "meaning": "society regulations, club regulations, constitution"
  },
  {
    "question": "水練",
    "answer": "すいれん",
    "meaning": "swimming practice"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍事衛星",
    "answer": "ぐんじえいせい",
    "meaning": "military satellite"
  },
  {
    "question": "鳩時計",
    "answer": "はとどけい",
    "meaning": "cuckoo clock"
  },
  {
    "question": "金剛力士",
    "answer": "こんごうりきし",
    "meaning": "Deva king, fierce guardian god (at a temple gate)"
  },
  {
    "question": "送り火",
    "answer": "おくりび",
    "meaning": "ceremonial bonfire (seeing off the spirits on the final night of O-Bon)"
  },
  {
    "question": "駅馬車",
    "answer": "えきばしゃ",
    "meaning": "stagecoach"
  },
  {
    "question": "内閣府",
    "answer": "ないかくふ",
    "meaning": "Cabinet Office"
  },
  {
    "question": "畜生道",
    "answer": "ちくしょうどう",
    "meaning": "animal realm, unforgivable action, indefensible lifestyle, incest"
  },
  {
    "question": "両派",
    "answer": "りょうは",
    "meaning": "both groups, both factions"
  },
  {
    "question": "仄白い",
    "answer": "ほのじろい",
    "meaning": "dimly white"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒褐色",
    "answer": "こっかっしょく",
    "meaning": "blackish brown"
  },
  {
    "question": "徴募",
    "answer": "ちょうぼ",
    "meaning": "enlistment, recruitment"
  },
  {
    "question": "山葵",
    "answer": "わさび",
    "meaning": "wasabi (Wasabia japonica), Japanese horseradish"
  },
  {
    "question": "馬鈴薯",
    "answer": "ばれいしょ",
    "meaning": "potato (Solanum tuberosum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "綱紀粛正",
    "answer": "こうきしゅくせい",
    "meaning": "enforcement of official discipline, tightening of discipline, eliminating corruption among governmen"
  },
  {
    "question": "雀荘",
    "answer": "ジャンそう",
    "meaning": "mahjong parlour, mahjong parlor"
  },
  {
    "question": "常春",
    "answer": "とこはる",
    "meaning": "everlasting spring"
  },
  {
    "question": "差し招く",
    "answer": "さしまねく",
    "meaning": "to beckon (to)"
  },
  {
    "question": "稀覯本",
    "answer": "きこうぼん",
    "meaning": "rare book"
  },
  {
    "question": "農林",
    "answer": "のうりん",
    "meaning": "agriculture and forestry"
  },
  {
    "question": "融点",
    "answer": "ゆうてん",
    "meaning": "fusion point, melting point"
  },
  {
    "question": "破戒",
    "answer": "はかい",
    "meaning": "breaking a commandment (usually religious), offense against the Buddhist commandments (offence)"
  },
  {
    "question": "雇い人",
    "answer": "やといにん",
    "meaning": "employee"
  },
  {
    "question": "新館",
    "answer": "しんかん",
    "meaning": "new building, annexe, annex"
  },
  {
    "question": "鋳物",
    "answer": "いもの",
    "meaning": "casting, cast-metal object"
  },
  {
    "question": "漫遊",
    "answer": "まんゆう",
    "meaning": "pleasure trip, tour"
  },
  {
    "question": "七福神",
    "answer": "しちふくじん",
    "meaning": "Seven Gods of Fortune, Seven Deities of Good Luck, Seven Lucky Gods"
  },
  {
    "question": "咲う",
    "answer": "わらう",
    "meaning": "to laugh, to smile, to sneer, to ridicule, to be dumbfounded, to be flabbergasted"
  },
  {
    "question": "音合わせ",
    "answer": "おとあわせ",
    "meaning": "(musical) tuning"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛敬",
    "answer": "あいきょう,あいぎょう,あいけい",
    "meaning": "charm, attractiveness, amiability, winsomeness, courtesy, ingratiating behaviour, entertainment, amu"
  },
  {
    "question": "環境汚染",
    "answer": "かんきょうおせん",
    "meaning": "environmental pollution"
  },
  {
    "question": "毀れる",
    "answer": "こわれる,こぼれる",
    "meaning": "to be broken, to break, to fall through, to come to nothing, to be chipped, to be nicked"
  },
  {
    "question": "限り無い",
    "answer": "かぎりない",
    "meaning": "eternal, unlimited, endless"
  },
  {
    "question": "瀬戸物",
    "answer": "せともの",
    "meaning": "earthenware, porcelain, china, pottery, crockery"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い種",
    "answer": "いいぐさ",
    "meaning": "remarks, comments, way of talking, speaking style, excuse, topic (of conversation)"
  },
  {
    "question": "炙り出し",
    "answer": "あぶりだし",
    "meaning": "invisible writing revealed by applying heat, writing done in invisible ink"
  },
  {
    "question": "間々",
    "answer": "まま",
    "meaning": "occasionally, now and then, sometimes"
  },
  {
    "question": "犬ころ",
    "answer": "いぬころ",
    "meaning": "pup, puppy, whelp"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓮っ葉",
    "answer": "はすっぱ",
    "meaning": "vulgar, wanton"
  },
  {
    "question": "珊瑚礁",
    "answer": "さんごしょう",
    "meaning": "coral reef"
  },
  {
    "question": "荒海",
    "answer": "あらうみ",
    "meaning": "rough sea, stormy sea"
  },
  {
    "question": "混血児",
    "answer": "こんけつじ",
    "meaning": "child of mixed parentage, mixed-race child"
  },
  {
    "question": "栄養士",
    "answer": "えいようし",
    "meaning": "dietitian, (licensed) nutritionist"
  },
  {
    "question": "山沿い",
    "answer": "やまぞい",
    "meaning": "along a mountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "望郷",
    "answer": "ぼうきょう",
    "meaning": "homesickness, nostalgia"
  },
  {
    "question": "膏薬",
    "answer": "こうやく,あぶらぐすり",
    "meaning": "plaster, patch, ointment, liniment"
  },
  {
    "question": "模範生",
    "answer": "もはんせい",
    "meaning": "model or exemplary student"
  },
  {
    "question": "後が無い",
    "answer": "あとがない",
    "meaning": "having one's back to the wall, having nowhere to go, having no way out, not having another chance"
  },
  {
    "question": "発刊",
    "answer": "はっかん",
    "meaning": "publish, start (new) publication"
  },
  {
    "question": "網状",
    "answer": "もうじょう,あみじょう",
    "meaning": "netlike, mesh-like, reticulated, vascular"
  },
  {
    "question": "風の便り",
    "answer": "かぜのたより",
    "meaning": "hearsay, rumour"
  },
  {
    "question": "攻め上る",
    "answer": "せめのぼる",
    "meaning": "to march on the capital"
  },
  {
    "question": "素案",
    "answer": "そあん",
    "meaning": "rough plan, draft"
  },
  {
    "question": "面従腹背",
    "answer": "めんじゅうふくはい",
    "meaning": "pretending to obey but secretly betraying (someone)"
  },
  {
    "question": "狼少年",
    "answer": "おおかみしょうねん",
    "meaning": "boy raised by wolves, boy who cried wolf"
  },
  {
    "question": "口述",
    "answer": "こうじゅつ",
    "meaning": "dictation, verbal statement"
  },
  {
    "question": "機先",
    "answer": "きせん",
    "meaning": "forestall"
  },
  {
    "question": "推し測る",
    "answer": "おしはかる",
    "meaning": "to guess, to conjecture, to surmise"
  },
  {
    "question": "野に下る",
    "answer": "やにくだる",
    "meaning": "to leave the government service"
  },
  {
    "question": "驕慢",
    "answer": "きょうまん",
    "meaning": "arrogance"
  },
  {
    "question": "悔し泣き",
    "answer": "くやしなき",
    "meaning": "crying from vexation, tears of regret"
  },
  {
    "question": "労働条件",
    "answer": "ろうどうじょうけん",
    "meaning": "working conditions"
  },
  {
    "question": "太鼓腹",
    "answer": "たいこばら",
    "meaning": "potbelly, paunch"
  },
  {
    "question": "前出",
    "answer": "ぜんしゅつ",
    "meaning": "aforementioned, above-mentioned, given above, previous"
  },
  {
    "question": "目的語",
    "answer": "もくてきご",
    "meaning": "object"
  },
  {
    "question": "飽かす",
    "answer": "あかす",
    "meaning": "to bore, to tire, to weary, to stultify, to use lavishly (and without regret)"
  },
  {
    "question": "死中",
    "answer": "しちゅう",
    "meaning": "fatal situation"
  },
  {
    "question": "ら行",
    "answer": "らぎょう",
    "meaning": "the 'ra' column of the Japanese syllabary table (ra, ri, ru, re, ro)"
  },
  {
    "question": "僭主",
    "answer": "せんしゅ",
    "meaning": "usurper, tyrant"
  },
  {
    "question": "四魔",
    "answer": "しま",
    "meaning": "the four kinds of demons that make trouble for sentient beings"
  },
  {
    "question": "石剣",
    "answer": "せっけん",
    "meaning": "sword-shaped stoneware found in archeological sites in eastern Japan dating to the end of the Jomon"
  },
  {
    "question": "不承",
    "answer": "ふしょう",
    "meaning": "dissent, disagreement, disapproval, objection, refusal"
  },
  {
    "question": "入廷",
    "answer": "にゅうてい",
    "meaning": "admission to the courtroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "箕",
    "answer": "き,み",
    "meaning": "Chinese 'winnowing basket' constellation (one of the 28 mansions), winnow, winnowing basket, winnowi"
  },
  {
    "question": "結石",
    "answer": "けっせき",
    "meaning": "calculus (concretion of minerals formed inside the body)"
  },
  {
    "question": "助産婦",
    "answer": "じょさんぷ",
    "meaning": "midwife"
  },
  {
    "question": "原動機",
    "answer": "げんどうき",
    "meaning": "motor"
  },
  {
    "question": "加増",
    "answer": "かぞう",
    "meaning": "increase, addition"
  },
  {
    "question": "複合企業",
    "answer": "ふくごうきぎょう",
    "meaning": "conglomerate, group of companies run as a single organization"
  },
  {
    "question": "道の駅",
    "answer": "みちのえき",
    "meaning": "roadside station (government-designated rest area found along roads and highways)"
  },
  {
    "question": "雪白",
    "answer": "せっぱく,ゆきじろ",
    "meaning": "snow-white, pure, immaculate, snow white, refined sugar"
  },
  {
    "question": "光熱",
    "answer": "こうねつ",
    "meaning": "light and heat"
  },
  {
    "question": "甘栗",
    "answer": "あまぐり",
    "meaning": "broiled sweet chestnuts"
  },
  {
    "question": "喫煙室",
    "answer": "きつえんしつ",
    "meaning": "smoking room, smoking compartment"
  },
  {
    "question": "水銀灯",
    "answer": "すいぎんとう",
    "meaning": "mercury lamp"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽騎兵",
    "answer": "けいきへい",
    "meaning": "light cavalry"
  },
  {
    "question": "牝馬",
    "answer": "ひんば,めうま,めま",
    "meaning": "mare, filly"
  },
  {
    "question": "挽歌",
    "answer": "ばんか",
    "meaning": "elegy, funeral song"
  },
  {
    "question": "留守録",
    "answer": "るすろく",
    "meaning": "unattended (video, audio) recording"
  },
  {
    "question": "鷹狩り",
    "answer": "たかがり",
    "meaning": "falconry"
  },
  {
    "question": "不落",
    "answer": "ふらく",
    "meaning": "impregnable"
  },
  {
    "question": "対陣",
    "answer": "たいじん",
    "meaning": "confrontation of armies"
  },
  {
    "question": "釣瓶",
    "answer": "つるべ",
    "meaning": "well bucket"
  },
  {
    "question": "油彩",
    "answer": "ゆさい",
    "meaning": "oil painting"
  },
  {
    "question": "違法駐車",
    "answer": "いほうちゅうしゃ",
    "meaning": "illegal parking"
  },
  {
    "question": "外角",
    "answer": "がいかく",
    "meaning": "external angle, exterior angle, outside corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "舶来品",
    "answer": "はくらいひん",
    "meaning": "imported article, imported goods"
  },
  {
    "question": "春色",
    "answer": "しゅんしょく",
    "meaning": "spring scenery"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾何",
    "answer": "きか,いくばく",
    "meaning": "geometry, how many, how much"
  },
  {
    "question": "選挙運動",
    "answer": "せんきょうんどう",
    "meaning": "election campaign, political campaign, campaigning, electioneering, canvassing"
  },
  {
    "question": "並列処理",
    "answer": "へいれつしょり",
    "meaning": "parallel processing, array processing"
  },
  {
    "question": "提訴",
    "answer": "ていそ",
    "meaning": "presenting a case, suing"
  },
  {
    "question": "叩頭",
    "answer": "こうとう",
    "meaning": "kowtow (bow made from a kneeling position wherein the forehead touches the ground)"
  },
  {
    "question": "三寸",
    "answer": "さんずん",
    "meaning": "three sun (ca. 9.1 cm), something small, short or thin (roughly the size of three sun), stall-keeper"
  },
  {
    "question": "官公庁",
    "answer": "かんこうちょう",
    "meaning": "government and municipal offices, public agencies"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍帽",
    "answer": "ぐんぼう",
    "meaning": "military cap"
  },
  {
    "question": "濁声",
    "answer": "だみごえ,だくせい",
    "meaning": "thick voice, hoarse voice, voice with a thick accent"
  },
  {
    "question": "青眼",
    "answer": "せいがん,あおめ",
    "meaning": "holding one's sword pointing towards the opponent's eyes (kendo stance), warm, welcoming eyes, blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "衆道",
    "answer": "しゅうどう,しゅどう",
    "meaning": "male homosexuality, pederasty"
  },
  {
    "question": "国章",
    "answer": "こくしょう",
    "meaning": "national emblem, (national) coat of arms"
  },
  {
    "question": "奸臣",
    "answer": "かんしん",
    "meaning": "disloyal retainer, treacherous subject"
  },
  {
    "question": "出生届",
    "answer": "しゅっしょうとどけ,しゅっせいとどけ",
    "meaning": "birth registration"
  },
  {
    "question": "明治維新",
    "answer": "めいじいしん",
    "meaning": "Meiji Restoration"
  },
  {
    "question": "佳人",
    "answer": "かじん",
    "meaning": "(female) beauty, beautiful woman"
  },
  {
    "question": "破魔矢",
    "answer": "はまや",
    "meaning": "(ceremonial) arrow used to drive off evil"
  },
  {
    "question": "愚図る",
    "answer": "ぐずる",
    "meaning": "to grumble, to be unsettled, to grizzle"
  },
  {
    "question": "上席",
    "answer": "じょうせき",
    "meaning": "seniority, precedence, upper seat"
  },
  {
    "question": "乳酸菌",
    "answer": "にゅうさんきん",
    "meaning": "lactic-acid bacilli"
  },
  {
    "question": "県民",
    "answer": "けんみん",
    "meaning": "citizen of a prefecture, prefectural citizen"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き下げ",
    "answer": "ひきさげ",
    "meaning": "reduction, cut"
  },
  {
    "question": "生爪",
    "answer": "なまづめ",
    "meaning": "fingernail"
  },
  {
    "question": "然るに",
    "answer": "しかるに",
    "meaning": "however, nevertheless, but, and yet, whereas, while, on the other hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "御三方",
    "answer": "おさんかた",
    "meaning": "three people"
  },
  {
    "question": "自動車道",
    "answer": "じどうしゃどう",
    "meaning": "expressway, motorway"
  },
  {
    "question": "才知",
    "answer": "さいち",
    "meaning": "wit and intelligence"
  },
  {
    "question": "財産分与",
    "answer": "ざいさんぶんよ",
    "meaning": "distribution of property"
  },
  {
    "question": "魚市場",
    "answer": "うおいちば",
    "meaning": "fish market"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱毛",
    "answer": "だつもう",
    "meaning": "hair loss, hair removal, epilation, depilation"
  },
  {
    "question": "染み抜き",
    "answer": "しみぬき",
    "meaning": "stain removal"
  },
  {
    "question": "町育ち",
    "answer": "まちそだち",
    "meaning": "being raised in a town"
  },
  {
    "question": "可視光線",
    "answer": "かしこうせん",
    "meaning": "visible ray"
  },
  {
    "question": "膨らす",
    "answer": "ふくらす",
    "meaning": "to expand, to inflate"
  },
  {
    "question": "練習曲",
    "answer": "れんしゅうきょく",
    "meaning": "etude"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛脚",
    "answer": "ひきゃく",
    "meaning": "express messenger, postman, mailman, courier"
  },
  {
    "question": "音圧",
    "answer": "おんあつ",
    "meaning": "sound pressure, acoustic pressure"
  },
  {
    "question": "剽軽",
    "answer": "ひょうきん",
    "meaning": "facetious, droll, funny"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛍光ペン",
    "answer": "けいこうペン",
    "meaning": "highlighter, highlighter pen"
  },
  {
    "question": "根競べ",
    "answer": "こんくらべ",
    "meaning": "endurance contest, test of endurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "企業家",
    "answer": "きぎょうか",
    "meaning": "industrialist, entrepreneur"
  },
  {
    "question": "有機体",
    "answer": "ゆうきたい",
    "meaning": "organic body, organism"
  },
  {
    "question": "遺漏",
    "answer": "いろう",
    "meaning": "omission"
  },
  {
    "question": "元気付く",
    "answer": "げんきづく",
    "meaning": "to get encouraged, to become heightened in spirits, to recover one's strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "全線",
    "answer": "ぜんせん",
    "meaning": "the whole line, all lines, the whole ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "多年草",
    "answer": "たねんそう",
    "meaning": "perennial plant"
  },
  {
    "question": "韓流",
    "answer": "ハンりゅう,かんりゅう",
    "meaning": "influx of South Korean pop culture (into Japan)"
  },
  {
    "question": "買値",
    "answer": "かいね",
    "meaning": "buying price, cost price, purchase price"
  },
  {
    "question": "草葉",
    "answer": "くさば",
    "meaning": "blades of grass"
  },
  {
    "question": "要旨",
    "answer": "ようし",
    "meaning": "point, essentials, gist, summary, fundamentals"
  },
  {
    "question": "鍋底",
    "answer": "なべぞこ",
    "meaning": "(inner) bottom of a pot, lingering recession"
  },
  {
    "question": "矮小化",
    "answer": "わいしょうか",
    "meaning": "reduction (in size), shrinking, minimization, trivializing (an issue), making light of, playing down"
  },
  {
    "question": "狭義",
    "answer": "きょうぎ",
    "meaning": "narrow sense (e.g. of a word)"
  },
  {
    "question": "向こう脛",
    "answer": "むこうずね",
    "meaning": "shin, front of lower leg"
  },
  {
    "question": "千人力",
    "answer": "せんにんりき",
    "meaning": "strength of a thousand men, cloth with the character for 'strength' written by a thousand men (soldi"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗褐色",
    "answer": "あんかっしょく",
    "meaning": "dark brown"
  },
  {
    "question": "商業主義",
    "answer": "しょうぎょうしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "commercialism"
  },
  {
    "question": "抜き出る",
    "answer": "ぬきでる",
    "meaning": "to surpass, to outdo, to excel, to stand out, to be outstanding, to be preeminent, to tower above (t"
  },
  {
    "question": "独裁的",
    "answer": "どくさいてき",
    "meaning": "dictatorial"
  },
  {
    "question": "滅私奉公",
    "answer": "めっしほうこう,めっしぼうこう",
    "meaning": "selfless devotion"
  },
  {
    "question": "破竹",
    "answer": "はちく",
    "meaning": "breaking bamboo"
  },
  {
    "question": "水物",
    "answer": "みずもの",
    "meaning": "liquid, beverage, drink, food with high water content, gamble, uncertain affair, matter of chance"
  },
  {
    "question": "箔押し",
    "answer": "はくおし",
    "meaning": "gold tooling, gilt tooling"
  },
  {
    "question": "敗色",
    "answer": "はいしょく",
    "meaning": "signs of defeat, negative turn of events"
  },
  {
    "question": "生米",
    "answer": "なまごめ",
    "meaning": "uncooked rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "不介入",
    "answer": "ふかいにゅう",
    "meaning": "noninvolvement, nonintervention, neutrality"
  },
  {
    "question": "曲り",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "一本調子",
    "answer": "いっぽんぢょうし,いっぽんちょうし",
    "meaning": "monotone, monotonous, dull, lacking variety"
  },
  {
    "question": "張り替え",
    "answer": "はりかえ",
    "meaning": "re-upholstering, re-covering, repapering"
  },
  {
    "question": "得々",
    "answer": "とくとく",
    "meaning": "triumphantly, proudly"
  },
  {
    "question": "一杯食う",
    "answer": "いっぱいくう",
    "meaning": "to be deceived"
  },
  {
    "question": "人間模様",
    "answer": "にんげんもよう",
    "meaning": "fabric (pattern) of human relationships"
  },
  {
    "question": "叢雨",
    "answer": "むらさめ",
    "meaning": "passing shower"
  },
  {
    "question": "百夜",
    "answer": "ももよ",
    "meaning": "many nights, hundred nights"
  },
  {
    "question": "古手",
    "answer": "ふるて",
    "meaning": "used article, worn-out article, veteran, old-timer, long-serving employee, long-established (way, me"
  },
  {
    "question": "喪神",
    "answer": "そうしん",
    "meaning": "absent-mindedness, stupor, stupefaction, abstraction, being stunned"
  },
  {
    "question": "叡山",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "烏天狗",
    "answer": "からすてんぐ",
    "meaning": "small, crow-billed tengu"
  },
  {
    "question": "萱",
    "answer": "かや",
    "meaning": "grass used for thatching, sedge used for thatching"
  },
  {
    "question": "薊",
    "answer": "あざみ",
    "meaning": "thistle (Cirsium spp.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "降誕祭",
    "answer": "こうたんさい",
    "meaning": "Christmas, Nativity, celebration of the birthday of a saint or great man"
  },
  {
    "question": "堀川",
    "answer": "ほりかわ",
    "meaning": "canal"
  },
  {
    "question": "双児",
    "answer": "そうじ",
    "meaning": "twins"
  },
  {
    "question": "旭日",
    "answer": "きょくじつ",
    "meaning": "rising sun"
  },
  {
    "question": "金蔵",
    "answer": "かねぐら,きんぞう",
    "meaning": "treasure house, treasury, financial supporter, patron, financier, backer"
  },
  {
    "question": "救貧院",
    "answer": "きゅうひんいん",
    "meaning": "poorhouse, almshouse, workhouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "限界集落",
    "answer": "げんかいしゅうらく",
    "meaning": "marginal village, depopulated village where most inhabitants are senior citizens"
  },
  {
    "question": "下野",
    "answer": "げや,しもつけ",
    "meaning": "retirement from public office, going into opposition, losing power, Japanese spirea (Spiraea Japonic"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎖す",
    "answer": "とざす,さす",
    "meaning": "to shut, to close, to fasten, to lock, to block (a street, entrance, etc.), to shut in (with snow, i"
  },
  {
    "question": "手毬",
    "answer": "てまり",
    "meaning": "traditional Japanese handball game"
  },
  {
    "question": "高雅",
    "answer": "こうが",
    "meaning": "refined, elegant, chaste"
  },
  {
    "question": "鞍上",
    "answer": "あんじょう",
    "meaning": "on top of a saddle"
  },
  {
    "question": "吃",
    "answer": "チー",
    "meaning": "forming a chow by picking up a tile discarded by another player"
  },
  {
    "question": "畠",
    "answer": "はたけ,はた",
    "meaning": "field (for fruits, vegetables, etc.), cultivated land, vegetable plot, kitchen garden, plantation, f"
  },
  {
    "question": "岩窟",
    "answer": "がんくつ",
    "meaning": "cave, cavern"
  },
  {
    "question": "堵",
    "answer": "と",
    "meaning": "fence, wall, hedge"
  },
  {
    "question": "百年戦争",
    "answer": "ひゃくねんせんそう",
    "meaning": "Hundred Years War (1337-1453)"
  },
  {
    "question": "農学",
    "answer": "のうがく",
    "meaning": "(science of) agriculture"
  },
  {
    "question": "三原色",
    "answer": "さんげんしょく",
    "meaning": "three primary colors (colours), trichromatic"
  },
  {
    "question": "白檀",
    "answer": "びゃくだん",
    "meaning": "Indian sandalwood (Santalum album), white sandalwood"
  },
  {
    "question": "赫怒",
    "answer": "かくど",
    "meaning": "greatly enraged, furious"
  },
  {
    "question": "度外れ",
    "answer": "どはずれ",
    "meaning": "extraordinary, excessive"
  },
  {
    "question": "杉林",
    "answer": "すぎばやし",
    "meaning": "cryptomeria forest"
  },
  {
    "question": "葦毛",
    "answer": "あしげ",
    "meaning": "dapple-grey (gray) (horse coat colour)"
  },
  {
    "question": "血塊",
    "answer": "けっかい",
    "meaning": "blood clot"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸一",
    "answer": "まるいち",
    "meaning": "bisected-circle seal"
  },
  {
    "question": "辱",
    "answer": "はじ,じょく",
    "meaning": "shame, embarrassment, disgrace"
  },
  {
    "question": "禿げ頭",
    "answer": "はげあたま",
    "meaning": "bald head, baldness"
  },
  {
    "question": "欄間",
    "answer": "らんま",
    "meaning": "(in Japanese architecture) transom"
  },
  {
    "question": "耳孔",
    "answer": "じこう",
    "meaning": "earhole"
  },
  {
    "question": "極低温",
    "answer": "きょくていおん",
    "meaning": "very (extremely) low temperature"
  },
  {
    "question": "祭服",
    "answer": "さいふく",
    "meaning": "vestments worn by priests and attendants (Shinto, Christian, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "泣き黒子",
    "answer": "なきぼくろ",
    "meaning": "mole under the eye (supposedly due to having cried)"
  },
  {
    "question": "放屁",
    "answer": "ほうひ,へひり",
    "meaning": "breaking wind, fart, farting, farter"
  },
  {
    "question": "卑賤",
    "answer": "ひせん",
    "meaning": "low class, lowly (position), humble (condition)"
  },
  {
    "question": "創始",
    "answer": "そうし",
    "meaning": "creation, founding, initiating"
  },
  {
    "question": "水菜",
    "answer": "みずな",
    "meaning": "mizuna (Brassica rapa var. nipposinica), potherb mustard, Elatostema umbellatum var. majus (variety"
  },
  {
    "question": "縁組み",
    "answer": "えんぐみ",
    "meaning": "betrothal, wedding, marriage into a family, matrimonial alliance, adoption"
  },
  {
    "question": "艶美",
    "answer": "えんび",
    "meaning": "beauty, charm"
  },
  {
    "question": "登り坂",
    "answer": "のぼりざか",
    "meaning": "ascent, uphill, upward slope, (gradual) upturn, increase"
  },
  {
    "question": "総合商社",
    "answer": "そうごうしょうしゃ",
    "meaning": "general trading company"
  },
  {
    "question": "衛星放送",
    "answer": "えいせいほうそう",
    "meaning": "satellite broadcasting"
  },
  {
    "question": "隔週",
    "answer": "かくしゅう",
    "meaning": "every other week, every two weeks"
  },
  {
    "question": "小文字",
    "answer": "こもじ",
    "meaning": "lowercase letter, small letter"
  },
  {
    "question": "自然淘汰",
    "answer": "しぜんとうた",
    "meaning": "natural selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "偏執狂",
    "answer": "へんしつきょう,へんしゅうきょう",
    "meaning": "monomania, monomaniac"
  },
  {
    "question": "盗用",
    "answer": "とうよう",
    "meaning": "embezzlement, fraudulent use, plagiarism, appropriation"
  },
  {
    "question": "真っ新",
    "answer": "まっさら",
    "meaning": "brand new, fresh"
  },
  {
    "question": "不心得",
    "answer": "ふこころえ",
    "meaning": "indiscretion, imprudence"
  },
  {
    "question": "葉物",
    "answer": "はもの",
    "meaning": "foliage plants"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝小便",
    "answer": "ねしょうべん",
    "meaning": "bed-wetting"
  },
  {
    "question": "雇用者",
    "answer": "こようしゃ",
    "meaning": "employee, employer, person hiring others"
  },
  {
    "question": "贈賄",
    "answer": "ぞうわい",
    "meaning": "bribery, graft"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉤状",
    "answer": "こうじょう,かぎじょう",
    "meaning": "hooklike, hook-shaped, unciform"
  },
  {
    "question": "隈無く",
    "answer": "くまなく",
    "meaning": "all over, everywhere, in every nook and cranny"
  },
  {
    "question": "強迫",
    "answer": "きょうはく",
    "meaning": "compelling, using duress"
  },
  {
    "question": "棒高跳び",
    "answer": "ぼうたかとび",
    "meaning": "pole vault"
  },
  {
    "question": "掛け時計",
    "answer": "かけどけい",
    "meaning": "wall clock"
  },
  {
    "question": "排他",
    "answer": "はいた",
    "meaning": "exclusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "硬軟",
    "answer": "こうなん",
    "meaning": "hardness and softness, hard line and moderate line"
  },
  {
    "question": "姦淫",
    "answer": "かんいん",
    "meaning": "adultery, fornication, illicit intercourse"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸儲け",
    "answer": "まるもうけ",
    "meaning": "clear profit, great profit (without any investment)"
  },
  {
    "question": "優等",
    "answer": "ゆうとう",
    "meaning": "(academic) excellence, superiority, honors (e.g. graduating with), cum laude"
  },
  {
    "question": "明り取り",
    "answer": "あかりとり",
    "meaning": "skylight, dormer, transom, dormer window"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍門",
    "answer": "ぐんもん",
    "meaning": "camp gate, general"
  },
  {
    "question": "過ぎ行く",
    "answer": "すぎゆく,すぎいく",
    "meaning": "to pass, to go past"
  },
  {
    "question": "大食",
    "answer": "たいしょく",
    "meaning": "gluttony"
  },
  {
    "question": "一翼",
    "answer": "いちよく",
    "meaning": "one wing, (a) role, (a) part"
  },
  {
    "question": "姦計",
    "answer": "かんけい",
    "meaning": "evil design, crafty plan, plot"
  },
  {
    "question": "三部",
    "answer": "さんぶ",
    "meaning": "three parts, three copies"
  },
  {
    "question": "三重奏",
    "answer": "さんじゅうそう",
    "meaning": "instrumental trio"
  },
  {
    "question": "荒立つ",
    "answer": "あらだつ",
    "meaning": "to become rough (waves, temper, etc.), to become excited, to become aggravated"
  },
  {
    "question": "水性",
    "answer": "すいせい,みずしょう",
    "meaning": "water-based, aqueous, water-soluble, fluidity, wanton"
  },
  {
    "question": "寒色",
    "answer": "かんしょく",
    "meaning": "cold color, cold colour"
  },
  {
    "question": "人情味",
    "answer": "にんじょうみ",
    "meaning": "human interest, kindness"
  },
  {
    "question": "粗探し",
    "answer": "あらさがし",
    "meaning": "finding fault (with), being picky"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛飲",
    "answer": "あいいん",
    "meaning": "drinking habitually, being fond of (a drink)"
  },
  {
    "question": "切れ込む",
    "answer": "きれこむ",
    "meaning": "to cut into"
  },
  {
    "question": "肉付け",
    "answer": "にくづけ",
    "meaning": "fleshing out, modeling, modelling"
  },
  {
    "question": "修祓",
    "answer": "しゅばつ,しゅうばつ,しゅうふつ",
    "meaning": "purification rite (esp. one held prior to a Shinto event)"
  },
  {
    "question": "沫",
    "answer": "あわ",
    "meaning": "bubble, foam, froth, head on beer"
  },
  {
    "question": "神門",
    "answer": "しんもん,じんもん",
    "meaning": "shrine gate"
  },
  {
    "question": "聖帝",
    "answer": "せいてい",
    "meaning": "virtuous emperor"
  },
  {
    "question": "一意",
    "answer": "いちい",
    "meaning": "one meaning, one thought, wholeheartedly, single-mindedly, devotedly, unique"
  },
  {
    "question": "篤志",
    "answer": "とくし",
    "meaning": "charity, benevolence, charitable spirit, interest (in public welfare, social enterprise, etc.), zeal"
  },
  {
    "question": "竜舎",
    "answer": "りゅうしゃ",
    "meaning": "ryūsha, spherical part of a pagoda finial between the hōju and suien"
  },
  {
    "question": "郷士",
    "answer": "ごうし",
    "meaning": "country samurai"
  },
  {
    "question": "才幹",
    "answer": "さいかん",
    "meaning": "ability"
  },
  {
    "question": "木型",
    "answer": "きがた",
    "meaning": "wooden form, wooden model, wooden pattern"
  },
  {
    "question": "石高",
    "answer": "こくだか",
    "meaning": "(crop) yield, stipend (orig. assessed on the basis of a crop), salary"
  },
  {
    "question": "鵞鳥",
    "answer": "がちょう",
    "meaning": "goose"
  },
  {
    "question": "法曹界",
    "answer": "ほうそうかい",
    "meaning": "legal circles"
  },
  {
    "question": "来援",
    "answer": "らいえん",
    "meaning": "assistance, support"
  },
  {
    "question": "全船",
    "answer": "ぜんせん",
    "meaning": "the whole line, all lines, the whole ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "急き込む",
    "answer": "せきこむ",
    "meaning": "to sound agitated, hurried, flustered, to be impatient"
  },
  {
    "question": "旋盤",
    "answer": "せんばん",
    "meaning": "lathe"
  },
  {
    "question": "統領",
    "answer": "とうりょう",
    "meaning": "ruler, leader, consul"
  },
  {
    "question": "感光",
    "answer": "かんこう",
    "meaning": "exposure, sensitization, sensitisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "蔵する",
    "answer": "ぞうする",
    "meaning": "to store, to contain"
  },
  {
    "question": "単座",
    "answer": "たんざ",
    "meaning": "single-seater, single-seated, sitting alone"
  },
  {
    "question": "福井",
    "answer": "ふくい",
    "meaning": "Fukui (city, prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "厚労省",
    "answer": "こうろうしょう",
    "meaning": "Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶席",
    "answer": "ちゃせき",
    "meaning": "tea room, tea ceremony"
  },
  {
    "question": "浸潤",
    "answer": "しんじゅん",
    "meaning": "infiltration, permeation"
  },
  {
    "question": "舞台監督",
    "answer": "ぶたいかんとく",
    "meaning": "stage director"
  },
  {
    "question": "日時計",
    "answer": "ひどけい",
    "meaning": "sundial"
  },
  {
    "question": "保護区",
    "answer": "ほごく",
    "meaning": "sanctuary, reserve (for wild animals), nature preserve"
  },
  {
    "question": "公邸",
    "answer": "こうてい",
    "meaning": "official residence"
  },
  {
    "question": "側方",
    "answer": "そくほう",
    "meaning": "lateral, sideways, (from) side to side"
  },
  {
    "question": "顔認証",
    "answer": "かおにんしょう",
    "meaning": "authentication by facial recognition"
  },
  {
    "question": "染め物",
    "answer": "そめもの",
    "meaning": "dyeing, dyed goods, goods to be dyed"
  },
  {
    "question": "火入れ",
    "answer": "ひいれ",
    "meaning": "fire pan, heating, first lighting (e.g. furnace), firing (e.g. forest), kindling, igniting, pasteuri"
  },
  {
    "question": "覇業",
    "answer": "はぎょう",
    "meaning": "domination, supremacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "先妻",
    "answer": "せんさい",
    "meaning": "former wife, late wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "飄然",
    "answer": "ひょうぜん",
    "meaning": "casually, aimlessly, abruptly, unexpectedly"
  },
  {
    "question": "党員",
    "answer": "とういん",
    "meaning": "party member"
  },
  {
    "question": "床上手",
    "answer": "とこじょうず",
    "meaning": "being good in bed, sexual performer"
  },
  {
    "question": "胴部",
    "answer": "どうぶ",
    "meaning": "torso, body, trunk"
  },
  {
    "question": "巨船",
    "answer": "きょせん",
    "meaning": "ocean liner"
  },
  {
    "question": "柔弱",
    "answer": "にゅうじゃく",
    "meaning": "weakness, effeminacy, enervation"
  },
  {
    "question": "突き落す",
    "answer": "つきおとす",
    "meaning": "to thrust down, to push off"
  },
  {
    "question": "後代",
    "answer": "こうだい",
    "meaning": "posterity, future generations"
  },
  {
    "question": "足切り",
    "answer": "あしきり",
    "meaning": "Japanese children's game, preliminary test to eliminate weak contenders"
  },
  {
    "question": "色ガラス",
    "answer": "いろガラス",
    "meaning": "coloured glass, colored glass"
  },
  {
    "question": "豚カツ",
    "answer": "とんカツ",
    "meaning": "tonkatsu, breaded pork cutlet"
  },
  {
    "question": "子供会",
    "answer": "こどもかい",
    "meaning": "organization for local children (for growth via sports, study, service, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "遺髪",
    "answer": "いはつ",
    "meaning": "hair of the deceased"
  },
  {
    "question": "習俗",
    "answer": "しゅうぞく",
    "meaning": "manners and customs, folkways, usage"
  },
  {
    "question": "淡色",
    "answer": "たんしょく",
    "meaning": "light color, light colour"
  },
  {
    "question": "貼",
    "answer": "ちょう",
    "meaning": "counter for doses of medicine, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "肩章",
    "answer": "けんしょう,かたじるし",
    "meaning": "shoulder mark, shoulder board, epaulette, epaulet"
  },
  {
    "question": "免税",
    "answer": "めんぜい",
    "meaning": "tax exemption, duty exemption"
  },
  {
    "question": "平安京",
    "answer": "へいあんきょう",
    "meaning": "ancient Kyoto"
  },
  {
    "question": "帰順",
    "answer": "きじゅん",
    "meaning": "submission, return to allegiance"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗視装置",
    "answer": "あんしそうち",
    "meaning": "night vision device"
  },
  {
    "question": "選民",
    "answer": "せんみん",
    "meaning": "the chosen people"
  },
  {
    "question": "茹で卵",
    "answer": "ゆでたまご",
    "meaning": "boiled egg"
  },
  {
    "question": "側道",
    "answer": "そくどう,そばみち",
    "meaning": "service road, frontage road, side road, shortcut"
  },
  {
    "question": "貴ぶ",
    "answer": "とうとぶ,たっとぶ",
    "meaning": "to value, to prize, to esteem, to respect"
  },
  {
    "question": "外板",
    "answer": "がいはん",
    "meaning": "panels, planks or plating on the hull of a ship or aircraft"
  },
  {
    "question": "憚り",
    "answer": "はばかり",
    "meaning": "hesitation, hindrance, washroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "火山活動",
    "answer": "かざんかつどう",
    "meaning": "volcanic activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "機上",
    "answer": "きじょう",
    "meaning": "aboard an aeroplane (airplane)"
  },
  {
    "question": "小破",
    "answer": "しょうは",
    "meaning": "slight damage"
  },
  {
    "question": "半身不随",
    "answer": "はんしんふずい",
    "meaning": "hemiplegia (paralysis on one side of the body)"
  },
  {
    "question": "松脂",
    "answer": "まつやに",
    "meaning": "(pine) resin, turpentine"
  },
  {
    "question": "鱗状",
    "answer": "りんじょう",
    "meaning": "scaly, scale-like"
  },
  {
    "question": "納品書",
    "answer": "のうひんしょ",
    "meaning": "statement of delivery, delivery slip, delivery note"
  },
  {
    "question": "屑籠",
    "answer": "くずかご",
    "meaning": "wastebasket, wastepaper basket"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨除け",
    "answer": "あまよけ",
    "meaning": "tarpaulin, shelter from rain, covering against rain"
  },
  {
    "question": "初志",
    "answer": "しょし",
    "meaning": "original intention"
  },
  {
    "question": "妻帯",
    "answer": "さいたい",
    "meaning": "having a wife, marrying (a woman), marriage"
  },
  {
    "question": "準備金",
    "answer": "じゅんびきん",
    "meaning": "reserve fund"
  },
  {
    "question": "近影",
    "answer": "きんえい",
    "meaning": "recent photograph or photography"
  },
  {
    "question": "私道",
    "answer": "しどう",
    "meaning": "private road, driveway"
  },
  {
    "question": "出頭命令",
    "answer": "しゅっとうめいれい",
    "meaning": "(issuing) order requiring somebody to report personally (to a police station), subpoena"
  },
  {
    "question": "疾風怒濤",
    "answer": "しっぷうどとう",
    "meaning": "storm and stress, Sturm und Drang"
  },
  {
    "question": "古人",
    "answer": "こじん",
    "meaning": "ancient people"
  },
  {
    "question": "利潤",
    "answer": "りじゅん",
    "meaning": "profit, returns"
  },
  {
    "question": "粗筋",
    "answer": "あらすじ",
    "meaning": "outline, summary, argument"
  },
  {
    "question": "舌先三寸",
    "answer": "したさきさんずん",
    "meaning": "eloquence or flattery designed to deceive"
  },
  {
    "question": "人品",
    "answer": "じんぴん",
    "meaning": "personal appearance, character, personality"
  },
  {
    "question": "生国",
    "answer": "しょうごく,しょうこく",
    "meaning": "one's native country, land of one's birth"
  },
  {
    "question": "空手形",
    "answer": "からてがた,くうてがた",
    "meaning": "bad (fictitious) bill, empty promise"
  },
  {
    "question": "平均台",
    "answer": "へいきんだい",
    "meaning": "balance beam (in gymnastics)"
  },
  {
    "question": "論説",
    "answer": "ろんせつ",
    "meaning": "editorial, dissertation"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠慮深い",
    "answer": "えんりょぶかい",
    "meaning": "reserved"
  },
  {
    "question": "風物",
    "answer": "ふうぶつ",
    "meaning": "natural features, scenery, things particular to a certain region or season, characteristic scenery a"
  },
  {
    "question": "近寄せる",
    "answer": "ちかよせる",
    "meaning": "to bring close, to bring near, to associate with (someone), to keep company with, to let come close"
  },
  {
    "question": "抱腹絶倒",
    "answer": "ほうふくぜっとう",
    "meaning": "laughing oneself into convulsions, splitting one's sides laughing, rolling with laughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "銅線",
    "answer": "どうせん",
    "meaning": "copper line, copper wire"
  },
  {
    "question": "一膳",
    "answer": "いちぜん",
    "meaning": "bowl (of rice), pair (of chopsticks)"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り止め",
    "answer": "とりやめ,とりとめ",
    "meaning": "cancellation, suspension, coherence, order, focus, point"
  },
  {
    "question": "味蕾",
    "answer": "みらい",
    "meaning": "taste bud"
  },
  {
    "question": "津々浦々",
    "answer": "つつうらうら,つづうらうら",
    "meaning": "all over the country, throughout the land, every nook and cranny of the land"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼び戻し",
    "answer": "よびもどし",
    "meaning": "pulling body slam"
  },
  {
    "question": "利き足",
    "answer": "ききあし",
    "meaning": "one's dominant foot"
  },
  {
    "question": "三重苦",
    "answer": "さんじゅうく",
    "meaning": "triple handicap (esp. blindness, deafness and mutism)"
  },
  {
    "question": "大風",
    "answer": "おおかぜ,たいふう,おおふう",
    "meaning": "gale, strong wind, high wind, arrogant, haughty, calm, placid"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗中模索",
    "answer": "あんちゅうもさく",
    "meaning": "groping in the dark, exploring new avenues without having any clues"
  },
  {
    "question": "被す",
    "answer": "かぶす",
    "meaning": "to cover (with something)"
  },
  {
    "question": "取柄",
    "answer": "とりえ",
    "meaning": "worth, merit, value, good point, redeeming feature, saving grace"
  },
  {
    "question": "弁務官",
    "answer": "べんむかん",
    "meaning": "commissioner"
  },
  {
    "question": "長月",
    "answer": "ながつき,ながづき",
    "meaning": "ninth month of the lunar calendar, September"
  },
  {
    "question": "防禦",
    "answer": "ぼうぎょ",
    "meaning": "defense, defence, safeguard, protection"
  },
  {
    "question": "渾沌",
    "answer": "こんとん",
    "meaning": "chaos, confusion, disorder, chaotic, confused, uncertain, disarrayed"
  },
  {
    "question": "美神",
    "answer": "びしん",
    "meaning": "god of beauty, goddess of beauty, Venus"
  },
  {
    "question": "葬儀社",
    "answer": "そうぎしゃ",
    "meaning": "undertaker's office, funeral home, funeral parlor"
  },
  {
    "question": "麻呂",
    "answer": "まろ",
    "meaning": "I, me, (person having) thin or shaved eyebrows, affectionate suffix for names of young men or pets"
  },
  {
    "question": "先天",
    "answer": "せんてん",
    "meaning": "inherent, innate"
  },
  {
    "question": "副署",
    "answer": "ふくしょ",
    "meaning": "countersignature"
  },
  {
    "question": "蔵人",
    "answer": "くろうど,くらんど,くらびと",
    "meaning": "keeper of imperial archives, worker skilled in the brewing of sake or soy sauce"
  },
  {
    "question": "山国",
    "answer": "やまぐに",
    "meaning": "mountainous country"
  },
  {
    "question": "会堂",
    "answer": "かいどう",
    "meaning": "church, chapel, synagogue, tabernacle"
  },
  {
    "question": "水上バス",
    "answer": "すいじょうバス",
    "meaning": "water bus"
  },
  {
    "question": "群雄",
    "answer": "ぐんゆう",
    "meaning": "rival chiefs"
  },
  {
    "question": "二穴",
    "answer": "にけつ",
    "meaning": "two holes, toilet with separate chambers for urine and faeces"
  },
  {
    "question": "紅炎",
    "answer": "こうえん",
    "meaning": "red flame, (solar) prominence"
  },
  {
    "question": "大蒜",
    "answer": "にんにく",
    "meaning": "garlic (Allium sativum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "法度",
    "answer": "はっと",
    "meaning": "law, ban, prohibition, ordinance"
  },
  {
    "question": "女男",
    "answer": "おんなおとこ",
    "meaning": "feminine man, effeminate man, masculine woman, mannish woman"
  },
  {
    "question": "漁協",
    "answer": "ぎょきょう",
    "meaning": "fishery cooperative"
  },
  {
    "question": "深更",
    "answer": "しんこう",
    "meaning": "middle of the night, dead of night, midnight"
  },
  {
    "question": "千枚通し",
    "answer": "せんまいどおし",
    "meaning": "awl, eyeleteer"
  },
  {
    "question": "両腰",
    "answer": "りょうごし",
    "meaning": "katana and wakizashi"
  },
  {
    "question": "大伽藍",
    "answer": "だいがらん",
    "meaning": "large temple edifice, large temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "文鳥",
    "answer": "ぶんちょう",
    "meaning": "Java sparrow, Java rice finch (Lonchura oryzivora, Padda oryzivora)"
  },
  {
    "question": "色町",
    "answer": "いろまち",
    "meaning": "red-light district"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷害",
    "answer": "れいがい",
    "meaning": "cold-weather damage (to crops)"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗赤色",
    "answer": "あんせきしょく",
    "meaning": "dark red"
  },
  {
    "question": "然らば",
    "answer": "しからば,さらば",
    "meaning": "if so, if it be so, in that case, then, farewell, be that so, however, though that may be the case"
  },
  {
    "question": "糠",
    "answer": "ぬか",
    "meaning": "rice bran"
  },
  {
    "question": "銃眼",
    "answer": "じゅうがん",
    "meaning": "loophole, crenel, gun port, porthole"
  },
  {
    "question": "定期預金",
    "answer": "ていきよきん",
    "meaning": "term deposit, (fixed) time deposit"
  },
  {
    "question": "可食部",
    "answer": "かしょくぶ",
    "meaning": "edible part"
  },
  {
    "question": "玉体",
    "answer": "ぎょくたい",
    "meaning": "the Emperor's person or presence"
  },
  {
    "question": "電位",
    "answer": "でんい",
    "meaning": "potential (electric)"
  },
  {
    "question": "厚揚げ",
    "answer": "あつあげ",
    "meaning": "thick fried tofu"
  },
  {
    "question": "狙い打ち",
    "answer": "ねらいうち",
    "meaning": "sharpshooting, shooting, sniping, setting a goal and carrying it out"
  },
  {
    "question": "不整合",
    "answer": "ふせいごう",
    "meaning": "inconsistency, mismatch, nonconformity, discordance, misalignment, unconformity"
  },
  {
    "question": "精神障害",
    "answer": "せいしんしょうがい",
    "meaning": "mental disorder, mental disability, mental illness"
  },
  {
    "question": "錦の御旗",
    "answer": "にしきのみはた",
    "meaning": "Imperial standard, worthy cause"
  },
  {
    "question": "声望",
    "answer": "せいぼう",
    "meaning": "fame, popularity, reputation"
  },
  {
    "question": "母語",
    "answer": "ぼご",
    "meaning": "mother tongue, native language, protolanguage, parent language"
  },
  {
    "question": "油膜",
    "answer": "ゆまく",
    "meaning": "oil film, oil slick"
  },
  {
    "question": "弘法",
    "answer": "ぐほう",
    "meaning": "spreading Buddhist teachings"
  },
  {
    "question": "桃尻",
    "answer": "ももじり",
    "meaning": "somebody who is bad at horse-riding, a fidgety, restless person"
  },
  {
    "question": "強壮剤",
    "answer": "きょうそうざい",
    "meaning": "tonic, pick-me-up"
  },
  {
    "question": "腰巻",
    "answer": "こしまき",
    "meaning": "loincloth, waistcloth, kimono underskirt"
  },
  {
    "question": "能弁",
    "answer": "のうべん",
    "meaning": "eloquence, oratory"
  },
  {
    "question": "配電",
    "answer": "はいでん",
    "meaning": "distribution of electricity"
  },
  {
    "question": "初詣で",
    "answer": "はつもうで",
    "meaning": "first shrine visit of New Year"
  },
  {
    "question": "厚焼き",
    "answer": "あつやき",
    "meaning": "frying or baking something thick (e.g. thick omelette)"
  },
  {
    "question": "亡ぶ",
    "answer": "ほろぶ",
    "meaning": "to be ruined, to go under, to perish, to be destroyed"
  },
  {
    "question": "台風一過",
    "answer": "たいふういっか",
    "meaning": "clear weather after a typhoon has passed"
  },
  {
    "question": "試乗",
    "answer": "しじょう",
    "meaning": "test drive, test ride, trial ride"
  },
  {
    "question": "扶養家族",
    "answer": "ふようかぞく",
    "meaning": "one's dependents"
  },
  {
    "question": "微塵切り",
    "answer": "みじんぎり",
    "meaning": "finely chopped (cooking)"
  },
  {
    "question": "刀匠",
    "answer": "とうしょう",
    "meaning": "swordsmith"
  },
  {
    "question": "消火栓",
    "answer": "しょうかせん",
    "meaning": "fire hydrant"
  },
  {
    "question": "起居",
    "answer": "ききょ,たちい",
    "meaning": "one's daily life, condition, well-being, state of one's health, standing and sitting, movements, sit"
  },
  {
    "question": "矢羽",
    "answer": "やばね",
    "meaning": "arrow feathers"
  },
  {
    "question": "半畳",
    "answer": "はんじょう",
    "meaning": "half tatami mat, heckling, jeering, interrupting, hissing"
  },
  {
    "question": "種籾",
    "answer": "たねもみ",
    "meaning": "seed rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "難渋",
    "answer": "なんじゅう",
    "meaning": "suffering, distress, difficulty, hardship, misery, being bogged down, hurdle"
  },
  {
    "question": "大脳皮質",
    "answer": "だいのうひしつ",
    "meaning": "cerebral cortex"
  },
  {
    "question": "破傷風",
    "answer": "はしょうふう",
    "meaning": "tetanus, lockjaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会通念",
    "answer": "しゃかいつうねん",
    "meaning": "idea commonly (generally) accepted in the world"
  },
  {
    "question": "盲",
    "answer": "めくら,めしい,もう",
    "meaning": "blindness, blind person, illiteracy, illiterate person, ignorance, ignoramus"
  },
  {
    "question": "川釣り",
    "answer": "かわづり",
    "meaning": "river fishing"
  },
  {
    "question": "勢い付く",
    "answer": "いきおいづく",
    "meaning": "to gather strength, to take heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "惜敗",
    "answer": "せきはい",
    "meaning": "regrettable defeat, defeat by a narrow margin"
  },
  {
    "question": "貧者",
    "answer": "ひんじゃ",
    "meaning": "poor person"
  },
  {
    "question": "団体競技",
    "answer": "だんたいきょうぎ",
    "meaning": "team sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪徳商法",
    "answer": "あくとくしょうほう",
    "meaning": "unscrupulous business practices, fraudulent business practices, crooked business practices"
  },
  {
    "question": "年子",
    "answer": "としご",
    "meaning": "child born within a year of another, children born in consecutive years"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶道具",
    "answer": "ちゃどうぐ",
    "meaning": "tea utensils"
  },
  {
    "question": "本式",
    "answer": "ほんしき",
    "meaning": "formal, orthodox, in earnest"
  },
  {
    "question": "要綱",
    "answer": "ようこう",
    "meaning": "main principle, gist, general plan, guidelines, outline"
  },
  {
    "question": "木の芽",
    "answer": "きのめ,このめ",
    "meaning": "leaf bud, bud of Japanese pepper tree (Xanthoxylum piperitum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "過小",
    "answer": "かしょう",
    "meaning": "too small"
  },
  {
    "question": "中学年",
    "answer": "ちゅうがくねん",
    "meaning": "middle grades of primary school (third and fourth grades)"
  },
  {
    "question": "重態",
    "answer": "じゅうたい",
    "meaning": "serious condition, critical condition"
  },
  {
    "question": "煽ぐ",
    "answer": "あおぐ",
    "meaning": "to fan, to incite, to instigate"
  },
  {
    "question": "量刑",
    "answer": "りょうけい",
    "meaning": "judge's sentence, assessment of a case"
  },
  {
    "question": "炊き立て",
    "answer": "たきたて",
    "meaning": "freshly cooked"
  },
  {
    "question": "皮脂",
    "answer": "ひし",
    "meaning": "sebum, sebaceous matter"
  },
  {
    "question": "案出",
    "answer": "あんしゅつ",
    "meaning": "contrivance, to invent, to devise, to think out"
  },
  {
    "question": "旧弊",
    "answer": "きゅうへい",
    "meaning": "old evils, long-standing abuses, old-fashioned ways, outdated notions, old-fashioned, outdated, outm"
  },
  {
    "question": "類友",
    "answer": "るいとも",
    "meaning": "hobby friend, friend gained through common interests or personality"
  },
  {
    "question": "証する",
    "answer": "しょうする",
    "meaning": "to prove, to verify, to guarantee, to promise"
  },
  {
    "question": "吐瀉",
    "answer": "としゃ",
    "meaning": "vomiting and diarrhea (diarrhoea)"
  },
  {
    "question": "代替え",
    "answer": "だいがえ",
    "meaning": "substitution, alternation, alternative, substitute"
  },
  {
    "question": "霊験",
    "answer": "れいげん,れいけん",
    "meaning": "miraculous efficacy, miracle, miraculous virtue"
  },
  {
    "question": "鏤める",
    "answer": "ちりばめる",
    "meaning": "to inlay, to set, to stud (e.g. star-studded sky), to enchase (something) with, to mount (gems)"
  },
  {
    "question": "穀類",
    "answer": "こくるい",
    "meaning": "grains"
  },
  {
    "question": "酷暑",
    "answer": "こくしょ",
    "meaning": "intense heat, severe heat"
  },
  {
    "question": "重宝がる",
    "answer": "ちょうほうがる",
    "meaning": "to find useful, to think highly of"
  },
  {
    "question": "物の道理",
    "answer": "もののどうり",
    "meaning": "the principle of the thing"
  },
  {
    "question": "真正直",
    "answer": "ましょうじき",
    "meaning": "perfectly honest"
  },
  {
    "question": "言語中枢",
    "answer": "げんごちゅうすう",
    "meaning": "language center (brain), language centre"
  },
  {
    "question": "一人子",
    "answer": "ひとりご,ひとりっこ",
    "meaning": "(an) only child"
  },
  {
    "question": "固結び",
    "answer": "かたむすび",
    "meaning": "reef knot, flat knot, square knot"
  },
  {
    "question": "神経痛",
    "answer": "しんけいつう",
    "meaning": "nerve pain, neuralgia"
  },
  {
    "question": "垂涎の的",
    "answer": "すいぜんのまと,すいえんのまと",
    "meaning": "object of avid desire, object of envy"
  },
  {
    "question": "氏素性",
    "answer": "うじすじょう",
    "meaning": "(a person's) family background, lineage"
  },
  {
    "question": "社運",
    "answer": "しゃうん",
    "meaning": "company fortunes, future of a company"
  },
  {
    "question": "目の玉",
    "answer": "めのたま",
    "meaning": "eyeball"
  },
  {
    "question": "人跡未踏",
    "answer": "じんせきみとう",
    "meaning": "unexplored"
  },
  {
    "question": "現有",
    "answer": "げんゆう",
    "meaning": "present, existing"
  },
  {
    "question": "響かす",
    "answer": "ひびかす",
    "meaning": "to make something resound"
  },
  {
    "question": "肥立ち",
    "answer": "ひだち",
    "meaning": "recovery after childbirth, growth (of a child)"
  },
  {
    "question": "前渡し",
    "answer": "まえわたし",
    "meaning": "advance payment, advance delivery"
  },
  {
    "question": "伸び率",
    "answer": "のびりつ",
    "meaning": "growth rate, coefficient of extension"
  },
  {
    "question": "枢木",
    "answer": "くるるぎ",
    "meaning": "sliding wooden bolt (for holding a door or window shut)"
  },
  {
    "question": "穢土",
    "answer": "えど",
    "meaning": "this impure world (as opposed to the pure land), feces, faeces"
  },
  {
    "question": "御母様",
    "answer": "おかあさま,おたあさま,おたたさま",
    "meaning": "mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "迦楼羅",
    "answer": "かるら",
    "meaning": "Garuda or Garua (man-bird deity and 'vahana' of Hindu-Buddhist myth)"
  },
  {
    "question": "渡海",
    "answer": "とかい",
    "meaning": "crossing the sea"
  },
  {
    "question": "苫",
    "answer": "とま",
    "meaning": "woven mat (of sedge, hay, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "法務官",
    "answer": "ほうむかん",
    "meaning": "legal officer, legal office, judge advocate (army), praetor, pretor"
  },
  {
    "question": "御父様",
    "answer": "おとうさま,おもうさま",
    "meaning": "father"
  },
  {
    "question": "駐機場",
    "answer": "ちゅうきじょう",
    "meaning": "aircraft parking apron"
  },
  {
    "question": "袍",
    "answer": "ほう",
    "meaning": "round-necked robe worn by members of nobility and the imperial court"
  },
  {
    "question": "全権大使",
    "answer": "ぜんけんたいし",
    "meaning": "ambassador plenipotentiary"
  },
  {
    "question": "教理",
    "answer": "きょうり",
    "meaning": "doctrine"
  },
  {
    "question": "公領",
    "answer": "こうりょう",
    "meaning": "duchy, dukedom, principality"
  },
  {
    "question": "本舗",
    "answer": "ほんぽ",
    "meaning": "head office, main shop"
  },
  {
    "question": "手羽",
    "answer": "てば",
    "meaning": "chicken wing"
  },
  {
    "question": "氏神",
    "answer": "うじがみ",
    "meaning": "patron god, tutelar deity, guardian deity, local deity"
  },
  {
    "question": "石山",
    "answer": "いしやま",
    "meaning": "stony mountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "校了",
    "answer": "こうりょう",
    "meaning": "proofreading completed"
  },
  {
    "question": "首長竜",
    "answer": "くびながりゅう",
    "meaning": "plesiosaur"
  },
  {
    "question": "福の神",
    "answer": "ふくのかみ",
    "meaning": "god of fortune, god of wealth"
  },
  {
    "question": "土佐犬",
    "answer": "とさけん,とさいぬ",
    "meaning": "tosa (Japanese dog breed)"
  },
  {
    "question": "出塁",
    "answer": "しゅつるい",
    "meaning": "getting on base, reaching first base, times on base, TOB"
  },
  {
    "question": "顆粒",
    "answer": "かりゅう",
    "meaning": "granule"
  },
  {
    "question": "昇任",
    "answer": "しょうにん",
    "meaning": "promotion, advancement"
  },
  {
    "question": "得票率",
    "answer": "とくひょうりつ",
    "meaning": "percentage of votes"
  },
  {
    "question": "降誕",
    "answer": "こうたん",
    "meaning": "birth (regal), nativity"
  },
  {
    "question": "総領",
    "answer": "そうりょう,すべおさ",
    "meaning": "eldest child, oldest child, first-born child, child who carries on the family name, pre-ritsuryo off"
  },
  {
    "question": "本誌",
    "answer": "ほんし",
    "meaning": "this magazine"
  },
  {
    "question": "玉石",
    "answer": "ぎょくせき,たまいし",
    "meaning": "gems and stones, wheat and chaff, wheat and tares, good and bad, pebble, round stone, boulder"
  },
  {
    "question": "陣列",
    "answer": "じんれつ",
    "meaning": "battle formation"
  },
  {
    "question": "八十万",
    "answer": "はちじゅうまん,やそよろず",
    "meaning": "800,000, eight hundred thousand, many"
  },
  {
    "question": "仮釈放",
    "answer": "かりしゃくほう",
    "meaning": "releasing on parole, conditional release"
  },
  {
    "question": "脹ら脛",
    "answer": "ふくらはぎ",
    "meaning": "calf (of leg)"
  },
  {
    "question": "夕御飯",
    "answer": "ゆうごはん",
    "meaning": "evening meal, dinner, supper"
  },
  {
    "question": "八つ橋",
    "answer": "やつはし",
    "meaning": "type of sweet made with bean paste (local delicacy in Kyoto), cinnamon-seasoned cracknel (cookie), z"
  },
  {
    "question": "沓",
    "answer": "くつ",
    "meaning": "shoe, shoes, boots, footwear, footgear"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄板",
    "answer": "うすいた",
    "meaning": "laminate, veneer"
  },
  {
    "question": "前夫",
    "answer": "ぜんぷ",
    "meaning": "former husband, late husband"
  },
  {
    "question": "松阪牛",
    "answer": "まつさかうし",
    "meaning": "Matsusaka beef"
  },
  {
    "question": "八角",
    "answer": "はっかく",
    "meaning": "octagon, star anise (Illicium verum), sailfin poacher (Podothecus sachi)"
  },
  {
    "question": "海開き",
    "answer": "うみびらき",
    "meaning": "opening of the beachgoing season"
  },
  {
    "question": "機内食",
    "answer": "きないしょく",
    "meaning": "in-flight meal"
  },
  {
    "question": "選挙区",
    "answer": "せんきょく",
    "meaning": "electoral district, precinct"
  },
  {
    "question": "含羞",
    "answer": "がんしゅう,はにかみ",
    "meaning": "shyness, bashfulness, (showing) signs of embarrassment"
  },
  {
    "question": "中華丼",
    "answer": "ちゅうかどんぶり,ちゅうかどん",
    "meaning": "bowl of rice with a chop-suey-like mixture on it"
  },
  {
    "question": "大逆罪",
    "answer": "たいぎゃくざい",
    "meaning": "(the crime of) high treason"
  },
  {
    "question": "忝い",
    "answer": "かたじけない",
    "meaning": "grateful, indebted"
  },
  {
    "question": "超高層",
    "answer": "ちょうこうそう",
    "meaning": "extreme height, high-rise (i.e. building)"
  },
  {
    "question": "乾布摩擦",
    "answer": "かんぷまさつ",
    "meaning": "rubdown with a dry towel"
  },
  {
    "question": "後添え",
    "answer": "のちぞえ",
    "meaning": "one's second wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "玩弄",
    "answer": "がんろう",
    "meaning": "making sport of, making a plaything of, toying with, trifling with, ridicule, mockery"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶後",
    "answer": "ぜつご",
    "meaning": "(of a kind) never to be seen again"
  },
  {
    "question": "威儀",
    "answer": "いぎ",
    "meaning": "dignity, majesty, dignified manner"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄物",
    "answer": "うすもの",
    "meaning": "lightweight fabric or clothing, silk gauze, thin silk"
  },
  {
    "question": "皓々",
    "answer": "こうこう",
    "meaning": "bright (esp. of the moon), broad and empty"
  },
  {
    "question": "敵弾",
    "answer": "てきだん",
    "meaning": "enemy bullet"
  },
  {
    "question": "横列",
    "answer": "おうれつ",
    "meaning": "rank (e.g. of soldiers), horizontal line"
  },
  {
    "question": "挿話",
    "answer": "そうわ",
    "meaning": "episode, side story, story within a story, aside, anecdote"
  },
  {
    "question": "古紙",
    "answer": "こし",
    "meaning": "used paper, paper for recycling"
  },
  {
    "question": "山崩れ",
    "answer": "やまくずれ",
    "meaning": "landslide"
  },
  {
    "question": "表象",
    "answer": "ひょうしょう",
    "meaning": "symbol, emblem, mental image, representation, idea"
  },
  {
    "question": "中洲",
    "answer": "なかす",
    "meaning": "sandbank (in a river), sandbar"
  },
  {
    "question": "山寺",
    "answer": "やまでら",
    "meaning": "mountain temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "北極圏",
    "answer": "ほっきょくけん",
    "meaning": "Arctic Circle, the Arctic"
  },
  {
    "question": "住民登録",
    "answer": "じゅうみんとうろく",
    "meaning": "resident registration"
  },
  {
    "question": "圧し殺す",
    "answer": "おしころす",
    "meaning": "to crush to death, to stifle to death, to squeeze to death, to stifle (a laugh, etc.), to muffle (on"
  },
  {
    "question": "余技",
    "answer": "よぎ",
    "meaning": "avocation, hobby"
  },
  {
    "question": "乳腺",
    "answer": "にゅうせん",
    "meaning": "mammary gland"
  },
  {
    "question": "横風",
    "answer": "おうふう,よこかぜ",
    "meaning": "arrogant, haughty, crosswind, side wind"
  },
  {
    "question": "タメ語",
    "answer": "タメご",
    "meaning": "casual language"
  },
  {
    "question": "箴言",
    "answer": "しんげん",
    "meaning": "proverb, maxim, aphorism, Proverbs (book of the Bible)"
  },
  {
    "question": "結節点",
    "answer": "けっせつてん",
    "meaning": "focal point, nodal point, node"
  },
  {
    "question": "島影",
    "answer": "しまかげ",
    "meaning": "faint outlines of an island, vague shape of an island, silhouette of an island"
  },
  {
    "question": "水餃子",
    "answer": "すいギョーザ",
    "meaning": "boiled gyoza"
  },
  {
    "question": "針鼠",
    "answer": "はりねずみ",
    "meaning": "hedgehog (any mammal of family Erinaceidae)"
  },
  {
    "question": "カリブ海",
    "answer": "カリブかい",
    "meaning": "Caribbean Sea"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝ち越し",
    "answer": "かちこし",
    "meaning": "having more wins than losses, taking the lead (in points, goals, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "歯科医",
    "answer": "しかい",
    "meaning": "dentist"
  },
  {
    "question": "玉乗り",
    "answer": "たまのり",
    "meaning": "balancing on a ball"
  },
  {
    "question": "全身麻酔",
    "answer": "ぜんしんますい",
    "meaning": "general anesthesia, general anaesthesia"
  },
  {
    "question": "強ち",
    "answer": "あながち",
    "meaning": "not necessarily, not entirely, not altogether"
  },
  {
    "question": "一周忌",
    "answer": "いっしゅうき",
    "meaning": "first anniversary of a person's death"
  },
  {
    "question": "年寄",
    "answer": "としより",
    "meaning": "old person, elderly person, senior citizen, trustee of the Japan Sumo Association, retired high-rank"
  },
  {
    "question": "粉ミルク",
    "answer": "こなミルク",
    "meaning": "milk powder, baby formula"
  },
  {
    "question": "背脂",
    "answer": "せあぶら",
    "meaning": "back fat, fatty upper part of roast pork"
  },
  {
    "question": "招致",
    "answer": "しょうち",
    "meaning": "invitation, summons, bidding (e.g. to host the Olympics), calling"
  },
  {
    "question": "旅券",
    "answer": "りょけん",
    "meaning": "passport"
  },
  {
    "question": "示談金",
    "answer": "じだんきん",
    "meaning": "settlement money, compensation to settle a case out of court"
  },
  {
    "question": "外来語",
    "answer": "がいらいご",
    "meaning": "loanword, foreign-origin word"
  },
  {
    "question": "貼り付け",
    "answer": "はりつけ",
    "meaning": "affixing, pasting, sticking"
  },
  {
    "question": "予後",
    "answer": "よご",
    "meaning": "prognosis, aftereffects, recuperation, convalescence"
  },
  {
    "question": "芋蔓式",
    "answer": "いもづるしき",
    "meaning": "one after another, in succession"
  },
  {
    "question": "擬態語",
    "answer": "ぎたいご",
    "meaning": "phenomime, mimetic word, word that mimics an action, condition, or manner that does not make a sound"
  },
  {
    "question": "歩合",
    "answer": "ぶあい",
    "meaning": "rate, ratio, percentage, commission, poundage"
  },
  {
    "question": "売約済み",
    "answer": "ばいやくすみ",
    "meaning": "Sold (typically a sign on something that has already been sold)"
  },
  {
    "question": "皮膚病",
    "answer": "ひふびょう",
    "meaning": "skin disease"
  },
  {
    "question": "福祉施設",
    "answer": "ふくししせつ",
    "meaning": "welfare institution, welfare facility"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻紙",
    "answer": "はながみ",
    "meaning": "tissue paper, facial tissue, paper handkerchief"
  },
  {
    "question": "仏心",
    "answer": "ぶっしん,ほとけごころ",
    "meaning": "Buddha's heart, Buddha's mercy, mercy, merciful heart, charity"
  },
  {
    "question": "甚く",
    "answer": "いたく",
    "meaning": "exceedingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "速歩",
    "answer": "はやあし,そくほ",
    "meaning": "quick pace, quick steps, quick march, trot (horse gait)"
  },
  {
    "question": "泉質",
    "answer": "せんしつ",
    "meaning": "hot spring water quality, spring quality, hot spring type"
  },
  {
    "question": "画竜点睛",
    "answer": "がりょうてんせい,がりゅうてんせい",
    "meaning": "finishing touch, completing (something) by executing the final, critical step"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿賃",
    "answer": "やどちん",
    "meaning": "hotel charges"
  },
  {
    "question": "付け所",
    "answer": "つけどころ",
    "meaning": "focus of one's attention, what one is looking for"
  },
  {
    "question": "曲線美",
    "answer": "きょくせんび",
    "meaning": "curvilinear beauty, curvaceousness"
  },
  {
    "question": "産地直送",
    "answer": "さんちちょくそう",
    "meaning": "direct from the farm, farm-fresh"
  },
  {
    "question": "現代版",
    "answer": "げんだいばん",
    "meaning": "modern version, modern edition, updated, contemporary edition"
  },
  {
    "question": "粘り勝ち",
    "answer": "ねばりがち",
    "meaning": "hard-fought win, winning through perseverance"
  },
  {
    "question": "柾",
    "answer": "まさき",
    "meaning": "Japanese spindletree (Euonymus japonicus)"
  },
  {
    "question": "清音",
    "answer": "せいおん",
    "meaning": "unvoiced consonant (except p) in Japanese"
  },
  {
    "question": "美作",
    "answer": "みまさか",
    "meaning": "Mimasaka (former province located in the northeast of present-day Okayama Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "枢密",
    "answer": "すうみつ",
    "meaning": "state secrets"
  },
  {
    "question": "紅梅",
    "answer": "こうばい,べにうめ",
    "meaning": "red-blossomed plum tree, red Japanese apricot"
  },
  {
    "question": "租界",
    "answer": "そかい",
    "meaning": "concession, settlement"
  },
  {
    "question": "排撃",
    "answer": "はいげき",
    "meaning": "rejection, denunciation"
  },
  {
    "question": "金剛力",
    "answer": "こんごうりき",
    "meaning": "superhuman (Herculean) strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "滝口",
    "answer": "たきぐち",
    "meaning": "top of a waterfall"
  },
  {
    "question": "剣玉",
    "answer": "けんだま",
    "meaning": "kendama, Japanese bilboquet (cup-and-ball game)"
  },
  {
    "question": "望楼",
    "answer": "ぼうろう",
    "meaning": "watchtower, observation tower, lookout"
  },
  {
    "question": "神降ろし",
    "answer": "かみおろし",
    "meaning": "invoking a deity during a festival held in that deity's honor, medium's invocation of a deity to tak"
  },
  {
    "question": "明王",
    "answer": "みょうおう",
    "meaning": "Wisdom King, Vidyaraja"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛟",
    "answer": "みずち,みつち",
    "meaning": "mizuchi, mythical dragon-like beast"
  },
  {
    "question": "応仁の乱",
    "answer": "おうにんのらん",
    "meaning": "Ōnin War (1467-1477)"
  },
  {
    "question": "会誌",
    "answer": "かいし",
    "meaning": "club bulletin"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒玉",
    "answer": "くろだま,くろたま,こくぎょく",
    "meaning": "black ball, black, round sigil, pupil, black candy, jet (gemstone)"
  },
  {
    "question": "畸形",
    "answer": "きけい",
    "meaning": "deformity, malformation, strange shape, unusual shape"
  },
  {
    "question": "警視正",
    "answer": "けいしせい",
    "meaning": "senior superintendent, police inspector"
  },
  {
    "question": "板長",
    "answer": "いたちょう",
    "meaning": "head chef"
  },
  {
    "question": "無量",
    "answer": "むりょう",
    "meaning": "immeasurable"
  },
  {
    "question": "錦鯉",
    "answer": "にしきごい",
    "meaning": "coloured carp, colored carp"
  },
  {
    "question": "擲弾",
    "answer": "てきだん",
    "meaning": "grenade"
  },
  {
    "question": "天下御免",
    "answer": "てんかごめん",
    "meaning": "licensed, chartered, officially allowed, legitimate"
  },
  {
    "question": "長持",
    "answer": "ながもち",
    "meaning": "long-lasting, long-wearing, wears well, nagamochi, large oblong chest (for clothing, personal effect"
  },
  {
    "question": "貞操帯",
    "answer": "ていそうたい",
    "meaning": "chastity belt"
  },
  {
    "question": "大リーグ",
    "answer": "だいリーグ",
    "meaning": "the Major Leagues, Major League Baseball, MLB"
  },
  {
    "question": "木蓮",
    "answer": "もくれん,きはちす",
    "meaning": "lily magnolia (Magnolia quinquepeta, Magnolia liliiflora), rose of Sharon (Hibiscus syriacus)"
  },
  {
    "question": "海自",
    "answer": "かいじ",
    "meaning": "Maritime Self-Defense Force"
  },
  {
    "question": "銅鉱",
    "answer": "どうこう",
    "meaning": "copper ore"
  },
  {
    "question": "炉端",
    "answer": "ろばた",
    "meaning": "fireside, hearth, by the fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "党内",
    "answer": "とうない",
    "meaning": "party-internal"
  },
  {
    "question": "豪農",
    "answer": "ごうのう",
    "meaning": "wealthy farmer"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀器",
    "answer": "ぎんき",
    "meaning": "silver utensil, silverware"
  },
  {
    "question": "木像",
    "answer": "もくぞう",
    "meaning": "wooden statue, wooden image, wooden idol"
  },
  {
    "question": "剣劇",
    "answer": "けんげき",
    "meaning": "sword play, samurai drama"
  },
  {
    "question": "本尊",
    "answer": "ほんぞん",
    "meaning": "principal object of worship at a temple (usu. a buddha or bodhisattva), principal image, idol, the m"
  },
  {
    "question": "伝搬",
    "answer": "でんぱん",
    "meaning": "transmission, propagation, spread"
  },
  {
    "question": "種芋",
    "answer": "たねいも",
    "meaning": "seed potato"
  },
  {
    "question": "優性",
    "answer": "ゆうせい",
    "meaning": "dominance, dominant"
  },
  {
    "question": "猪突",
    "answer": "ちょとつ",
    "meaning": "recklessness, foolhardiness"
  },
  {
    "question": "懐石",
    "answer": "かいせき",
    "meaning": "kaiseki, sophisticated traditional Japanese cuisine brought in courses, simple meal eaten before tea"
  },
  {
    "question": "不公正",
    "answer": "ふこうせい",
    "meaning": "injustice, unfairness"
  },
  {
    "question": "齧歯類",
    "answer": "げっしるい",
    "meaning": "rodent"
  },
  {
    "question": "以南",
    "answer": "いなん",
    "meaning": "south of, and south"
  },
  {
    "question": "ヒレ肉",
    "answer": "ヒレにく",
    "meaning": "fillet, tenderloin"
  },
  {
    "question": "洗礼名",
    "answer": "せんれいめい",
    "meaning": "Christian name, baptismal name"
  },
  {
    "question": "電磁石",
    "answer": "でんじしゃく",
    "meaning": "electromagnet"
  },
  {
    "question": "焚き木",
    "answer": "たきぎ",
    "meaning": "piece(s) of firewood (esp. chopped or split from logs), kindling (twigs, branches, etc.), firewood"
  },
  {
    "question": "外征",
    "answer": "がいせい",
    "meaning": "foreign campaign"
  },
  {
    "question": "麦藁",
    "answer": "むぎわら",
    "meaning": "wheat straw, barley straw"
  },
  {
    "question": "真東",
    "answer": "まひがし",
    "meaning": "due east"
  },
  {
    "question": "市町村",
    "answer": "しちょうそん",
    "meaning": "cities, towns and villages, municipalities"
  },
  {
    "question": "縫い針",
    "answer": "ぬいばり",
    "meaning": "sewing needle"
  },
  {
    "question": "海老反り",
    "answer": "えびぞり",
    "meaning": "holding out one or both hands and arching one's body backward like a shrimp (in kabuki, represents b"
  },
  {
    "question": "中興の祖",
    "answer": "ちゅうこうのそ",
    "meaning": "ancestor who rejuvenated a dynasty or a family"
  },
  {
    "question": "二人羽織",
    "answer": "ににんばおり",
    "meaning": "'Helping Hands' comedy performance, performance in which one person wears a haori on their shoulders"
  },
  {
    "question": "救命胴衣",
    "answer": "きゅうめいどうい",
    "meaning": "life-jacket, life-vest"
  },
  {
    "question": "堅焼き",
    "answer": "かたやき",
    "meaning": "hard-baked, hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "十二単",
    "answer": "じゅうにひとえ",
    "meaning": "twelve-layered ceremonial kimono (worn by a court lady), ajuga (Ajuga nipponensis), bugle"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗礁",
    "answer": "あんしょう",
    "meaning": "reef, sunken rock, unforeseen difficulty"
  },
  {
    "question": "箸休め",
    "answer": "はしやすめ",
    "meaning": "entremets, intermezzo, small palate-cleansing dish served between courses"
  },
  {
    "question": "手隙",
    "answer": "てすき",
    "meaning": "not busy, unengaged, being free, leisure"
  },
  {
    "question": "葡萄色",
    "answer": "ぶどういろ,えびいろ",
    "meaning": "dark purple, grape (colour), reddish brown, maroon"
  },
  {
    "question": "駐輪",
    "answer": "ちゅうりん",
    "meaning": "parking one's bicycle"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄材",
    "answer": "てつざい",
    "meaning": "iron material"
  },
  {
    "question": "お零れ",
    "answer": "おこぼれ",
    "meaning": "leavings, leftovers"
  },
  {
    "question": "蚤",
    "answer": "のみ",
    "meaning": "flea"
  },
  {
    "question": "縦軸",
    "answer": "たてじく,じゅうじく",
    "meaning": "vertical axis, vertical line, vertical shaft, spindle, connection between past and present"
  },
  {
    "question": "自負心",
    "answer": "じふしん",
    "meaning": "pride, self-confidence, self-esteem, self-conceit"
  },
  {
    "question": "逆上せる",
    "answer": "のぼせる",
    "meaning": "to feel dizzy, to have blood rush to one's head, to lose one's cool, to be obsessed, to be infatuate"
  },
  {
    "question": "抽象化",
    "answer": "ちゅうしょうか",
    "meaning": "abstraction"
  },
  {
    "question": "洟",
    "answer": "はな",
    "meaning": "snivel, nasal mucus, snot"
  },
  {
    "question": "時代物",
    "answer": "じだいもの",
    "meaning": "antique, historical object, pre-Meiji period drama, period piece"
  },
  {
    "question": "等速",
    "answer": "とうそく",
    "meaning": "uniform velocity"
  },
  {
    "question": "芥",
    "answer": "ごみ,あくた,ごもく",
    "meaning": "rubbish, trash, garbage, refuse"
  },
  {
    "question": "忠勤",
    "answer": "ちゅうきん",
    "meaning": "loyalty, loyal (faithful) service"
  },
  {
    "question": "赦免",
    "answer": "しゃめん",
    "meaning": "pardon, remission, amnesty"
  },
  {
    "question": "亜熱帯",
    "answer": "あねったい",
    "meaning": "subtropics"
  },
  {
    "question": "来校",
    "answer": "らいこう",
    "meaning": "school visit"
  },
  {
    "question": "強制執行",
    "answer": "きょうせいしっこう",
    "meaning": "compulsory execution, forcible execution"
  },
  {
    "question": "少年犯罪",
    "answer": "しょうねんはんざい",
    "meaning": "juvenile crime, juvenile delinquency"
  },
  {
    "question": "馬肉",
    "answer": "ばにく",
    "meaning": "horsemeat"
  },
  {
    "question": "醜男",
    "answer": "ぶおとこ,しこお",
    "meaning": "ugly man, strong, brawny man"
  },
  {
    "question": "善く",
    "answer": "よく",
    "meaning": "nicely, properly, well, skillfully, skilfully, frequently, often, I'm glad that you ..., thank you f"
  },
  {
    "question": "妙味",
    "answer": "みょうみ",
    "meaning": "exquisiteness, charm, beauty, nice point, advantage, profit, gain"
  },
  {
    "question": "不法行為",
    "answer": "ふほうこうい",
    "meaning": "tort, illegal act, illegal activity, offence, offense"
  },
  {
    "question": "快気",
    "answer": "かいき",
    "meaning": "recovery"
  },
  {
    "question": "私学",
    "answer": "しがく",
    "meaning": "private (non-governmental) school (college, university)"
  },
  {
    "question": "洋ゲー",
    "answer": "ようゲー",
    "meaning": "Western video game"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍用犬",
    "answer": "ぐんようけん",
    "meaning": "war dog"
  },
  {
    "question": "壁板",
    "answer": "かべいた",
    "meaning": "wallboard, wall decoration"
  },
  {
    "question": "人為",
    "answer": "じんい",
    "meaning": "human work, human agency, art, artificiality"
  },
  {
    "question": "案内書",
    "answer": "あんないしょ",
    "meaning": "guidebook, guide"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶請け",
    "answer": "ちゃうけ",
    "meaning": "cake or snack served with tea"
  },
  {
    "question": "一倍",
    "answer": "いちばい",
    "meaning": "one share, one amount"
  },
  {
    "question": "興亡",
    "answer": "こうぼう",
    "meaning": "rise and fall, ups and downs"
  },
  {
    "question": "音の壁",
    "answer": "おとのかべ",
    "meaning": "sound barrier"
  },
  {
    "question": "自費出版",
    "answer": "じひしゅっぱん",
    "meaning": "self-publishing, publishing at one's own expense"
  },
  {
    "question": "御足労",
    "answer": "ごそくろう",
    "meaning": "inviting another to one's home, office, etc., the trouble of coming (going)"
  },
  {
    "question": "財界人",
    "answer": "ざいかいじん",
    "meaning": "financier, business leader"
  },
  {
    "question": "憂さ",
    "answer": "うさ",
    "meaning": "gloom, melancholy"
  },
  {
    "question": "騙し絵",
    "answer": "だましえ",
    "meaning": "trompe l'oeil"
  },
  {
    "question": "高齢化",
    "answer": "こうれいか",
    "meaning": "population ageing (aging)"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪賢い",
    "answer": "わるがしこい",
    "meaning": "cunning, crafty, wily, sly"
  },
  {
    "question": "日用",
    "answer": "にちよう,ひよう",
    "meaning": "daily use, daily employment, hiring by the day, day's wages"
  },
  {
    "question": "青天",
    "answer": "せいてん",
    "meaning": "blue sky"
  },
  {
    "question": "繰り回す",
    "answer": "くりまわす",
    "meaning": "to roll over (debt)"
  },
  {
    "question": "日の入り",
    "answer": "ひのいり",
    "meaning": "sunset"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄色人種",
    "answer": "おうしょくじんしゅ,こうしょくじんしゅ",
    "meaning": "yellow race, Mongoloid race"
  },
  {
    "question": "過去る",
    "answer": "すぎさる",
    "meaning": "to pass, to pass by"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼き直す",
    "answer": "やきなおす",
    "meaning": "to grill again, to rehash"
  },
  {
    "question": "生い立つ",
    "answer": "おいたつ",
    "meaning": "to grow, to develop, to grow up"
  },
  {
    "question": "快方",
    "answer": "かいほう",
    "meaning": "convalescence"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶入れ",
    "answer": "ちゃいれ",
    "meaning": "tea container (usually for thick tea used at the tea ceremony)"
  },
  {
    "question": "画素",
    "answer": "がそ",
    "meaning": "picture element, image pixel, PEL"
  },
  {
    "question": "治する",
    "answer": "じする,ちする",
    "meaning": "to be cured, to be healed, to cure, to heal, to rule"
  },
  {
    "question": "陽当たり",
    "answer": "ひあたり",
    "meaning": "exposure to the sun, sunny place"
  },
  {
    "question": "浅学",
    "answer": "せんがく",
    "meaning": "shallow knowledge, superficial learning"
  },
  {
    "question": "跳び越す",
    "answer": "とびこす",
    "meaning": "to leap over"
  },
  {
    "question": "真鶴",
    "answer": "まなづる",
    "meaning": "white-naped crane (Grus vipio)"
  },
  {
    "question": "藤花",
    "answer": "とうか",
    "meaning": "wisteria flower"
  },
  {
    "question": "久世",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "御陵",
    "answer": "ごりょう",
    "meaning": "imperial tomb"
  },
  {
    "question": "白洲",
    "answer": "しらす",
    "meaning": "white sandbar, white sandbank, area in a garden or entrance of a house laid with white sand or pebbl"
  },
  {
    "question": "観月",
    "answer": "かんげつ",
    "meaning": "moon viewing (esp. during the eight month of the lunar calendar)"
  },
  {
    "question": "ペンキ屋",
    "answer": "ペンキや",
    "meaning": "painter (of buildings, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "野薔薇",
    "answer": "のばら,のいばら",
    "meaning": "wild rose, briar, multiflora rose (Rosa multiflora), baby rose, Japanese rose"
  },
  {
    "question": "革命政府",
    "answer": "かくめいせいふ",
    "meaning": "revolutionary government"
  },
  {
    "question": "枢密院",
    "answer": "すうみついん",
    "meaning": "(Japanese) Privy Council (abolished in 1947)"
  },
  {
    "question": "神将",
    "answer": "じんしょう,しんしょう",
    "meaning": "divine generals who protect pilgrims, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "金糸雀",
    "answer": "カナリア,カナリヤ,きんしじゃく",
    "meaning": "canary (esp. the island canary, Serinus canaria)"
  },
  {
    "question": "大祓",
    "answer": "おおはらえ,おおはらい",
    "meaning": "great purification, purification rite performed twice a year, before daijōsai and after major disast"
  },
  {
    "question": "豚丼",
    "answer": "ぶたどん,とんどん",
    "meaning": "rice covered with pork and vegetables"
  },
  {
    "question": "水雷",
    "answer": "すいらい,みずがみなり,みずかみなり",
    "meaning": "torpedo, (sea) mine, underwater mine, thunder accompanied by rain, lightning that does not start a f"
  },
  {
    "question": "報道官",
    "answer": "ほうどうかん",
    "meaning": "press officer, press secretary"
  },
  {
    "question": "仰有る",
    "answer": "おっしゃる",
    "meaning": "to say, to speak, to tell, to talk"
  },
  {
    "question": "角灯",
    "answer": "かくとう",
    "meaning": "square hand-lantern"
  },
  {
    "question": "愚人",
    "answer": "ぐじん",
    "meaning": "fool"
  },
  {
    "question": "遣り方",
    "answer": "やりかた",
    "meaning": "way (of doing), manner, method, means"
  },
  {
    "question": "隷下",
    "answer": "れいか",
    "meaning": "subordinates, followers"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍令",
    "answer": "ぐんれい",
    "meaning": "military command"
  },
  {
    "question": "澄明",
    "answer": "ちょうめい",
    "meaning": "clear and bright"
  },
  {
    "question": "献体",
    "answer": "けんたい",
    "meaning": "body donation, becoming naked"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓬髪",
    "answer": "ほうはつ",
    "meaning": "unkempt hair, disheveled hair, tousled hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "下宿屋",
    "answer": "げしゅくや",
    "meaning": "lodging house"
  },
  {
    "question": "宇宙線",
    "answer": "うちゅうせん",
    "meaning": "cosmic ray"
  },
  {
    "question": "地ビール",
    "answer": "じビール",
    "meaning": "local beer, microbrew"
  },
  {
    "question": "更生施設",
    "answer": "こうせいしせつ",
    "meaning": "rehabilitation facilities, halfway house"
  },
  {
    "question": "爆心",
    "answer": "ばくしん",
    "meaning": "center of an explosion, centre of an explosion"
  },
  {
    "question": "切り絵",
    "answer": "きりえ",
    "meaning": "cutout, cutout picture, papercut art"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓄電",
    "answer": "ちくでん",
    "meaning": "storage of electricity"
  },
  {
    "question": "俸禄",
    "answer": "ほうろく",
    "meaning": "retainer's stipend, official pay, salary"
  },
  {
    "question": "散文的",
    "answer": "さんぶんてき",
    "meaning": "prosaic"
  },
  {
    "question": "万葉集",
    "answer": "まんようしゅう",
    "meaning": "Man'yōshū (8th century anthology of Japanese poetry)"
  },
  {
    "question": "男殺し",
    "answer": "おとこごろし",
    "meaning": "temptress, flirt, minx, coquette, charmer, siren, man-trap, murder of a man, murderer of a man"
  },
  {
    "question": "神の僕",
    "answer": "かみのしのべ",
    "meaning": "Servant of God (in Christianity)"
  },
  {
    "question": "矩形",
    "answer": "くけい,さしがた",
    "meaning": "rectangle"
  },
  {
    "question": "海底火山",
    "answer": "かいていかざん",
    "meaning": "submarine volcano"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会福祉",
    "answer": "しゃかいふくし",
    "meaning": "social welfare"
  },
  {
    "question": "開腹",
    "answer": "かいふく",
    "meaning": "making a surgical incision in the abdomen"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶息",
    "answer": "ぜっそく",
    "meaning": "expiry, dying, death"
  },
  {
    "question": "署名運動",
    "answer": "しょめいうんどう",
    "meaning": "signature-collecting campaign"
  },
  {
    "question": "病身",
    "answer": "びょうしん",
    "meaning": "weak constitution, ill health"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛞蝓",
    "answer": "なめくじ",
    "meaning": "slug"
  },
  {
    "question": "白眉",
    "answer": "はくび",
    "meaning": "finest example, the best (of), white eyebrows"
  },
  {
    "question": "千秋楽",
    "answer": "せんしゅうらく",
    "meaning": "concluding festivities, concluding program, concluding programme, final day of a tournament"
  },
  {
    "question": "凶星",
    "answer": "きょうせい",
    "meaning": "star of bad omen"
  },
  {
    "question": "嬰児",
    "answer": "えいじ,みどりご",
    "meaning": "infant, baby"
  },
  {
    "question": "所信",
    "answer": "しょしん",
    "meaning": "belief, conviction, opinion"
  },
  {
    "question": "合成樹脂",
    "answer": "ごうせいじゅし",
    "meaning": "plastics, synthetic resins"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒土",
    "answer": "こくど,くろつち",
    "meaning": "black terracotta, black soil"
  },
  {
    "question": "再選",
    "answer": "さいせん",
    "meaning": "re-election"
  },
  {
    "question": "自由形",
    "answer": "じゆうがた",
    "meaning": "freestyle (e.g. swimming event)"
  },
  {
    "question": "不撓不屈",
    "answer": "ふとうふくつ",
    "meaning": "tenacity, indomitableness, dauntlessness, inflexibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "日溜まり",
    "answer": "ひだまり",
    "meaning": "sunny spot, exposure to the sun"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸窓",
    "answer": "まるまど",
    "meaning": "circular window, round window"
  },
  {
    "question": "千度",
    "answer": "せんど,ちたび",
    "meaning": "thousand times"
  },
  {
    "question": "蕩々",
    "answer": "とうとう",
    "meaning": "vast, calm"
  },
  {
    "question": "罪名",
    "answer": "ざいめい",
    "meaning": "name of a crime, charge"
  },
  {
    "question": "続刊",
    "answer": "ぞっかん",
    "meaning": "continuing publication"
  },
  {
    "question": "不具",
    "answer": "ふぐ",
    "meaning": "deformity, distortion, disability, cripple, word written at the end of a letter"
  },
  {
    "question": "砲丸投げ",
    "answer": "ほうがんなげ",
    "meaning": "shot put"
  },
  {
    "question": "三和土",
    "answer": "たたき",
    "meaning": "hard-packed dirt (clay, gravel, etc.) floor, concrete floor"
  },
  {
    "question": "叙す",
    "answer": "じょす",
    "meaning": "to relate, to narrate, to describe, to confer (a rank)"
  },
  {
    "question": "食い倒れ",
    "answer": "くいだおれ",
    "meaning": "bringing ruin upon oneself by extravagance in food"
  },
  {
    "question": "橋梁",
    "answer": "きょうりょう",
    "meaning": "bridge"
  },
  {
    "question": "揺り戻し",
    "answer": "ゆりもどし",
    "meaning": "swinging back, aftershock, backlash"
  },
  {
    "question": "臨時雇い",
    "answer": "りんじやとい",
    "meaning": "temporary employment or employee"
  },
  {
    "question": "棚卸し",
    "answer": "たなおろし",
    "meaning": "stocktaking, inventory count, faultfinding"
  },
  {
    "question": "然る後",
    "answer": "しかるのち",
    "meaning": "thereafter, after doing that, followed by"
  },
  {
    "question": "明晩",
    "answer": "みょうばん",
    "meaning": "tomorrow evening"
  },
  {
    "question": "逆落とし",
    "answer": "さかおとし",
    "meaning": "dropping (something) headfirst down a precipice, downhill rush, plunging down a precipice"
  },
  {
    "question": "如何程",
    "answer": "いかほど",
    "meaning": "how much, how many, however"
  },
  {
    "question": "小耳",
    "answer": "こみみ",
    "meaning": "overhear, happened to hear that"
  },
  {
    "question": "最右翼",
    "answer": "さいうよく",
    "meaning": "dominant person, preeminent person, strongest contender"
  },
  {
    "question": "定額",
    "answer": "ていがく",
    "meaning": "ration, fixed amount"
  },
  {
    "question": "合す",
    "answer": "あわす,がっす",
    "meaning": "to match (rhythm, speed, etc.), to join together, to unite, to combine, to add up, to face, to be op"
  },
  {
    "question": "御影石",
    "answer": "みかげいし",
    "meaning": "granite"
  },
  {
    "question": "千金",
    "answer": "せんきん",
    "meaning": "1000 pounds, 1000 kan, 1000 yen, 1000 pieces of gold, great weight, pricelessness"
  },
  {
    "question": "領する",
    "answer": "りょうする",
    "meaning": "to own, to receive, to understand"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼き豚",
    "answer": "やきぶた",
    "meaning": "roast pork, baseball fan"
  },
  {
    "question": "五文字",
    "answer": "ごもじ",
    "meaning": "five letters, five signs, first five syllables of a waka or haiku"
  },
  {
    "question": "不満足",
    "answer": "ふまんぞく",
    "meaning": "dissatisfaction, discontent, displeasure"
  },
  {
    "question": "他愛",
    "answer": "たあい,たわい",
    "meaning": "altruism, sanity, soundness of mind, prudence and discretion, drunkenness"
  },
  {
    "question": "種々雑多",
    "answer": "しゅじゅざった",
    "meaning": "all sorts of, various, miscellaneous, motley"
  },
  {
    "question": "緊急車両",
    "answer": "きんきゅうしゃりょう",
    "meaning": "emergency vehicle"
  },
  {
    "question": "集積回路",
    "answer": "しゅうせきかいろ",
    "meaning": "integrated-circuit"
  },
  {
    "question": "驚喜",
    "answer": "きょうき",
    "meaning": "pleasant surprise"
  },
  {
    "question": "上得意",
    "answer": "じょうとくい",
    "meaning": "good customer, prime customer, valued clientele"
  },
  {
    "question": "粒状",
    "answer": "りゅうじょう,つぶじょう",
    "meaning": "granular, granulated"
  },
  {
    "question": "大会社",
    "answer": "だいがいしゃ",
    "meaning": "large industrial company, major corporation, big business"
  },
  {
    "question": "服飾品",
    "answer": "ふくしょくひん",
    "meaning": "accessories"
  },
  {
    "question": "飽き性",
    "answer": "あきしょう",
    "meaning": "fickle nature, flighty temperament, inconstant person"
  },
  {
    "question": "謹厳実直",
    "answer": "きんげんじっちょく",
    "meaning": "sober and honest"
  },
  {
    "question": "虎口",
    "answer": "ここう",
    "meaning": "tiger's den, jaws of death, dangerous place"
  },
  {
    "question": "根菜類",
    "answer": "こんさいるい",
    "meaning": "root crops"
  },
  {
    "question": "火中",
    "answer": "かちゅう,ほなか",
    "meaning": "in the fire, in the flames, burning (something)"
  },
  {
    "question": "足癖",
    "answer": "あしくせ",
    "meaning": "gait, one's manner of walking, technique involving tripping the opponent"
  },
  {
    "question": "縫い方",
    "answer": "ぬいかた",
    "meaning": "sewing method, sewer"
  },
  {
    "question": "伸び盛り",
    "answer": "のびざかり",
    "meaning": "growth period, period of rapid growth"
  },
  {
    "question": "出版物",
    "answer": "しゅっぱんぶつ",
    "meaning": "publication"
  },
  {
    "question": "北向き",
    "answer": "きたむき",
    "meaning": "facing north, northern exposure"
  },
  {
    "question": "火の元",
    "answer": "ひのもと",
    "meaning": "place where fire is likely to break out, possible cause of a fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "機が熟す",
    "answer": "きがじゅくす",
    "meaning": "for the time to be ripe"
  },
  {
    "question": "臆病風",
    "answer": "おくびょうかぜ",
    "meaning": "loss of nerve"
  },
  {
    "question": "渡会",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "坎",
    "answer": "かん",
    "meaning": "pit, hole, kan (one of the trigrams of the I Ching: water, north)"
  },
  {
    "question": "立夏",
    "answer": "りっか",
    "meaning": "first day of summer (approx. May 6)"
  },
  {
    "question": "書痴",
    "answer": "しょち",
    "meaning": "book nut, bibliomaniac, bookworm"
  },
  {
    "question": "北天",
    "answer": "ほくてん",
    "meaning": "northern sky"
  },
  {
    "question": "御子様",
    "answer": "おこさま",
    "meaning": "(someone else's) child, child, kid"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍令部",
    "answer": "ぐんれいぶ",
    "meaning": "Naval General Staff"
  },
  {
    "question": "炎天",
    "answer": "えんてん",
    "meaning": "blazing heat, scorching sun"
  },
  {
    "question": "参勤交代",
    "answer": "さんきんこうたい",
    "meaning": "daimyo's alternating Edo residence, official attendance service (by a daimyo in the Edo era)"
  },
  {
    "question": "刃金",
    "answer": "はがね",
    "meaning": "steel"
  },
  {
    "question": "揚句",
    "answer": "あげく",
    "meaning": "after (a long process), at the end of, last line (of a renga)"
  },
  {
    "question": "修道会",
    "answer": "しゅうどうかい",
    "meaning": "(Catholic) order"
  },
  {
    "question": "代理者",
    "answer": "だいりしゃ",
    "meaning": "proxy, agent, substitute, deputy, alternate, representative, attorney"
  },
  {
    "question": "嵯峨",
    "answer": "さが",
    "meaning": "precipitous"
  },
  {
    "question": "梵天",
    "answer": "ぼんてん",
    "meaning": "Brahma-Deva"
  },
  {
    "question": "転瞬",
    "answer": "てんしゅん",
    "meaning": "blink of an eye, instant, moment"
  },
  {
    "question": "出城",
    "answer": "でじろ",
    "meaning": "branch castle"
  },
  {
    "question": "具わる",
    "answer": "そなわる",
    "meaning": "to be furnished with, to be provided with, to be equipped with, to be possessed of, to be endowed wi"
  },
  {
    "question": "樺太",
    "answer": "からふと",
    "meaning": "Karafuto (Japanese name for Sakhalin)"
  },
  {
    "question": "南ア",
    "answer": "なんア,みなみア",
    "meaning": "South Africa"
  },
  {
    "question": "光波",
    "answer": "こうは",
    "meaning": "light waves"
  },
  {
    "question": "夷",
    "answer": "えびす,い",
    "meaning": "peoples formerly of northern Japan with distinct language and culture (i.e. the Ainu), provincial (i"
  },
  {
    "question": "映じる",
    "answer": "えいじる",
    "meaning": "to be reflected (in), to be mirrored (in), to impress (a person)"
  },
  {
    "question": "台北",
    "answer": "タイペイ,たいほく",
    "meaning": "Taipei"
  },
  {
    "question": "落雁",
    "answer": "らくがん",
    "meaning": "rakugan, dry confection of starch (e.g. rice, soy or barley flour) and sugar, mixed and pressed into"
  },
  {
    "question": "養蚕",
    "answer": "ようさん",
    "meaning": "sericulture, silkworm culture, silkworm raising"
  },
  {
    "question": "至尊",
    "answer": "しそん,しいそん",
    "meaning": "extreme reverence, deeply revered person, the Emperor"
  },
  {
    "question": "弱化",
    "answer": "じゃっか",
    "meaning": "weakening"
  },
  {
    "question": "回転扉",
    "answer": "かいてんとびら",
    "meaning": "revolving door"
  },
  {
    "question": "油虫",
    "answer": "あぶらむし",
    "meaning": "aphid, plant louse, cockroach, Japanese house bat (Pipistrellus abramus), hanger-on, parasite, visit"
  },
  {
    "question": "無題",
    "answer": "むだい",
    "meaning": "untitled, titleless, without a title, no subject (email)"
  },
  {
    "question": "箸置き",
    "answer": "はしおき",
    "meaning": "chopstick rest"
  },
  {
    "question": "宣する",
    "answer": "せんする",
    "meaning": "to announce, to declare"
  },
  {
    "question": "宣誓書",
    "answer": "せんせいしょ",
    "meaning": "(written) oath"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨女",
    "answer": "あめおんな",
    "meaning": "woman who brings the rain with her wherever she goes, woman who is constantly unlucky with the weath"
  },
  {
    "question": "同定",
    "answer": "どうてい",
    "meaning": "identification"
  },
  {
    "question": "宗教裁判",
    "answer": "しゅうきょうさいばん",
    "meaning": "the Inquisition"
  },
  {
    "question": "天下泰平",
    "answer": "てんかたいへい",
    "meaning": "peace and tranquillity, halcyon times of peace, peaceful world"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍歴",
    "answer": "ぐんれき",
    "meaning": "(one's) military service record"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄路",
    "answer": "てつろ",
    "meaning": "railroad, railway"
  },
  {
    "question": "導管",
    "answer": "どうかん",
    "meaning": "conduit, pipe, duct, vessel"
  },
  {
    "question": "鏡文字",
    "answer": "かがみもじ",
    "meaning": "mirror writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "民主国家",
    "answer": "みんしゅこっか",
    "meaning": "democracy, democratic nation"
  },
  {
    "question": "慣熟",
    "answer": "かんじゅく",
    "meaning": "proficiency, mastery, competence, becoming proficient (in)"
  },
  {
    "question": "甘露煮",
    "answer": "かんろに",
    "meaning": "candied (chestnuts), sweetened boiled fish"
  },
  {
    "question": "登板",
    "answer": "とうばん",
    "meaning": "taking the mound, pitching a game"
  },
  {
    "question": "精米",
    "answer": "せいまい",
    "meaning": "rice polishing, polished rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "堅守",
    "answer": "けんしゅ",
    "meaning": "strong defense, strong defence"
  },
  {
    "question": "遣り手",
    "answer": "やりて",
    "meaning": "skilled person, capable person, shrewd person, go-getter, hotshot, doer, performer, agent, giver, be"
  },
  {
    "question": "博物学",
    "answer": "はくぶつがく",
    "meaning": "natural history"
  },
  {
    "question": "剽悍",
    "answer": "ひょうかん",
    "meaning": "fierceness, daring"
  },
  {
    "question": "職位",
    "answer": "しょくい",
    "meaning": "employment position or rank"
  },
  {
    "question": "独奏",
    "answer": "どくそう",
    "meaning": "(instrumental) solo, recital"
  },
  {
    "question": "攣",
    "answer": "てなえ",
    "meaning": "arm disability, someone with disabled arms"
  },
  {
    "question": "逆しま",
    "answer": "さかしま",
    "meaning": "reverse, inversion, upside down, unreasonable, absurd, wrong"
  },
  {
    "question": "久方振り",
    "answer": "ひさかたぶり",
    "meaning": "long time (since the last time), first in a long time"
  },
  {
    "question": "鍍金",
    "answer": "めっき,ときん",
    "meaning": "plating (chrome, gold, silver, etc.), coating, gilding, gilt, pretense, pretence, simulation"
  },
  {
    "question": "婦人科",
    "answer": "ふじんか",
    "meaning": "gynecology department, gynecology"
  },
  {
    "question": "一旗",
    "answer": "ひとはた",
    "meaning": "(one) flag"
  },
  {
    "question": "女役",
    "answer": "おんなやく",
    "meaning": "female role (e.g. in film), female part, occupation deemed fit for a woman, passive role in a male h"
  },
  {
    "question": "時代小説",
    "answer": "じだいしょうせつ",
    "meaning": "historical novel"
  },
  {
    "question": "参ずる",
    "answer": "さんずる",
    "meaning": "to come, to go, to participate, to perform Zen meditation"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄黒い",
    "answer": "うすぐろい",
    "meaning": "blackish, dark, dusky"
  },
  {
    "question": "鋳潰す",
    "answer": "いつぶす",
    "meaning": "to melt down"
  },
  {
    "question": "水力",
    "answer": "すいりょく",
    "meaning": "hydraulic power, water power"
  },
  {
    "question": "手提げ鞄",
    "answer": "てさげかばん",
    "meaning": "handbag, purse, briefcase, attache case"
  },
  {
    "question": "三部作",
    "answer": "さんぶさく",
    "meaning": "trilogy"
  },
  {
    "question": "排卵",
    "answer": "はいらん",
    "meaning": "ovulation"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇貨",
    "answer": "きか",
    "meaning": "curiosity, rare item, rarity, rare opportunity which could be beneficial"
  },
  {
    "question": "政治生命",
    "answer": "せいじせいめい",
    "meaning": "political life"
  },
  {
    "question": "譬える",
    "answer": "たとえる",
    "meaning": "to compare (something) to, to liken, to speak figuratively, to use a simile, to use a metaphor"
  },
  {
    "question": "鮒",
    "answer": "ふな",
    "meaning": "crucian carp (Carassius spp.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "色狂い",
    "answer": "いろきちがい,いろぐるい",
    "meaning": "erotomania, sexual obsession, sexual maniac"
  },
  {
    "question": "流行歌",
    "answer": "りゅうこうか,はやりうた",
    "meaning": "popular song, hit song"
  },
  {
    "question": "水資源",
    "answer": "みずしげん",
    "meaning": "water resources"
  },
  {
    "question": "厳寒",
    "answer": "げんかん",
    "meaning": "intense cold"
  },
  {
    "question": "全日",
    "answer": "ぜんじつ",
    "meaning": "all days"
  },
  {
    "question": "昇竜",
    "answer": "しょうりゅう",
    "meaning": "rising dragon, great dash"
  },
  {
    "question": "飾り窓",
    "answer": "かざりまど",
    "meaning": "display window, shop window"
  },
  {
    "question": "港湾都市",
    "answer": "こうわんとし",
    "meaning": "port city, harbour city, harbor city"
  },
  {
    "question": "名コンビ",
    "answer": "めいコンビ",
    "meaning": "great pair, well-oiled two-man team"
  },
  {
    "question": "上首尾",
    "answer": "じょうしゅび",
    "meaning": "great success, happy result, good result"
  },
  {
    "question": "正邪",
    "answer": "せいじゃ",
    "meaning": "right and wrong, right or wrong"
  },
  {
    "question": "中古車",
    "answer": "ちゅうこしゃ",
    "meaning": "used car, secondhand car"
  },
  {
    "question": "邪魔臭い",
    "answer": "じゃまくさい",
    "meaning": "troublesome, pain in the butt"
  },
  {
    "question": "都落ち",
    "answer": "みやこおち",
    "meaning": "leaving (fleeing) the capital"
  },
  {
    "question": "控除",
    "answer": "こうじょ",
    "meaning": "subtraction, deduction (e.g. tax), subsidy"
  },
  {
    "question": "強力粉",
    "answer": "きょうりきこ",
    "meaning": "bread flour (high gluten), strong flour, hard flour"
  },
  {
    "question": "世事",
    "answer": "せじ,せいじ",
    "meaning": "worldly affairs, ways of the world"
  },
  {
    "question": "間の間",
    "answer": "あいのま",
    "meaning": "room connecting the two main rooms of a building, intermediate room"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち札",
    "answer": "もちふだ",
    "meaning": "cards in one's hand, one's hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "泳法",
    "answer": "えいほう",
    "meaning": "swimming style"
  },
  {
    "question": "手捌き",
    "answer": "てさばき",
    "meaning": "handling, manipulation"
  },
  {
    "question": "公費",
    "answer": "こうひ",
    "meaning": "public expense, public funds, public money, public expenditure"
  },
  {
    "question": "起業家",
    "answer": "きぎょうか",
    "meaning": "entrepreneur, person who starts a new business"
  },
  {
    "question": "競輪",
    "answer": "けいりん",
    "meaning": "keirin, cycle racing event, usu. 2km with a paced start and sprint finish"
  },
  {
    "question": "奏する",
    "answer": "そうする",
    "meaning": "to report to the Emperor, to play (musical instrument), to accomplish"
  },
  {
    "question": "倍増し",
    "answer": "ばいまし",
    "meaning": "doubling"
  },
  {
    "question": "傷病",
    "answer": "しょうびょう",
    "meaning": "injuries and sickness, wounds and illness"
  },
  {
    "question": "強請り",
    "answer": "ねだり,ゆすり",
    "meaning": "begging, pestering, pleading, coaxing, blackmail, extortion, racketeering, blackmailer, extortionist"
  },
  {
    "question": "愚兄",
    "answer": "ぐけい",
    "meaning": "foolish older brother, older brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄利多売",
    "answer": "はくりたばい",
    "meaning": "small profits and quick returns"
  },
  {
    "question": "燃え残り",
    "answer": "もえのこり",
    "meaning": "embers"
  },
  {
    "question": "敬慕",
    "answer": "けいぼ",
    "meaning": "love and respect"
  },
  {
    "question": "指数関数",
    "answer": "しすうかんすう",
    "meaning": "exponential function"
  },
  {
    "question": "糞食らえ",
    "answer": "くそくらえ",
    "meaning": "eat shit!, fuck off!, fuck you!"
  },
  {
    "question": "顕示",
    "answer": "けんじ",
    "meaning": "manifestation, public show, showing conspicuously"
  },
  {
    "question": "筆文字",
    "answer": "ふでもじ",
    "meaning": "character written by brush, brush-stroke character"
  },
  {
    "question": "性徴",
    "answer": "せいちょう",
    "meaning": "sexual characteristics"
  },
  {
    "question": "降り口",
    "answer": "おりぐち,おりくち",
    "meaning": "top (of a flight of stairs), exit involving a descent (e.g. from a bus)"
  },
  {
    "question": "文中",
    "answer": "ぶんちゅう",
    "meaning": "in the sentence, in the text, Bunchū era (of the Southern Court) (1372.4.?-1375.5.27)"
  },
  {
    "question": "青息吐息",
    "answer": "あおいきといき",
    "meaning": "deep distress"
  },
  {
    "question": "車検",
    "answer": "しゃけん",
    "meaning": "vehicle inspection"
  },
  {
    "question": "秋めく",
    "answer": "あきめく",
    "meaning": "to become autumnal"
  },
  {
    "question": "適格",
    "answer": "てきかく,てっかく",
    "meaning": "eligible, qualified, competent"
  },
  {
    "question": "適材",
    "answer": "てきざい",
    "meaning": "man fit for the post, right person"
  },
  {
    "question": "床暖房",
    "answer": "ゆかだんぼう",
    "meaning": "floor heating, underfloor heating"
  },
  {
    "question": "子殺し",
    "answer": "こごろし",
    "meaning": "infanticide, filicide"
  },
  {
    "question": "立て替え",
    "answer": "たてかえ",
    "meaning": "advancing money, temporary payment for someone else, payment on behalf of another party, with the ex"
  },
  {
    "question": "在校",
    "answer": "ざいこう",
    "meaning": "being in school, being a student of"
  },
  {
    "question": "小作り",
    "answer": "こづくり",
    "meaning": "small build, small size"
  },
  {
    "question": "人間像",
    "answer": "にんげんぞう",
    "meaning": "image of (an ideal) person"
  },
  {
    "question": "再雇用",
    "answer": "さいこよう",
    "meaning": "reemployment"
  },
  {
    "question": "抵当",
    "answer": "ていとう",
    "meaning": "mortgage, security, hypothec, pledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "已む",
    "answer": "やむ",
    "meaning": "to cease, to stop, to be over"
  },
  {
    "question": "青地",
    "answer": "あおじ",
    "meaning": "blue cloth, blue ground, blue background"
  },
  {
    "question": "日照時間",
    "answer": "にっしょうじかん",
    "meaning": "daylight hours, hours of sunshine"
  },
  {
    "question": "速効",
    "answer": "そっこう",
    "meaning": "speedy effect"
  },
  {
    "question": "口寂しい",
    "answer": "くちさびしい,くちざみしい,くちさみしい",
    "meaning": "craving for food, a cigarette, etc., longing to have something in one's mouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "怠け癖",
    "answer": "なまけぐせ",
    "meaning": "habit of idleness (laziness), indolence"
  },
  {
    "question": "和洋",
    "answer": "わよう",
    "meaning": "Japan and Europe"
  },
  {
    "question": "同系",
    "answer": "どうけい",
    "meaning": "affiliated, akin"
  },
  {
    "question": "目通し",
    "answer": "めどおし",
    "meaning": "glancing through"
  },
  {
    "question": "曇らす",
    "answer": "くもらす",
    "meaning": "to encloud, to make dim, to make dull, to tarnish, to obscure, to darken, to muffle"
  },
  {
    "question": "排す",
    "answer": "はいす",
    "meaning": "to push aside, to overcome (e.g. difficulties), to reject, to align, to put in order, to push open"
  },
  {
    "question": "刷り",
    "answer": "すり",
    "meaning": "printing"
  },
  {
    "question": "骨を拾う",
    "answer": "ほねをひろう",
    "meaning": "to collect the ashes of the deceased, to look after someone's affairs after he dies"
  },
  {
    "question": "野伏せり",
    "answer": "のぶせり",
    "meaning": "mountain-dwelling robber, brigand"
  },
  {
    "question": "玄冬",
    "answer": "げんとう,けんとう",
    "meaning": "winter"
  },
  {
    "question": "外惑星",
    "answer": "がいわくせい",
    "meaning": "outer planet"
  },
  {
    "question": "導体",
    "answer": "どうたい",
    "meaning": "conductor (electricity)"
  },
  {
    "question": "北朝",
    "answer": "ほくちょう",
    "meaning": "Northern Court (Japan, 1336-1392), Northern Dynasty, Northern Dynasties (China, 420-589)"
  },
  {
    "question": "因幡",
    "answer": "いなば",
    "meaning": "Inaba (former province located in the east of present-day Tottori Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "統帥",
    "answer": "とうすい",
    "meaning": "supreme command, high command"
  },
  {
    "question": "直流",
    "answer": "ちょくりゅう",
    "meaning": "direct current, DC"
  },
  {
    "question": "禁裏",
    "answer": "きんり",
    "meaning": "Imperial Palace, Imperial Court"
  },
  {
    "question": "往なす",
    "answer": "いなす",
    "meaning": "to parry, to sidestep, to dodge"
  },
  {
    "question": "佐々",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "棋",
    "answer": "ご",
    "meaning": "go, board game of capturing territory"
  },
  {
    "question": "変針",
    "answer": "へんしん",
    "meaning": "veering"
  },
  {
    "question": "銅山",
    "answer": "どうざん",
    "meaning": "copper mine"
  },
  {
    "question": "国分寺",
    "answer": "こくぶんじ",
    "meaning": "state-supported provincial temple (Nara period)"
  },
  {
    "question": "掏摸",
    "answer": "すり",
    "meaning": "pickpocket"
  },
  {
    "question": "幕臣",
    "answer": "ばくしん",
    "meaning": "shogunate retainer, shogunate vassal"
  },
  {
    "question": "輸液",
    "answer": "ゆえき",
    "meaning": "transfusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "国税",
    "answer": "こくぜい",
    "meaning": "national tax"
  },
  {
    "question": "水牢",
    "answer": "みずろう",
    "meaning": "(punishment by being placed in a) water-filled chamber"
  },
  {
    "question": "再審",
    "answer": "さいしん",
    "meaning": "retrial, reopening of a case, review, reexamination"
  },
  {
    "question": "駐在員",
    "answer": "ちゅうざいいん",
    "meaning": "resident employee, local staff, representative of a local office, employee assigned to an office"
  },
  {
    "question": "宝船",
    "answer": "たからぶね",
    "meaning": "treasure ship, picture of a treasure ship bearing the Seven Gods of Good Fortune"
  },
  {
    "question": "女主",
    "answer": "おんなあるじ",
    "meaning": "female owner, proprietress, landlady"
  },
  {
    "question": "火祭り",
    "answer": "ひまつり",
    "meaning": "fire festival (often celebrating the absence of fires), New Year's ritual at Izumo Shrine, festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "旋転",
    "answer": "せんてん",
    "meaning": "revolution, gyration, whirling, rotation"
  },
  {
    "question": "藩士",
    "answer": "はんし",
    "meaning": "feudal retainer or warrior"
  },
  {
    "question": "頻る",
    "answer": "しきる",
    "meaning": "to do ... incessantly, to do ... hard, to happen repeatedly, to happen over and over again"
  },
  {
    "question": "駐在武官",
    "answer": "ちゅうざいぶかん",
    "meaning": "military attaché"
  },
  {
    "question": "打刀",
    "answer": "うちがたな",
    "meaning": "katana (sword worn on the hip edge up by samurai)"
  },
  {
    "question": "情人",
    "answer": "じょうじん,じょうにん",
    "meaning": "lover, sweetheart, mistress"
  },
  {
    "question": "無敵艦隊",
    "answer": "むてきかんたい",
    "meaning": "Spanish Armada, invincible armada"
  },
  {
    "question": "山嶺",
    "answer": "さんれい",
    "meaning": "mountaintop, summit"
  },
  {
    "question": "領袖",
    "answer": "りょうしゅう",
    "meaning": "leader, chief, boss"
  },
  {
    "question": "横縞",
    "answer": "よこじま",
    "meaning": "horizontal stripes, lateral stripes"
  },
  {
    "question": "十五夜",
    "answer": "じゅうごや",
    "meaning": "night of the full moon, the night of the 15th day of the 8th lunar month"
  },
  {
    "question": "恩賜",
    "answer": "おんし",
    "meaning": "Imperial gift"
  },
  {
    "question": "世人",
    "answer": "せじん,よひと",
    "meaning": "the people, the public, the world"
  },
  {
    "question": "誠心",
    "answer": "せいしん",
    "meaning": "sincerity"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹馬",
    "answer": "たけうま,ちくば",
    "meaning": "stilts (for walking), hobby horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "眼鏡っ娘",
    "answer": "めがねっこ",
    "meaning": "girl (usu. attractive) with glasses, glasses-wearing girl"
  },
  {
    "question": "域内",
    "answer": "いきない",
    "meaning": "inside the area"
  },
  {
    "question": "利他",
    "answer": "りた",
    "meaning": "altruism"
  },
  {
    "question": "人工授精",
    "answer": "じんこうじゅせい",
    "meaning": "artificial insemination, intrauterine insemination, IUI"
  },
  {
    "question": "竪穴",
    "answer": "たてあな",
    "meaning": "pit, shaft"
  },
  {
    "question": "錬る",
    "answer": "ねる",
    "meaning": "to temper (steel)"
  },
  {
    "question": "灰白色",
    "answer": "かいはくしょく",
    "meaning": "grayish white, greyish white"
  },
  {
    "question": "殴殺",
    "answer": "おうさつ",
    "meaning": "beating to death, striking dead"
  },
  {
    "question": "巧緻",
    "answer": "こうち",
    "meaning": "elaborate, exquisite, detailed"
  },
  {
    "question": "製錬",
    "answer": "せいれん",
    "meaning": "refining, refinement, smelting"
  },
  {
    "question": "淫婦",
    "answer": "いんぷ",
    "meaning": "woman of loose morals, lewd woman, prostitute, whore, harlot"
  },
  {
    "question": "遜る",
    "answer": "へりくだる",
    "meaning": "to deprecate oneself and praise the listener, to abase oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "鋳る",
    "answer": "いる",
    "meaning": "to cast, to mint, to coin"
  },
  {
    "question": "大水",
    "answer": "おおみず",
    "meaning": "flood"
  },
  {
    "question": "芋掘り",
    "answer": "いもほり",
    "meaning": "digging for sweet potatoes (esp. as an outing), sweet potato digger"
  },
  {
    "question": "運否天賦",
    "answer": "うんぷてんぷ",
    "meaning": "trusting to chance, having a go at something"
  },
  {
    "question": "音楽学校",
    "answer": "おんがくがっこう",
    "meaning": "school of music, academy of music, conservatory"
  },
  {
    "question": "仇名",
    "answer": "あだな",
    "meaning": "nickname, rumor of a romance (rumour)"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗然",
    "answer": "あんぜん",
    "meaning": "dark, gloomy, black, unclear, doleful, discouraged, disappointed, tearful, dispirited"
  },
  {
    "question": "警戒線",
    "answer": "けいかいせん",
    "meaning": "warning line, police cordon"
  },
  {
    "question": "三役",
    "answer": "さんやく",
    "meaning": "three highest ranks (wrestling, unions, etc.), three parts, three divisions"
  },
  {
    "question": "雅楽",
    "answer": "ががく",
    "meaning": "old Japanese court music, gagaku"
  },
  {
    "question": "普遍性",
    "answer": "ふへんせい",
    "meaning": "universality, ubiquity, omnipresence, catholicity"
  },
  {
    "question": "多面体",
    "answer": "ためんたい",
    "meaning": "polyhedron"
  },
  {
    "question": "未分化",
    "answer": "みぶんか",
    "meaning": "undifferentiated, unspecialized"
  },
  {
    "question": "作付け",
    "answer": "さくづけ,さくつけ",
    "meaning": "planting"
  },
  {
    "question": "温み",
    "answer": "ぬくみ",
    "meaning": "warmth"
  },
  {
    "question": "漢数字",
    "answer": "かんすうじ",
    "meaning": "Chinese characters which express numbers"
  },
  {
    "question": "勢力範囲",
    "answer": "せいりょくはんい",
    "meaning": "sphere of influence"
  },
  {
    "question": "ユダヤ教",
    "answer": "ユダヤきょう",
    "meaning": "Judaism"
  },
  {
    "question": "原理主義",
    "answer": "げんりしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "fundamentalism"
  },
  {
    "question": "租税",
    "answer": "そぜい",
    "meaning": "taxes, taxation"
  },
  {
    "question": "手投げ",
    "answer": "てなげ",
    "meaning": "throwing with the hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "自罰的",
    "answer": "じばつてき",
    "meaning": "intropunitive, self-punishing"
  },
  {
    "question": "屯",
    "answer": "たむろ,たむら,トン",
    "meaning": "gathering, place where people gather, police station, camp, barracks, ton (now usu. a metric ton, i."
  },
  {
    "question": "獣姦",
    "answer": "じゅうかん",
    "meaning": "bestiality, sodomy"
  },
  {
    "question": "刃文",
    "answer": "はもん",
    "meaning": "temper pattern of a sword blade"
  },
  {
    "question": "借財",
    "answer": "しゃくざい",
    "meaning": "loan, debt, liability"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き手",
    "answer": "ひきて,ひきで",
    "meaning": "knob, handle, catch, patron, right hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "綿々",
    "answer": "めんめん",
    "meaning": "unbroken, endless, continuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "着払い",
    "answer": "ちゃくばらい",
    "meaning": "payment on delivery, cash on delivery, COD"
  },
  {
    "question": "新譜",
    "answer": "しんぷ",
    "meaning": "newly-released music, new release (CD, album, etc.), new score, new composition"
  },
  {
    "question": "婿取り",
    "answer": "むことり",
    "meaning": "adopting a son-in-law into one's family, marrying off one's daughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "化石燃料",
    "answer": "かせきねんりょう",
    "meaning": "fossil fuel"
  },
  {
    "question": "労働組合",
    "answer": "ろうどうくみあい",
    "meaning": "labor union, labour union, trade union"
  },
  {
    "question": "砂肝",
    "answer": "すなぎも",
    "meaning": "gizzard"
  },
  {
    "question": "基軸",
    "answer": "きじく",
    "meaning": "basis, foundation, core, criterion, standard"
  },
  {
    "question": "八つ目",
    "answer": "やつめ",
    "meaning": "eighth (place, position, etc.), having eight eyes, having many eyes, (of a fabric) having a loose kn"
  },
  {
    "question": "民放",
    "answer": "みんぽう",
    "meaning": "commercial broadcast"
  },
  {
    "question": "意を得る",
    "answer": "いをえる",
    "meaning": "to get (e.g. the gist of something), to understand, to turn out as one thought"
  },
  {
    "question": "後事",
    "answer": "こうじ",
    "meaning": "future affairs, affairs after one's death"
  },
  {
    "question": "回転軸",
    "answer": "かいてんじく",
    "meaning": "axis of revolution"
  },
  {
    "question": "相互扶助",
    "answer": "そうごふじょ",
    "meaning": "mutual aid"
  },
  {
    "question": "殿上人",
    "answer": "てんじょうびと",
    "meaning": "courtier, court official"
  },
  {
    "question": "負ぶさる",
    "answer": "おぶさる",
    "meaning": "to ride on a person's shoulders, to be carried on a person's back"
  },
  {
    "question": "保証書",
    "answer": "ほしょうしょ",
    "meaning": "written guarantee, guarantee letter, warranty, warranty card"
  },
  {
    "question": "乱取り",
    "answer": "らんどり",
    "meaning": "randori (freestyle judo training)"
  },
  {
    "question": "疾しい",
    "answer": "やましい",
    "meaning": "feeling guilty, having a guilty conscience, having qualms about"
  },
  {
    "question": "納骨",
    "answer": "のうこつ",
    "meaning": "placing (a person's) ashes inside a funerary urn (or a tomb or ossuary), depositing ashes"
  },
  {
    "question": "変声期",
    "answer": "へんせいき",
    "meaning": "period when one's voice changes, (age of) puberty"
  },
  {
    "question": "南南東",
    "answer": "なんなんとう",
    "meaning": "south-southeast, south-south-east"
  },
  {
    "question": "片寄る",
    "answer": "かたよる",
    "meaning": "to lean (to one side), to incline, to be unbalanced (e.g. diet), to be unduly weighted towards, to b"
  },
  {
    "question": "宅地",
    "answer": "たくち",
    "meaning": "building lot, residential land"
  },
  {
    "question": "対角",
    "answer": "たいかく",
    "meaning": "diagonal, opposite angle"
  },
  {
    "question": "可及的",
    "answer": "かきゅうてき",
    "meaning": "as ... as possible"
  },
  {
    "question": "農作",
    "answer": "のうさく",
    "meaning": "farming"
  },
  {
    "question": "台詞回し",
    "answer": "せりふまわし",
    "meaning": "theatrical elocution"
  },
  {
    "question": "色遣い",
    "answer": "いろづかい",
    "meaning": "colour usage, color usage, use of colour"
  },
  {
    "question": "高速度",
    "answer": "こうそくど",
    "meaning": "high speed"
  },
  {
    "question": "線状",
    "answer": "せんじょう",
    "meaning": "linear"
  },
  {
    "question": "文節",
    "answer": "ぶんせつ",
    "meaning": "phrase, clause, basic linguistic unit in Japanese grammar"
  },
  {
    "question": "自動翻訳",
    "answer": "じどうほんやく",
    "meaning": "machine translation, automatic translation, MT"
  },
  {
    "question": "一輪挿し",
    "answer": "いちりんざし",
    "meaning": "vase for one flower"
  },
  {
    "question": "着眼",
    "answer": "ちゃくがん",
    "meaning": "focusing on, paying attention to, observation, perception, taking notice of"
  },
  {
    "question": "人非人",
    "answer": "にんぴにん",
    "meaning": "inhuman person, fiend, beast, brute"
  },
  {
    "question": "奥行",
    "answer": "おくゆき",
    "meaning": "depth, length"
  },
  {
    "question": "打ち殺す",
    "answer": "ぶちころす,うちころす",
    "meaning": "to kill by hitting, to beat to death, to slaughter, to shoot to death"
  },
  {
    "question": "地上階",
    "answer": "ちじょうかい",
    "meaning": "above-ground floor, ground floor"
  },
  {
    "question": "巻数",
    "answer": "かんすう,かんじゅ,かんず",
    "meaning": "volume number, reel number, scroll number, number of volumes, number of reels, number of scrolls, nu"
  },
  {
    "question": "清む",
    "answer": "すむ",
    "meaning": "to become clear (water, air, etc.), to become transparent, to resonate clearly (e.g. voice), to beco"
  },
  {
    "question": "風の子",
    "answer": "かぜのこ",
    "meaning": "outdoor creatures"
  },
  {
    "question": "中外",
    "answer": "ちゅうがい",
    "meaning": "home and abroad, domestic and foreign, inside and outside, interior and exterior"
  },
  {
    "question": "自己満",
    "answer": "じこまん",
    "meaning": "self-satisfaction, (self-)complacency"
  },
  {
    "question": "就いて",
    "answer": "ついて",
    "meaning": "about, concerning, as to, regarding"
  },
  {
    "question": "口達者",
    "answer": "くちだっしゃ,くちたっしゃ",
    "meaning": "eloquent, glib, talkative, fluent, voluble, having the gift of gab, smooth talker, glib talker"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪言",
    "answer": "あくげん,あくごん",
    "meaning": "uncomplimentary remarks, slander"
  },
  {
    "question": "顔が立つ",
    "answer": "かおがたつ",
    "meaning": "to save one's face, to maintain one's status"
  },
  {
    "question": "数寄",
    "answer": "すき",
    "meaning": "refined taste, elegant pursuits"
  },
  {
    "question": "文月",
    "answer": "ふみづき,ふづき",
    "meaning": "seventh month of the lunar calendar"
  },
  {
    "question": "和国",
    "answer": "わこく",
    "meaning": "Japan, name for Japan used in ancient China"
  },
  {
    "question": "万天",
    "answer": "ばんてん",
    "meaning": "the whole world"
  },
  {
    "question": "大形",
    "answer": "おおぎょう,おおがた",
    "meaning": "exaggeration, large, large-sized, large-scale, big"
  },
  {
    "question": "谷風",
    "answer": "たにかぜ",
    "meaning": "valley wind"
  },
  {
    "question": "天道虫",
    "answer": "てんとうむし",
    "meaning": "ladybug (Harmonia axyridis), ladybird"
  },
  {
    "question": "切子",
    "answer": "きりこ",
    "meaning": "facet, facetted object"
  },
  {
    "question": "外典",
    "answer": "がいてん,げてん,げでん",
    "meaning": "Apocrypha (i.e. as opposed to the Biblical canon), non-Buddhist writings (esp. Confucian writings)"
  },
  {
    "question": "剣奴",
    "answer": "けんど",
    "meaning": "gladiator"
  },
  {
    "question": "干し葡萄",
    "answer": "ほしぶどう",
    "meaning": "raisin, raisins"
  },
  {
    "question": "乙種",
    "answer": "おつしゅ",
    "meaning": "B-grade, second-class"
  },
  {
    "question": "支隊",
    "answer": "したい",
    "meaning": "detached force, detachment"
  },
  {
    "question": "磯辺",
    "answer": "いそべ",
    "meaning": "seashore, beach, food wrapped in nori"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤本",
    "answer": "あかほん,あかぼん",
    "meaning": "pulp fiction, dime novel, akahon, university entrance exam workbook (published by Kyōgakusha), story"
  },
  {
    "question": "国許",
    "answer": "くにもと",
    "meaning": "one's home, hometown, native place, birthplace"
  },
  {
    "question": "無彩色",
    "answer": "むさいしょく",
    "meaning": "neutral colour, neutral color, achromatic (colour, color)"
  },
  {
    "question": "幕舎",
    "answer": "ばくしゃ",
    "meaning": "camp"
  },
  {
    "question": "饗",
    "answer": "きょう,あえ",
    "meaning": "treating someone (to food or drink), entertaining someone (as one's guest)"
  },
  {
    "question": "捕鯨",
    "answer": "ほげい",
    "meaning": "whaling, whale hunting, whale fishing"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒲焼",
    "answer": "かばやき",
    "meaning": "loach or eel dipped and broiled in soy-based sauce"
  },
  {
    "question": "働き蜂",
    "answer": "はたらきばち",
    "meaning": "worker bee, hard worker"
  },
  {
    "question": "松竹梅",
    "answer": "しょうちくばい",
    "meaning": "pine, bamboo and plum (an auspicious grouping), high, middle and low (ranking), top, middle and bott"
  },
  {
    "question": "瓦版",
    "answer": "かわらばん",
    "meaning": "tile block print (newspaper in Tokugawa period)"
  },
  {
    "question": "時間割り",
    "answer": "じかんわり",
    "meaning": "timetable (esp. a weekly school timetable), schedule"
  },
  {
    "question": "植木屋",
    "answer": "うえきや",
    "meaning": "gardener"
  },
  {
    "question": "掏る",
    "answer": "する",
    "meaning": "to pickpocket, to steal"
  },
  {
    "question": "地下茎",
    "answer": "ちかけい",
    "meaning": "rhizome"
  },
  {
    "question": "攻囲",
    "answer": "こうい",
    "meaning": "siege"
  },
  {
    "question": "呉服店",
    "answer": "ごふくてん",
    "meaning": "kimono fabrics store, draper"
  },
  {
    "question": "古里",
    "answer": "ふるさと",
    "meaning": "home town, birthplace, native place, one's old home, ruins, historic remains"
  },
  {
    "question": "杭打ち",
    "answer": "くいうち",
    "meaning": "pile-driving, piling"
  },
  {
    "question": "唯々",
    "answer": "ただただ,いい",
    "meaning": "absolutely, only, obedient, submissive, tame, slavish"
  },
  {
    "question": "花蜜",
    "answer": "かみつ",
    "meaning": "nectar"
  },
  {
    "question": "県下",
    "answer": "けんか",
    "meaning": "in the prefecture, prefectural"
  },
  {
    "question": "同母",
    "answer": "どうぼ",
    "meaning": "same mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "母港",
    "answer": "ぼこう",
    "meaning": "home port"
  },
  {
    "question": "絵札",
    "answer": "えふだ",
    "meaning": "face card, court card, picture card (in utagaruta or iroha karuta)"
  },
  {
    "question": "儒教",
    "answer": "じゅきょう",
    "meaning": "Confucianism"
  },
  {
    "question": "五月病",
    "answer": "ごがつびょう",
    "meaning": "blues experienced by college freshmen or workplace recruits shortly after beginning school or work,"
  },
  {
    "question": "劇毒",
    "answer": "げきどく",
    "meaning": "deadly poison"
  },
  {
    "question": "連山",
    "answer": "れんざん",
    "meaning": "mountain range, Lian Shan (Xia period method of Chinese divination)"
  },
  {
    "question": "宗教法人",
    "answer": "しゅうきょうほうじん",
    "meaning": "religious organization, religious organisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "遣り口",
    "answer": "やりくち",
    "meaning": "way (of doing), method"
  },
  {
    "question": "機種変",
    "answer": "きしゅへん",
    "meaning": "changing cell phone models"
  },
  {
    "question": "流罪",
    "answer": "るざい",
    "meaning": "banishment, exile"
  },
  {
    "question": "訴状",
    "answer": "そじょう",
    "meaning": "petition, complaint, (legal) brief"
  },
  {
    "question": "油絵の具",
    "answer": "あぶらえのぐ",
    "meaning": "oil paints, oil colors (colours), oils"
  },
  {
    "question": "塩基配列",
    "answer": "えんきはいれつ",
    "meaning": "base sequence (e.g. of DNA)"
  },
  {
    "question": "高窓",
    "answer": "たかまど",
    "meaning": "high window, clerestory window"
  },
  {
    "question": "生臭坊主",
    "answer": "なまぐさぼうず",
    "meaning": "degenerate monk, corrupt priest"
  },
  {
    "question": "事実婚",
    "answer": "じじつこん",
    "meaning": "de facto marriage, common-law marriage"
  },
  {
    "question": "時化",
    "answer": "しけ",
    "meaning": "stormy weather (at sea), poor catch of fish (due to stormy seas), poor turn-out, recession"
  },
  {
    "question": "三回忌",
    "answer": "さんかいき",
    "meaning": "second anniversary of a death"
  },
  {
    "question": "群れ集う",
    "answer": "むれつどう",
    "meaning": "to crowd together"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦略物資",
    "answer": "せんりゃくぶっし",
    "meaning": "strategic resources, strategic materials"
  },
  {
    "question": "領空侵犯",
    "answer": "りょうくうしんぱん",
    "meaning": "airspace incursion, airspace violation"
  },
  {
    "question": "来院",
    "answer": "らいいん",
    "meaning": "visit to a hospital, temple, school, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "卸値",
    "answer": "おろしね",
    "meaning": "wholesale price"
  },
  {
    "question": "幕下",
    "answer": "まくした",
    "meaning": "third highest division, wrestlers of the third highest division"
  },
  {
    "question": "手役",
    "answer": "てやく",
    "meaning": "scoring combination in one's dealt hand (i.e. at the start of a game), meld in a starting hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "殖える",
    "answer": "ふえる",
    "meaning": "to increase, to multiply"
  },
  {
    "question": "実動",
    "answer": "じつどう",
    "meaning": "operating (e.g. of trains, cars), running, working"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会面",
    "answer": "しゃかいめん",
    "meaning": "social page (of newspaper), local news page"
  },
  {
    "question": "病没",
    "answer": "びょうぼつ",
    "meaning": "dying of illness, dying of natural causes"
  },
  {
    "question": "拙劣",
    "answer": "せつれつ",
    "meaning": "clumsy, unskillful"
  },
  {
    "question": "会陰",
    "answer": "えいん",
    "meaning": "perineum"
  },
  {
    "question": "輸出品",
    "answer": "ゆしゅつひん",
    "meaning": "exported goods"
  },
  {
    "question": "海綿",
    "answer": "かいめん,うみわた",
    "meaning": "sponge"
  },
  {
    "question": "染物",
    "answer": "そめもの",
    "meaning": "dyeing, dyed goods, goods to be dyed"
  },
  {
    "question": "四十路",
    "answer": "よそじ",
    "meaning": "age forty, one's forties"
  },
  {
    "question": "交歓",
    "answer": "こうかん",
    "meaning": "exchange of courtesies (cordialities), fraternization, fraternisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "ガテン系",
    "answer": "ガテンけい",
    "meaning": "physical work, physical worker, blue-collar worker"
  },
  {
    "question": "お神酒",
    "answer": "おみき",
    "meaning": "sacred wine or sake, sake offered to the gods, sake"
  },
  {
    "question": "据え付け",
    "answer": "すえつけ",
    "meaning": "installation, setting, fitting, mounting"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち木",
    "answer": "たちき",
    "meaning": "standing tree, standing timber"
  },
  {
    "question": "催眠療法",
    "answer": "さいみんりょうほう",
    "meaning": "hypnotherapy"
  },
  {
    "question": "覚束無い",
    "answer": "おぼつかない,かくそくない",
    "meaning": "uncertain, doubtful, unpromising, unreliable, unsteady, insecure, shaky, faltering, unclear, vague,"
  },
  {
    "question": "御苦労様",
    "answer": "ごくろうさま",
    "meaning": "thank you for your hard work, I appreciate your efforts"
  },
  {
    "question": "捕物",
    "answer": "とりもの",
    "meaning": "capture, arrest"
  },
  {
    "question": "物の本",
    "answer": "もののほん",
    "meaning": "some book, book about that subject, books"
  },
  {
    "question": "野暮天",
    "answer": "やぼてん",
    "meaning": "boorishness, coarseness, stupidity"
  },
  {
    "question": "実演販売",
    "answer": "じつえんはんばい",
    "meaning": "product demonstration, sales demonstration"
  },
  {
    "question": "打法",
    "answer": "だほう",
    "meaning": "batting form"
  },
  {
    "question": "塒",
    "answer": "とぐろ,ねぐら",
    "meaning": "coil, roost, nest, pad, crib, one's home, sleeping place"
  },
  {
    "question": "報連相",
    "answer": "ほうれんそう",
    "meaning": "reporting, contacting, and consultation"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍事教練",
    "answer": "ぐんじきょうれん",
    "meaning": "military training"
  },
  {
    "question": "豚箱",
    "answer": "ぶたばこ",
    "meaning": "police cell, lockup"
  },
  {
    "question": "上流社会",
    "answer": "じょうりゅうしゃかい",
    "meaning": "upper classes"
  },
  {
    "question": "借り主",
    "answer": "かりぬし",
    "meaning": "borrower, debtor, tenant, lessee, renter"
  },
  {
    "question": "上水道",
    "answer": "じょうすいどう",
    "meaning": "waterworks"
  },
  {
    "question": "点取り",
    "answer": "てんとり",
    "meaning": "competition for school marks, keeping score, score"
  },
  {
    "question": "並立",
    "answer": "へいりつ",
    "meaning": "standing abreast"
  },
  {
    "question": "陸揚げ",
    "answer": "りくあげ",
    "meaning": "unloading (a ship), landing"
  },
  {
    "question": "霰",
    "answer": "あられ",
    "meaning": "hail (esp. hailballs under 5 mm), graupel, dicing, small cubes, roasted mochi pieces (usu. flavoured"
  },
  {
    "question": "整形外科",
    "answer": "せいけいげか",
    "meaning": "orthopedic surgery, orthopaedic surgery, orthopedics, orthopaedics, plastic surgery, cosmetic surger"
  },
  {
    "question": "小数",
    "answer": "しょうすう",
    "meaning": "fraction (part of), decimal fraction"
  },
  {
    "question": "西向き",
    "answer": "にしむき",
    "meaning": "facing west"
  },
  {
    "question": "奨める",
    "answer": "すすめる",
    "meaning": "to recommend (someone to do), to advise, to encourage, to urge, to recommend (a book, someone for a"
  },
  {
    "question": "安々",
    "answer": "やすやす",
    "meaning": "calmly, peacefully, painlessly, comfortably"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇を衒う",
    "answer": "きをてらう",
    "meaning": "to make a display of one's originality (eccentricity), to deliberately act oddly (e.g. to get attent"
  },
  {
    "question": "磯臭い",
    "answer": "いそくさい",
    "meaning": "smelling of the sea, smelling of the seashore"
  },
  {
    "question": "未処理",
    "answer": "みしょり",
    "meaning": "untreated, left unattended (to), still to be dealt with, unprocessed"
  },
  {
    "question": "金字塔",
    "answer": "きんじとう",
    "meaning": "pyramid, monumental work, landmark achievement"
  },
  {
    "question": "二間",
    "answer": "ふたま,にけん",
    "meaning": "two rooms, two ken (approx. 3.6m)"
  },
  {
    "question": "湯を使う",
    "answer": "ゆをつかう",
    "meaning": "to take a hot bath"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦渦",
    "answer": "せんか",
    "meaning": "chaos of war, war turmoil"
  },
  {
    "question": "彼の子",
    "answer": "あのこ",
    "meaning": "that girl, that kid, you (mainly used by a brothel owner or senior prostitutes when addressing serva"
  },
  {
    "question": "耐震",
    "answer": "たいしん",
    "meaning": "resistant to earthquakes"
  },
  {
    "question": "成育",
    "answer": "せいいく",
    "meaning": "growth (to maturity), being brought up, growing up, raising"
  },
  {
    "question": "衣食",
    "answer": "いしょく",
    "meaning": "food and clothing, livelihood, living, to feed and clothe"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜明かし",
    "answer": "よあかし",
    "meaning": "staying up all night, all-night vigil"
  },
  {
    "question": "曲げ",
    "answer": "まげ",
    "meaning": "flexure, bending"
  },
  {
    "question": "貧富",
    "answer": "ひんぷ",
    "meaning": "wealth and poverty, rich and poor"
  },
  {
    "question": "鳴神",
    "answer": "なるかみ",
    "meaning": "thunder"
  },
  {
    "question": "御息所",
    "answer": "みやすどころ,みやすんどころ",
    "meaning": "concubine of an emperor, female court attendant who serves in the emperor's bedchamber"
  },
  {
    "question": "除幕式",
    "answer": "じょまくしき",
    "meaning": "unveiling ceremony"
  },
  {
    "question": "専制政治",
    "answer": "せんせいせいじ",
    "meaning": "despotic government, autocracy"
  },
  {
    "question": "波高",
    "answer": "はこう",
    "meaning": "wave height"
  },
  {
    "question": "自由貿易",
    "answer": "じゆうぼうえき",
    "meaning": "free trade"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄床",
    "answer": "かなとこ",
    "meaning": "anvil"
  },
  {
    "question": "自由民",
    "answer": "じゆうみん",
    "meaning": "free people, free men"
  },
  {
    "question": "火計",
    "answer": "かけい,ひばかり",
    "meaning": "fire attack, attacking and burning enemy troops, warships, provisions, etc., pottery fired in Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "傀儡師",
    "answer": "かいらいし,くぐつし",
    "meaning": "puppeteer, puppet player, wirepuller, string-puller, man behind the scenes"
  },
  {
    "question": "白鳥の湖",
    "answer": "はくちょうのみずうみ",
    "meaning": "Swan Lake (ballet)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻汁",
    "answer": "はなじる,はなしる,びじゅう",
    "meaning": "(liquid) nasal mucus, nasal discharge, pituita, snot"
  },
  {
    "question": "一夜干し",
    "answer": "いちやぼし",
    "meaning": "fish salted and dried overnight"
  },
  {
    "question": "手燭",
    "answer": "てしょく,しゅしょく",
    "meaning": "portable candlestick"
  },
  {
    "question": "当行",
    "answer": "とうこう",
    "meaning": "our bank"
  },
  {
    "question": "下田",
    "answer": "げでん",
    "meaning": "worn-out rice land"
  },
  {
    "question": "光跡",
    "answer": "こうせき",
    "meaning": "traces of a moving light, trail (e.g. of a meteor)"
  },
  {
    "question": "堅城",
    "answer": "けんじょう",
    "meaning": "strong fortress"
  },
  {
    "question": "尺八",
    "answer": "しゃくはち",
    "meaning": "shakuhachi, end-blown fippleless bamboo flute, blow job, fellatio"
  },
  {
    "question": "中立国",
    "answer": "ちゅうりつこく",
    "meaning": "neutral power"
  },
  {
    "question": "城兵",
    "answer": "じょうへい",
    "meaning": "castle garrison"
  },
  {
    "question": "天秤座",
    "answer": "てんびんざ",
    "meaning": "Libra (constellation), the Scales"
  },
  {
    "question": "弔辞",
    "answer": "ちょうじ",
    "meaning": "message of condolence, memorial address"
  },
  {
    "question": "公安警察",
    "answer": "こうあんけいさつ",
    "meaning": "security police"
  },
  {
    "question": "塩基",
    "answer": "えんき",
    "meaning": "base"
  },
  {
    "question": "四川",
    "answer": "しせん",
    "meaning": "Sichuan (China), Szechuan, Szechwan"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾久しい",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "賓",
    "answer": "まろうど,まろうと,まれびと",
    "meaning": "visitor from afar, guest, joy-bringing spirit from the divine realms"
  },
  {
    "question": "帰還兵",
    "answer": "きかんへい",
    "meaning": "returned soldier"
  },
  {
    "question": "町方",
    "answer": "まちかた",
    "meaning": "town"
  },
  {
    "question": "放埒",
    "answer": "ほうらつ",
    "meaning": "licentious, profligate, dissipated, riotous, wild"
  },
  {
    "question": "岩穴",
    "answer": "いわあな",
    "meaning": "cavern, grotto"
  },
  {
    "question": "物柔らか",
    "answer": "ものやわらか",
    "meaning": "mild, mild-mannered, gentle"
  },
  {
    "question": "尼寺",
    "answer": "あまでら",
    "meaning": "nunnery, convent"
  },
  {
    "question": "鮑",
    "answer": "あわび",
    "meaning": "abalone, ear shell"
  },
  {
    "question": "汽船",
    "answer": "きせん",
    "meaning": "steamship, steamboat, steamer"
  },
  {
    "question": "失語症",
    "answer": "しつごしょう",
    "meaning": "aphasia (loss of speech)"
  },
  {
    "question": "弩級",
    "answer": "どきゅう",
    "meaning": "dreadnought class (of warship)"
  },
  {
    "question": "服薬",
    "answer": "ふくやく",
    "meaning": "taking medicine"
  },
  {
    "question": "小僧っ子",
    "answer": "こぞっこ",
    "meaning": "brat, greenhorn, novice, green youth, child"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨男",
    "answer": "あめおとこ",
    "meaning": "man who brings the rain with him wherever he goes, man who is constantly unlucky with the weather"
  },
  {
    "question": "蹲",
    "answer": "つくばい",
    "meaning": "stone wash basin found in Japanese gardens"
  },
  {
    "question": "紡錘",
    "answer": "ぼうすい,つむ",
    "meaning": "spindle"
  },
  {
    "question": "質草",
    "answer": "しちぐさ",
    "meaning": "article for pawning"
  },
  {
    "question": "闇商人",
    "answer": "やみしょうにん",
    "meaning": "black marketeer"
  },
  {
    "question": "緑柱石",
    "answer": "りょくちゅうせき",
    "meaning": "beryl"
  },
  {
    "question": "藤棚",
    "answer": "ふじだな",
    "meaning": "wisteria trellis, wisteria arbor (arbour), wisteria pergola"
  },
  {
    "question": "袷",
    "answer": "あわせ",
    "meaning": "lined kimono"
  },
  {
    "question": "艶消し",
    "answer": "つやけし",
    "meaning": "frosted (glass), matted, disillusionment, letdown"
  },
  {
    "question": "一尺",
    "answer": "いっしゃく",
    "meaning": "approx. 30 cm"
  },
  {
    "question": "国鉄",
    "answer": "こくてつ",
    "meaning": "national railway (esp. former Japan National Railways)"
  },
  {
    "question": "交接",
    "answer": "こうせつ",
    "meaning": "sexual intercourse"
  },
  {
    "question": "散水",
    "answer": "さんすい",
    "meaning": "sprinkling water over, irrigating"
  },
  {
    "question": "一里",
    "answer": "いちり",
    "meaning": "2.44 miles"
  },
  {
    "question": "峻別",
    "answer": "しゅんべつ",
    "meaning": "rigorous distinction"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒丸",
    "answer": "くろまる",
    "meaning": "black spot, black dot, bull's-eye, middle dot, interpunct"
  },
  {
    "question": "時価総額",
    "answer": "じかそうがく",
    "meaning": "market capitalization, market capitalisation, market cap"
  },
  {
    "question": "連投",
    "answer": "れんとう",
    "meaning": "pitching in consecutive games, making multiple posts (on a website), posting multiple comments"
  },
  {
    "question": "座標軸",
    "answer": "ざひょうじく",
    "meaning": "coordinate axis"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄工所",
    "answer": "てっこうじょ",
    "meaning": "ironworks"
  },
  {
    "question": "自由主義",
    "answer": "じゆうしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "liberalism"
  },
  {
    "question": "監査役",
    "answer": "かんさやく",
    "meaning": "auditor, inspector"
  },
  {
    "question": "鳥瞰",
    "answer": "ちょうかん",
    "meaning": "overlooking, looking down at, having an overhead view, having a bird's-eye view, having a high-angle"
  },
  {
    "question": "紹興酒",
    "answer": "しょうこうしゅ",
    "meaning": "shaoxingjiu (Chinese alcohol made from rice or glutinous millet)"
  },
  {
    "question": "祝電",
    "answer": "しゅくでん",
    "meaning": "congratulatory telegram"
  },
  {
    "question": "花崗岩",
    "answer": "かこうがん",
    "meaning": "granite"
  },
  {
    "question": "青目",
    "answer": "あおめ",
    "meaning": "blue eyes, a Westerner"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜光虫",
    "answer": "やこうちゅう",
    "meaning": "Noctiluca scintillans (luminescent species of dinoflagellate)"
  },
  {
    "question": "木琴",
    "answer": "もっきん",
    "meaning": "xylophone"
  },
  {
    "question": "誕生石",
    "answer": "たんじょうせき",
    "meaning": "birthstone"
  },
  {
    "question": "料金所",
    "answer": "りょうきんじょ,りょうきんしょ",
    "meaning": "tollgate, toll booth"
  },
  {
    "question": "往き来",
    "answer": "ゆきき,いきき",
    "meaning": "coming and going, keeping in touch, visiting each other, street traffic, highway"
  },
  {
    "question": "小火器",
    "answer": "しょうかき",
    "meaning": "small arms"
  },
  {
    "question": "敢闘",
    "answer": "かんとう",
    "meaning": "fighting bravely"
  },
  {
    "question": "隔て",
    "answer": "へだて",
    "meaning": "partition, distinction"
  },
  {
    "question": "折良く",
    "answer": "おりよく",
    "meaning": "fortunately, luckily"
  },
  {
    "question": "勇躍",
    "answer": "ゆうやく",
    "meaning": "taking heart, being in high spirits"
  },
  {
    "question": "鍋奉行",
    "answer": "なべぶぎょう",
    "meaning": "person who pushily takes charge when cooking a hot pot at the table, hotpot boss"
  },
  {
    "question": "地形図",
    "answer": "ちけいず",
    "meaning": "topographic map, elevation map"
  },
  {
    "question": "止血剤",
    "answer": "しけつざい",
    "meaning": "hemostatic agent (haemostatic), styptic"
  },
  {
    "question": "先般",
    "answer": "せんぱん",
    "meaning": "some time ago, the other day"
  },
  {
    "question": "爛熟",
    "answer": "らんじゅく",
    "meaning": "overripeness, full maturity, full development"
  },
  {
    "question": "任命権",
    "answer": "にんめいけん",
    "meaning": "appointive power"
  },
  {
    "question": "手緩い",
    "answer": "てぬるい",
    "meaning": "lax, lenient, slow"
  },
  {
    "question": "斜向かい",
    "answer": "はすむかい",
    "meaning": "catercorner, diagonally opposite"
  },
  {
    "question": "水嵩",
    "answer": "みずかさ",
    "meaning": "volume of water (in a river, pond, flood, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "船中",
    "answer": "せんちゅう",
    "meaning": "on board a ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "等距離",
    "answer": "とうきょり",
    "meaning": "equidistant"
  },
  {
    "question": "和歌山",
    "answer": "わかやま",
    "meaning": "Wakayama (city, prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "駄文",
    "answer": "だぶん",
    "meaning": "poor piece of writing, my poor writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り違え",
    "answer": "とりちがえ",
    "meaning": "mix-up, mistake, misunderstanding"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗緑色",
    "answer": "あんりょくしょく",
    "meaning": "dark green"
  },
  {
    "question": "図表",
    "answer": "ずひょう",
    "meaning": "chart, diagram, graph, figure"
  },
  {
    "question": "人員整理",
    "answer": "じんいんせいり",
    "meaning": "workforce reduction, personnel cut"
  },
  {
    "question": "括れる",
    "answer": "くびれる",
    "meaning": "to be constricted"
  },
  {
    "question": "警戒色",
    "answer": "けいかいしょく",
    "meaning": "warning color, warning colour"
  },
  {
    "question": "原子核",
    "answer": "げんしかく",
    "meaning": "nucleus, atomic nucleus"
  },
  {
    "question": "擲つ",
    "answer": "なげうつ",
    "meaning": "to throw away, to abandon, to give up, to relinquish, to lay down (one's life)"
  },
  {
    "question": "切り取り",
    "answer": "きりとり,きりどり",
    "meaning": "cutting, tearing off, cutting off, clipping, cutting (for a railroad, highway, etc.), cut, robbery w"
  },
  {
    "question": "折悪しく",
    "answer": "おりあしく",
    "meaning": "unfortunately, at a bad time, at an unfortunate moment"
  },
  {
    "question": "氷る",
    "answer": "こおる",
    "meaning": "to freeze, to be frozen over, to congeal"
  },
  {
    "question": "就職難",
    "answer": "しゅうしょくなん",
    "meaning": "difficulty of finding employment (due to a job shortage)"
  },
  {
    "question": "変り種",
    "answer": "かわりだね",
    "meaning": "something out of the ordinary, variant, variety, exception, novelty, person with an unusual characte"
  },
  {
    "question": "狂い死に",
    "answer": "くるいじに",
    "meaning": "death in madness, dying insane"
  },
  {
    "question": "蜘蛛の子",
    "answer": "くものこ",
    "meaning": "baby spider"
  },
  {
    "question": "小兵",
    "answer": "こひょう",
    "meaning": "small build, small stature"
  },
  {
    "question": "力点",
    "answer": "りきてん",
    "meaning": "emphasis, stress, main point, importance, point of a lever where force is applied"
  },
  {
    "question": "高邁",
    "answer": "こうまい",
    "meaning": "noble, lofty, high-minded"
  },
  {
    "question": "無添加",
    "answer": "むてんか",
    "meaning": "additive-free"
  },
  {
    "question": "意志薄弱",
    "answer": "いしはくじゃく",
    "meaning": "weak-willed, lacking a purpose, lacking will power to be patient, purposeful, or resolute"
  },
  {
    "question": "貞節",
    "answer": "ていせつ",
    "meaning": "chastity, fidelity, faithfulness, virtue"
  },
  {
    "question": "略歴",
    "answer": "りゃくれき",
    "meaning": "brief personal record, short curriculum vitae, short CV"
  },
  {
    "question": "零度",
    "answer": "れいど",
    "meaning": "zero degrees (Celsius), freezing point, zero (on a scale)"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い換え",
    "answer": "いいかえ",
    "meaning": "putting in other words"
  },
  {
    "question": "厄払い",
    "answer": "やくはらい,やくばらい",
    "meaning": "exorcism, ceremonial cleansing from evil influence"
  },
  {
    "question": "筆舌",
    "answer": "ひつぜつ",
    "meaning": "written and spoken words, description"
  },
  {
    "question": "眼精疲労",
    "answer": "がんせいひろう",
    "meaning": "eyestrain"
  },
  {
    "question": "目覚ます",
    "answer": "めざます",
    "meaning": "to wake up"
  },
  {
    "question": "早咲き",
    "answer": "はやざき",
    "meaning": "early blooming, early flowering"
  },
  {
    "question": "札入れ",
    "answer": "さついれ",
    "meaning": "wallet, billfold"
  },
  {
    "question": "具体策",
    "answer": "ぐたいさく",
    "meaning": "concrete plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "山百合",
    "answer": "やまゆり",
    "meaning": "golden-rayed lily (Lilium auratum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "冠位",
    "answer": "かんい",
    "meaning": "system indicating court ranks by headgear colors (colours)"
  },
  {
    "question": "玉串",
    "answer": "たまぐし,たまくし",
    "meaning": "branch of a sacred tree (esp. sakaki) with paper or cotton strips attached (used as an offering), sa"
  },
  {
    "question": "立華",
    "answer": "りっか",
    "meaning": "rikka, formal style of ikebana"
  },
  {
    "question": "安居",
    "answer": "あんきょ,あんご",
    "meaning": "easy life, varsika (meditation retreat; usu. for 90 days starting on the 15th day of the 4th month o"
  },
  {
    "question": "予備選挙",
    "answer": "よびせんきょ",
    "meaning": "preliminary election, primary (election)"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶話会",
    "answer": "さわかい,ちゃわかい",
    "meaning": "tea party"
  },
  {
    "question": "黛",
    "answer": "まゆずみ",
    "meaning": "eyebrow pencil, blackened eyebrows, (metaphorically) distant mountain range"
  },
  {
    "question": "審議官",
    "answer": "しんぎかん",
    "meaning": "Assistant Vice-Minister, Deputy Director-General, Councillor"
  },
  {
    "question": "龍眼",
    "answer": "りゅうがん",
    "meaning": "longan (Euphoria longana)"
  },
  {
    "question": "英仏",
    "answer": "えいふつ",
    "meaning": "Britain and France, Anglo-French"
  },
  {
    "question": "債",
    "answer": "さい",
    "meaning": "debt, loan"
  },
  {
    "question": "組頭",
    "answer": "くみがしら",
    "meaning": "group leader"
  },
  {
    "question": "点字",
    "answer": "てんじ",
    "meaning": "Braille"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶唱",
    "answer": "ぜっしょう",
    "meaning": "superb poem or song"
  },
  {
    "question": "巡査長",
    "answer": "じゅんさちょう",
    "meaning": "head patrol officer"
  },
  {
    "question": "食餌",
    "answer": "しょくじ",
    "meaning": "food (esp. for a medical diet)"
  },
  {
    "question": "羽撃く",
    "answer": "はばたく",
    "meaning": "to flap (wings), to spread one's wings, to go out into the world"
  },
  {
    "question": "酒盃",
    "answer": "さかずき,さかづき,しゅはい",
    "meaning": "sake cup, cup for alcoholic beverages, wine cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "連立",
    "answer": "れんりつ",
    "meaning": "coalition, alliance, union, standing side-by-side"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒眼鏡",
    "answer": "くろめがね",
    "meaning": "sunglasses, shady glasses, dark glasses"
  },
  {
    "question": "船外活動",
    "answer": "せんがいかつどう",
    "meaning": "extravehicular activity, EVA"
  },
  {
    "question": "番小屋",
    "answer": "ばんごや",
    "meaning": "guard house"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨月",
    "answer": "うげつ",
    "meaning": "being unable to see the (harvest) moon because of rain, fifth lunar month"
  },
  {
    "question": "金時",
    "answer": "きんとき",
    "meaning": "red, red kidney bean, sweet potato (any of a number of different cultivars with red skin), bowl of s"
  },
  {
    "question": "善哉",
    "answer": "ぜんざい",
    "meaning": "well done!, bravo!, zenzai, red bean soup made with azuki beans"
  },
  {
    "question": "島育ち",
    "answer": "しまそだち",
    "meaning": "brought up on an island"
  },
  {
    "question": "排水量",
    "answer": "はいすいりょう",
    "meaning": "displacement (e.g. of a ship), volume of wastewater"
  },
  {
    "question": "護摩",
    "answer": "ごま",
    "meaning": "homa, Buddhist rite of burning wooden sticks to ask a deity for blessings"
  },
  {
    "question": "多面",
    "answer": "ためん",
    "meaning": "many-sided, multifaceted"
  },
  {
    "question": "古屋",
    "answer": "ふるや,こおく",
    "meaning": "old house, deserted house"
  },
  {
    "question": "鬼子母神",
    "answer": "きしもじん,きしぼじん",
    "meaning": "Hariti (goddess of childbirth and children)"
  },
  {
    "question": "金時計",
    "answer": "きんどけい",
    "meaning": "gold watch"
  },
  {
    "question": "重湯",
    "answer": "おもゆ",
    "meaning": "thin rice gruel, rice water"
  },
  {
    "question": "清明",
    "answer": "せいめい",
    "meaning": "pure and clear, 'clear and bright' solar term (approx. April 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗証",
    "answer": "あんしょう",
    "meaning": "code, cipher, password"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち点",
    "answer": "もちてん",
    "meaning": "points (already) allotted to one, points (already) gained (in earlier rounds)"
  },
  {
    "question": "白書",
    "answer": "はくしょ",
    "meaning": "white paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "魚鱗",
    "answer": "ぎょりん",
    "meaning": "fish scales"
  },
  {
    "question": "系統樹",
    "answer": "けいとうじゅ",
    "meaning": "phylogenetic tree, genealogical tree, family tree, evolutionary tree, dendrogram"
  },
  {
    "question": "外患",
    "answer": "がいかん",
    "meaning": "external pressure, foreign threat"
  },
  {
    "question": "著作権法",
    "answer": "ちょさくけんほう",
    "meaning": "(Japanese) Copyright Act"
  },
  {
    "question": "既刊",
    "answer": "きかん",
    "meaning": "already published"
  },
  {
    "question": "白絹",
    "answer": "しらぎぬ,しろぎぬ,しろきぬ",
    "meaning": "white silk"
  },
  {
    "question": "身中",
    "answer": "しんちゅう",
    "meaning": "within one's body"
  },
  {
    "question": "信愛",
    "answer": "しんあい",
    "meaning": "love and believe in, intimacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿痾",
    "answer": "しゅくあ",
    "meaning": "chronic disease"
  },
  {
    "question": "穴子",
    "answer": "あなご",
    "meaning": "garden eel, conger eel (esp. the common Japanese conger, Conger myriaster)"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽石",
    "answer": "かるいし",
    "meaning": "pumice stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "被覆",
    "answer": "ひふく",
    "meaning": "coating, covering, cover"
  },
  {
    "question": "最恐",
    "answer": "さいきょう",
    "meaning": "scariest, most frightening"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍国主義",
    "answer": "ぐんこくしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "militarism"
  },
  {
    "question": "鸚鵡",
    "answer": "おうむ",
    "meaning": "(large) parrot (incl. the cockatoo)"
  },
  {
    "question": "副題",
    "answer": "ふくだい",
    "meaning": "subtitle, subheading"
  },
  {
    "question": "減免",
    "answer": "げんめん",
    "meaning": "reduction and exemption (e.g. taxes), mitigation and remission (e.g. in criminal law)"
  },
  {
    "question": "ざく切り",
    "answer": "ざくぎり",
    "meaning": "cutting into chunks (esp. vegetables)"
  },
  {
    "question": "裏街道",
    "answer": "うらかいどう",
    "meaning": "byroad, byway"
  },
  {
    "question": "嫁いびり",
    "answer": "よめいびり",
    "meaning": "bullying a young wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "小坊主",
    "answer": "こぼうず",
    "meaning": "young priest, scamp"
  },
  {
    "question": "薀蓄",
    "answer": "うんちく",
    "meaning": "great erudition, extensive knowledge, vast stock of knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "峻険",
    "answer": "しゅんけん",
    "meaning": "steep, precipitous"
  },
  {
    "question": "大芝居",
    "answer": "おおしばい",
    "meaning": "large-scale play, play with an A-list cast, big act, big charade, false display, theatre with a gove"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶対値",
    "answer": "ぜったいち",
    "meaning": "absolute value"
  },
  {
    "question": "送料",
    "answer": "そうりょう",
    "meaning": "postage, carriage, shipping charge"
  },
  {
    "question": "南極大陸",
    "answer": "なんきょくたいりく",
    "meaning": "Antarctica"
  },
  {
    "question": "天然痘",
    "answer": "てんねんとう",
    "meaning": "smallpox, variola"
  },
  {
    "question": "横木",
    "answer": "よこき,よこぎ",
    "meaning": "crosspiece, bar, rail"
  },
  {
    "question": "一入",
    "answer": "ひとしお",
    "meaning": "still more, especially"
  },
  {
    "question": "類例",
    "answer": "るいれい",
    "meaning": "similar instance, similar case, parallel case, analogy"
  },
  {
    "question": "貸し付け",
    "answer": "かしつけ",
    "meaning": "loan"
  },
  {
    "question": "港内",
    "answer": "こうない",
    "meaning": "inside the harbour, inside the harbor"
  },
  {
    "question": "発出",
    "answer": "はっしゅつ",
    "meaning": "issue, sending out"
  },
  {
    "question": "タバコ屋",
    "answer": "タバコや",
    "meaning": "tobacconist"
  },
  {
    "question": "家鳴り",
    "answer": "やなり",
    "meaning": "rattling of a house"
  },
  {
    "question": "切り合い",
    "answer": "きりあい",
    "meaning": "crossing swords, fighting with swords, cutting each other (in fighting)"
  },
  {
    "question": "白茶ける",
    "answer": "しらちゃける",
    "meaning": "to fade, to discolour, to discolor"
  },
  {
    "question": "燦燦",
    "answer": "さんさん",
    "meaning": "brilliant, bright"
  },
  {
    "question": "工業化",
    "answer": "こうぎょうか",
    "meaning": "industrialization, industrialisation, establishing a production system, putting something into produ"
  },
  {
    "question": "国際化",
    "answer": "こくさいか",
    "meaning": "internationalization, internationalisation, i18n (in IT)"
  },
  {
    "question": "再読",
    "answer": "さいどく",
    "meaning": "rereading"
  },
  {
    "question": "撫で斬り",
    "answer": "なでぎり",
    "meaning": "clean sweep, killing several with one sword sweep"
  },
  {
    "question": "上げ底",
    "answer": "あげぞこ,あげそこ",
    "meaning": "false bottom, fake bottom, raised bottom, platform (shoes), kick (of a bottle), exaggeration, overst"
  },
  {
    "question": "利己",
    "answer": "りこ",
    "meaning": "self-interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "大功",
    "answer": "たいこう",
    "meaning": "distinguished or meritorious service"
  },
  {
    "question": "甥御",
    "answer": "おいご",
    "meaning": "(another person's) nephew"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠国",
    "answer": "えんごく,おんごく",
    "meaning": "distant land, remote country, province far from the capital"
  },
  {
    "question": "粗塩",
    "answer": "あらじお,あらしお",
    "meaning": "coarse salt, unrefined salt"
  },
  {
    "question": "背反",
    "answer": "はいはん",
    "meaning": "revolting, rebellion, going against, contradiction, antinomy"
  },
  {
    "question": "程度問題",
    "answer": "ていどもんだい",
    "meaning": "question of degree"
  },
  {
    "question": "偶発",
    "answer": "ぐうはつ",
    "meaning": "sudden outbreak, accidental, incidental"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱着",
    "answer": "だっちゃく",
    "meaning": "attaching and detaching, putting on and removing, installing and removing, desorption"
  },
  {
    "question": "内助の功",
    "answer": "ないじょのこう",
    "meaning": "fruits of one's wife's labour (in assisting her husband's career, e.g. by running the household)"
  },
  {
    "question": "物干し台",
    "answer": "ものほしだい",
    "meaning": "clothes-drying platform, place for drying laundry"
  },
  {
    "question": "変温動物",
    "answer": "へんおんどうぶつ",
    "meaning": "poikilotherm"
  },
  {
    "question": "権威主義",
    "answer": "けんいしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "authoritarianism"
  },
  {
    "question": "飯粒",
    "answer": "めしつぶ",
    "meaning": "grain of boiled rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "図画",
    "answer": "ずが,とが",
    "meaning": "drawing, painting, picture"
  },
  {
    "question": "節回し",
    "answer": "ふしまわし",
    "meaning": "melody, intonation"
  },
  {
    "question": "強権発動",
    "answer": "きょうけんはつどう",
    "meaning": "invoking the coercive power of the state, calling upon the power of the state"
  },
  {
    "question": "陰干し",
    "answer": "かげぼし",
    "meaning": "drying in the shade"
  },
  {
    "question": "付す",
    "answer": "ふす",
    "meaning": "to affix, to append, to attach, to entrust, to refer, to handle (as such), to follow (the leader), t"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪縁",
    "answer": "あくえん",
    "meaning": "evil destiny or connection, unfortunate love"
  },
  {
    "question": "犬猿",
    "answer": "けんえん",
    "meaning": "cats and dogs (as an example of a bad relationship), dogs and monkeys"
  },
  {
    "question": "自由業",
    "answer": "じゆうぎょう",
    "meaning": "self-employed profession (e.g. actor, artist), liberal profession"
  },
  {
    "question": "腹上死",
    "answer": "ふくじょうし",
    "meaning": "death during sexual intercourse"
  },
  {
    "question": "抽象",
    "answer": "ちゅうしょう",
    "meaning": "abstract"
  },
  {
    "question": "水彩",
    "answer": "すいさい",
    "meaning": "watercolor painting"
  },
  {
    "question": "大衆的",
    "answer": "たいしゅうてき",
    "meaning": "popular (among the general public), populist, plebian, low-brow, widely liked"
  },
  {
    "question": "与し易い",
    "answer": "くみしやすい",
    "meaning": "easy to deal with, tractable, manageable"
  },
  {
    "question": "慈雨",
    "answer": "じう",
    "meaning": "welcome rain, beneficial rain, blessed rain, rain that comes after a drought"
  },
  {
    "question": "合板",
    "answer": "ごうはん,ごうばん",
    "meaning": "veneer board, plywood, joint publication"
  },
  {
    "question": "耐水",
    "answer": "たいすい",
    "meaning": "water-resistant, waterproof"
  },
  {
    "question": "目が利く",
    "answer": "めがきく",
    "meaning": "to have an eye for"
  },
  {
    "question": "内幕",
    "answer": "うちまく,ないまく",
    "meaning": "lowdown, inside curtain, inside information, hidden circumstances, inside facts, inner workings, und"
  },
  {
    "question": "吊り上げ",
    "answer": "つりあげ",
    "meaning": "mechanism used to lift an actor onto the stage (in kabuki)"
  },
  {
    "question": "茹で蛸",
    "answer": "ゆでだこ,ゆでたこ",
    "meaning": "boiled octopus, person as red as a lobster"
  },
  {
    "question": "立往生",
    "answer": "たちおうじょう",
    "meaning": "being brought to a standstill, being stranded, getting stuck, stalling, deadlock, being stumped, bei"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶対視",
    "answer": "ぜったいし",
    "meaning": "taking something as absolute truth, regarding something as absolute"
  },
  {
    "question": "品名",
    "answer": "ひんめい",
    "meaning": "product name, name of an article"
  },
  {
    "question": "詫び入る",
    "answer": "わびいる",
    "meaning": "to apologize sincerely, to apologise sincerely"
  },
  {
    "question": "茹る",
    "answer": "ゆだる,うだる",
    "meaning": "to boil, to seethe, to be oppressed by heat"
  },
  {
    "question": "食い付き",
    "answer": "くいつき",
    "meaning": "bite (in fishing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "下層階級",
    "answer": "かそうかいきゅう",
    "meaning": "proletariat, lower classes"
  },
  {
    "question": "でも医者",
    "answer": "でもいしゃ",
    "meaning": "quack (doctor)"
  },
  {
    "question": "足速",
    "answer": "あしばや",
    "meaning": "fast (walking), quick, brisk, quick (passing of time), rapid, swift"
  },
  {
    "question": "乳繰る",
    "answer": "ちちくる",
    "meaning": "to have a secret affair, to meet secretly (for two persons), to flirt with one another"
  },
  {
    "question": "落ち行く",
    "answer": "おちゆく",
    "meaning": "to flee, to take flight, to be ruined, to go down in the world, to settle down (e.g. in one location"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い回す",
    "answer": "いいまわす",
    "meaning": "to express in a roundabout way"
  },
  {
    "question": "二等分",
    "answer": "にとうぶん",
    "meaning": "bisection"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜凪",
    "answer": "よなぎ",
    "meaning": "evening calm"
  },
  {
    "question": "舞人",
    "answer": "まいびと,まいうど,まいにん",
    "meaning": "dancer (esp. a bugaku dancer)"
  },
  {
    "question": "斛",
    "answer": "こく",
    "meaning": "koku, traditional unit of volume, approx. 180.4 litres, measure of a Japanese-style boat's loading c"
  },
  {
    "question": "祐天寺",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "寛政",
    "answer": "かんせい",
    "meaning": "Kansei era (1789.1.25-1801.2.5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "射影",
    "answer": "しゃえい",
    "meaning": "projection"
  },
  {
    "question": "弔詞",
    "answer": "ちょうし",
    "meaning": "message of condolence, memorial address"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄鉄鉱",
    "answer": "おうてっこう",
    "meaning": "iron pyrites, fool's gold, pyrite"
  },
  {
    "question": "詠み手",
    "answer": "よみて",
    "meaning": "writer (of a poem), composer (of a poem)"
  },
  {
    "question": "擬人",
    "answer": "ぎじん",
    "meaning": "simulation of a person"
  },
  {
    "question": "太陰",
    "answer": "たいいん",
    "meaning": "the Moon, the greater yin (in yin-yang)"
  },
  {
    "question": "婆娑羅",
    "answer": "ばさら,ばしゃら",
    "meaning": "acting without restraint, self-indulgence, wild license, eccentricity, being pretentious, putting on"
  },
  {
    "question": "久保",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "黒髭",
    "answer": "くろひげ",
    "meaning": "black beard, type of noh mask with a black beard and protruding chin"
  },
  {
    "question": "光体",
    "answer": "こうたい",
    "meaning": "luminous body"
  },
  {
    "question": "恵方巻",
    "answer": "えほうまき",
    "meaning": "ehōmaki, uncut sushi roll eaten during setsubun"
  },
  {
    "question": "泣き女",
    "answer": "なきおんな",
    "meaning": "professional female mourner, keener"
  },
  {
    "question": "若大将",
    "answer": "わかだいしょう",
    "meaning": "young commander, young leader, young master"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗紫色",
    "answer": "あんししょく",
    "meaning": "dark purple"
  },
  {
    "question": "枢軸国",
    "answer": "すうじくこく",
    "meaning": "(World War II) Axis powers"
  },
  {
    "question": "巡視船",
    "answer": "じゅんしせん",
    "meaning": "patrol boat"
  },
  {
    "question": "酋長",
    "answer": "しゅうちょう",
    "meaning": "chieftain"
  },
  {
    "question": "肘掛椅子",
    "answer": "ひじかけいす",
    "meaning": "armchair, chair with arm rests, senior staff"
  },
  {
    "question": "民主政治",
    "answer": "みんしゅせいじ",
    "meaning": "democratic government"
  },
  {
    "question": "空馬",
    "answer": "からうま",
    "meaning": "unburdened horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "夢路",
    "answer": "ゆめじ",
    "meaning": "dreamland, land of Nod, realm of dreams"
  },
  {
    "question": "与力",
    "answer": "よりき",
    "meaning": "feudal era police rank"
  },
  {
    "question": "一回生",
    "answer": "いっかいせい",
    "meaning": "first year (college) student, freshman, graduate of one year's standing"
  },
  {
    "question": "唱歌",
    "answer": "しょうか",
    "meaning": "singing, songs"
  },
  {
    "question": "神授",
    "answer": "しんじゅ",
    "meaning": "divine gift"
  },
  {
    "question": "蝦",
    "answer": "かえる,えび",
    "meaning": "frog, prawn, shrimp, lobster, crayfish"
  },
  {
    "question": "協約",
    "answer": "きょうやく",
    "meaning": "pact, convention, agreement"
  },
  {
    "question": "練り餌",
    "answer": "ねりえ,ねりえさ",
    "meaning": "paste bird feed, paste fishing bait"
  },
  {
    "question": "偽書",
    "answer": "ぎしょ",
    "meaning": "spurious letter, apocryphal book, forgery"
  },
  {
    "question": "官房",
    "answer": "かんぼう",
    "meaning": "government secretariat"
  },
  {
    "question": "佐世保",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "法制",
    "answer": "ほうせい",
    "meaning": "legislation, laws"
  },
  {
    "question": "槻",
    "answer": "けやき,つき",
    "meaning": "Japanese zelkova (species of elm-like tree, Zelkowa serrata)"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀鉱",
    "answer": "ぎんこう",
    "meaning": "silver mine, ore"
  },
  {
    "question": "火影",
    "answer": "ほかげ",
    "meaning": "firelight, shadows or forms moving in firelight"
  },
  {
    "question": "擱座",
    "answer": "かくざ",
    "meaning": "running aground, stranding, being disabled (of a tank, train, etc.), being put out of action"
  },
  {
    "question": "葛籠",
    "answer": "つづら",
    "meaning": "wicker clothes hamper"
  },
  {
    "question": "外衣",
    "answer": "がいい",
    "meaning": "outer garment"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼子",
    "answer": "よびこ",
    "meaning": "whistle"
  },
  {
    "question": "如意棒",
    "answer": "にょいぼう",
    "meaning": "magic staff"
  },
  {
    "question": "串揚げ",
    "answer": "くしあげ",
    "meaning": "kushiage, deep-fried skewered meat and vegetables"
  },
  {
    "question": "気魄",
    "answer": "きはく",
    "meaning": "spirit, soul, drive, vigor, vigour"
  },
  {
    "question": "魍魎",
    "answer": "もうりょう",
    "meaning": "all kinds of spirits and goblins"
  },
  {
    "question": "慶長",
    "answer": "けいちょう",
    "meaning": "Keichō era (1596.10.27-1615.7.13)"
  },
  {
    "question": "粘土質",
    "answer": "ねんどしつ",
    "meaning": "clay-like, clayey, argillaceous"
  },
  {
    "question": "忍びの者",
    "answer": "しのびのもの",
    "meaning": "ninja"
  },
  {
    "question": "外輪",
    "answer": "がいりん,そとわ",
    "meaning": "outer ring, external ring, rim (of a wheel), paddle wheel, out-toe walking, duck-footed walking"
  },
  {
    "question": "雪祭り",
    "answer": "ゆきまつり",
    "meaning": "snow festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "道教",
    "answer": "どうきょう,みちおしえ",
    "meaning": "Taoism, Daoism, tiger beetle (esp. the Japanese tiger beetle, Cicindela japonica)"
  },
  {
    "question": "居館",
    "answer": "きょかん",
    "meaning": "residence, mansion, estate, dwelling"
  },
  {
    "question": "部局",
    "answer": "ぶきょく",
    "meaning": "department, bureau, section, part"
  },
  {
    "question": "眉宇",
    "answer": "びう",
    "meaning": "brow, brows"
  },
  {
    "question": "直参",
    "answer": "じきさん",
    "meaning": "immediate follower (of the shogun)"
  },
  {
    "question": "折り鶴",
    "answer": "おりづる",
    "meaning": "folded paper crane"
  },
  {
    "question": "讒言",
    "answer": "ざんげん",
    "meaning": "false charge, slander, defamation"
  },
  {
    "question": "瞋恚",
    "answer": "しんい,しんに,しんね",
    "meaning": "dosa (ill will, antipathy), irateness, anger"
  },
  {
    "question": "債務者",
    "answer": "さいむしゃ",
    "meaning": "debtor"
  },
  {
    "question": "実地試験",
    "answer": "じっちしけん",
    "meaning": "practical test"
  },
  {
    "question": "水瓶座",
    "answer": "みずがめざ",
    "meaning": "Aquarius (constellation), the Water Carrier, the Water Bearer"
  },
  {
    "question": "室町幕府",
    "answer": "むろまちばくふ",
    "meaning": "Muromachi shogunate (1336-1573 CE)"
  },
  {
    "question": "守り刀",
    "answer": "まもりがたな",
    "meaning": "sword for self-defense, sword for self-defence"
  },
  {
    "question": "金管楽器",
    "answer": "きんかんがっき",
    "meaning": "brass instrument"
  },
  {
    "question": "籐椅子",
    "answer": "とういす",
    "meaning": "wicker(work) (cane, rattan) chair"
  },
  {
    "question": "不法滞在",
    "answer": "ふほうたいざい",
    "meaning": "illegal residence (in a country), illegal stay, illegal overstaying (of a visa)"
  },
  {
    "question": "既得権",
    "answer": "きとくけん",
    "meaning": "vested rights"
  },
  {
    "question": "逆臣",
    "answer": "ぎゃくしん",
    "meaning": "treacherous retainer"
  },
  {
    "question": "修行者",
    "answer": "しゅぎょうじゃ,すぎょうざ",
    "meaning": "practitioner of Buddhism, practitioner of austerities, disciplinant, practitioner of martial arts"
  },
  {
    "question": "繚乱",
    "answer": "りょうらん",
    "meaning": "profusely (esp. flowers blooming in great profusion)"
  },
  {
    "question": "狂い咲き",
    "answer": "くるいざき",
    "meaning": "off-season flowering"
  },
  {
    "question": "網焼き",
    "answer": "あみやき",
    "meaning": "grilling, broiling"
  },
  {
    "question": "天気図",
    "answer": "てんきず",
    "meaning": "weather map"
  },
  {
    "question": "三尺",
    "answer": "さんじゃく",
    "meaning": "3 Japanese feet, waistband, belt, cloth girdle"
  },
  {
    "question": "食玩",
    "answer": "しょくがん",
    "meaning": "small toy sold with food, premium"
  },
  {
    "question": "躁鬱",
    "answer": "そううつ",
    "meaning": "manic depression, mood swing"
  },
  {
    "question": "法螺",
    "answer": "ほら",
    "meaning": "boasting, bragging, big talk, conch (esp. Charonia tritonis), trumpet shell"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍律",
    "answer": "ぐんりつ",
    "meaning": "martial law, articles of war, military disciple, military law"
  },
  {
    "question": "不在証明",
    "answer": "ふざいしょうめい",
    "meaning": "alibi"
  },
  {
    "question": "中途採用",
    "answer": "ちゅうとさいよう",
    "meaning": "mid-career recruitment"
  },
  {
    "question": "送風",
    "answer": "そうふう",
    "meaning": "ventilation"
  },
  {
    "question": "複合体",
    "answer": "ふくごうたい",
    "meaning": "complex"
  },
  {
    "question": "離間",
    "answer": "りかん",
    "meaning": "estrangement, alienation, sowing discord, driving a wedge"
  },
  {
    "question": "図版",
    "answer": "ずはん",
    "meaning": "plate, illustration, figure"
  },
  {
    "question": "国家試験",
    "answer": "こっかしけん",
    "meaning": "state examination"
  },
  {
    "question": "壊走",
    "answer": "かいそう",
    "meaning": "rout, stampede"
  },
  {
    "question": "紙粘土",
    "answer": "かみねんど",
    "meaning": "papier mâché"
  },
  {
    "question": "定期入れ",
    "answer": "ていきいれ",
    "meaning": "commuter pass container, holder for a season ticket"
  },
  {
    "question": "宇宙遊泳",
    "answer": "うちゅうゆうえい",
    "meaning": "space walk"
  },
  {
    "question": "取手",
    "answer": "とって,とりて",
    "meaning": "handle, grip, knob, recipient, receiver, acceptor, taker, skilled practitioner (of judo, sumo, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "角質",
    "answer": "かくしつ",
    "meaning": "keratin, corneum, cuticle, collagen, horny substance"
  },
  {
    "question": "湿疹",
    "answer": "しっしん",
    "meaning": "eczema, rash"
  },
  {
    "question": "旗幟",
    "answer": "きし,きしょく",
    "meaning": "flag, banner, ensign, emblem"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜長",
    "answer": "よなが",
    "meaning": "long night (esp. of autumn)"
  },
  {
    "question": "痛風",
    "answer": "つうふう",
    "meaning": "gout"
  },
  {
    "question": "平均気温",
    "answer": "へいきんきおん",
    "meaning": "average temperature"
  },
  {
    "question": "女主人公",
    "answer": "おんなしゅじんこう",
    "meaning": "heroine, female protagonist"
  },
  {
    "question": "謙譲",
    "answer": "けんじょう",
    "meaning": "modesty, humility"
  },
  {
    "question": "家督相続",
    "answer": "かとくそうぞく",
    "meaning": "succession to headship of a family"
  },
  {
    "question": "入れ換え",
    "answer": "いれかえ",
    "meaning": "replacement, substitution, change, shunting (rail), switching"
  },
  {
    "question": "伸べる",
    "answer": "のべる",
    "meaning": "to lay out (a futon), to make (bed), to spread out, to stretch, to widen, to postpone, to extend"
  },
  {
    "question": "精華",
    "answer": "せいか",
    "meaning": "essence, quintessence, flower, glory"
  },
  {
    "question": "学割",
    "answer": "がくわり",
    "meaning": "student discount"
  },
  {
    "question": "置き換え",
    "answer": "おきかえ",
    "meaning": "replacement, substitute, displacement, transposition, reset"
  },
  {
    "question": "匍匐",
    "answer": "ほふく",
    "meaning": "creeping, crawling, sneaking"
  },
  {
    "question": "空洞化",
    "answer": "くうどうか",
    "meaning": "making hollow, making meaningless, deindustrialization, deindustrialisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "好戦",
    "answer": "こうせん",
    "meaning": "belligerence"
  },
  {
    "question": "分度器",
    "answer": "ぶんどき",
    "meaning": "protractor"
  },
  {
    "question": "付帯",
    "answer": "ふたい",
    "meaning": "incidental, ancillary, accessory, secondary, collateral"
  },
  {
    "question": "低劣",
    "answer": "ていれつ",
    "meaning": "low grade, inferiority, coarseness, vulgarity"
  },
  {
    "question": "百科",
    "answer": "ひゃっか",
    "meaning": "many objects (for study), encyclopedia, encyclopaedia"
  },
  {
    "question": "集中豪雨",
    "answer": "しゅうちゅうごうう",
    "meaning": "local downpour, severe rain fall"
  },
  {
    "question": "種蒔き",
    "answer": "たねまき",
    "meaning": "sowing seeds, planting seeds, scattering seeds"
  },
  {
    "question": "禁制品",
    "answer": "きんせいひん",
    "meaning": "contraband (goods), prohibited goods"
  },
  {
    "question": "亜流",
    "answer": "ありゅう",
    "meaning": "(inferior) imitator, epigone, poor imitation, copycat, follower, adherent, person belonging to the s"
  },
  {
    "question": "叩き台",
    "answer": "たたきだい",
    "meaning": "chopping block, springboard for discussion, draft proposal, tentative plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "横軸",
    "answer": "よこじく",
    "meaning": "abscissa, horizontal axis, horizontal scroll"
  },
  {
    "question": "変速",
    "answer": "へんそく",
    "meaning": "shifting gears, changing gears"
  },
  {
    "question": "髪結",
    "answer": "かみゆい,かみい",
    "meaning": "hairdresser, hairdressing"
  },
  {
    "question": "面罵",
    "answer": "めんば",
    "meaning": "abusing someone to his (her) face"
  },
  {
    "question": "消極",
    "answer": "しょうきょく",
    "meaning": "passive, negative, conservative, depolarization"
  },
  {
    "question": "上前",
    "answer": "うわまえ",
    "meaning": "part of the fabric that is wrapped farthest from the skin when wearing a garment that is wrapped in"
  },
  {
    "question": "同中",
    "answer": "おなちゅう",
    "meaning": "student at the same middle school, graduate of the same middle school"
  },
  {
    "question": "伝送",
    "answer": "でんそう",
    "meaning": "transmission, communication, circulation, dissemination, diffusion, propagation, delivery"
  },
  {
    "question": "死に装束",
    "answer": "しにしょうぞく",
    "meaning": "burial clothes, clothes worn to commit suicide"
  },
  {
    "question": "分譲",
    "answer": "ぶんじょう",
    "meaning": "selling (real-estate) lots"
  },
  {
    "question": "横紙破り",
    "answer": "よこがみやぶり",
    "meaning": "acting illogically"
  },
  {
    "question": "聴講",
    "answer": "ちょうこう",
    "meaning": "lecture attendance, auditing"
  },
  {
    "question": "仏閣",
    "answer": "ぶっかく",
    "meaning": "Buddhist temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会保障",
    "answer": "しゃかいほしょう",
    "meaning": "social security"
  },
  {
    "question": "深慮",
    "answer": "しんりょ",
    "meaning": "deliberate, careful, thoughtful, thoughtfulness, prudence"
  },
  {
    "question": "角膜",
    "answer": "かくまく",
    "meaning": "cornea"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱輪",
    "answer": "だつりん",
    "meaning": "wheel flying off its axle"
  },
  {
    "question": "定量",
    "answer": "ていりょう",
    "meaning": "fixed quantity"
  },
  {
    "question": "廃絶",
    "answer": "はいぜつ",
    "meaning": "abolition, elimination, extinction, discontinuation"
  },
  {
    "question": "医学界",
    "answer": "いがくかい",
    "meaning": "medical world, medical circles, medical community"
  },
  {
    "question": "感嘆符",
    "answer": "かんたんふ",
    "meaning": "exclamation point, exclamation mark"
  },
  {
    "question": "型崩れ",
    "answer": "かたくずれ",
    "meaning": "losing shape, getting out of shape"
  },
  {
    "question": "鳥目",
    "answer": "とりめ,ちょうもく",
    "meaning": "night-blindness, cash, money, zeni coin"
  },
  {
    "question": "大汗",
    "answer": "おおあせ,たいかん",
    "meaning": "heavy sweating, a great deal of sweat, Great Khan, Grand Khan"
  },
  {
    "question": "手旗信号",
    "answer": "てばたしんごう",
    "meaning": "flag signaling, semaphore"
  },
  {
    "question": "益虫",
    "answer": "えきちゅう",
    "meaning": "useful insect"
  },
  {
    "question": "気候変動",
    "answer": "きこうへんどう",
    "meaning": "climate change"
  },
  {
    "question": "空調設備",
    "answer": "くうちょうせつび",
    "meaning": "air conditioner"
  },
  {
    "question": "冥利",
    "answer": "みょうり",
    "meaning": "providence, luck, favor, favour, advantage"
  },
  {
    "question": "化学繊維",
    "answer": "かがくせんい",
    "meaning": "synthetic fiber, synthetic fibre, chemical fiber, chemical fibre"
  },
  {
    "question": "最後っ屁",
    "answer": "さいごっぺ",
    "meaning": "stink bomb, foul odour emitted from the anal sacs of a frightened weasel, final desperate tactic"
  },
  {
    "question": "本革",
    "answer": "ほんがわ,ほんかわ",
    "meaning": "real leather"
  },
  {
    "question": "纏め",
    "answer": "まとめ",
    "meaning": "settlement, conclusion, summary"
  },
  {
    "question": "懇親",
    "answer": "こんしん",
    "meaning": "friendship, intimacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "重んずる",
    "answer": "おもんずる",
    "meaning": "to honor, to honour, to respect, to esteem, to prize"
  },
  {
    "question": "認識不足",
    "answer": "にんしきぶそく",
    "meaning": "lack of knowledge or understanding"
  },
  {
    "question": "降神",
    "answer": "こうしん",
    "meaning": "spiritualism, spiritism"
  },
  {
    "question": "母衣",
    "answer": "ほろ",
    "meaning": "canopy (esp. the cloth or canvas used for it), awning, top (of a convertible), hood, helmet cape, cl"
  },
  {
    "question": "欧州連合",
    "answer": "おうしゅうれんごう",
    "meaning": "European Union, EU"
  },
  {
    "question": "陽電子",
    "answer": "ようでんし",
    "meaning": "positron"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤色巨星",
    "answer": "せきしょくきょせい",
    "meaning": "red giant (star)"
  },
  {
    "question": "浅海",
    "answer": "せんかい",
    "meaning": "shallow sea"
  },
  {
    "question": "棒振り",
    "answer": "ぼうふり",
    "meaning": "waving a stick, conductor (orchestra, etc.), Edo policeman"
  },
  {
    "question": "出水",
    "answer": "しゅっすい,でみず",
    "meaning": "flood, freshet, inundation"
  },
  {
    "question": "旧都",
    "answer": "きゅうと",
    "meaning": "old capital, former capital"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀狐",
    "answer": "ぎんぎつね",
    "meaning": "silver fox"
  },
  {
    "question": "心魂",
    "answer": "しんこん",
    "meaning": "heart and soul, one's soul (heart)"
  },
  {
    "question": "霊符",
    "answer": "れいふ",
    "meaning": "charm, amulet, talisman"
  },
  {
    "question": "真作",
    "answer": "しんさく",
    "meaning": "authentic work (as opposed to a fake)"
  },
  {
    "question": "天外",
    "answer": "てんがい",
    "meaning": "beyond the heavens, farthest regions, furthest regions"
  },
  {
    "question": "山陽",
    "answer": "さんよう",
    "meaning": "south side of a mountain, Sanyo district"
  },
  {
    "question": "源五郎",
    "answer": "げんごろう",
    "meaning": "diving beetle, Japanese predacious diving beetle (Cybister japonicus)"
  },
  {
    "question": "才子",
    "answer": "さいし",
    "meaning": "talented man, clever man"
  },
  {
    "question": "落人",
    "answer": "おちうど,おちゅうど",
    "meaning": "defeated soldier fleeing the enemy"
  },
  {
    "question": "信教",
    "answer": "しんきょう",
    "meaning": "religious belief, faith"
  },
  {
    "question": "閉架",
    "answer": "へいか",
    "meaning": "closed-stacks (e.g. in a library), closed shelf system"
  },
  {
    "question": "亡命政権",
    "answer": "ぼうめいせいけん",
    "meaning": "government in exile"
  },
  {
    "question": "如来",
    "answer": "にょらい",
    "meaning": "Tathagata, perfected one (suffix of high-ranking Buddhist deities)"
  },
  {
    "question": "古女房",
    "answer": "ふるにょうぼう",
    "meaning": "good old wife, one's wife of many years"
  },
  {
    "question": "床几",
    "answer": "しょうぎ",
    "meaning": "camp stool, folding stool"
  },
  {
    "question": "割符",
    "answer": "わりふ,わっぷ",
    "meaning": "tally, check, piece of wood or paper split in half and given to each party as a form of proof (e.g."
  },
  {
    "question": "肉ジャガ",
    "answer": "にくジャガ",
    "meaning": "nikujaga, meat and potato stew"
  },
  {
    "question": "史料",
    "answer": "しりょう",
    "meaning": "historical materials, historical records, historical sources, archives"
  },
  {
    "question": "冬毛",
    "answer": "ふゆげ",
    "meaning": "winter fur, winter plumage"
  },
  {
    "question": "謝恩会",
    "answer": "しゃおんかい",
    "meaning": "thank-you party"
  },
  {
    "question": "総髪",
    "answer": "そうはつ",
    "meaning": "wearing one's hair knotted in the back"
  },
  {
    "question": "策源地",
    "answer": "さくげんち",
    "meaning": "strategic base"
  },
  {
    "question": "化学療法",
    "answer": "かがくりょうほう",
    "meaning": "chemotherapy"
  },
  {
    "question": "弦月",
    "answer": "げんげつ",
    "meaning": "crescent moon"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄合",
    "answer": "よりあい",
    "meaning": "meeting, gathering, village assembly, two wrestlers approaching each other"
  },
  {
    "question": "花押",
    "answer": "かおう",
    "meaning": "written seal, stylized signature"
  },
  {
    "question": "立像",
    "answer": "りつぞう",
    "meaning": "standing statue, standing image"
  },
  {
    "question": "貴顕",
    "answer": "きけん",
    "meaning": "distinguished person"
  },
  {
    "question": "単衣",
    "answer": "たんい,ひとえ,ひとえぎぬ",
    "meaning": "unlined kimono, one kimono, a single kimono, unlined kimono worn as an undergarment by court nobles"
  },
  {
    "question": "自閉症",
    "answer": "じへいしょう",
    "meaning": "autism"
  },
  {
    "question": "公会堂",
    "answer": "こうかいどう",
    "meaning": "town hall, public hall"
  },
  {
    "question": "空堀",
    "answer": "からぼり",
    "meaning": "dry moat"
  },
  {
    "question": "密漁",
    "answer": "みつりょう",
    "meaning": "poaching (fish or seafood)"
  },
  {
    "question": "雪駄",
    "answer": "せった,せきだ,せちだ",
    "meaning": "leather-soled sandals (geta)"
  },
  {
    "question": "禅譲",
    "answer": "ぜんじょう",
    "meaning": "abdication (of a Chinese emperor) in favor of a virtuous successor (as opposed to an heir), smooth t"
  },
  {
    "question": "三面鏡",
    "answer": "さんめんきょう",
    "meaning": "three-sided mirror"
  },
  {
    "question": "熾る",
    "answer": "おこる",
    "meaning": "to catch fire (of charcoal), to start burning, to burn away, to burn merrily"
  },
  {
    "question": "二親",
    "answer": "ふたおや,にしん",
    "meaning": "both parents"
  },
  {
    "question": "気違い",
    "answer": "きちがい",
    "meaning": "madness, madman, enthusiast, freak, junkie"
  },
  {
    "question": "守護聖人",
    "answer": "しゅごせいじん",
    "meaning": "patron saint"
  },
  {
    "question": "風林火山",
    "answer": "ふうりんかざん",
    "meaning": "as fast as the wind, as quiet as the forest, as daring as fire, and immovable as the mountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "干菓子",
    "answer": "ひがし",
    "meaning": "dried candies, dried confectionary, cookies"
  },
  {
    "question": "兄弟分",
    "answer": "きょうだいぶん",
    "meaning": "buddy, pal, sworn brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "逃散",
    "answer": "ちょうさん,とうさん",
    "meaning": "fleeing in all directions, (in Japanese history, a reference to) farmers who abandoned their fields"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛮声",
    "answer": "ばんせい",
    "meaning": "rough voice"
  },
  {
    "question": "蝟集",
    "answer": "いしゅう",
    "meaning": "swarm, throng, flock together"
  },
  {
    "question": "僧帽筋",
    "answer": "そうぼうきん",
    "meaning": "trapezius muscle"
  },
  {
    "question": "石焼き",
    "answer": "いしやき",
    "meaning": "porcelain, baking by means of hot stones or pebbles"
  },
  {
    "question": "二重写し",
    "answer": "にじゅううつし",
    "meaning": "double exposure"
  },
  {
    "question": "笛吹",
    "answer": "ふえふき",
    "meaning": "flute player, flutist, flautist, piper"
  },
  {
    "question": "煎じ薬",
    "answer": "せんじぐすり",
    "meaning": "(medical) decoction, infusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "排熱",
    "answer": "はいねつ",
    "meaning": "remaining heat, waste heat"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶縁体",
    "answer": "ぜつえんたい",
    "meaning": "insulator"
  },
  {
    "question": "虫垂炎",
    "answer": "ちゅうすいえん",
    "meaning": "appendicitis"
  },
  {
    "question": "出っ歯",
    "answer": "でっぱ",
    "meaning": "protruding tooth, overbite, bucktooth"
  },
  {
    "question": "小劇場",
    "answer": "しょうげきじょう",
    "meaning": "little theater, small theater"
  },
  {
    "question": "渋柿",
    "answer": "しぶがき",
    "meaning": "astringent persimmon"
  },
  {
    "question": "感興",
    "answer": "かんきょう",
    "meaning": "interest, fun, inspiration"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛息",
    "answer": "あいそく",
    "meaning": "(your) beloved son, cute boy"
  },
  {
    "question": "湯葉",
    "answer": "ゆば",
    "meaning": "tofu skin, dried beancurd, delicacy made from the skin of gently boiled soybean milk"
  },
  {
    "question": "味醂",
    "answer": "みりん",
    "meaning": "mirin, type of sweet rice wine used in cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "区民",
    "answer": "くみん",
    "meaning": "ward residents"
  },
  {
    "question": "近在",
    "answer": "きんざい",
    "meaning": "neighboring villages, neighbouring villages, suburban districts"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷や飯",
    "answer": "ひやめし",
    "meaning": "cold rice, hanger-on, dependent, disgraced former actor"
  },
  {
    "question": "燃料電池",
    "answer": "ねんりょうでんち",
    "meaning": "fuel cell"
  },
  {
    "question": "四つ辻",
    "answer": "よつつじ",
    "meaning": "crossroads, intersection, crossway, carrefour"
  },
  {
    "question": "謹厳",
    "answer": "きんげん",
    "meaning": "stern, grave, solemn, sobersided"
  },
  {
    "question": "回数券",
    "answer": "かいすうけん",
    "meaning": "book of tickets"
  },
  {
    "question": "同校",
    "answer": "どうこう",
    "meaning": "same school"
  },
  {
    "question": "六尺",
    "answer": "ろくしゃく",
    "meaning": "six feet, traditional Japanese G-string for men, palanquin bearer"
  },
  {
    "question": "創意",
    "answer": "そうい",
    "meaning": "original idea, originality"
  },
  {
    "question": "主筋",
    "answer": "しゅうすじ,しゅすじ,しゅきん",
    "meaning": "people close to the head man, main reinforcement (in a reinforced-concrete structure)"
  },
  {
    "question": "屈従",
    "answer": "くつじゅう",
    "meaning": "servile submission, subservience"
  },
  {
    "question": "持て成し",
    "answer": "もてなし",
    "meaning": "hospitality, reception, treatment, service, entertainment, (light) refreshment, entertaining with fo"
  },
  {
    "question": "半ダース",
    "answer": "はんダース",
    "meaning": "half-dozen, half-a-dozen"
  },
  {
    "question": "創世神話",
    "answer": "そうせいしんわ",
    "meaning": "creation myth"
  },
  {
    "question": "果し合い",
    "answer": "はたしあい",
    "meaning": "duel"
  },
  {
    "question": "嫁取り",
    "answer": "よめとり",
    "meaning": "taking a wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "追加予算",
    "answer": "ついかよさん",
    "meaning": "supplementary budget"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹の子",
    "answer": "たけのこ",
    "meaning": "bamboo shoot, inexperienced doctor, quack"
  },
  {
    "question": "技芸",
    "answer": "ぎげい",
    "meaning": "arts, crafts, handicrafts"
  },
  {
    "question": "隠微",
    "answer": "いんび",
    "meaning": "obscurity, mystery, abstruseness"
  },
  {
    "question": "縊る",
    "answer": "くびる",
    "meaning": "to strangle to death"
  },
  {
    "question": "給付",
    "answer": "きゅうふ",
    "meaning": "payment, provision, benefit, present, delivery, performance"
  },
  {
    "question": "本を正す",
    "answer": "もとをただす",
    "meaning": "to go to the bottom of an affair, to inquire into the origin"
  },
  {
    "question": "黙禱",
    "answer": "もくとう",
    "meaning": "silent prayer"
  },
  {
    "question": "当院",
    "answer": "とういん",
    "meaning": "this institution, this parliament, this hospital, this clinic"
  },
  {
    "question": "掛け流し",
    "answer": "かけながし",
    "meaning": "free-flowing (hot spring, irrigation, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "臥薪嘗胆",
    "answer": "がしんしょうたん",
    "meaning": "going through thick and thin to attain one's objective, enduring unspeakable hardships for the sake"
  },
  {
    "question": "召し捕る",
    "answer": "めしとる",
    "meaning": "to arrest, to apprehend"
  },
  {
    "question": "福々しい",
    "answer": "ふくぶくしい",
    "meaning": "(plump and) happy-looking"
  },
  {
    "question": "東経",
    "answer": "とうけい",
    "meaning": "east longitude"
  },
  {
    "question": "姦通",
    "answer": "かんつう",
    "meaning": "adultery"
  },
  {
    "question": "自己実現",
    "answer": "じこじつげん",
    "meaning": "self-actualization, self-fulfillment, self-realization"
  },
  {
    "question": "卓抜",
    "answer": "たくばつ",
    "meaning": "excellence, superiority, preeminence, prevalence"
  },
  {
    "question": "船賃",
    "answer": "ふなちん",
    "meaning": "passage, fare, shipping charges"
  },
  {
    "question": "幼妻",
    "answer": "おさなづま",
    "meaning": "very young bride, child bride, childish wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "傍証",
    "answer": "ぼうしょう",
    "meaning": "supporting evidence, corroboration"
  },
  {
    "question": "脾臓",
    "answer": "ひぞう",
    "meaning": "spleen"
  },
  {
    "question": "慰み物",
    "answer": "なぐさみもの",
    "meaning": "source of amusement, plaything"
  },
  {
    "question": "進歩的",
    "answer": "しんぽてき",
    "meaning": "progressive"
  },
  {
    "question": "神経ガス",
    "answer": "しんけいガス",
    "meaning": "nerve gas, nerve agent"
  },
  {
    "question": "我を張る",
    "answer": "がをはる",
    "meaning": "to insist on one's own ideas"
  },
  {
    "question": "仮託",
    "answer": "かたく",
    "meaning": "pretext, pretense, pretence"
  },
  {
    "question": "踊り食い",
    "answer": "おどりぐい",
    "meaning": "eating live seafood (e.g. ice gobies, shrimp) while still moving"
  },
  {
    "question": "霊柩車",
    "answer": "れいきゅうしゃ",
    "meaning": "hearse"
  },
  {
    "question": "措く",
    "answer": "おく",
    "meaning": "to stop (doing something), to cease, to put aside, to leave as is, to leave alone, to exclude, to ex"
  },
  {
    "question": "私小説",
    "answer": "ししょうせつ,わたくししょうせつ",
    "meaning": "I-novel, novel narrated in the first person"
  },
  {
    "question": "殿中",
    "answer": "でんちゅう",
    "meaning": "in the palace"
  },
  {
    "question": "気鋭",
    "answer": "きえい",
    "meaning": "spirited, energetic"
  },
  {
    "question": "隠喩",
    "answer": "いんゆ",
    "meaning": "metaphor"
  },
  {
    "question": "室内着",
    "answer": "しつないぎ",
    "meaning": "loungewear, comfortable clothing worn at home"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄刃",
    "answer": "うすば",
    "meaning": "thin (blade)"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち歌",
    "answer": "もちうた",
    "meaning": "one's song repertoire, songs one can sing"
  },
  {
    "question": "精神分析",
    "answer": "せいしんぶんせき",
    "meaning": "psychoanalysis"
  },
  {
    "question": "日の目",
    "answer": "ひのめ",
    "meaning": "sunlight"
  },
  {
    "question": "一穴",
    "answer": "いっけつ",
    "meaning": "one hole, toilet bowl (for both urination and defecation), effective point for moxibustion, one-woma"
  },
  {
    "question": "地下資源",
    "answer": "ちかしげん",
    "meaning": "underground resources"
  },
  {
    "question": "当腹",
    "answer": "とうふく,とうぶく,むかいばら",
    "meaning": "child born to one's current wife, child born to one's legal wife (as opposed to one's concubine, etc"
  },
  {
    "question": "二の足",
    "answer": "にのあし",
    "meaning": "second step, hesitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "経済大国",
    "answer": "けいざいたいこく",
    "meaning": "economic superpower, economic powerhouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "老い先",
    "answer": "おいさき",
    "meaning": "remaining years (of one's life)"
  },
  {
    "question": "突貫作業",
    "answer": "とっかんさぎょう",
    "meaning": "rush work, crash program, working on a crash basis, working at top speed"
  },
  {
    "question": "強心臓",
    "answer": "きょうしんぞう",
    "meaning": "boldness, guts, courage, gall, sangfroid"
  },
  {
    "question": "前説",
    "answer": "ぜんせつ,まえせつ",
    "meaning": "former opinion, warm-up (before an act or a TV show recording), prologue, introduction"
  },
  {
    "question": "大降り",
    "answer": "おおぶり",
    "meaning": "heavy rain, storm"
  },
  {
    "question": "間に合い",
    "answer": "まにあい",
    "meaning": "makeshift"
  },
  {
    "question": "人車",
    "answer": "じんしゃ",
    "meaning": "rickshaw, jinrikisha"
  },
  {
    "question": "手懸かり",
    "answer": "てがかり",
    "meaning": "clue, lead, key, trail, scent, track, handhold, hold"
  },
  {
    "question": "藤壺",
    "answer": "ふじつぼ",
    "meaning": "acorn barnacle (Balanomorpha spp.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "狒狒",
    "answer": "ひひ",
    "meaning": "baboon, lecher, dirty old man, skirt-chaser"
  },
  {
    "question": "善導",
    "answer": "ぜんどう",
    "meaning": "proper guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "籾",
    "answer": "もみ",
    "meaning": "unhulled rice, rice in the husk, paddy, rice husks, chaff"
  },
  {
    "question": "病院船",
    "answer": "びょういんせん",
    "meaning": "hospital ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "御山",
    "answer": "おやま,みやま",
    "meaning": "mountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "一里塚",
    "answer": "いちりづか",
    "meaning": "milestone (1 ri apart)"
  },
  {
    "question": "常陸",
    "answer": "ひたち",
    "meaning": "Hitachi (former province located in the major part of present-day Ibaraki Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "新帝",
    "answer": "しんてい",
    "meaning": "new emperor"
  },
  {
    "question": "罐",
    "answer": "かん,かま",
    "meaning": "can, tin, canned food, boiler"
  },
  {
    "question": "反日",
    "answer": "はんにち",
    "meaning": "anti-Japanese"
  },
  {
    "question": "水母",
    "answer": "くらげ,すいぼ",
    "meaning": "jellyfish, medusa"
  },
  {
    "question": "向島",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "丹後",
    "answer": "たんご",
    "meaning": "Tango (former province located in the north of present-day Kyōto Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "州兵",
    "answer": "しゅうへい",
    "meaning": "National Guard (esp. USA), National Guard member"
  },
  {
    "question": "対敵",
    "answer": "たいてき",
    "meaning": "confronting the enemy, hostilities"
  },
  {
    "question": "市電",
    "answer": "しでん",
    "meaning": "municipal railway, city streetcar, tram"
  },
  {
    "question": "宮内庁",
    "answer": "くないちょう",
    "meaning": "Imperial Household Agency"
  },
  {
    "question": "運転台",
    "answer": "うんてんだい",
    "meaning": "driver's seat"
  },
  {
    "question": "筐",
    "answer": "はこ,かたみ",
    "meaning": "box, case, chest, package, pack, crate, car (of a train, etc.), shamisen case, shamisen, public buil"
  },
  {
    "question": "街娼",
    "answer": "がいしょう",
    "meaning": "prostitute, whore, streetwalker"
  },
  {
    "question": "呵呵",
    "answer": "かか",
    "meaning": "sound of laughter"
  },
  {
    "question": "従属国",
    "answer": "じゅうぞくこく",
    "meaning": "dependency, appanage"
  },
  {
    "question": "如雨露",
    "answer": "じょうろ,じょろ",
    "meaning": "watering can, watering pot, sprinkling can"
  },
  {
    "question": "野沢菜",
    "answer": "のざわな",
    "meaning": "rape (Brassica rapa), common rape, cole, coleseed, coleseed greens"
  },
  {
    "question": "嗄れ声",
    "answer": "しゃがれごえ,しわがれごえ,かれごえ",
    "meaning": "hoarse voice, husky voice"
  },
  {
    "question": "兵権",
    "answer": "へいけん",
    "meaning": "military authority"
  },
  {
    "question": "病毒",
    "answer": "びょうどく",
    "meaning": "virus"
  },
  {
    "question": "花器",
    "answer": "かき",
    "meaning": "flower vase"
  },
  {
    "question": "下面",
    "answer": "かめん",
    "meaning": "underside, undersurface, inferior surface"
  },
  {
    "question": "命数",
    "answer": "めいすう",
    "meaning": "span of life, one's term of existence, one's time (alive), one's days, destiny, fate, assigning a na"
  },
  {
    "question": "争闘",
    "answer": "そうとう",
    "meaning": "strife, struggle"
  },
  {
    "question": "毒手",
    "answer": "どくしゅ",
    "meaning": "a dirty or underhanded trick"
  },
  {
    "question": "番付",
    "answer": "ばんづけ",
    "meaning": "ranked list (entertainers, sumo wrestlers, millionaires, etc.), program (e.g. theatre)"
  },
  {
    "question": "無能力",
    "answer": "むのうりょく",
    "meaning": "incompetence, inability, disability, incapacity"
  },
  {
    "question": "血腫",
    "answer": "けっしゅ",
    "meaning": "hematoma, haematoma"
  },
  {
    "question": "綿入れ",
    "answer": "わたいれ",
    "meaning": "padding with cotton, garment padded with cotton, wadded clothes"
  },
  {
    "question": "虚心",
    "answer": "きょしん",
    "meaning": "open-minded, receptive, free from preconceived ideas"
  },
  {
    "question": "僧服",
    "answer": "そうふく",
    "meaning": "priest's garb"
  },
  {
    "question": "とも無く",
    "answer": "ともなく",
    "meaning": "somehow, without knowing (it), unconsciously, unthinkingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "降着",
    "answer": "こうちゃく",
    "meaning": "landing, touchdown, splashdown, demotion (horse racing), accretion"
  },
  {
    "question": "後肢",
    "answer": "こうし",
    "meaning": "hindlimb, hindlimbs, hind leg, hind legs"
  },
  {
    "question": "春期",
    "answer": "しゅんき",
    "meaning": "spring term (e.g. school), spring period"
  },
  {
    "question": "中盤戦",
    "answer": "ちゅうばんせん",
    "meaning": "the midst of a campaign"
  },
  {
    "question": "枕草子",
    "answer": "まくらのそうし",
    "meaning": "The Pillow Book (by Sei Shonagon)"
  },
  {
    "question": "示現",
    "answer": "じげん",
    "meaning": "manifestation (of a celestial being)"
  },
  {
    "question": "笹舟",
    "answer": "ささぶね",
    "meaning": "toy bamboo-leaf boat"
  },
  {
    "question": "徳島",
    "answer": "とくしま",
    "meaning": "Tokushima (city, prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "絹布",
    "answer": "けんぷ",
    "meaning": "silk, silk cloth"
  },
  {
    "question": "玩具箱",
    "answer": "おもちゃばこ",
    "meaning": "toy box, toy chest"
  },
  {
    "question": "興隆",
    "answer": "こうりゅう",
    "meaning": "rise, prosperity"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼き栗",
    "answer": "やきぐり",
    "meaning": "roasted chestnuts"
  },
  {
    "question": "粗挽き",
    "answer": "あらびき",
    "meaning": "coarsely ground (e.g. coffee, grain), minced (e.g. meat)"
  },
  {
    "question": "円舞曲",
    "answer": "えんぶきょく",
    "meaning": "waltz (composition)"
  },
  {
    "question": "水抜き",
    "answer": "みずぬき",
    "meaning": "draining (esp. pipes from water for the winter), drainhole, drain, drainage"
  },
  {
    "question": "素寒貧",
    "answer": "すかんぴん",
    "meaning": "penniless, extremely poor, destitute"
  },
  {
    "question": "木魚",
    "answer": "もくぎょ",
    "meaning": "fish gong, fish wood block, temple block, round, hollow, wood block (vaguely fish-shaped, usu. with"
  },
  {
    "question": "遊底",
    "answer": "ゆうてい",
    "meaning": "breechblock (of a gun)"
  },
  {
    "question": "法医学",
    "answer": "ほういがく",
    "meaning": "forensic medicine, forensic pathology, medical jurisprudence, legal medicine"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗渠",
    "answer": "あんきょ",
    "meaning": "subterranean drain, culvert, conduit"
  },
  {
    "question": "袱紗",
    "answer": "ふくさ",
    "meaning": "small silk wrapper, small cloth for wiping tea utensils, crepe wrapper"
  },
  {
    "question": "状態変化",
    "answer": "じょうたいへんか",
    "meaning": "phase change, state change, transformation"
  },
  {
    "question": "酒肴",
    "answer": "しゅこう,さけさかな",
    "meaning": "food and (alcoholic) drinks, food eaten with an alcoholic drink, accompaniment to a drink"
  },
  {
    "question": "交換留学",
    "answer": "こうかんりゅうがく",
    "meaning": "(student) exchange, study abroad"
  },
  {
    "question": "帰京",
    "answer": "ききょう",
    "meaning": "returning to (one's home in) Tokyo, returning to (one's home in) the capital"
  },
  {
    "question": "慶応",
    "answer": "けいおう",
    "meaning": "Keiō era (1865.4.7-1868.9.8)"
  },
  {
    "question": "流量",
    "answer": "りゅうりょう",
    "meaning": "flow rate (esp. water or electricity), quantity of flow, capacity (of output or throughput per unit"
  },
  {
    "question": "前書き",
    "answer": "まえがき",
    "meaning": "preface, foreword, preamble"
  },
  {
    "question": "好材料",
    "answer": "こうざいりょう",
    "meaning": "good material, valuable data, positive factor (for the stock market), good news"
  },
  {
    "question": "亀甲",
    "answer": "きっこう,きこう",
    "meaning": "tortoise shell"
  },
  {
    "question": "満座",
    "answer": "まんざ",
    "meaning": "the whole assembly, the full house, whole group, everyone"
  },
  {
    "question": "鈍間",
    "answer": "のろま",
    "meaning": "blockhead, dunce, dimwit, dolt, slowcoach, slowpoke"
  },
  {
    "question": "箱買い",
    "answer": "はこがい",
    "meaning": "buying by the box"
  },
  {
    "question": "道具立て",
    "answer": "どうぐだて",
    "meaning": "preparation of tools"
  },
  {
    "question": "向精神薬",
    "answer": "こうせいしんやく",
    "meaning": "psychotropic drug"
  },
  {
    "question": "足搔き",
    "answer": "あがき",
    "meaning": "struggling, pawing (e.g. horses' hooves)"
  },
  {
    "question": "甘えっ子",
    "answer": "あまえっこ",
    "meaning": "spoilt child"
  },
  {
    "question": "均質",
    "answer": "きんしつ",
    "meaning": "homogeneous, homogeneity"
  },
  {
    "question": "台尻",
    "answer": "だいじり",
    "meaning": "butt of a gun"
  },
  {
    "question": "湯量",
    "answer": "ゆりょう",
    "meaning": "quantity of hot spring water"
  },
  {
    "question": "五月晴れ",
    "answer": "さつきばれ",
    "meaning": "fine weather during the rainy season"
  },
  {
    "question": "免停",
    "answer": "めんてい",
    "meaning": "driving license suspension"
  },
  {
    "question": "伺候",
    "answer": "しこう",
    "meaning": "waiting upon (someone)"
  },
  {
    "question": "古馴染み",
    "answer": "ふるなじみ",
    "meaning": "old friend"
  },
  {
    "question": "創造的",
    "answer": "そうぞうてき",
    "meaning": "creative"
  },
  {
    "question": "糸屑",
    "answer": "いとくず",
    "meaning": "lint (as in a clothes dryer or a pocket), waste thread, fibers, such as might wrap around the gears"
  },
  {
    "question": "自然石",
    "answer": "しぜんせき,じねんせき",
    "meaning": "fieldstone"
  },
  {
    "question": "姿焼き",
    "answer": "すがたやき",
    "meaning": "seafood cooked whole so that it retains its original form"
  },
  {
    "question": "山風",
    "answer": "さんぷう,やまかぜ",
    "meaning": "mountain wind"
  },
  {
    "question": "備忘録",
    "answer": "びぼうろく",
    "meaning": "notebook, memorandum, commonplace book"
  },
  {
    "question": "日払い",
    "answer": "ひばらい",
    "meaning": "daily wages, payment by the day"
  },
  {
    "question": "天然ガス",
    "answer": "てんねんガス",
    "meaning": "natural gas"
  },
  {
    "question": "実効",
    "answer": "じっこう",
    "meaning": "practical effect, efficacy, efficiency"
  },
  {
    "question": "半ドン",
    "answer": "はんドン",
    "meaning": "half-holiday, sixth round (in a game of 12 rounds)"
  },
  {
    "question": "極め付き",
    "answer": "きわめつき",
    "meaning": "certified (as genuine, valuable, etc.), guaranteed (article), of established reputation, acknowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "変型",
    "answer": "へんけい",
    "meaning": "variety, variation"
  },
  {
    "question": "紅顔",
    "answer": "こうがん",
    "meaning": "rosy cheeks"
  },
  {
    "question": "同時通訳",
    "answer": "どうじつうやく",
    "meaning": "simultaneous interpretation, simultaneous interpreting"
  },
  {
    "question": "巧む",
    "answer": "たくむ",
    "meaning": "to devise, to plot, to plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "切片",
    "answer": "せっぺん",
    "meaning": "segment, slice, section, fragment, intercept"
  },
  {
    "question": "睡眠障害",
    "answer": "すいみんしょうがい",
    "meaning": "sleep disorder"
  },
  {
    "question": "悴む",
    "answer": "かじかむ",
    "meaning": "to grow numb with cold"
  },
  {
    "question": "混交",
    "answer": "こんこう",
    "meaning": "mixture, intermixture, mixing up, jumbling together, contamination, creation of unorthodox words or"
  },
  {
    "question": "朱肉",
    "answer": "しゅにく",
    "meaning": "thick red ink (used for signature seals), red ink pad, vermillion ink, cinnabar ink"
  },
  {
    "question": "父の日",
    "answer": "ちちのひ",
    "meaning": "Father's Day (3rd Sunday of June)"
  },
  {
    "question": "高山病",
    "answer": "こうざんびょう",
    "meaning": "altitude sickness, mountain sickness"
  },
  {
    "question": "饗する",
    "answer": "きょうする",
    "meaning": "to treat, to feast, to provide dinner for"
  },
  {
    "question": "音節",
    "answer": "おんせつ",
    "meaning": "syllable"
  },
  {
    "question": "給餌",
    "answer": "きゅうじ",
    "meaning": "feeding (an animal)"
  },
  {
    "question": "猛襲",
    "answer": "もうしゅう",
    "meaning": "fierce attack, furious attack"
  },
  {
    "question": "多角形",
    "answer": "たかくけい,たかっけい",
    "meaning": "polygon"
  },
  {
    "question": "腹時計",
    "answer": "はらどけい",
    "meaning": "one's internal clock"
  },
  {
    "question": "明け渡し",
    "answer": "あけわたし",
    "meaning": "evacuation, surrender"
  },
  {
    "question": "豊乳",
    "answer": "ほうにゅう",
    "meaning": "full breasts, large breasts, ample breasts, breast augmentation"
  },
  {
    "question": "体制側",
    "answer": "たいせいがわ",
    "meaning": "the establishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "自助努力",
    "answer": "じじょどりょく",
    "meaning": "self-help efforts, independent efforts, self-supporting endeavor"
  },
  {
    "question": "塗り絵",
    "answer": "ぬりえ",
    "meaning": "picture for coloring in (colouring)"
  },
  {
    "question": "古美術",
    "answer": "こびじゅつ",
    "meaning": "antiques, old works of art"
  },
  {
    "question": "公益",
    "answer": "こうえき",
    "meaning": "public interest, public benefit, public good"
  },
  {
    "question": "三角関数",
    "answer": "さんかくかんすう",
    "meaning": "trigonometric function"
  },
  {
    "question": "旧名",
    "answer": "きゅうめい",
    "meaning": "former name, maiden name"
  },
  {
    "question": "夢か現か",
    "answer": "ゆめかうつつか",
    "meaning": "feeling as if in a dream"
  },
  {
    "question": "縫い取る",
    "answer": "ぬいとる",
    "meaning": "to embroider"
  },
  {
    "question": "独身生活",
    "answer": "どくしんせいかつ",
    "meaning": "bachelor's life, life of a bachelor"
  },
  {
    "question": "完コピ",
    "answer": "かんコピ",
    "meaning": "perfect imitation (of a song, dance routine, etc., usu. by an amateur)"
  },
  {
    "question": "剃髪",
    "answer": "ていはつ",
    "meaning": "tonsure, cutting off the hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会正義",
    "answer": "しゃかいせいぎ",
    "meaning": "social justice"
  },
  {
    "question": "月見酒",
    "answer": "つきみざけ",
    "meaning": "sake for moon viewing parties"
  },
  {
    "question": "張り子",
    "answer": "はりこ",
    "meaning": "papier mâché, player who is not a dealer (in cards)"
  },
  {
    "question": "顰める",
    "answer": "しかめる,ひそめる",
    "meaning": "to pull a wry face, to screw one's face up, to pucker one's face, to scowl, to grimace, to frown, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶目",
    "answer": "ちゃめ",
    "meaning": "playful, mischievous, joker, prankster, scamp, rascal, brown eyes"
  },
  {
    "question": "プチ家出",
    "answer": "プチいえで",
    "meaning": "running away from home for a very short time"
  },
  {
    "question": "異説",
    "answer": "いせつ",
    "meaning": "different view, alternative theory, dissenting view"
  },
  {
    "question": "実物大",
    "answer": "じつぶつだい",
    "meaning": "actual size"
  },
  {
    "question": "人待ち顔",
    "answer": "ひとまちがお",
    "meaning": "looking like one is waiting for someone"
  },
  {
    "question": "公式的",
    "answer": "こうしきてき",
    "meaning": "formulaic, official"
  },
  {
    "question": "遊び友達",
    "answer": "あそびともだち",
    "meaning": "playmate, companion, friend to play with"
  },
  {
    "question": "最下",
    "answer": "さいか",
    "meaning": "the lowest, the worst"
  },
  {
    "question": "綻ばす",
    "answer": "ほころばす",
    "meaning": "to rip up (a seam), to burst, to tear, to break out (e.g. into a smile)"
  },
  {
    "question": "述語",
    "answer": "じゅつご",
    "meaning": "predicate"
  },
  {
    "question": "縮み",
    "answer": "ちぢみ",
    "meaning": "shrinkage, cotton crepe"
  },
  {
    "question": "慰留",
    "answer": "いりゅう",
    "meaning": "dissuasion (from resigning, leaving, etc.), persuading (to stay)"
  },
  {
    "question": "計り",
    "answer": "はかり",
    "meaning": "measurements, weighing"
  },
  {
    "question": "堅め",
    "answer": "かため",
    "meaning": "hardness, firmness"
  },
  {
    "question": "涙脆い",
    "answer": "なみだもろい",
    "meaning": "easily moved to tears, given to weeping, lachrymose"
  },
  {
    "question": "三行半",
    "answer": "さんぎょうはん,みくだりはん",
    "meaning": "three and a half lines, letter of divorce"
  },
  {
    "question": "事足る",
    "answer": "ことたる",
    "meaning": "to suffice, to serve the purpose, to be satisfied"
  },
  {
    "question": "実社会",
    "answer": "じっしゃかい",
    "meaning": "real world, society"
  },
  {
    "question": "耐用年数",
    "answer": "たいようねんすう",
    "meaning": "(machine's) service life"
  },
  {
    "question": "年甲斐",
    "answer": "としがい",
    "meaning": "one's age"
  },
  {
    "question": "媚び諂う",
    "answer": "こびへつらう",
    "meaning": "to toady, to be obsequious"
  },
  {
    "question": "差支え",
    "answer": "さしつかえ",
    "meaning": "hindrance, impediment"
  },
  {
    "question": "右寄り",
    "answer": "みぎより",
    "meaning": "right of center (politically), right-leaning, tending to the right"
  },
  {
    "question": "未熟児",
    "answer": "みじゅくじ",
    "meaning": "premature baby"
  },
  {
    "question": "年恰好",
    "answer": "としかっこう",
    "meaning": "apparent age (of someone), rough age"
  },
  {
    "question": "里桜",
    "answer": "さとざくら",
    "meaning": "any oriental variety of cherry tree descended from the Oshima cherry"
  },
  {
    "question": "麗質",
    "answer": "れいしつ",
    "meaning": "genius, beauty, charm"
  },
  {
    "question": "帙",
    "answer": "ちつ",
    "meaning": "protective covering for a book (often in the form of a folding case with clasps), counter for book c"
  },
  {
    "question": "贋造",
    "answer": "がんぞう",
    "meaning": "counterfeiting, forgery, fabrication"
  },
  {
    "question": "梁山泊",
    "answer": "りょうざんぱく",
    "meaning": "place of assemblage for the bold and ambitious"
  },
  {
    "question": "石筆",
    "answer": "せきひつ",
    "meaning": "slate pencil"
  },
  {
    "question": "霊域",
    "answer": "れいいき",
    "meaning": "sacred ground, sacred precincts"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿老",
    "answer": "しゅくろう",
    "meaning": "old men, elders, seniors, veterans"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛染",
    "answer": "あいぜん",
    "meaning": "being drawn to something one loves, amorous passion, Ragaraja (esoteric school deity of love)"
  },
  {
    "question": "雪豹",
    "answer": "ゆきひょう",
    "meaning": "snow leopard (Panthera uncia), ounce"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄子",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄ちゃん",
    "answer": "てっちゃん",
    "meaning": "trainspotter, railway enthusiast, railfan"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛍石",
    "answer": "ほたるいし,けいせき",
    "meaning": "fluorite, fluorspar"
  },
  {
    "question": "遊民",
    "answer": "ゆうみん",
    "meaning": "idler, the unemployed"
  },
  {
    "question": "魔羅",
    "answer": "まら",
    "meaning": "obstacle to Buddhist practice, penis"
  },
  {
    "question": "遡航",
    "answer": "そこう",
    "meaning": "going upstream, sailing against the current"
  },
  {
    "question": "憩",
    "answer": "いこい",
    "meaning": "rest, relaxation"
  },
  {
    "question": "奥山",
    "answer": "おくやま",
    "meaning": "remote mountain, mountain recesses"
  },
  {
    "question": "地衣類",
    "answer": "ちいるい",
    "meaning": "lichens"
  },
  {
    "question": "風来",
    "answer": "ふうらい",
    "meaning": "frivolity, unpredictability, erraticism, first-time guest in a red-light district"
  },
  {
    "question": "若狭",
    "answer": "わかさ",
    "meaning": "Wakasa (former province located in the south of present-day Fukui Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "美事",
    "answer": "みごと",
    "meaning": "splendid, magnificent, excellent, fine, superb, beautiful, admirable, utter (esp. defeat), total, co"
  },
  {
    "question": "逆子",
    "answer": "さかご",
    "meaning": "breech presentation (feet or buttocks-first birth), breech delivery, breech birth"
  },
  {
    "question": "対日",
    "answer": "たいにち",
    "meaning": "toward Japan, with Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "糧秣",
    "answer": "りょうまつ",
    "meaning": "military provisions and cavalry horse fodder"
  },
  {
    "question": "山塊",
    "answer": "さんかい",
    "meaning": "mountain mass, massif"
  },
  {
    "question": "広東語",
    "answer": "カントンご",
    "meaning": "Cantonese (language)"
  },
  {
    "question": "図録",
    "answer": "ずろく",
    "meaning": "illustrated book, picture book"
  },
  {
    "question": "阿波踊り",
    "answer": "あわおどり",
    "meaning": "Awa Odori Festival (Tokushima)"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝間",
    "answer": "ねま",
    "meaning": "bedroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "突堤",
    "answer": "とってい",
    "meaning": "breakwater"
  },
  {
    "question": "海賊版",
    "answer": "かいぞくばん",
    "meaning": "pirated edition, pirated version, bootleg copy"
  },
  {
    "question": "迎賓",
    "answer": "げいひん",
    "meaning": "welcoming honored guests (esp. from overseas)"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀杯",
    "answer": "ぎんぱい",
    "meaning": "silver cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "帥",
    "answer": "そち,そつ",
    "meaning": "director of the Dazaifu"
  },
  {
    "question": "氷晶",
    "answer": "ひょうしょう",
    "meaning": "ice crystals"
  },
  {
    "question": "雄雄しい",
    "answer": "おおしい",
    "meaning": "manly, brave, heroic"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒石",
    "answer": "くろいし",
    "meaning": "black stone, black (go pieces)"
  },
  {
    "question": "外事",
    "answer": "がいじ",
    "meaning": "foreign affairs"
  },
  {
    "question": "博物",
    "answer": "はくぶつ",
    "meaning": "natural history, wide learning, broad area of learning"
  },
  {
    "question": "仮免許",
    "answer": "かりめんきょ",
    "meaning": "temporary license, temporary licence"
  },
  {
    "question": "腹膜",
    "answer": "ふくまく",
    "meaning": "peritoneum"
  },
  {
    "question": "密貿易",
    "answer": "みつぼうえき",
    "meaning": "smuggling"
  },
  {
    "question": "シャム猫",
    "answer": "シャムねこ",
    "meaning": "Siamese cat"
  },
  {
    "question": "法理",
    "answer": "ほうり",
    "meaning": "legal principle"
  },
  {
    "question": "光学系",
    "answer": "こうがくけい",
    "meaning": "optical system"
  },
  {
    "question": "静止衛星",
    "answer": "せいしえいせい",
    "meaning": "satellite in geosynchronous orbit"
  },
  {
    "question": "内務大臣",
    "answer": "ないむだいじん",
    "meaning": "prewar Home Minister"
  },
  {
    "question": "回転木馬",
    "answer": "かいてんもくば",
    "meaning": "merry-go-round, carousel"
  },
  {
    "question": "紐パン",
    "answer": "ひもパン",
    "meaning": "string bikini, g-string, thong"
  },
  {
    "question": "母子手帳",
    "answer": "ぼしてちょう",
    "meaning": "maternity health record book, mother and child health notebook"
  },
  {
    "question": "艫",
    "answer": "とも,ろ",
    "meaning": "stern, stern (of a ship), bow (of a ship), prow"
  },
  {
    "question": "枢要",
    "answer": "すうよう",
    "meaning": "(most) important, principal, pivotal, key, cardinal"
  },
  {
    "question": "反射率",
    "answer": "はんしゃりつ",
    "meaning": "reflectance"
  },
  {
    "question": "有限会社",
    "answer": "ゆうげんがいしゃ",
    "meaning": "limited company, company structure for small businesses, abolished in 2006 (YK)"
  },
  {
    "question": "白蟻",
    "answer": "しろあり",
    "meaning": "termite, white ant"
  },
  {
    "question": "薫風",
    "answer": "くんぷう",
    "meaning": "balmy breeze, summer breeze"
  },
  {
    "question": "予行",
    "answer": "よこう",
    "meaning": "rehearsal"
  },
  {
    "question": "運ゲー",
    "answer": "うんゲー",
    "meaning": "game of chance"
  },
  {
    "question": "業病",
    "answer": "ごうびょう",
    "meaning": "incurable disease"
  },
  {
    "question": "増派",
    "answer": "ぞうは",
    "meaning": "reinforcements"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼き場",
    "answer": "やきば",
    "meaning": "crematory, place where things are burned"
  },
  {
    "question": "埋伏",
    "answer": "まいふく",
    "meaning": "(dental) impaction"
  },
  {
    "question": "際物",
    "answer": "きわもの",
    "meaning": "seasonal goods, seasonal items, item of short-lived interest, faddish product, ephemeral work, topic"
  },
  {
    "question": "哀訴",
    "answer": "あいそ",
    "meaning": "appeal, complaint"
  },
  {
    "question": "撤兵",
    "answer": "てっぺい",
    "meaning": "withdrawal of troops"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽油",
    "answer": "けいゆ",
    "meaning": "diesel oil, gas oil, light oil"
  },
  {
    "question": "怪光",
    "answer": "かいこう",
    "meaning": "mysterious light"
  },
  {
    "question": "五穀",
    "answer": "ごこく",
    "meaning": "the five grains (wheat, rice, beans, millet (awa and kibi))"
  },
  {
    "question": "映画祭",
    "answer": "えいがさい",
    "meaning": "film festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "確定申告",
    "answer": "かくていしんこく",
    "meaning": "final income tax return, final declaration, final report"
  },
  {
    "question": "話者",
    "answer": "わしゃ",
    "meaning": "speaker, narrator"
  },
  {
    "question": "無限軌道",
    "answer": "むげんきどう",
    "meaning": "continuous track, caterpillar track"
  },
  {
    "question": "無事故",
    "answer": "むじこ",
    "meaning": "without accident"
  },
  {
    "question": "高利",
    "answer": "こうり",
    "meaning": "high interest rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "見舞",
    "answer": "みまい",
    "meaning": "visiting ill or distressed people, writing get-well letters, get-well gifts, get-well letters, expre"
  },
  {
    "question": "錯",
    "answer": "こすり",
    "meaning": "rubbing, scrubbing, scraping"
  },
  {
    "question": "夏中",
    "answer": "げちゅう,なつじゅう,なつなか",
    "meaning": "period during which monks may go into a summer retreat, whole summer, summer long, midsummer, height"
  },
  {
    "question": "牛飼い",
    "answer": "うしかい",
    "meaning": "cattleman, raising cattle"
  },
  {
    "question": "互助会",
    "answer": "ごじょかい",
    "meaning": "benefit society"
  },
  {
    "question": "仮装行列",
    "answer": "かそうぎょうれつ",
    "meaning": "costume parade"
  },
  {
    "question": "不労所得",
    "answer": "ふろうしょとく",
    "meaning": "unearned income"
  },
  {
    "question": "腹膜炎",
    "answer": "ふくまくえん",
    "meaning": "peritonitis"
  },
  {
    "question": "和姦",
    "answer": "わかん",
    "meaning": "(consensual) sexual intercourse"
  },
  {
    "question": "経済成長",
    "answer": "けいざいせいちょう",
    "meaning": "economic growth"
  },
  {
    "question": "群雲",
    "answer": "むらくも",
    "meaning": "gathering clouds, group of clouds"
  },
  {
    "question": "表口",
    "answer": "おもてぐち",
    "meaning": "front door"
  },
  {
    "question": "地歩",
    "answer": "ちほ",
    "meaning": "one's stand, foothold, position"
  },
  {
    "question": "謝絶",
    "answer": "しゃぜつ",
    "meaning": "refusal"
  },
  {
    "question": "下取り",
    "answer": "したどり",
    "meaning": "trade in, part exchange"
  },
  {
    "question": "耳垢",
    "answer": "みみあか,じこう",
    "meaning": "earwax, cerumen"
  },
  {
    "question": "合いの子",
    "answer": "あいのこ",
    "meaning": "person of mixed parentage, crossbreed, Eurasian, mulatto, hybrid"
  },
  {
    "question": "畏縮",
    "answer": "いしゅく",
    "meaning": "wincing, cowering, shrinking, flinching, recoiling"
  },
  {
    "question": "華僑",
    "answer": "かきょう",
    "meaning": "overseas Chinese"
  },
  {
    "question": "等身",
    "answer": "とうしん",
    "meaning": "body proportions"
  },
  {
    "question": "無認可",
    "answer": "むにんか",
    "meaning": "unapproved, lack of approval"
  },
  {
    "question": "大震災",
    "answer": "だいしんさい",
    "meaning": "great earthquake (disaster), Great Kanto earthquake of 1923"
  },
  {
    "question": "俗悪",
    "answer": "ぞくあく",
    "meaning": "worldliness, vulgarity, coarseness"
  },
  {
    "question": "来し方",
    "answer": "きしかた,こしかた",
    "meaning": "the past"
  },
  {
    "question": "摩滅",
    "answer": "まめつ",
    "meaning": "defacement, abrasion, wear and tear, crushing of a nerve"
  },
  {
    "question": "水溶液",
    "answer": "すいようえき",
    "meaning": "(translucent) aqueous solution"
  },
  {
    "question": "象嵌",
    "answer": "ぞうがん",
    "meaning": "inlay (work), inlaying"
  },
  {
    "question": "脳出血",
    "answer": "のうしゅっけつ",
    "meaning": "cerebral hemorrhage, cerebral haemorrhage"
  },
  {
    "question": "欧風",
    "answer": "おうふう",
    "meaning": "European style, Occidental"
  },
  {
    "question": "万馬券",
    "answer": "まんばけん",
    "meaning": "betting ticket with a payout of at least 100 times (horse racing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "芝居小屋",
    "answer": "しばいごや",
    "meaning": "playhouse, theatre, theater"
  },
  {
    "question": "万国",
    "answer": "ばんこく",
    "meaning": "all countries, the whole world, universal, all nations"
  },
  {
    "question": "着岸",
    "answer": "ちゃくがん",
    "meaning": "reaching the shore, docking a boat"
  },
  {
    "question": "周縁",
    "answer": "しゅうえん",
    "meaning": "fringe, rim, periphery, borders, outskirts"
  },
  {
    "question": "溶岩流",
    "answer": "ようがんりゅう",
    "meaning": "lava flow"
  },
  {
    "question": "想像妊娠",
    "answer": "そうぞうにんしん",
    "meaning": "false pregnancy, pseudocyesis"
  },
  {
    "question": "積立金",
    "answer": "つみたてきん",
    "meaning": "reserve (fund), deposit"
  },
  {
    "question": "人馬一体",
    "answer": "じんばいったい",
    "meaning": "unity of rider and horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "緊急逮捕",
    "answer": "きんきゅうたいほ",
    "meaning": "arrest without warrant"
  },
  {
    "question": "始皇帝",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "間遠",
    "answer": "まどお",
    "meaning": "at long distance, in long intervals"
  },
  {
    "question": "揺り返し",
    "answer": "ゆりかえし",
    "meaning": "aftershock, afterquake"
  },
  {
    "question": "吹き流し",
    "answer": "ふきながし",
    "meaning": "streamer, pennant, windsock"
  },
  {
    "question": "初売り",
    "answer": "はつうり",
    "meaning": "first business conducted by retailers in the New Year"
  },
  {
    "question": "丼物",
    "answer": "どんぶりもの,どんもの",
    "meaning": "bowl of rice with food on top"
  },
  {
    "question": "無縁仏",
    "answer": "むえんぼとけ",
    "meaning": "person (or their spirit) who died with no one to tend their grave"
  },
  {
    "question": "弁済",
    "answer": "べんさい",
    "meaning": "repayment, settlement (of a debt), paying off, reimbursement (of expenses)"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝ち馬",
    "answer": "かちうま",
    "meaning": "winning horse, winner"
  },
  {
    "question": "地動説",
    "answer": "ちどうせつ",
    "meaning": "heliocentric theory, Copernican theory, heliocentrism, heliocentricism"
  },
  {
    "question": "鬨",
    "answer": "とき",
    "meaning": "battle cry, war cry"
  },
  {
    "question": "突き抜く",
    "answer": "つきぬく",
    "meaning": "to pierce, to shoot through, to penetrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "白紙撤回",
    "answer": "はくしてっかい",
    "meaning": "complete revocation, total retraction"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤鼻",
    "answer": "あかはな",
    "meaning": "red nose"
  },
  {
    "question": "省内",
    "answer": "しょうない",
    "meaning": "in the ministry, in the department"
  },
  {
    "question": "暴政",
    "answer": "ぼうせい",
    "meaning": "tyranny"
  },
  {
    "question": "謝する",
    "answer": "しゃする",
    "meaning": "to thank, to apologize, to apologise, to say farewell, to retreat, to retire, to refuse, to pay back"
  },
  {
    "question": "段々畑",
    "answer": "だんだんばたけ",
    "meaning": "terraced fields, terraced farm"
  },
  {
    "question": "課外",
    "answer": "かがい",
    "meaning": "extracurricular"
  },
  {
    "question": "七つの海",
    "answer": "ななつのうみ",
    "meaning": "the seven seas"
  },
  {
    "question": "真西",
    "answer": "まにし",
    "meaning": "due west"
  },
  {
    "question": "品不足",
    "answer": "しなぶそく",
    "meaning": "shortage of stock, scarcity of goods"
  },
  {
    "question": "麦芽",
    "answer": "ばくが",
    "meaning": "malt"
  },
  {
    "question": "地代",
    "answer": "ちだい,じだい",
    "meaning": "land rent"
  },
  {
    "question": "伝法",
    "answer": "でんぼう,でんぽう",
    "meaning": "teaching Buddhism, rough person, bullying, ostentatious bravado"
  },
  {
    "question": "金蔓",
    "answer": "かねづる",
    "meaning": "source of revenue, financial supporter"
  },
  {
    "question": "成り切る",
    "answer": "なりきる",
    "meaning": "to turn completely into, to become completely"
  },
  {
    "question": "本籍",
    "answer": "ほんせき",
    "meaning": "one's registered domicile (as recorded in the family register), one's legal domicile (as opposed to"
  },
  {
    "question": "小売り",
    "answer": "こうり",
    "meaning": "retail"
  },
  {
    "question": "幕の内",
    "answer": "まくのうち",
    "meaning": "box lunch (containing rice and 10-15 small portions of fish, meat, and vegetables), highest-ranking"
  },
  {
    "question": "過重",
    "answer": "かじゅう",
    "meaning": "overweight, too heavy (burden, workload, etc.), too severe"
  },
  {
    "question": "升目",
    "answer": "ますめ",
    "meaning": "measure, square (e.g. of graph paper or Japanese manuscript paper), box (e.g. on a form)"
  },
  {
    "question": "事業家",
    "answer": "じぎょうか",
    "meaning": "enterprising man, businessman, industrialist"
  },
  {
    "question": "小論文",
    "answer": "しょうろんぶん",
    "meaning": "short essay, pamphlet, tract"
  },
  {
    "question": "腐らす",
    "answer": "くさらす",
    "meaning": "to let spoil, to leave to rot, to cause to rot, to corrode, to discourage, to dishearten"
  },
  {
    "question": "機械文明",
    "answer": "きかいぶんめい",
    "meaning": "technical civilization, technical civilisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "朝会",
    "answer": "ちょうかい,あさかい",
    "meaning": "morning assembly, morning gathering, morning meeting, early morning tea ceremony (on a summer day)"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨避け",
    "answer": "あまよけ",
    "meaning": "tarpaulin, shelter from rain, covering against rain"
  },
  {
    "question": "糖尿",
    "answer": "とうにょう",
    "meaning": "glycosuria, glucosuria, urine sugar"
  },
  {
    "question": "自縄自縛",
    "answer": "じじょうじばく",
    "meaning": "being caught in one's own trap, being hoisted by one's own petard"
  },
  {
    "question": "古物",
    "answer": "こぶつ,ふるもの",
    "meaning": "antique, old article, secondhand goods"
  },
  {
    "question": "捉まえる",
    "answer": "つかまえる",
    "meaning": "to grab, to clutch, to grasp, to seize, to hold on to, to catch hold of (someone), to stop (e.g. a s"
  },
  {
    "question": "導入部",
    "answer": "どうにゅうぶ",
    "meaning": "introduction"
  },
  {
    "question": "詣で",
    "answer": "もうで",
    "meaning": "pilgrimage, visit"
  },
  {
    "question": "反旗",
    "answer": "はんき",
    "meaning": "standard of revolt, banner of rebellion"
  },
  {
    "question": "愚図愚図",
    "answer": "ぐずぐず",
    "meaning": "slowly, tardily, dawdling, lingering, hesitantly, complaining, grumbling, unsettled (e.g. weather),"
  },
  {
    "question": "不味",
    "answer": "ふみ",
    "meaning": "distaste, unsavoriness, unsavouriness"
  },
  {
    "question": "最安値",
    "answer": "さいやすね",
    "meaning": "all-time low (price, in trading), record low, new low"
  },
  {
    "question": "道楽者",
    "answer": "どうらくもの",
    "meaning": "libertine, playboy, rake, debauchee, fast liver, lazy person"
  },
  {
    "question": "甘味料",
    "answer": "かんみりょう",
    "meaning": "sweetener (sugar, honey, saccharin, maltose, etc.), sweetening agent, sweetening"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り口",
    "answer": "とりくち",
    "meaning": "technique, techniques"
  },
  {
    "question": "緑一色",
    "answer": "リューイーソー",
    "meaning": "all green, winning hand consisting only of exclusively green tiles (green dragons and suited bamboo"
  },
  {
    "question": "狐色",
    "answer": "きつねいろ",
    "meaning": "light brown, golden brown"
  },
  {
    "question": "素人臭い",
    "answer": "しろうとくさい",
    "meaning": "amateurish"
  },
  {
    "question": "困憊",
    "answer": "こんぱい",
    "meaning": "exhaustion, fatigue"
  },
  {
    "question": "選り抜き",
    "answer": "よりぬき,えりぬき",
    "meaning": "the very best, elite"
  },
  {
    "question": "確変",
    "answer": "かくへん",
    "meaning": "stochastic variable, random variable"
  },
  {
    "question": "情報検索",
    "answer": "じょうほうけんさく",
    "meaning": "information retrieval"
  },
  {
    "question": "純情可憐",
    "answer": "じゅんじょうかれん",
    "meaning": "pure of heart and pretty"
  },
  {
    "question": "先端技術",
    "answer": "せんたんぎじゅつ",
    "meaning": "high-technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "腫物",
    "answer": "しゅもつ,はれもの",
    "meaning": "tumor, tumour, swelling, boil, abscess"
  },
  {
    "question": "学的",
    "answer": "がくてき",
    "meaning": "scholarly, scholastic, academic"
  },
  {
    "question": "及第",
    "answer": "きゅうだい",
    "meaning": "passing (an examination), making the grade"
  },
  {
    "question": "月初め",
    "answer": "つきはじめ",
    "meaning": "beginning of month"
  },
  {
    "question": "四辺",
    "answer": "しへん",
    "meaning": "neighbourhood, neighborhood, vicinity, all sides, frontiers (of a country), four sides (of a shape)"
  },
  {
    "question": "物自体",
    "answer": "ものじたい",
    "meaning": "Ding an sich, thing in itself"
  },
  {
    "question": "湯通し",
    "answer": "ゆどおし",
    "meaning": "soaking fabric in lukewarm water (to soften and remove starch), desizing, moistening with steam, bla"
  },
  {
    "question": "一巻き",
    "answer": "ひとまき",
    "meaning": "one roll, one book, one volume, rolling once, wrapping once around"
  },
  {
    "question": "申し出で",
    "answer": "もうしいで",
    "meaning": "proposal, request, claim, report, notice, offer"
  },
  {
    "question": "短艇",
    "answer": "たんてい",
    "meaning": "(small) boat"
  },
  {
    "question": "夏鳥",
    "answer": "なつどり",
    "meaning": "a bird of summer"
  },
  {
    "question": "工部",
    "answer": "こうぶ",
    "meaning": "Ministry of Works (Tang-dynasty China)"
  },
  {
    "question": "守護代",
    "answer": "しゅごだい",
    "meaning": "acting shugo (Kamakura or Muromachi period military governor)"
  },
  {
    "question": "邯鄲の夢",
    "answer": "かんたんのゆめ",
    "meaning": "vain dream of wealth and splendour (splendor)"
  },
  {
    "question": "高徳",
    "answer": "こうとく",
    "meaning": "eminent virtue"
  },
  {
    "question": "興行師",
    "answer": "こうぎょうし",
    "meaning": "showman, show manager"
  },
  {
    "question": "洛中",
    "answer": "らくちゅう",
    "meaning": "inside the capital"
  },
  {
    "question": "国民党",
    "answer": "こくみんとう",
    "meaning": "Constitutional Nationalist Party (1910-1922), Guomindang (Chinese Nationalist Party), Kuomintang"
  },
  {
    "question": "宣下",
    "answer": "せんげ",
    "meaning": "imperial proclamation"
  },
  {
    "question": "肉柱",
    "answer": "にくちゅう",
    "meaning": "adductor muscle (of a bivalve)"
  },
  {
    "question": "基本法",
    "answer": "きほんほう",
    "meaning": "fundamental law, basic (organic) law"
  },
  {
    "question": "死毒",
    "answer": "しどく",
    "meaning": "ptomaine poisoning"
  },
  {
    "question": "血球",
    "answer": "けっきゅう",
    "meaning": "blood cell"
  },
  {
    "question": "雪洞",
    "answer": "せつどう,ぼんぼり",
    "meaning": "snow cave, paper-covered lamp or lantern"
  },
  {
    "question": "中性子星",
    "answer": "ちゅうせいしせい",
    "meaning": "neutron star"
  },
  {
    "question": "通信員",
    "answer": "つうしんいん",
    "meaning": "correspondent, reporter"
  },
  {
    "question": "上総",
    "answer": "かずさ",
    "meaning": "Kazusa (former province located in the central part of present-day Chiba Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "血統主義",
    "answer": "けっとうしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "jus sanguinis, principle that citizenship is determined by that of one's parents"
  },
  {
    "question": "祭器",
    "answer": "さいき",
    "meaning": "equipment used in rituals"
  },
  {
    "question": "年代記",
    "answer": "ねんだいき",
    "meaning": "annals, chronicle, chronology"
  },
  {
    "question": "火箭",
    "answer": "かせん,ひや",
    "meaning": "fire arrow, incendiary arrow, rocket"
  },
  {
    "question": "画く",
    "answer": "えがく,かく",
    "meaning": "to draw, to paint, to sketch, to depict, to describe, to picture in one's mind, to imagine, to form"
  },
  {
    "question": "工科",
    "answer": "こうか",
    "meaning": "engineering course"
  },
  {
    "question": "発議",
    "answer": "はつぎ,ほつぎ",
    "meaning": "proposal, suggestion, motion, initiative"
  },
  {
    "question": "超電導",
    "answer": "ちょうでんどう",
    "meaning": "superconductivity, super-conductivity"
  },
  {
    "question": "魔障",
    "answer": "ましょう",
    "meaning": "obstacle to Buddhist practice"
  },
  {
    "question": "釜飯",
    "answer": "かまめし",
    "meaning": "rice, meat and vegetable dish served in a small pot"
  },
  {
    "question": "讃岐",
    "answer": "さぬき",
    "meaning": "Sanuki (former province located in present-day Kagawa Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "虚け",
    "answer": "うつけ",
    "meaning": "absentmindedness, dreaminess, simpleton, fool"
  },
  {
    "question": "民主党",
    "answer": "みんしゅとう",
    "meaning": "Democratic Party (esp. DPJ or US Democratic Party)"
  },
  {
    "question": "暴騰",
    "answer": "ぼうとう",
    "meaning": "sudden rise, sharp rise, boom, skyrocketing"
  },
  {
    "question": "見棄てる",
    "answer": "みすてる",
    "meaning": "to abandon, to fail, to desert, to forsake"
  },
  {
    "question": "陰翳",
    "answer": "いんえい",
    "meaning": "shadow, shade, shading, gloom, nuance, shades of meaning, subtleties"
  },
  {
    "question": "白石",
    "answer": "しろいし",
    "meaning": "white stone, white (go pieces)"
  },
  {
    "question": "戴天",
    "answer": "たいてん",
    "meaning": "one's earthly existence, living under heaven"
  },
  {
    "question": "御側",
    "answer": "おそば",
    "meaning": "near, close, beside, vicinity, proximity, besides, while, attendant, retainer, vassal"
  },
  {
    "question": "優艶",
    "answer": "ゆうえん",
    "meaning": "charming, fascinating, beautiful, elegant, graceful, sweet, delicate"
  },
  {
    "question": "裸形",
    "answer": "らぎょう",
    "meaning": "nakedness, naked body"
  },
  {
    "question": "総べる",
    "answer": "すべる",
    "meaning": "to rule over, to govern, to command, to control, to integrate, to consolidate, to unite, to incorpor"
  },
  {
    "question": "霙",
    "answer": "みぞれ",
    "meaning": "sleet, daikon shavings, grated daikon, shaved ice topped with honey"
  },
  {
    "question": "口金",
    "answer": "くちがね",
    "meaning": "(metal) cap, clasp, mouthpiece, socket (for light, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "水煮",
    "answer": "みずに",
    "meaning": "boil in water"
  },
  {
    "question": "三国同盟",
    "answer": "さんごくどうめい",
    "meaning": "triple alliance"
  },
  {
    "question": "謝肉祭",
    "answer": "しゃにくさい",
    "meaning": "carnival (festival held before Lent)"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄玉",
    "answer": "おうぎょく,こうぎょく",
    "meaning": "topaz"
  },
  {
    "question": "助成",
    "answer": "じょせい",
    "meaning": "assisting, assistance, fostering, aiding"
  },
  {
    "question": "通気孔",
    "answer": "つうきこう",
    "meaning": "vent, vent hole, air hole"
  },
  {
    "question": "内視鏡",
    "answer": "ないしきょう",
    "meaning": "endoscope"
  },
  {
    "question": "舞茸",
    "answer": "まいたけ",
    "meaning": "hen-of-the-woods (species of polypore mushroom, Grifola frondosa)"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛媛",
    "answer": "えひめ",
    "meaning": "Ehime (prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "繁々",
    "answer": "しげしげ",
    "meaning": "frequently, often, (staring) fixedly, narrowly, closely, steadily"
  },
  {
    "question": "横様",
    "answer": "よこざま,よこさま",
    "meaning": "wickedness, sideways, unreasonable"
  },
  {
    "question": "弁財天",
    "answer": "べんざいてん,べざいてん",
    "meaning": "Benzaiten, Saraswati, goddess of music, eloquence, also wealth and water"
  },
  {
    "question": "空豆",
    "answer": "そらまめ",
    "meaning": "broad bean (Vicia faba), horse bean, fava bean"
  },
  {
    "question": "豊後",
    "answer": "ぶんご",
    "meaning": "Bungo (former province located in present-day Ōita Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "陣羽織",
    "answer": "じんばおり",
    "meaning": "battle surcoat"
  },
  {
    "question": "七種",
    "answer": "ななくさ",
    "meaning": "the seven spring flowers, the seven fall flowers, the seven autumn flowers, the seventh of January,"
  },
  {
    "question": "陰々",
    "answer": "いんいん",
    "meaning": "dark and desolate, forlorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "剛勇",
    "answer": "ごうゆう",
    "meaning": "bravery, prowess"
  },
  {
    "question": "読点",
    "answer": "とうてん",
    "meaning": "comma"
  },
  {
    "question": "菓",
    "answer": "か",
    "meaning": "fruit, counter for fruit"
  },
  {
    "question": "山姥",
    "answer": "やまうば,やまんば",
    "meaning": "mountain witch, yamauba"
  },
  {
    "question": "観光都市",
    "answer": "かんこうとし",
    "meaning": "tourist city"
  },
  {
    "question": "埋設",
    "answer": "まいせつ",
    "meaning": "laying underground (e.g. cables), burying (e.g. pipe)"
  },
  {
    "question": "威名",
    "answer": "いめい",
    "meaning": "fame, prestige"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶筒",
    "answer": "ちゃづつ",
    "meaning": "tea caddy"
  },
  {
    "question": "食道楽",
    "answer": "しょくどうらく,くいどうらく",
    "meaning": "gourmand, epicure"
  },
  {
    "question": "詭道",
    "answer": "きどう",
    "meaning": "deceptive methods, questionable means"
  },
  {
    "question": "主文",
    "answer": "しゅぶん",
    "meaning": "the text, the main clause, the main part of a document"
  },
  {
    "question": "卑近",
    "answer": "ひきん",
    "meaning": "common, simple"
  },
  {
    "question": "国法",
    "answer": "こくほう",
    "meaning": "national law"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄せ鍋",
    "answer": "よせなべ",
    "meaning": "pot of chicken or seafood, and vegetables in a dashi broth, usu. cooked at the table (traditionally"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍事政権",
    "answer": "ぐんじせいけん",
    "meaning": "military regime"
  },
  {
    "question": "倒れ臥す",
    "answer": "たおれふす",
    "meaning": "to fall flat, to fall face down"
  },
  {
    "question": "急坂",
    "answer": "きゅうはん,きゅうざか",
    "meaning": "steep slope, steep gradient"
  },
  {
    "question": "帝国主義",
    "answer": "ていこくしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "imperialism"
  },
  {
    "question": "新語",
    "answer": "しんご",
    "meaning": "new word, neologism, word of recent origin, recent word, modern term"
  },
  {
    "question": "炭酸ガス",
    "answer": "たんさんガス",
    "meaning": "carbon dioxide (gas)"
  },
  {
    "question": "四半期",
    "answer": "しはんき",
    "meaning": "quarter (of a year)"
  },
  {
    "question": "浅黄",
    "answer": "あさぎ",
    "meaning": "light yellow, pale blue-green"
  },
  {
    "question": "君主制",
    "answer": "くんしゅせい",
    "meaning": "monarchy"
  },
  {
    "question": "艶麗",
    "answer": "えんれい",
    "meaning": "dazzling (beauty)"
  },
  {
    "question": "主動",
    "answer": "しゅどう",
    "meaning": "leadership"
  },
  {
    "question": "判ずる",
    "answer": "はんずる",
    "meaning": "to judge, to decide, to solve, to decipher, to puzzle out, to interpret, to divine, to guess, to mak"
  },
  {
    "question": "綱紀",
    "answer": "こうき",
    "meaning": "law and order, discipline"
  },
  {
    "question": "投光器",
    "answer": "とうこうき",
    "meaning": "floodlight, floodlight projector"
  },
  {
    "question": "五線譜",
    "answer": "ごせんふ",
    "meaning": "staff notation"
  },
  {
    "question": "常任",
    "answer": "じょうにん",
    "meaning": "standing, regular, permanent"
  },
  {
    "question": "機具",
    "answer": "きぐ",
    "meaning": "(tools and) equipment"
  },
  {
    "question": "喜捨",
    "answer": "きしゃ",
    "meaning": "almsgiving"
  },
  {
    "question": "御供",
    "answer": "おとも",
    "meaning": "attendant, companion"
  },
  {
    "question": "直答",
    "answer": "じきとう,ちょくとう",
    "meaning": "prompt answer, direct personal answer"
  },
  {
    "question": "行手",
    "answer": "ゆきて,いきて",
    "meaning": "someone who is going"
  },
  {
    "question": "性具",
    "answer": "せいぐ",
    "meaning": "sex toy, sex aid"
  },
  {
    "question": "山本",
    "answer": "やまもと",
    "meaning": "foot of a mountain, base of a mountain, mine, colliery, owner of a mountain, operator of a mine"
  },
  {
    "question": "内諾",
    "answer": "ないだく",
    "meaning": "informal consent, private consent"
  },
  {
    "question": "最低賃金",
    "answer": "さいていちんぎん",
    "meaning": "minimum wage"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗車口",
    "answer": "じょうしゃぐち",
    "meaning": "entrance (for passengers at a train station), passenger door (on a train, bus, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "羊歯",
    "answer": "しだ",
    "meaning": "fern (esp. species Gleichenia japonica), fernery"
  },
  {
    "question": "不可知",
    "answer": "ふかち",
    "meaning": "unknowable, mysterious"
  },
  {
    "question": "予算編成",
    "answer": "よさんへんせい",
    "meaning": "budget compilation (by the Cabinet)"
  },
  {
    "question": "口伝え",
    "answer": "くちづたえ",
    "meaning": "oral instruction, passing information by word-of-mouth, oral tradition"
  },
  {
    "question": "来臨",
    "answer": "らいりん",
    "meaning": "attendance, presence, visit, coming, advent"
  },
  {
    "question": "激憤",
    "answer": "げきふん",
    "meaning": "resentment, indignation"
  },
  {
    "question": "土俵際",
    "answer": "どひょうぎわ",
    "meaning": "edge of the ring, verge, brink, critical moment, last moment"
  },
  {
    "question": "疾うに",
    "answer": "とうに",
    "meaning": "long ago, a long time ago, already"
  },
  {
    "question": "腕比べ",
    "answer": "うでくらべ",
    "meaning": "contest (of strength or skill)"
  },
  {
    "question": "怪奇小説",
    "answer": "かいきしょうせつ",
    "meaning": "mystery novel"
  },
  {
    "question": "人気商売",
    "answer": "にんきしょうばい",
    "meaning": "occupations dependent on public favor (favour)"
  },
  {
    "question": "小便臭い",
    "answer": "しょうべんくさい",
    "meaning": "stinking of urine, childish, immature, inexperienced"
  },
  {
    "question": "締め括り",
    "answer": "しめくくり",
    "meaning": "conclusion, end, completion, summing up, supervision"
  },
  {
    "question": "欄外",
    "answer": "らんがい",
    "meaning": "margin"
  },
  {
    "question": "照明灯",
    "answer": "しょうめいとう",
    "meaning": "light used for brightly lighting up a plaza, building, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "経営戦略",
    "answer": "けいえいせんりゃく",
    "meaning": "management strategy"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱け殻",
    "answer": "ぬけがら",
    "meaning": "cast-off skin (snake, insect, etc.), husk, empty shell, exuvia, exuviae"
  },
  {
    "question": "真北",
    "answer": "まきた,しんぽく",
    "meaning": "due north, true north, geodetic north"
  },
  {
    "question": "内開き",
    "answer": "うちびらき",
    "meaning": "opening inward (e.g. door, window)"
  },
  {
    "question": "公権力",
    "answer": "こうけんりょく",
    "meaning": "public power, governmental authority"
  },
  {
    "question": "全学",
    "answer": "ぜんがく",
    "meaning": "whole college"
  },
  {
    "question": "一続き",
    "answer": "ひとつづき",
    "meaning": "chain (of), series (of), sequence, suite (e.g. of rooms)"
  },
  {
    "question": "心棒",
    "answer": "しんぼう",
    "meaning": "shaft, axle, mandrel, arbor, centre of a group"
  },
  {
    "question": "半身浴",
    "answer": "はんしんよく",
    "meaning": "half body bathing, hip bath"
  },
  {
    "question": "猫被り",
    "answer": "ねこかぶり",
    "meaning": "feigned innocence or naivete, beguiling innocence, wolf in sheep's clothing"
  },
  {
    "question": "失火",
    "answer": "しっか",
    "meaning": "accidental fire, fire caused by negligence, misfire, failure to ignite"
  },
  {
    "question": "強兵",
    "answer": "きょうへい",
    "meaning": "powerful army, strengthening of the military"
  },
  {
    "question": "飽かず",
    "answer": "あかず",
    "meaning": "with untiring zeal"
  },
  {
    "question": "将に",
    "answer": "まさに",
    "meaning": "exactly, surely, certainly, just, right then, just then, at that moment, just (about to), on the ver"
  },
  {
    "question": "首尾一貫",
    "answer": "しゅびいっかん",
    "meaning": "consistent, unchanging from beginning to end"
  },
  {
    "question": "胡蝶蘭",
    "answer": "こちょうらん",
    "meaning": "moth orchid (Phalaenopsis)"
  },
  {
    "question": "発券",
    "answer": "はっけん",
    "meaning": "issuing (a banknote, ticket, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "美魔女",
    "answer": "びまじょ",
    "meaning": "middle-aged woman who looks very young for her age (as through 'magic')"
  },
  {
    "question": "百年目",
    "answer": "ひゃくねんめ",
    "meaning": "the hundredth year, out of luck, (at the) end of one's rope, rare chance, unusually good fortune"
  },
  {
    "question": "見得",
    "answer": "みえ",
    "meaning": "pose, posture"
  },
  {
    "question": "近代国家",
    "answer": "きんだいこっか",
    "meaning": "modern state, modern nation"
  },
  {
    "question": "周波",
    "answer": "しゅうは",
    "meaning": "cycle, wave, frequency"
  },
  {
    "question": "国有",
    "answer": "こくゆう",
    "meaning": "national ownership, state ownership, government ownership"
  },
  {
    "question": "厳冬",
    "answer": "げんとう",
    "meaning": "severe winter"
  },
  {
    "question": "独裁政治",
    "answer": "どくさいせいじ",
    "meaning": "dictatorship, despotic government"
  },
  {
    "question": "炊き込む",
    "answer": "たきこむ",
    "meaning": "to cook (something) with rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "季節風",
    "answer": "きせつふう",
    "meaning": "seasonal winds"
  },
  {
    "question": "常在",
    "answer": "じょうざい",
    "meaning": "resident, indigenous, always existing"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒸留水",
    "answer": "じょうりゅうすい",
    "meaning": "distilled water"
  },
  {
    "question": "包括的",
    "answer": "ほうかつてき",
    "meaning": "comprehensive, inclusive, encompassing"
  },
  {
    "question": "筆遣い",
    "answer": "ふでづかい",
    "meaning": "brushwork, handling of one's brush, command of one's pen, penmanship"
  },
  {
    "question": "順手",
    "answer": "じゅんて",
    "meaning": "overhand grip"
  },
  {
    "question": "年増女",
    "answer": "としまおんな",
    "meaning": "woman past her prime"
  },
  {
    "question": "目抜き",
    "answer": "めぬき",
    "meaning": "principal, main, important, fashionable"
  },
  {
    "question": "二本差し",
    "answer": "にほんざし",
    "meaning": "two-sworded (samurai)"
  },
  {
    "question": "億万",
    "answer": "おくまん",
    "meaning": "millions and millions"
  },
  {
    "question": "特出",
    "answer": "とくしゅつ",
    "meaning": "prominence, superiority"
  },
  {
    "question": "旋毛",
    "answer": "つむじ,せんもう",
    "meaning": "hair whorl"
  },
  {
    "question": "病歴",
    "answer": "びょうれき",
    "meaning": "clinical (case) history"
  },
  {
    "question": "離れ小島",
    "answer": "はなれこじま",
    "meaning": "small isolated island"
  },
  {
    "question": "猿回し",
    "answer": "さるまわし",
    "meaning": "showman who trains performing monkeys"
  },
  {
    "question": "独立心",
    "answer": "どくりつしん",
    "meaning": "independent spirit"
  },
  {
    "question": "鈍行",
    "answer": "どんこう",
    "meaning": "ordinary train, slow train"
  },
  {
    "question": "汗顔",
    "answer": "かんがん",
    "meaning": "ashamed"
  },
  {
    "question": "穴狙い",
    "answer": "あなねらい",
    "meaning": "aiming for a lucky break (e.g. in horse racing, betting on an unlikely horse)"
  },
  {
    "question": "余勢",
    "answer": "よせい",
    "meaning": "surplus power, momentum, impetus, inertia"
  },
  {
    "question": "脛当て",
    "answer": "すねあて",
    "meaning": "greaves, shin guards"
  },
  {
    "question": "同梱",
    "answer": "どうこん",
    "meaning": "including (in a package), packing together with"
  },
  {
    "question": "相好",
    "answer": "そうごう",
    "meaning": "features, appearance"
  },
  {
    "question": "民間信仰",
    "answer": "みんかんしんこう",
    "meaning": "folk beliefs, folk religion"
  },
  {
    "question": "性差別",
    "answer": "せいさべつ",
    "meaning": "sexual discrimination, sex discrimination, sexism"
  },
  {
    "question": "山原",
    "answer": "やんばる",
    "meaning": "mountain areas of Kunigami County in Northern Okinawa"
  },
  {
    "question": "折本",
    "answer": "おりほん",
    "meaning": "folding book, folded sections of a book"
  },
  {
    "question": "川獺",
    "answer": "かわうそ",
    "meaning": "otter (Lutra lutra), Japanese river otter (Lutra lutra whiteleyi)"
  },
  {
    "question": "識閾",
    "answer": "しきいき",
    "meaning": "threshold of consciousness"
  },
  {
    "question": "隠岐",
    "answer": "おき",
    "meaning": "Oki (former province located on Oki Island in present-day Shimane Prefecture), Oki (island)"
  },
  {
    "question": "謹啓",
    "answer": "きんけい",
    "meaning": "Dear Sir or Madam, Dear Sirs, Gentlemen"
  },
  {
    "question": "白軍",
    "answer": "はくぐん",
    "meaning": "White Army (any of the armies that opposed the Bolsheviks during the Russian Revolution)"
  },
  {
    "question": "妻君",
    "answer": "さいくん,めぎみ",
    "meaning": "one's wife, wife (of somebody below the speaker in rank)"
  },
  {
    "question": "邪術",
    "answer": "じゃじゅつ",
    "meaning": "evil ways, sorcery"
  },
  {
    "question": "浜風",
    "answer": "はまかぜ",
    "meaning": "sea breeze, beach wind"
  },
  {
    "question": "天火",
    "answer": "てんか,てんぴ",
    "meaning": "fire caused by lightning, oven"
  },
  {
    "question": "北辺",
    "answer": "ほくへん",
    "meaning": "northern extremity"
  },
  {
    "question": "破邪顕正",
    "answer": "はじゃけんしょう",
    "meaning": "(sense of) crushing evil and spreading the truth"
  },
  {
    "question": "大日",
    "answer": "だいにち",
    "meaning": "Mahavairocana (Tathagata), Great Sun, Supreme Buddha of Sino-Japanese esoteric Buddhism"
  },
  {
    "question": "対手",
    "answer": "たいしゅ,あいて",
    "meaning": "opponent (in combat)"
  },
  {
    "question": "壮挙",
    "answer": "そうきょ",
    "meaning": "ambitious (heroic) undertaking, daring enterprise, grand scheme"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄親",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "幽界",
    "answer": "ゆうかい",
    "meaning": "hades, realm of the dead"
  },
  {
    "question": "帆走",
    "answer": "はんそう",
    "meaning": "sailing"
  },
  {
    "question": "半角",
    "answer": "はんかく",
    "meaning": "half-width characters (e.g. romaji), single-byte characters, en quad"
  },
  {
    "question": "車室",
    "answer": "しゃしつ",
    "meaning": "compartment (of a train), interior (of a car)"
  },
  {
    "question": "朱鷺",
    "answer": "とき,しゅろ",
    "meaning": "Japanese crested ibis (Nipponia nippon), crested ibis"
  },
  {
    "question": "識見",
    "answer": "しきけん,しっけん",
    "meaning": "views, opinion, discernment, pride, self-respect, insight"
  },
  {
    "question": "餓鬼道",
    "answer": "がきどう",
    "meaning": "hungry ghost (preta) realm"
  },
  {
    "question": "左大臣",
    "answer": "さだいじん",
    "meaning": "Minister of the Left (official in Nara and Heian periods)"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗務",
    "answer": "じょうむ",
    "meaning": "doing transport-related work"
  },
  {
    "question": "木場",
    "answer": "きば",
    "meaning": "lumberyard"
  },
  {
    "question": "航空母艦",
    "answer": "こうくうぼかん",
    "meaning": "aircraft carrier"
  },
  {
    "question": "音韻",
    "answer": "おんいん",
    "meaning": "vocal sound, phoneme"
  },
  {
    "question": "海豚",
    "answer": "いるか",
    "meaning": "dolphin (or other small toothed whales, such as porpoises, belugas, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "神命",
    "answer": "しんめい",
    "meaning": "divine command, heaven's will"
  },
  {
    "question": "揚陸艦",
    "answer": "ようりくかん",
    "meaning": "landing ship, amphibious warfare ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "樹高",
    "answer": "じゅこう",
    "meaning": "tree height"
  },
  {
    "question": "自然法則",
    "answer": "しぜんほうそく",
    "meaning": "law of nature, natural law"
  },
  {
    "question": "莫",
    "answer": "まな",
    "meaning": "must not, may not"
  },
  {
    "question": "弦楽",
    "answer": "げんがく",
    "meaning": "music for strings, string music"
  },
  {
    "question": "立札",
    "answer": "たてふだ",
    "meaning": "bulletin board, notice board, billboard, roadside sign, sign on a post, usu. wooden, esp. containing"
  },
  {
    "question": "公立学校",
    "answer": "こうりつがっこう",
    "meaning": "public school"
  },
  {
    "question": "入市",
    "answer": "にゅうし",
    "meaning": "entering a city"
  },
  {
    "question": "鱧",
    "answer": "はも,はむ",
    "meaning": "daggertooth pike conger (Muraenesox cinereus), (in Northern Japan) conger eel, garden eel"
  },
  {
    "question": "御庭番",
    "answer": "おにわばん",
    "meaning": "spy working for the Edo shogunate, oniwaban"
  },
  {
    "question": "柱廊",
    "answer": "ちゅうろう",
    "meaning": "pillared corridor"
  },
  {
    "question": "磁界",
    "answer": "じかい",
    "meaning": "magnetic field"
  },
  {
    "question": "読者層",
    "answer": "どくしゃそう",
    "meaning": "readership, target audience (of a magazine)"
  },
  {
    "question": "三つ揃い",
    "answer": "みつぞろい",
    "meaning": "three-piece suit"
  },
  {
    "question": "体外受精",
    "answer": "たいがいじゅせい",
    "meaning": "in vitro fertilization, in vitro fertilisation, IVF"
  },
  {
    "question": "力感",
    "answer": "りきかん",
    "meaning": "power, force"
  },
  {
    "question": "急進",
    "answer": "きゅうしん",
    "meaning": "rapid progress, radical"
  },
  {
    "question": "百獣",
    "answer": "ひゃくじゅう",
    "meaning": "all kinds of animals"
  },
  {
    "question": "伽羅",
    "answer": "きゃら",
    "meaning": "aloes wood (Taxus cuspidata var. nana), aloes-wood perfume, aloes-wood incense"
  },
  {
    "question": "原潜",
    "answer": "げんせん",
    "meaning": "nuclear submarine"
  },
  {
    "question": "評決",
    "answer": "ひょうけつ",
    "meaning": "decision, verdict"
  },
  {
    "question": "代読",
    "answer": "だいどく",
    "meaning": "reading for another"
  },
  {
    "question": "旧道",
    "answer": "きゅうどう",
    "meaning": "old road"
  },
  {
    "question": "姻戚",
    "answer": "いんせき",
    "meaning": "relative by marriage, affinity"
  },
  {
    "question": "二字",
    "answer": "にじ",
    "meaning": "two characters, name"
  },
  {
    "question": "存念",
    "answer": "ぞんねん",
    "meaning": "opinion, idea"
  },
  {
    "question": "菅",
    "answer": "すげ,すが",
    "meaning": "sedge (Cyperaceae spp., esp. members of genus Carex)"
  },
  {
    "question": "照門",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "水疱",
    "answer": "すいほう",
    "meaning": "blister"
  },
  {
    "question": "塩化",
    "answer": "えんか",
    "meaning": "chloride"
  },
  {
    "question": "所得税",
    "answer": "しょとくぜい",
    "meaning": "income tax"
  },
  {
    "question": "草叢",
    "answer": "くさむら",
    "meaning": "the grass, grassy place (esp. with long dense grass)"
  },
  {
    "question": "立脚点",
    "answer": "りっきゃくてん",
    "meaning": "standpoint, position, viewpoint, footing, starting point, basis (e.g. of an argument), grounds"
  },
  {
    "question": "殷々",
    "answer": "いんいん",
    "meaning": "roaring, booming, bellowing, pealing, reverberating, rumbling"
  },
  {
    "question": "ジュラ紀",
    "answer": "ジュラき",
    "meaning": "Jurassic Period, Jurassic"
  },
  {
    "question": "稀薄",
    "answer": "きはく",
    "meaning": "thin (e.g. air), diluted, sparse, lean, weak, rarified, rarefied, lacking (e.g. empathy), deficient,"
  },
  {
    "question": "石筍",
    "answer": "せきじゅん",
    "meaning": "stalagmite"
  },
  {
    "question": "塩抜き",
    "answer": "しおぬき",
    "meaning": "desalinating with water, salt removal"
  },
  {
    "question": "遊撃戦",
    "answer": "ゆうげきせん",
    "meaning": "guerrilla warfare, unconventional warfare"
  },
  {
    "question": "思想犯",
    "answer": "しそうはん",
    "meaning": "ideological offense, crime of espousing dangerous ideas, political crime, ideological offender, thou"
  },
  {
    "question": "四手",
    "answer": "しで",
    "meaning": "zigzag-shaped paper streamer often used to adorn Shinto-related objects, hornbeam (deciduous tree in"
  },
  {
    "question": "政治権力",
    "answer": "せいじけんりょく",
    "meaning": "political force"
  },
  {
    "question": "発話",
    "answer": "はつわ",
    "meaning": "utterance, speech"
  },
  {
    "question": "北進",
    "answer": "ほくしん",
    "meaning": "proceeding north"
  },
  {
    "question": "氷海",
    "answer": "ひょうかい",
    "meaning": "frozen sea, icy waters"
  },
  {
    "question": "適確",
    "answer": "てきかく,てっかく",
    "meaning": "precise, accurate, appropriate, exactly the right"
  },
  {
    "question": "後送",
    "answer": "こうそう",
    "meaning": "sending to the rear (esp. a soldier), evacuation from the front, sending later"
  },
  {
    "question": "不信任",
    "answer": "ふしんにん",
    "meaning": "non-confidence, lack of confidence"
  },
  {
    "question": "供回り",
    "answer": "ともまわり",
    "meaning": "retinue, suite"
  },
  {
    "question": "学位",
    "answer": "がくい",
    "meaning": "(academic) degree"
  },
  {
    "question": "液体燃料",
    "answer": "えきたいねんりょう",
    "meaning": "liquid fuel"
  },
  {
    "question": "法具",
    "answer": "ほうぐ",
    "meaning": "ritual implements"
  },
  {
    "question": "足長",
    "answer": "あしなが,そくちょう",
    "meaning": "long-legged(ness), foot length"
  },
  {
    "question": "物納",
    "answer": "ぶつのう",
    "meaning": "payment in kind"
  },
  {
    "question": "東亜",
    "answer": "とうあ",
    "meaning": "East Asia, the Orient"
  },
  {
    "question": "血漿",
    "answer": "けっしょう",
    "meaning": "plasma, blood plasma"
  },
  {
    "question": "衛星通信",
    "answer": "えいせいつうしん",
    "meaning": "satellite communication"
  },
  {
    "question": "凶猛",
    "answer": "きょうもう",
    "meaning": "fierce"
  },
  {
    "question": "霊鳥",
    "answer": "れいちょう",
    "meaning": "sacred bird"
  },
  {
    "question": "司法機関",
    "answer": "しほうきかん",
    "meaning": "judicial branch (of government), judicial organ"
  },
  {
    "question": "箭",
    "answer": "や,さ",
    "meaning": "arrow, wedge, chock"
  },
  {
    "question": "無得点",
    "answer": "むとくてん",
    "meaning": "scoreless (game or competition)"
  },
  {
    "question": "麝香",
    "answer": "じゃこう",
    "meaning": "musk"
  },
  {
    "question": "生春巻き",
    "answer": "なまはるまき",
    "meaning": "fresh spring roll (i.e. not fried), summer roll, Vietnamese salad roll"
  },
  {
    "question": "全体主義",
    "answer": "ぜんたいしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "totalitarianism"
  },
  {
    "question": "繊",
    "answer": "せん",
    "meaning": "daikon julienne, julienned daikon, one ten-millionth"
  },
  {
    "question": "喊声",
    "answer": "かんせい",
    "meaning": "battle cry"
  },
  {
    "question": "花籠",
    "answer": "はなかご,けこ,はなこ",
    "meaning": "flower basket, flower basket (or plate) used for flower-scattering rituals"
  },
  {
    "question": "暇乞い",
    "answer": "いとまごい",
    "meaning": "leave-taking, offering one's resignation, farewell visit"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛇体",
    "answer": "じゃたい",
    "meaning": "body of a snake, serpentine"
  },
  {
    "question": "石榴",
    "answer": "ざくろ,せきりゅう,じゃくろ",
    "meaning": "pomegranate (Punica granatum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鳥葬",
    "answer": "ちょうそう",
    "meaning": "sky burial (funeral ritual in which the body of the deceased is exposed to be eaten by birds)"
  },
  {
    "question": "後進国",
    "answer": "こうしんこく",
    "meaning": "undeveloped country, third world country"
  },
  {
    "question": "権高",
    "answer": "けんだか",
    "meaning": "pride, haughtiness"
  },
  {
    "question": "檄文",
    "answer": "げきぶん",
    "meaning": "written appeal, manifesto, declaration"
  },
  {
    "question": "群舞",
    "answer": "ぐんぶ",
    "meaning": "group dancing"
  },
  {
    "question": "白味噌",
    "answer": "しろみそ",
    "meaning": "light-brown miso"
  },
  {
    "question": "愁眉",
    "answer": "しゅうび",
    "meaning": "worried look, melancholy air"
  },
  {
    "question": "微糖",
    "answer": "びとう",
    "meaning": "very low in sugar content"
  },
  {
    "question": "麻縄",
    "answer": "あさなわ",
    "meaning": "hemp rope"
  },
  {
    "question": "武辺",
    "answer": "ぶへん",
    "meaning": "military affairs, military people"
  },
  {
    "question": "刻一刻",
    "answer": "こくいっこく",
    "meaning": "moment by moment, hour by hour"
  },
  {
    "question": "数理",
    "answer": "すうり",
    "meaning": "mathematical principle, mathematics, arithmetic, figures, accounts"
  },
  {
    "question": "泰平",
    "answer": "たいへい",
    "meaning": "peace, tranquility, tranquillity, happy-go-lucky"
  },
  {
    "question": "四方山話",
    "answer": "よもやまばなし",
    "meaning": "talk about various topics"
  },
  {
    "question": "切削",
    "answer": "せっさく",
    "meaning": "cutting (e.g. metal)"
  },
  {
    "question": "実相",
    "answer": "じっそう",
    "meaning": "reality, real state of affairs, true state of affairs, true form of all things as they are, ultimate"
  },
  {
    "question": "恩讐",
    "answer": "おんしゅう",
    "meaning": "love and hate"
  },
  {
    "question": "委託販売",
    "answer": "いたくはんばい",
    "meaning": "consignment sale"
  },
  {
    "question": "理外",
    "answer": "りがい",
    "meaning": "supra-rational"
  },
  {
    "question": "地縁",
    "answer": "ちえん",
    "meaning": "territorial relationship, regional bond"
  },
  {
    "question": "陳腐化",
    "answer": "ちんぷか",
    "meaning": "obsolescence, becoming obsolete (of a product, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "野辺",
    "answer": "のべ",
    "meaning": "field"
  },
  {
    "question": "四球",
    "answer": "しきゅう",
    "meaning": "four balls, base on balls, a walk"
  },
  {
    "question": "暴風域",
    "answer": "ぼうふういき",
    "meaning": "storm area (winds of 25mps or more)"
  },
  {
    "question": "磨ぐ",
    "answer": "とぐ",
    "meaning": "to sharpen, to hone, to whet, to grind, to wash (rice), to scour, to polish, to burnish"
  },
  {
    "question": "悠揚",
    "answer": "ゆうよう",
    "meaning": "self-possessed, calm"
  },
  {
    "question": "美術史",
    "answer": "びじゅつし",
    "meaning": "art history"
  },
  {
    "question": "無休",
    "answer": "むきゅう",
    "meaning": "without a holiday, nonstop"
  },
  {
    "question": "筆下ろし",
    "answer": "ふでおろし",
    "meaning": "using a new brush for the first time, doing something for the first time, man losing his virginity ("
  },
  {
    "question": "賢察",
    "answer": "けんさつ",
    "meaning": "discernment"
  },
  {
    "question": "尖鋭",
    "answer": "せんえい",
    "meaning": "radical, acute, sharp"
  },
  {
    "question": "霜焼け",
    "answer": "しもやけ",
    "meaning": "frostbite, chilblains"
  },
  {
    "question": "雲上人",
    "answer": "うんじょうびと",
    "meaning": "the nobility"
  },
  {
    "question": "要地",
    "answer": "ようち",
    "meaning": "important place, strategic point, critical location"
  },
  {
    "question": "固形燃料",
    "answer": "こけいねんりょう",
    "meaning": "solid fuel"
  },
  {
    "question": "証拠書類",
    "answer": "しょうこしょるい",
    "meaning": "documentary evidence, documentation"
  },
  {
    "question": "仏滅",
    "answer": "ぶつめつ",
    "meaning": "Buddha's death, very unlucky day (according to old almanacs)"
  },
  {
    "question": "小額",
    "answer": "しょうがく",
    "meaning": "small sum (e.g. of money), small denomination"
  },
  {
    "question": "擬音語",
    "answer": "ぎおんご",
    "meaning": "onomatopoeic word"
  },
  {
    "question": "自棄酒",
    "answer": "やけざけ",
    "meaning": "drowning one's cares in drink, drinking in desperation"
  },
  {
    "question": "更年期",
    "answer": "こうねんき",
    "meaning": "menopause, change of life"
  },
  {
    "question": "陰日向",
    "answer": "かげひなた",
    "meaning": "double-faced"
  },
  {
    "question": "幹線",
    "answer": "かんせん",
    "meaning": "main line, trunk line"
  },
  {
    "question": "行末",
    "answer": "ゆくすえ,ぎょうまつ",
    "meaning": "one's future, one's fate, one's way, one's path, end of a line (of writing), line break"
  },
  {
    "question": "取替える",
    "answer": "とりかえる",
    "meaning": "to exchange, to swap, to barter, to replace, to substitute"
  },
  {
    "question": "鬱状態",
    "answer": "うつじょうたい",
    "meaning": "depressive state (e.g. of manic depression), depressive condition"
  },
  {
    "question": "デモ行進",
    "answer": "デモこうしん",
    "meaning": "demonstration parade"
  },
  {
    "question": "区立",
    "answer": "くりつ",
    "meaning": "established by the ward"
  },
  {
    "question": "鯉口",
    "answer": "こいぐち",
    "meaning": "mouth of a (sword) sheath"
  },
  {
    "question": "付け届け",
    "answer": "つけとどけ",
    "meaning": "gift, present, tip, bribe"
  },
  {
    "question": "片恋",
    "answer": "かたこい",
    "meaning": "unrequited love, one-sided love"
  },
  {
    "question": "非常警戒",
    "answer": "ひじょうけいかい",
    "meaning": "special guard"
  },
  {
    "question": "詫び状",
    "answer": "わびじょう",
    "meaning": "letter of apology"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗用",
    "answer": "じょうよう",
    "meaning": "using for riding, passenger use"
  },
  {
    "question": "女房役",
    "answer": "にょうぼうやく",
    "meaning": "assistant, right-hand man, subordinate, wifely role"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会奉仕",
    "answer": "しゃかいほうし",
    "meaning": "voluntary social service"
  },
  {
    "question": "煎",
    "answer": "せん,ジョン,チョン",
    "meaning": "infusing (tea), infusion, jeon, Korean dish of meat, vegetables, etc. coated in flour and egg and fr"
  },
  {
    "question": "一編",
    "answer": "いっぺん",
    "meaning": "piece (e.g. poetry), poem, essay, book, story"
  },
  {
    "question": "健康美",
    "answer": "けんこうび",
    "meaning": "healthy beauty"
  },
  {
    "question": "単純労働",
    "answer": "たんじゅんろうどう",
    "meaning": "unskilled labor, simple labor, menial job"
  },
  {
    "question": "二次関数",
    "answer": "にじかんすう",
    "meaning": "quadratic function"
  },
  {
    "question": "考証",
    "answer": "こうしょう",
    "meaning": "(historical) investigation"
  },
  {
    "question": "脊椎動物",
    "answer": "せきついどうぶつ",
    "meaning": "vertebrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "元本",
    "answer": "がんぽん,げんぽん",
    "meaning": "principal (invest.), capital"
  },
  {
    "question": "高配",
    "answer": "こうはい",
    "meaning": "(your) consideration, attention, trouble, kindness, good offices, high dividends, high rate of retur"
  },
  {
    "question": "二男",
    "answer": "じなん",
    "meaning": "second son"
  },
  {
    "question": "盛り土",
    "answer": "もりど,もりつち",
    "meaning": "embankment (for road, railway, etc.), raising the ground level, fill"
  },
  {
    "question": "返納",
    "answer": "へんのう",
    "meaning": "returning (to the authorities), restoring"
  },
  {
    "question": "粗熱",
    "answer": "あらねつ",
    "meaning": "the heat of food just after cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "振り落す",
    "answer": "ふりおとす",
    "meaning": "to shake off, to throw off"
  },
  {
    "question": "中折れ",
    "answer": "なかおれ",
    "meaning": "felt hat, fedora, trilby, stopping in the middle, being interrupted in the middle, being broken in t"
  },
  {
    "question": "注す",
    "answer": "さす",
    "meaning": "to pour, to add (liquid), to serve (drinks), to put on (lipstick, etc.), to apply, to colour, to dye"
  },
  {
    "question": "信託",
    "answer": "しんたく",
    "meaning": "trust, entrusting"
  },
  {
    "question": "道ならぬ",
    "answer": "みちならぬ",
    "meaning": "immoral"
  },
  {
    "question": "前開き",
    "answer": "まえあき,まえびらき",
    "meaning": "opening in front (clothing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "万国旗",
    "answer": "ばんこくき,ばんこっき",
    "meaning": "flags of all nations"
  },
  {
    "question": "面取り",
    "answer": "めんとり",
    "meaning": "chamfering, beveling, bevelling, rounding the edges (of a vegetable), trimming the corners"
  },
  {
    "question": "敢え無い",
    "answer": "あえない",
    "meaning": "tragic"
  },
  {
    "question": "出生地",
    "answer": "しゅっしょうち,しゅっせいち",
    "meaning": "birthplace"
  },
  {
    "question": "読本",
    "answer": "とくほん,どくほん,よみほん",
    "meaning": "reading-book, reader, guidebook, manual, textbook (esp. a pre-war elementary school Japanese languag"
  },
  {
    "question": "御目通り",
    "answer": "おめどおり",
    "meaning": "audience (with a person of high standing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "買い言葉",
    "answer": "かいことば",
    "meaning": "tit for tat"
  },
  {
    "question": "相続税",
    "answer": "そうぞくぜい",
    "meaning": "inheritance tax, death duty"
  },
  {
    "question": "老若",
    "answer": "ろうにゃく,ろうじゃく",
    "meaning": "young and old, all ages"
  },
  {
    "question": "空騒ぎ",
    "answer": "からさわぎ",
    "meaning": "making a fuss, Much Ado about Nothing (Shakespeare)"
  },
  {
    "question": "多面的",
    "answer": "ためんてき",
    "meaning": "multifaceted, versatile"
  },
  {
    "question": "近付き",
    "answer": "ちかづき",
    "meaning": "acquaintance, making someone's acquaintance"
  },
  {
    "question": "微増",
    "answer": "びぞう",
    "meaning": "slight increase, marginal rise"
  },
  {
    "question": "直輸入",
    "answer": "じきゆにゅう,ちょくゆにゅう",
    "meaning": "direct import"
  },
  {
    "question": "解け合う",
    "answer": "とけあう",
    "meaning": "to come to a mutual understanding, to cancel mutually (contract, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "憎からず",
    "answer": "にくからず",
    "meaning": "affectionately, tenderly, lovingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "若気",
    "answer": "わかげ,にやけ,にゃけ",
    "meaning": "youthful impetuosity, youthful vitality, male homosexual's partner, buttocks, anus"
  },
  {
    "question": "乱切り",
    "answer": "らんぎり",
    "meaning": "chopping (vegetables) into chunks"
  },
  {
    "question": "卒業論文",
    "answer": "そつぎょうろんぶん",
    "meaning": "graduation thesis"
  },
  {
    "question": "午前様",
    "answer": "ごぜんさま",
    "meaning": "coming home after midnight, person who comes home after midnight"
  },
  {
    "question": "流し場",
    "answer": "ながしば",
    "meaning": "place for showering next to a tub"
  },
  {
    "question": "群集心理",
    "answer": "ぐんしゅうしんり",
    "meaning": "mass psychology, mob psychology, crowd psychology, herd mentality, group mind"
  },
  {
    "question": "膾",
    "answer": "なます",
    "meaning": "namasu, dish of raw fish and vegetables seasoned in vinegar"
  },
  {
    "question": "当て字",
    "answer": "あてじ",
    "meaning": "kanji used as a phonetic symbol, instead of for the meaning, phonetic-equivalent character, substitu"
  },
  {
    "question": "東北東",
    "answer": "とうほくとう",
    "meaning": "east-northeast, ENE"
  },
  {
    "question": "売り時",
    "answer": "うりどき",
    "meaning": "good time to sell"
  },
  {
    "question": "念ずる",
    "answer": "ねんずる",
    "meaning": "to wish (for), to pray (for), to hope (for), to pray silently, to recite (Buddha's name, sutras, etc"
  },
  {
    "question": "一風呂",
    "answer": "ひとふろ",
    "meaning": "(a) bath"
  },
  {
    "question": "客扱い",
    "answer": "きゃくあつかい",
    "meaning": "hospitality, treating like a guest"
  },
  {
    "question": "生煮え",
    "answer": "なまにえ",
    "meaning": "half-cooked, rare, ambiguous, vague, immature"
  },
  {
    "question": "腰椎",
    "answer": "ようつい",
    "meaning": "lumbar vertebra, lumbar vertebrae"
  },
  {
    "question": "女冥利",
    "answer": "おんなみょうり",
    "meaning": "joy of being born a woman, good fortune of being born a woman"
  },
  {
    "question": "急がす",
    "answer": "いそがす",
    "meaning": "to hurry up, to press on, to hasten"
  },
  {
    "question": "別天地",
    "answer": "べってんち",
    "meaning": "another world"
  },
  {
    "question": "四君子",
    "answer": "しくんし",
    "meaning": "the four gentlemen (plum, chrysanthemum, orchid, and bamboo)"
  },
  {
    "question": "旧派",
    "answer": "きゅうは",
    "meaning": "old school, old style"
  },
  {
    "question": "山名",
    "answer": "さんめい",
    "meaning": "name of a mountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "東天",
    "answer": "とうてん",
    "meaning": "the eastern sky"
  },
  {
    "question": "阿闍梨",
    "answer": "あじゃり,あざり",
    "meaning": "high monk (esp. one of correct conduct who acts as a role model for his pupils), high priest, initia"
  },
  {
    "question": "琵琶法師",
    "answer": "びわほうし",
    "meaning": "lute priest, biwa-playing minstrel, travelling pre-Meiji musical performer (usu. blind and dressed l"
  },
  {
    "question": "実世界",
    "answer": "じっせかい",
    "meaning": "real world, outside world (e.g. the world outside of school)"
  },
  {
    "question": "曲輪",
    "answer": "くるわ",
    "meaning": "district, quarter, enclosure, area enclosed by earthwork, red-light district"
  },
  {
    "question": "大銀杏",
    "answer": "おおいちょう",
    "meaning": "large ginkgo tree, ginkgo-leaf top-knot worn by makuuchi and juryo division wrestlers"
  },
  {
    "question": "輪転機",
    "answer": "りんてんき",
    "meaning": "rotary press"
  },
  {
    "question": "重巡洋艦",
    "answer": "じゅうじゅんようかん",
    "meaning": "heavy cruiser"
  },
  {
    "question": "登園",
    "answer": "とうえん",
    "meaning": "going to kindergarten (nursery school, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "碓",
    "answer": "うす",
    "meaning": "millstone, mortar"
  },
  {
    "question": "金管",
    "answer": "きんかん",
    "meaning": "brass (musical) instrument"
  },
  {
    "question": "南京",
    "answer": "ナンキン",
    "meaning": "Nanjing, Nanking, pumpkin, squash, Chinese, Southeast Asian, foreign, rare, precious, cute"
  },
  {
    "question": "串焼",
    "answer": "くしやき",
    "meaning": "grilling on a skewer, spit-roasting"
  },
  {
    "question": "肉腫",
    "answer": "にくしゅ",
    "meaning": "sarcoma"
  },
  {
    "question": "綾取り",
    "answer": "あやとり",
    "meaning": "cat's cradle"
  },
  {
    "question": "異類",
    "answer": "いるい",
    "meaning": "varieties, different kinds"
  },
  {
    "question": "羽搏く",
    "answer": "はばたく",
    "meaning": "to flap (wings), to spread one's wings, to go out into the world"
  },
  {
    "question": "浄瑠璃",
    "answer": "じょうるり",
    "meaning": "jōruri, type of dramatic recitation accompanied by a shamisen (associated with Japanese puppet theat"
  },
  {
    "question": "緊縮",
    "answer": "きんしゅく",
    "meaning": "shrinkage, contraction, economy, retrenchment"
  },
  {
    "question": "塔屋",
    "answer": "とうや,とうおく",
    "meaning": "rooftop structure, e.g. tower, elevator machine room, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "宿将",
    "answer": "しゅくしょう",
    "meaning": "veteran general"
  },
  {
    "question": "爾",
    "answer": "なんじ,おれ,しか",
    "meaning": "thou, you, like that, as such, yeah, uh-huh"
  },
  {
    "question": "骨粉",
    "answer": "こっぷん",
    "meaning": "bone meal, powdered bone"
  },
  {
    "question": "恣",
    "answer": "ほしいまま",
    "meaning": "selfish, self-indulgent, arbitrary"
  },
  {
    "question": "備中",
    "answer": "びっちゅう",
    "meaning": "Bitchū (former province located in the west of present-day Okayama Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "月例",
    "answer": "げつれい",
    "meaning": "monthly"
  },
  {
    "question": "野伏",
    "answer": "のぶし",
    "meaning": "hermit, mountain ascetic, itinerant priest, mountain-dwelling robber, brigand"
  },
  {
    "question": "新暦",
    "answer": "しんれき",
    "meaning": "the solar calendar, the Gregorian calendar"
  },
  {
    "question": "無資格",
    "answer": "むしかく",
    "meaning": "unqualified, unlicensed, uncertified"
  },
  {
    "question": "小槌",
    "answer": "こづち",
    "meaning": "(small) mallet, gavel"
  },
  {
    "question": "制海権",
    "answer": "せいかいけん",
    "meaning": "control of the sea, command of the sea"
  },
  {
    "question": "審判員",
    "answer": "しんぱんいん,しんばんいん",
    "meaning": "referee, umpire"
  },
  {
    "question": "列国",
    "answer": "れっこく",
    "meaning": "nations, states"
  },
  {
    "question": "特装",
    "answer": "とくそう",
    "meaning": "specially equipped, customized, customised"
  },
  {
    "question": "規準",
    "answer": "きじゅん",
    "meaning": "standard, basis, criterion, norm, reference, datum"
  },
  {
    "question": "婆や",
    "answer": "ばあや",
    "meaning": "elderly housekeeper, elderly maid, wet nurse, nanny"
  },
  {
    "question": "番屋",
    "answer": "ばんや",
    "meaning": "sentry box, guardhouse, guard lodge, (Edo period) police box"
  },
  {
    "question": "嗤笑",
    "answer": "ししょう",
    "meaning": "sneer"
  },
  {
    "question": "獄舎",
    "answer": "ごくしゃ",
    "meaning": "prison (building), jail"
  },
  {
    "question": "蘭学",
    "answer": "らんがく",
    "meaning": "Dutch studies, studies of Western knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "忍び歩き",
    "answer": "しのびあるき,しのびありき",
    "meaning": "travelling incognito (traveling), quiet steps, creeping around"
  },
  {
    "question": "孤影",
    "answer": "こえい",
    "meaning": "lonely figure"
  },
  {
    "question": "夕景",
    "answer": "ゆうけい,せっけい,せきけい",
    "meaning": "evening, dusk, evening scene, evening landscape, light of the setting sun"
  },
  {
    "question": "懇談会",
    "answer": "こんだんかい",
    "meaning": "social gathering, informal get-together, colloquium, panel discussion"
  },
  {
    "question": "板ガラス",
    "answer": "いたガラス",
    "meaning": "plate glass, sheet glass"
  },
  {
    "question": "勿",
    "answer": "まな",
    "meaning": "must not, may not"
  },
  {
    "question": "丁半",
    "answer": "ちょうはん",
    "meaning": "even and odd numbers (on dice), chō-han, gambling game in which two dice are thrown and players bet"
  },
  {
    "question": "稗",
    "answer": "ひえ",
    "meaning": "barnyard millet (Echinochloa esculenta), Japanese millet, sanwa millet"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒ビール",
    "answer": "くろビール",
    "meaning": "stout, dark beer, porter's ale"
  },
  {
    "question": "開港",
    "answer": "かいこう",
    "meaning": "opening a port (seaport, airport, etc.), starting operations at a port, opening a port to foreign ve"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀行家",
    "answer": "ぎんこうか",
    "meaning": "banker, bank proprietor, bank manager"
  },
  {
    "question": "血戦",
    "answer": "けっせん",
    "meaning": "bloody battle"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒鉛",
    "answer": "こくえん",
    "meaning": "graphite"
  },
  {
    "question": "爆轟",
    "answer": "ばくごう",
    "meaning": "detonation"
  },
  {
    "question": "専科",
    "answer": "せんか",
    "meaning": "specialized course, specialised course, something that is specialized for a certain field or applica"
  },
  {
    "question": "親権者",
    "answer": "しんけんしゃ",
    "meaning": "person exercising parental authority"
  },
  {
    "question": "残兵",
    "answer": "ざんぺい",
    "meaning": "remnants of a defeated army"
  },
  {
    "question": "叩き売り",
    "answer": "たたきうり",
    "meaning": "sacrifice sale, bargain sale, discount sale"
  },
  {
    "question": "旅客船",
    "answer": "りょかくせん,りょきゃくせん",
    "meaning": "passenger ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "機種変更",
    "answer": "きしゅへんこう",
    "meaning": "model change (esp. mobile phone), model upgrade"
  },
  {
    "question": "聖像",
    "answer": "せいぞう",
    "meaning": "sacred image, icon"
  },
  {
    "question": "御嬢さん",
    "answer": "おじょうさん",
    "meaning": "(another's) daughter, young lady"
  },
  {
    "question": "荘重",
    "answer": "そうちょう",
    "meaning": "solemn, grave, impressive"
  },
  {
    "question": "川風",
    "answer": "かわかぜ",
    "meaning": "breeze off a river"
  },
  {
    "question": "雌馬",
    "answer": "めうま",
    "meaning": "mare, filly"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍拡",
    "answer": "ぐんかく",
    "meaning": "expansion of armaments"
  },
  {
    "question": "部落",
    "answer": "ぶらく",
    "meaning": "hamlet, subunit of village, burakumin area"
  },
  {
    "question": "在日",
    "answer": "ざいにち",
    "meaning": "resident in Japan (of a foreigner), situated in Japan (e.g. of an embassy), Korean living in Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "鏡の間",
    "answer": "かがみのま",
    "meaning": "room behind the curtain of a noh stage, where the actors prepare, greenroom (noh), mirror room, hall"
  },
  {
    "question": "万金",
    "answer": "まんきん",
    "meaning": "immense sum (of money), ten thousand yen"
  },
  {
    "question": "詠嘆",
    "answer": "えいたん",
    "meaning": "exclamation, admiration"
  },
  {
    "question": "新法",
    "answer": "しんぽう",
    "meaning": "new law, new method"
  },
  {
    "question": "厖大",
    "answer": "ぼうだい",
    "meaning": "huge, vast, enormous, colossal, extensive, large"
  },
  {
    "question": "走路",
    "answer": "そうろ",
    "meaning": "race track, course, express trail"
  },
  {
    "question": "魚籠",
    "answer": "びく",
    "meaning": "(wicker) basket used for carrying fish, creel"
  },
  {
    "question": "克つ",
    "answer": "かつ",
    "meaning": "to win, to gain victory"
  },
  {
    "question": "家鴨",
    "answer": "あひる",
    "meaning": "domestic duck"
  },
  {
    "question": "儀仗兵",
    "answer": "ぎじょうへい",
    "meaning": "guard of honor, guard of honour"
  },
  {
    "question": "双発",
    "answer": "そうはつ",
    "meaning": "two-motored"
  },
  {
    "question": "終礼",
    "answer": "しゅうれい",
    "meaning": "assembly at the end of the day (at a company or school, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "冥途",
    "answer": "めいど",
    "meaning": "Hades, the underworld, the other world, realm of the dead"
  },
  {
    "question": "連作障害",
    "answer": "れんさくしょうがい",
    "meaning": "repeated cultivation damage (same crop, same soil), continuous cropping hazard, replant failure"
  },
  {
    "question": "神学校",
    "answer": "しんがっこう",
    "meaning": "theological school, seminary"
  },
  {
    "question": "女流",
    "answer": "じょりゅう",
    "meaning": "woman (writer, artist, aviator, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "炎色",
    "answer": "えんしょく",
    "meaning": "flame (color, colour), flame scarlet, bright reddish, orange"
  },
  {
    "question": "吊り革",
    "answer": "つりかわ",
    "meaning": "strap (to hang onto)"
  },
  {
    "question": "蹌踉めく",
    "answer": "よろめく",
    "meaning": "to stagger, to misconduct oneself, to have a love affair, to waver, to feel some inclination"
  },
  {
    "question": "羽目板",
    "answer": "はめいた",
    "meaning": "wainscoting, wainscotting, wood paneling"
  },
  {
    "question": "非常呼集",
    "answer": "ひじょうこしゅう",
    "meaning": "special call-up"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹細工",
    "answer": "たけざいく",
    "meaning": "bamboo work, bamboo ware"
  },
  {
    "question": "官僚的",
    "answer": "かんりょうてき",
    "meaning": "bureaucratic"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒟蒻",
    "answer": "こんにゃく",
    "meaning": "konnyaku (Amorphophallus konjac), konjac, devil's tongue, konnyaku jelly, konjac jelly, devil's tong"
  },
  {
    "question": "微光",
    "answer": "びこう",
    "meaning": "faint light"
  },
  {
    "question": "襤褸切れ",
    "answer": "ぼろきれ",
    "meaning": "old cloth, rag"
  },
  {
    "question": "循環器",
    "answer": "じゅんかんき",
    "meaning": "circulatory organ"
  },
  {
    "question": "書留",
    "answer": "かきとめ",
    "meaning": "registered mail, registered post, registration (of mail), (putting on) record, writing down, noting"
  },
  {
    "question": "喚問",
    "answer": "かんもん",
    "meaning": "summons"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑じる",
    "answer": "まじる",
    "meaning": "to be mixed, to be blended with, to be combined, to associate with, to mingle with, to interest, to"
  },
  {
    "question": "家伝",
    "answer": "かでん",
    "meaning": "family tradition"
  },
  {
    "question": "球筋",
    "answer": "たますじ",
    "meaning": "course of a thrown ball, course of a hit ball (golf, tennis, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "大恐慌",
    "answer": "だいきょうこう",
    "meaning": "Great Depression"
  },
  {
    "question": "旱魃",
    "answer": "かんばつ",
    "meaning": "drought, long spell (period) of dry weather"
  },
  {
    "question": "飼葉",
    "answer": "かいば",
    "meaning": "fodder"
  },
  {
    "question": "上がり框",
    "answer": "あがりがまち,あがりかまち",
    "meaning": "piece of wood at front edge of entranceway floor, agarikamachi"
  },
  {
    "question": "雛壇",
    "answer": "ひなだん",
    "meaning": "tiered doll stand (for hina dolls), tiered platform, tiered gallery"
  },
  {
    "question": "綿雲",
    "answer": "わたぐも",
    "meaning": "fleecy clouds (esp. cumulus clouds)"
  },
  {
    "question": "爺婆",
    "answer": "じじばば",
    "meaning": "old people"
  },
  {
    "question": "完調",
    "answer": "かんちょう",
    "meaning": "one's best form"
  },
  {
    "question": "吐気",
    "answer": "はきけ",
    "meaning": "nausea, sickness in the stomach"
  },
  {
    "question": "灯明",
    "answer": "とうみょう",
    "meaning": "light offered to a god or Buddha, votive light"
  },
  {
    "question": "米食",
    "answer": "べいしょく",
    "meaning": "rice-based or centered diet (centred)"
  },
  {
    "question": "待合い",
    "answer": "まちあい",
    "meaning": "rendezvous, meeting, assignation, area where guests gather before the start of a tea ceremony, waiti"
  },
  {
    "question": "山海",
    "answer": "さんかい",
    "meaning": "mountains and seas"
  },
  {
    "question": "三角筋",
    "answer": "さんかくきん",
    "meaning": "deltoid (muscle)"
  },
  {
    "question": "画像処理",
    "answer": "がぞうしょり",
    "meaning": "image processing"
  },
  {
    "question": "獅子座",
    "answer": "ししざ",
    "meaning": "Leo (constellation), the Lion, Buddha's seat, seat of a high monk"
  },
  {
    "question": "席を蹴る",
    "answer": "せきをける",
    "meaning": "to stomp out (of a room, etc.), to storm out"
  },
  {
    "question": "督促状",
    "answer": "とくそくじょう",
    "meaning": "demand note, dunning letter (note)"
  },
  {
    "question": "逐電",
    "answer": "ちくでん",
    "meaning": "flight, absconding"
  },
  {
    "question": "張り渡す",
    "answer": "はりわたす",
    "meaning": "to string along (of rope, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "天気雨",
    "answer": "てんきあめ",
    "meaning": "sun shower, sudden rain from a blue sky"
  },
  {
    "question": "川上",
    "answer": "かわかみ",
    "meaning": "upper reaches of a river, upstream"
  },
  {
    "question": "空車",
    "answer": "くうしゃ,からぐるま",
    "meaning": "empty conveyance, empty taxi, free taxi, having spaces available (of a parking lot)"
  },
  {
    "question": "手向かい",
    "answer": "てむかい",
    "meaning": "resistance"
  },
  {
    "question": "世の習い",
    "answer": "よのならい",
    "meaning": "the way of the world, the lay of the land, the inescapable circumstances (of life)"
  },
  {
    "question": "外連味",
    "answer": "けれんみ",
    "meaning": "pretense, affectation, showiness"
  },
  {
    "question": "措いて",
    "answer": "おいて",
    "meaning": "except, no other"
  },
  {
    "question": "賞する",
    "answer": "しょうする",
    "meaning": "to praise, to extol, to laud, to appreciate, to admire"
  },
  {
    "question": "車間距離",
    "answer": "しゃかんきょり",
    "meaning": "distance between two cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "若鶏",
    "answer": "わかどり",
    "meaning": "chick, chicken"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇手",
    "answer": "きしゅ",
    "meaning": "surprise move"
  },
  {
    "question": "生殖器官",
    "answer": "せいしょくきかん",
    "meaning": "reproductive organ, reproductive system"
  },
  {
    "question": "官民",
    "answer": "かんみん",
    "meaning": "government and people, government and private sector, public and private sector"
  },
  {
    "question": "南蛮漬け",
    "answer": "なんばんづけ",
    "meaning": "roasted or deep-fried fish or meat, marinated in a spicy sauce"
  },
  {
    "question": "車回し",
    "answer": "くるままわし",
    "meaning": "turnaround (e.g. at the end of a driveway)"
  },
  {
    "question": "煮卵",
    "answer": "にたまご",
    "meaning": "egg boiled, peeled, and steeped in soy sauce marinade"
  },
  {
    "question": "蝶結び",
    "answer": "ちょうむすび",
    "meaning": "bow, bowknot"
  },
  {
    "question": "利尿",
    "answer": "りにょう",
    "meaning": "diuresis"
  },
  {
    "question": "蚕食",
    "answer": "さんしょく",
    "meaning": "encroachment, making inroads (into), (slow but steady) invasion"
  },
  {
    "question": "払い戻す",
    "answer": "はらいもどす",
    "meaning": "to repay, to pay back, to refund, to reimburse"
  },
  {
    "question": "排ガス",
    "answer": "はいガス",
    "meaning": "exhaust gas, exhaust fumes"
  },
  {
    "question": "蔵う",
    "answer": "しまう",
    "meaning": "to finish, to stop, to end, to put an end to, to bring to a close, to close (a business, etc.), to c"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷涼",
    "answer": "れいりょう",
    "meaning": "cool, cold"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻下",
    "answer": "びか",
    "meaning": "upper-lip, subnasal"
  },
  {
    "question": "耐水性",
    "answer": "たいすいせい",
    "meaning": "water resistance"
  },
  {
    "question": "毛筋",
    "answer": "けすじ",
    "meaning": "hair, hairline, minor details, comb lines in hair, comb tracks"
  },
  {
    "question": "揺すり",
    "answer": "ゆすり",
    "meaning": "blackmail, extortion, racketeering, blackmailer, extortionist"
  },
  {
    "question": "借り入れ",
    "answer": "かりいれ",
    "meaning": "debt"
  },
  {
    "question": "懲らす",
    "answer": "こらす",
    "meaning": "to chastise, to punish, to discipline"
  },
  {
    "question": "乞い願う",
    "answer": "こいねがう",
    "meaning": "to beg, to request, to beseech, to implore, to entreat"
  },
  {
    "question": "入眠",
    "answer": "にゅうみん",
    "meaning": "falling asleep, sleep onset"
  },
  {
    "question": "日本書紀",
    "answer": "にほんしょき",
    "meaning": "Nihon Shoki, Nihongi, Chronicles of Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "歴史小説",
    "answer": "れきししょうせつ",
    "meaning": "historical novel"
  },
  {
    "question": "早打ち",
    "answer": "はやうち",
    "meaning": "fast typing, fast beating, fast drumming"
  },
  {
    "question": "悲喜劇",
    "answer": "ひきげき",
    "meaning": "tragicomedy"
  },
  {
    "question": "分割統治",
    "answer": "ぶんかつとうち",
    "meaning": "divide and rule, divide and conquer"
  },
  {
    "question": "差し出る",
    "answer": "さしでる",
    "meaning": "to be forward, to stick one's nose into, to meddle, to be intrusive, to jut out, to protrude, to ove"
  },
  {
    "question": "弊",
    "answer": "へい",
    "meaning": "bad habit, harm, my, our"
  },
  {
    "question": "名演",
    "answer": "めいえん",
    "meaning": "fine performance, tour de force"
  },
  {
    "question": "抱え",
    "answer": "かかえ",
    "meaning": "armful, employee"
  },
  {
    "question": "渾然一体",
    "answer": "こんぜんいったい",
    "meaning": "in complete harmony"
  },
  {
    "question": "経済観念",
    "answer": "けいざいかんねん",
    "meaning": "sense of economy"
  },
  {
    "question": "言語学",
    "answer": "げんごがく",
    "meaning": "linguistics"
  },
  {
    "question": "利便",
    "answer": "りべん",
    "meaning": "convenience"
  },
  {
    "question": "他薦",
    "answer": "たせん,たぜん",
    "meaning": "recommendation"
  },
  {
    "question": "校名",
    "answer": "こうめい",
    "meaning": "name of a school"
  },
  {
    "question": "青田買い",
    "answer": "あおたがい",
    "meaning": "speculatively buying a rice harvest, while the fields are still green, recruiting of university stud"
  },
  {
    "question": "全国紙",
    "answer": "ぜんこくし",
    "meaning": "national paper, paper with a national circulation"
  },
  {
    "question": "見辛い",
    "answer": "みづらい",
    "meaning": "hard to see, indistinct, obscure, illegible, painful to look at"
  },
  {
    "question": "色即是空",
    "answer": "しきそくぜくう",
    "meaning": "form is emptiness, matter is void, all is vanity"
  },
  {
    "question": "爪立つ",
    "answer": "つまだつ",
    "meaning": "to stand on tiptoe"
  },
  {
    "question": "買い替え",
    "answer": "かいかえ",
    "meaning": "buying a replacement, replacing by buying something new"
  },
  {
    "question": "製造業",
    "answer": "せいぞうぎょう",
    "meaning": "manufacturing industry"
  },
  {
    "question": "縮れ毛",
    "answer": "ちぢれげ",
    "meaning": "curly hair, kinky hair, frizzy hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "仇をなす",
    "answer": "あだをなす",
    "meaning": "to do (someone) a wrong, to do (someone) an ill turn, to take revenge, to resent, to bear a grudge"
  },
  {
    "question": "預り",
    "answer": "あずかり",
    "meaning": "under custody, under supervision, undecided match, draw, tie"
  },
  {
    "question": "猛暑日",
    "answer": "もうしょび",
    "meaning": "extremely hot day, day on which the temperature rises above 35 degrees Celsius (official definition)"
  },
  {
    "question": "暴れ者",
    "answer": "あばれもの",
    "meaning": "roughneck"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷暗所",
    "answer": "れいあんしょ",
    "meaning": "cool, dark place"
  },
  {
    "question": "躓き",
    "answer": "つまずき",
    "meaning": "stumbling, failure, misstep"
  },
  {
    "question": "腹下し",
    "answer": "はらくだし",
    "meaning": "laxative, purgative, evacuant, loose bowels, diarrhea, diarrhoea"
  },
  {
    "question": "猫に小判",
    "answer": "ねこにこばん",
    "meaning": "pearls cast before swine, great waste"
  },
  {
    "question": "塞がり",
    "answer": "ふさがり,ふたがり",
    "meaning": "being closed, being blocked up, being occupied, hindrance, impedance, unlucky direction (in Onmyōdō;"
  },
  {
    "question": "王化",
    "answer": "おうか",
    "meaning": "imperial influence, assimilation of new territory"
  },
  {
    "question": "孵卵器",
    "answer": "ふらんき",
    "meaning": "incubator"
  },
  {
    "question": "美風",
    "answer": "びふう",
    "meaning": "beautiful custom, fine custom, good custom"
  },
  {
    "question": "羌",
    "answer": "きょう,きょん",
    "meaning": "Qiang (Chinese ethnic group), Reeves's muntjac (Muntiacus reeves, species of barking deer), Chinese"
  },
  {
    "question": "教場",
    "answer": "きょうじょう",
    "meaning": "classroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "三高",
    "answer": "さんこう",
    "meaning": "being highly educated, having a high salary and being tall, three highs, high-valued yen, high stock"
  },
  {
    "question": "舞殿",
    "answer": "まいどの",
    "meaning": "court music pavilion in a Shinto shrine, kagura hall"
  },
  {
    "question": "素因",
    "answer": "そいん",
    "meaning": "basic factor, (medical) predisposition, diathesis"
  },
  {
    "question": "反魂香",
    "answer": "はんごんこう",
    "meaning": "incense which supposedly allows the spirit of a departed loved one to be seen in the smoke"
  },
  {
    "question": "刀自",
    "answer": "とうじ,とじ",
    "meaning": "lady, matron, mistress, housekeeper"
  },
  {
    "question": "星祭り",
    "answer": "ほしまつり",
    "meaning": "Star Festival (held in July or August), Tanabata"
  },
  {
    "question": "胞衣",
    "answer": "えな,ほうい,ほうえ",
    "meaning": "afterbirth, placenta"
  },
  {
    "question": "梯団",
    "answer": "ていだん",
    "meaning": "echelon"
  },
  {
    "question": "校区",
    "answer": "こうく",
    "meaning": "school district, school area"
  },
  {
    "question": "農政",
    "answer": "のうせい",
    "meaning": "agricultural administration"
  },
  {
    "question": "住民投票",
    "answer": "じゅうみんとうひょう",
    "meaning": "local referendum, poll of residents, plebiscite"
  },
  {
    "question": "内廷",
    "answer": "ないてい",
    "meaning": "harem, inside the palace, the palace"
  },
  {
    "question": "来島",
    "answer": "らいとう",
    "meaning": "arriving on an island"
  },
  {
    "question": "優勝杯",
    "answer": "ゆうしょうはい",
    "meaning": "championship cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "祖師",
    "answer": "そし",
    "meaning": "founder of a sect"
  },
  {
    "question": "耐暑",
    "answer": "たいしょ",
    "meaning": "resistance to heat"
  },
  {
    "question": "宮様",
    "answer": "みやさま",
    "meaning": "prince, princess"
  },
  {
    "question": "偽金",
    "answer": "にせがね",
    "meaning": "counterfeit money"
  },
  {
    "question": "王朝時代",
    "answer": "おうちょうじだい",
    "meaning": "Dynastic period (the Nara period and esp. the Heian period, characterized by the rule of the emperor"
  },
  {
    "question": "病理学",
    "answer": "びょうりがく",
    "meaning": "pathology"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜祭り",
    "answer": "よまつり",
    "meaning": "night festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "継子",
    "answer": "ままこ,けいし,ままっこ",
    "meaning": "stepchild"
  },
  {
    "question": "余弦",
    "answer": "よげん",
    "meaning": "cosine"
  },
  {
    "question": "脳炎",
    "answer": "のうえん",
    "meaning": "brain inflammation, encephalitis, cerebritis"
  },
  {
    "question": "風靡",
    "answer": "ふうび",
    "meaning": "overwhelming, conquering, dominating, sweeping (the world), swaying"
  },
  {
    "question": "手塩",
    "answer": "てしお",
    "meaning": "table salt, small plate"
  },
  {
    "question": "其の方",
    "answer": "そのかた,そのほう",
    "meaning": "that person, you (referring to one's inferior)"
  },
  {
    "question": "杓",
    "answer": "ひしゃく,ひさく,しゃく",
    "meaning": "ladle, dipper, scoop, wild chervil (Anthriscus sylvestris), cow parsley, keck, Queen Anne's lace"
  },
  {
    "question": "紅花",
    "answer": "べにばな,こうか",
    "meaning": "safflower (Carthamus tinctorius), dyer's safflower"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿営",
    "answer": "しゅくえい",
    "meaning": "billeting, camp"
  },
  {
    "question": "日露",
    "answer": "にちろ",
    "meaning": "Japan and Russia, Russo-Japanese"
  },
  {
    "question": "綬",
    "answer": "じゅ",
    "meaning": "ribbon, cordon"
  },
  {
    "question": "水木",
    "answer": "みずき,すいもく",
    "meaning": "dogwood (Cornus controversa), Wednesday and Thursday"
  },
  {
    "question": "奔騰",
    "answer": "ほんとう",
    "meaning": "soar (e.g. in price), jump, boom, sudden ride"
  },
  {
    "question": "新茶",
    "answer": "しんちゃ",
    "meaning": "first tea of the season"
  },
  {
    "question": "山家",
    "answer": "やまが,さんか,さんげ",
    "meaning": "mountain villa, house in the mountains, mountain retreat, Mountain School (of Song-period Tiantai Bu"
  },
  {
    "question": "平生",
    "answer": "へいぜい",
    "meaning": "usual, ordinary"
  },
  {
    "question": "連関",
    "answer": "れんかん",
    "meaning": "connection, relation, linkage"
  },
  {
    "question": "倒幕",
    "answer": "とうばく",
    "meaning": "overthrow of the shogunate"
  },
  {
    "question": "菩提樹",
    "answer": "ぼだいじゅ",
    "meaning": "Tilia miqueliana (species of linden tree), sacred fig (Ficus religiosa), bodhi tree, bo tree, peepal"
  },
  {
    "question": "朱唇",
    "answer": "しゅしん",
    "meaning": "red lips"
  },
  {
    "question": "宇宙速度",
    "answer": "うちゅうそくど",
    "meaning": "escape velocity, orbital velocity, cosmic speed, space velocity"
  },
  {
    "question": "血小板",
    "answer": "けっしょうばん",
    "meaning": "platelet, thrombocyte"
  },
  {
    "question": "練習生",
    "answer": "れんしゅうせい",
    "meaning": "student, trainee"
  },
  {
    "question": "書見台",
    "answer": "しょけんだい",
    "meaning": "bookrest"
  },
  {
    "question": "星団",
    "answer": "せいだん",
    "meaning": "star cluster"
  },
  {
    "question": "酒保",
    "answer": "しゅほ",
    "meaning": "canteen, post exchange, PX"
  },
  {
    "question": "極右",
    "answer": "きょくう",
    "meaning": "far right (in politics), extreme right, ultraconservative"
  },
  {
    "question": "神楽殿",
    "answer": "かぐらでん",
    "meaning": "kagura hall (at a shrine), sacred dance stage"
  },
  {
    "question": "其奴",
    "answer": "そいつ,そやつ,すやつ",
    "meaning": "he, she, that person, that guy, that fellow, that, that one, that thing"
  },
  {
    "question": "御上",
    "answer": "おかみ",
    "meaning": "the Emperor, His Majesty, the government, the authorities, proprietress, hostess, landlady, mistress"
  },
  {
    "question": "音曲",
    "answer": "おんぎょく",
    "meaning": "songs with samisen accompaniment, musical performance"
  },
  {
    "question": "客員",
    "answer": "きゃくいん,かくいん",
    "meaning": "guest member, associate member, honorary member"
  },
  {
    "question": "国公立",
    "answer": "こっこうりつ",
    "meaning": "national and public"
  },
  {
    "question": "下足",
    "answer": "げそく,げそ",
    "meaning": "footwear (esp. outdoor shoes, as opposed to slippers, etc.), footgear, squid tentacles"
  },
  {
    "question": "屋形船",
    "answer": "やかたぶね",
    "meaning": "houseboat, pleasure boat (large, roofed)"
  },
  {
    "question": "担々麺",
    "answer": "タンタンめん",
    "meaning": "Szechuan dish of noodles covered with a sauce of sesame paste and chili oil"
  },
  {
    "question": "英米",
    "answer": "えいべい",
    "meaning": "Britain-America"
  },
  {
    "question": "雷鳥",
    "answer": "らいちょう",
    "meaning": "ptarmigan (Lagopus muta, esp. the Japanese ptarmigan, Lagopus muta japonica), grouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "傾城",
    "answer": "けいせい",
    "meaning": "beauty, siren, courtesan, prostitute"
  },
  {
    "question": "入庁",
    "answer": "にゅうちょう",
    "meaning": "becoming employed by a government office, agency, board, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "悉",
    "answer": "ことごと",
    "meaning": "everything"
  },
  {
    "question": "酒粕",
    "answer": "さけかす",
    "meaning": "sake lees"
  },
  {
    "question": "納骨堂",
    "answer": "のうこつどう",
    "meaning": "ossuary, crypt, charnel house"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀玉",
    "answer": "ぎんだま",
    "meaning": "silver ball"
  },
  {
    "question": "長打",
    "answer": "ちょうだ",
    "meaning": "long hit, slugging, extra-base hit"
  },
  {
    "question": "学童保育",
    "answer": "がくどうほいく",
    "meaning": "care of schoolchildren outside of school time"
  },
  {
    "question": "排水路",
    "answer": "はいすいろ",
    "meaning": "drainage channel"
  },
  {
    "question": "最高裁",
    "answer": "さいこうさい",
    "meaning": "Supreme Court"
  },
  {
    "question": "書類送検",
    "answer": "しょるいそうけん",
    "meaning": "sending documents to a prosecutor, filing charges"
  },
  {
    "question": "雛人形",
    "answer": "ひなにんぎょう",
    "meaning": "hina doll, doll displayed during the Girls' Festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪魔払い",
    "answer": "あくまばらい",
    "meaning": "exorcism"
  },
  {
    "question": "枯木",
    "answer": "かれき",
    "meaning": "dead tree, withered tree, leafless tree, bare tree"
  },
  {
    "question": "和三盆",
    "answer": "わさんぼん",
    "meaning": "refined Japanese sugar"
  },
  {
    "question": "余禄",
    "answer": "よろく",
    "meaning": "additional gain"
  },
  {
    "question": "内風呂",
    "answer": "うちぶろ",
    "meaning": "indoor bath, bath for family (not public) use"
  },
  {
    "question": "平家物語",
    "answer": "へいけものがたり",
    "meaning": "The Tale of the Heike, Heike Monogatari"
  },
  {
    "question": "有線放送",
    "answer": "ゆうせんほうそう",
    "meaning": "cable broadcast"
  },
  {
    "question": "内ゲバ",
    "answer": "うちゲバ",
    "meaning": "violence within a (student) sect, internal strife"
  },
  {
    "question": "回想録",
    "answer": "かいそうろく",
    "meaning": "memoirs, reminiscence"
  },
  {
    "question": "佞臣",
    "answer": "ねいしん",
    "meaning": "crafty courtier, traitor"
  },
  {
    "question": "自尊",
    "answer": "じそん",
    "meaning": "self-respect, esteem, self-importance, pride"
  },
  {
    "question": "復員",
    "answer": "ふくいん",
    "meaning": "demobilization, demobilisation, repatriation"
  },
  {
    "question": "浮沈",
    "answer": "ふちん",
    "meaning": "floating and sinking, rise and fall, ebb and flow, ups and downs"
  },
  {
    "question": "人生哲学",
    "answer": "じんせいてつがく",
    "meaning": "philosophy of life"
  },
  {
    "question": "剣光",
    "answer": "けんこう",
    "meaning": "light emanating from a sword, shimmering of a sword"
  },
  {
    "question": "論証",
    "answer": "ろんしょう",
    "meaning": "proof, certain truth, demonstration, argumentation"
  },
  {
    "question": "虱",
    "answer": "しらみ,しし",
    "meaning": "louse (esp. a sucking louse), lice"
  },
  {
    "question": "イタ電",
    "answer": "イタでん",
    "meaning": "crank call, prank call, nuisance call, train decorated with anime characters"
  },
  {
    "question": "大太鼓",
    "answer": "おおだいこ,だだいこ",
    "meaning": "large drum, bass drum, dadaiko drum, large drum used for outdoor bugaku and gagaku performances"
  },
  {
    "question": "妥結",
    "answer": "だけつ",
    "meaning": "settlement, an agreement"
  },
  {
    "question": "都市化",
    "answer": "としか",
    "meaning": "urbanization, urbanisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "覘く",
    "answer": "のぞく",
    "meaning": "to peek (through a keyhole, gap, etc.), to look down into (a ravine, etc.), to peek into (a shop, bo"
  },
  {
    "question": "消化管",
    "answer": "しょうかかん",
    "meaning": "alimentary canal"
  },
  {
    "question": "空メール",
    "answer": "からメール",
    "meaning": "blank email (e.g. for signing up to an email list)"
  },
  {
    "question": "高野豆腐",
    "answer": "こうやどうふ",
    "meaning": "freeze-dried tofu"
  },
  {
    "question": "愉楽",
    "answer": "ゆらく",
    "meaning": "pleasure"
  },
  {
    "question": "流動性",
    "answer": "りゅうどうせい",
    "meaning": "liquidity (esp. financial), fluidity, mobility (social, job, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "捲土重来",
    "answer": "けんどじゅうらい,けんどちょうらい",
    "meaning": "recouping one's strength for a renewed attack (on), making another attempt with redoubled efforts"
  },
  {
    "question": "催涙",
    "answer": "さいるい",
    "meaning": "lacrimator, dacryagogue, tear-inducing agent"
  },
  {
    "question": "見返し",
    "answer": "みかえし",
    "meaning": "endpaper (of a book), end-paper, facing (material sewn on the inside edge of a garment), looking bac"
  },
  {
    "question": "国是",
    "answer": "こくぜ",
    "meaning": "national policy"
  },
  {
    "question": "凧揚げ",
    "answer": "たこあげ",
    "meaning": "kite flying"
  },
  {
    "question": "番傘",
    "answer": "ばんがさ",
    "meaning": "coarse oilpaper umbrella"
  },
  {
    "question": "大相撲",
    "answer": "おおずもう",
    "meaning": "professional sumo wrestling"
  },
  {
    "question": "遺留",
    "answer": "いりゅう",
    "meaning": "bequest"
  },
  {
    "question": "路駐",
    "answer": "ろちゅう",
    "meaning": "parking on the streets, on-street parking"
  },
  {
    "question": "促成栽培",
    "answer": "そくせいさいばい",
    "meaning": "forcing (plants, vegetables, etc.), artificially hastening the growth of plants (by controlling heat"
  },
  {
    "question": "乱視",
    "answer": "らんし",
    "meaning": "astigmatism"
  },
  {
    "question": "追い撃ち",
    "answer": "おいうち",
    "meaning": "attacking a fleeing enemy, additional attack on a weakened enemy, additional blow to an already unfo"
  },
  {
    "question": "入来",
    "answer": "にゅうらい",
    "meaning": "august visit, arrival"
  },
  {
    "question": "二叉",
    "answer": "ふたまた",
    "meaning": "seeing two people (i.e. romantically) at the same time, two-timing, bifurcation, fork, branch, dicho"
  },
  {
    "question": "笑い皺",
    "answer": "わらいじわ",
    "meaning": "laugh line, smile line, nasolabial fold"
  },
  {
    "question": "狂言回し",
    "answer": "きょうげんまわし",
    "meaning": "supporting, but indispensable role, major supporting role"
  },
  {
    "question": "墓参",
    "answer": "はかまいり,ぼさん",
    "meaning": "visit to a grave"
  },
  {
    "question": "涼気",
    "answer": "りょうき",
    "meaning": "cool air"
  },
  {
    "question": "球面",
    "answer": "きゅうめん",
    "meaning": "spherical surface"
  },
  {
    "question": "足形",
    "answer": "あしがた",
    "meaning": "footprint, soleprint, last, wooden mold for shoes or tabi (mould)"
  },
  {
    "question": "綿埃",
    "answer": "わたぼこり",
    "meaning": "dustballs, cotton dust, fluff, flecks of fibre (fiber)"
  },
  {
    "question": "噎ぶ",
    "answer": "むせぶ",
    "meaning": "to be choked, to be stifled, to be smothered"
  },
  {
    "question": "乾燥剤",
    "answer": "かんそうざい",
    "meaning": "drying agent"
  },
  {
    "question": "重層的",
    "answer": "じゅうそうてき",
    "meaning": "stratified, multilayered"
  },
  {
    "question": "行楽地",
    "answer": "こうらくち",
    "meaning": "tourist resort, holiday resort"
  },
  {
    "question": "巻き尺",
    "answer": "まきじゃく",
    "meaning": "tape measure"
  },
  {
    "question": "仰向く",
    "answer": "あおむく",
    "meaning": "to look upward"
  },
  {
    "question": "湯治場",
    "answer": "とうじば",
    "meaning": "hot-spring health resort"
  },
  {
    "question": "洗い桶",
    "answer": "あらいおけ",
    "meaning": "washtub, dishpan, washing-up bowl"
  },
  {
    "question": "儲け物",
    "answer": "もうけもの",
    "meaning": "good bargain, (a) find, godsend, (a) steal"
  },
  {
    "question": "ソーダ水",
    "answer": "ソーダすい",
    "meaning": "soda water"
  },
  {
    "question": "落成",
    "answer": "らくせい",
    "meaning": "completion (of a building)"
  },
  {
    "question": "情報通信",
    "answer": "じょうほうつうしん",
    "meaning": "telecommunications"
  },
  {
    "question": "星条旗",
    "answer": "せいじょうき",
    "meaning": "Stars and Stripes (US flag), Star-Spangled Banner (US anthem)"
  },
  {
    "question": "完膚",
    "answer": "かんぷ",
    "meaning": "unwounded skin"
  },
  {
    "question": "耳鼻科",
    "answer": "じびか",
    "meaning": "otolaryngology, ear, nose, and throat department"
  },
  {
    "question": "曳光弾",
    "answer": "えいこうだん",
    "meaning": "tracer bullet, star shell, flare bomb"
  },
  {
    "question": "ちょい役",
    "answer": "ちょいやく",
    "meaning": "small part (e.g. in a film), bit part, extra"
  },
  {
    "question": "難行",
    "answer": "なんぎょう",
    "meaning": "penance"
  },
  {
    "question": "幸甚",
    "answer": "こうじん",
    "meaning": "pleased, obliged, appreciative"
  },
  {
    "question": "機能障害",
    "answer": "きのうしょうがい",
    "meaning": "functional disorder, dysfunction"
  },
  {
    "question": "感受",
    "answer": "かんじゅ",
    "meaning": "(radio) receptivity, sensitivity, susceptibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "質実",
    "answer": "しつじつ",
    "meaning": "simplicity, plainness"
  },
  {
    "question": "魚卵",
    "answer": "ぎょらん",
    "meaning": "fish eggs, roe, hard roe"
  },
  {
    "question": "青魚",
    "answer": "あおざかな,あおうお",
    "meaning": "blueback (any fish with a bluish back, such as the Japanese sardine), black carp (Mylopharyngodon pi"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸損",
    "answer": "まるぞん",
    "meaning": "total loss"
  },
  {
    "question": "歯痛",
    "answer": "しつう,はいた",
    "meaning": "toothache"
  },
  {
    "question": "切抜き",
    "answer": "きりぬき",
    "meaning": "clipping (of newspaper article, etc.), cutting, scrap (for a scrapbook), cut-out (picture, coloured"
  },
  {
    "question": "金属疲労",
    "answer": "きんぞくひろう",
    "meaning": "metal fatigue"
  },
  {
    "question": "空撮",
    "answer": "くうさつ",
    "meaning": "aerial photography"
  },
  {
    "question": "触り合う",
    "answer": "ふりあう",
    "meaning": "to touch each other"
  },
  {
    "question": "陰々滅々",
    "answer": "いんいんめつめつ",
    "meaning": "gloomy and depressing, mournful"
  },
  {
    "question": "熨斗",
    "answer": "のし,ぬし",
    "meaning": "noshi, long thin strip of dried abalone in folded patterned paper, attached to a gift"
  },
  {
    "question": "千手観音",
    "answer": "せんじゅかんのん",
    "meaning": "thousand-armed Avalokiteshvara, thousand-armed Kannon"
  },
  {
    "question": "帰りしな",
    "answer": "かえりしな",
    "meaning": "when about to go back, on the way back, on the way home"
  },
  {
    "question": "足掛け",
    "answer": "あしかけ",
    "meaning": "leg trip (in sumo, judo, etc.), foothold, pedal, indicates a consecutive period of time incl. incomp"
  },
  {
    "question": "鬼が笑う",
    "answer": "おにがわらう",
    "meaning": "to be laughable, to be unrealistic"
  },
  {
    "question": "思し召す",
    "answer": "おぼしめす",
    "meaning": "to think (only used to speak of others), to turn one's attention toward (only used to speak of other"
  },
  {
    "question": "学校法人",
    "answer": "がっこうほうじん",
    "meaning": "(legally) incorporated educational institution"
  },
  {
    "question": "三顧の礼",
    "answer": "さんこのれい",
    "meaning": "showing special confidence and courtesy (to someone, often to convince them to take a post, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "生臭",
    "answer": "なまぐさ",
    "meaning": "something that smells of fish or blood, meat and fish, degenerate monk, corrupt priest"
  },
  {
    "question": "床面積",
    "answer": "ゆかめんせき",
    "meaning": "floor space"
  },
  {
    "question": "物議",
    "answer": "ぶつぎ",
    "meaning": "public discussion, public criticism, controversy"
  },
  {
    "question": "申込み",
    "answer": "もうしこみ",
    "meaning": "application, entry, request, subscription, offer, proposal, overture, challenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "百選",
    "answer": "ひゃくせん",
    "meaning": "top hundred, hundred best"
  },
  {
    "question": "降水量",
    "answer": "こうすいりょう",
    "meaning": "amount of precipitation, precipitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "雲泥",
    "answer": "うんでい",
    "meaning": "great difference"
  },
  {
    "question": "身を窶す",
    "answer": "みをやつす",
    "meaning": "to be enthralled by, to be disguised as"
  },
  {
    "question": "断続",
    "answer": "だんぞく",
    "meaning": "intermittence, being intermittent, occurring intermittently"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽佻浮薄",
    "answer": "けいちょうふはく",
    "meaning": "frivolity, levity, shallowness, superficiality"
  },
  {
    "question": "柱状",
    "answer": "ちゅうじょう",
    "meaning": "shape of a pillar or column"
  },
  {
    "question": "果報",
    "answer": "かほう",
    "meaning": "good fortune, luck, happiness, vipaka (retribution)"
  },
  {
    "question": "一計",
    "answer": "いっけい",
    "meaning": "plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "枝振り",
    "answer": "えだぶり",
    "meaning": "shape of a tree"
  },
  {
    "question": "玉石混淆",
    "answer": "ぎょくせきこんこう",
    "meaning": "mixture of wheat and chaff, mixture of the good and bad, jumble of wheat and tares"
  },
  {
    "question": "口軽",
    "answer": "くちがる",
    "meaning": "loose-lipped, talkative"
  },
  {
    "question": "何遍",
    "answer": "なんべん",
    "meaning": "how many times, how often"
  },
  {
    "question": "作り事",
    "answer": "つくりごと",
    "meaning": "fabrication, lie, fiction"
  },
  {
    "question": "十二指腸",
    "answer": "じゅうにしちょう",
    "meaning": "duodenum"
  },
  {
    "question": "異彩",
    "answer": "いさい",
    "meaning": "conspicuousness (usu. color), prominence, distinctiveness"
  },
  {
    "question": "慈善家",
    "answer": "じぜんか",
    "meaning": "charitable person, philanthropist"
  },
  {
    "question": "快楽主義",
    "answer": "かいらくしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "hedonism"
  },
  {
    "question": "長々しい",
    "answer": "ながながしい",
    "meaning": "long, drawn-out, tedious"
  },
  {
    "question": "生活者",
    "answer": "せいかつしゃ",
    "meaning": "consumer, ordinary citizen, stakeholder, person who lives on (e.g. situation, income, place)"
  },
  {
    "question": "塞翁が馬",
    "answer": "さいおうがうま",
    "meaning": "the future is unpredictable, inscrutable are the ways of heaven, the irony of fate"
  },
  {
    "question": "常軌",
    "answer": "じょうき",
    "meaning": "normal course (of action), proper course, regular way"
  },
  {
    "question": "是認",
    "answer": "ぜにん",
    "meaning": "approval"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い渋る",
    "answer": "いいしぶる",
    "meaning": "to hesitate to say"
  },
  {
    "question": "糠に釘",
    "answer": "ぬかにくぎ",
    "meaning": "having no effect, waste of effort"
  },
  {
    "question": "年寄る",
    "answer": "としよる",
    "meaning": "to grow old"
  },
  {
    "question": "慰む",
    "answer": "なぐさむ",
    "meaning": "to feel comforted, to be in good spirits, to feel better, to forget one's worries, to trifle with, t"
  },
  {
    "question": "天祐",
    "answer": "てんゆう",
    "meaning": "divine aid, divine grace, providential help"
  },
  {
    "question": "正正",
    "answer": "せいせい",
    "meaning": "accurate, exact, punctual, neat"
  },
  {
    "question": "原器",
    "answer": "げんき",
    "meaning": "standard (for weights and measures)"
  },
  {
    "question": "門中",
    "answer": "もんちゅう",
    "meaning": "family clan based on the paternal line, sharing the same tomb and performing rituals together (Okina"
  },
  {
    "question": "吹部",
    "answer": "すいぶ",
    "meaning": "concert band (at a school), wind ensemble"
  },
  {
    "question": "祥",
    "answer": "しょう",
    "meaning": "omen (usu. good), (auspicious) sign, first two anniversaries of a person's death"
  },
  {
    "question": "聖画",
    "answer": "せいが",
    "meaning": "religious painting, sacred painting"
  },
  {
    "question": "揚羽",
    "answer": "あげは",
    "meaning": "swallowtail butterfly (esp. the citrus swallowtail butterfly, Papilio xuthus)"
  },
  {
    "question": "堀江",
    "answer": "ほりえ",
    "meaning": "canal"
  },
  {
    "question": "一向一揆",
    "answer": "いっこういっき",
    "meaning": "Jōdo Shinshū Buddhist uprising (Muromachi and Warring States periods)"
  },
  {
    "question": "尸",
    "answer": "しかばね,かばね,し",
    "meaning": "corpse, kanji 'corpse' radical"
  },
  {
    "question": "五山",
    "answer": "ごさん,ござん",
    "meaning": "five most important temples of a region"
  },
  {
    "question": "法王庁",
    "answer": "ほうおうちょう",
    "meaning": "Curia"
  },
  {
    "question": "分署",
    "answer": "ぶんしょ",
    "meaning": "substation, branch office"
  },
  {
    "question": "兎馬",
    "answer": "うさぎうま",
    "meaning": "donkey"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿坊",
    "answer": "しゅくぼう",
    "meaning": "visitor's or pilgrims' lodgings in a temple, priest's quarters"
  },
  {
    "question": "五節",
    "answer": "ごせつ",
    "meaning": "the five festivals (January 7, March 3, May 5, July 7 and September 9)"
  },
  {
    "question": "受容器",
    "answer": "じゅようき",
    "meaning": "receptor, acceptor"
  },
  {
    "question": "土方",
    "answer": "どかた,つちかた",
    "meaning": "construction worker, laborer (labourer), navvy"
  },
  {
    "question": "自縛",
    "answer": "じばく",
    "meaning": "being circumscribed by one's own words and actions"
  },
  {
    "question": "決選投票",
    "answer": "けっせんとうひょう",
    "meaning": "final vote, run-off ballot"
  },
  {
    "question": "飴屋",
    "answer": "あめや",
    "meaning": "candy shop, candy maker"
  },
  {
    "question": "促成",
    "answer": "そくせい",
    "meaning": "promotion of growth"
  },
  {
    "question": "弾道弾",
    "answer": "だんどうだん",
    "meaning": "(ballistic) missile"
  },
  {
    "question": "巻き物",
    "answer": "まきもの",
    "meaning": "scroll, rolled book, makimono, scarf, muffler, stole, sushi made rolled in nori seaweed with a core"
  },
  {
    "question": "学府",
    "answer": "がくふ",
    "meaning": "educational institution, academic centre, academic center"
  },
  {
    "question": "南北朝",
    "answer": "なんぼくちょう",
    "meaning": "Northern and Southern Courts (Japan, 1336-1392), Northern and Southern Dynasties, Northern and South"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜来",
    "answer": "やらい",
    "meaning": "overnight, since last night"
  },
  {
    "question": "咬合",
    "answer": "こうごう",
    "meaning": "occlusion (dentistry)"
  },
  {
    "question": "性的指向",
    "answer": "せいてきしこう",
    "meaning": "sexual orientation"
  },
  {
    "question": "海王星",
    "answer": "かいおうせい",
    "meaning": "Neptune (planet)"
  },
  {
    "question": "霊地",
    "answer": "れいち",
    "meaning": "sacred ground"
  },
  {
    "question": "月見草",
    "answer": "つきみそう",
    "meaning": "evening primrose (esp. the fourwing evening primrose, Oenothera tetraptera)"
  },
  {
    "question": "野苺",
    "answer": "のいちご",
    "meaning": "wild strawberry (Fragaria vesca)"
  },
  {
    "question": "詔",
    "answer": "みことのり,しょう",
    "meaning": "imperial decree, imperial edict"
  },
  {
    "question": "珪素",
    "answer": "けいそ",
    "meaning": "silicon (Si)"
  },
  {
    "question": "幻肢痛",
    "answer": "げんしつう",
    "meaning": "phantom pain"
  },
  {
    "question": "指相撲",
    "answer": "ゆびずもう",
    "meaning": "thumb wrestling"
  },
  {
    "question": "磁気嵐",
    "answer": "じきあらし",
    "meaning": "magnetic storm"
  },
  {
    "question": "植物人間",
    "answer": "しょくぶつにんげん",
    "meaning": "human vegetable (i.e. someone in a vegetative state)"
  },
  {
    "question": "水浴",
    "answer": "すいよく",
    "meaning": "a bath, bathing"
  },
  {
    "question": "揺動",
    "answer": "ようどう",
    "meaning": "titubation, shaking, swinging"
  },
  {
    "question": "取引所",
    "answer": "とりひきじょ",
    "meaning": "(a stock) exchange"
  },
  {
    "question": "僧形",
    "answer": "そうぎょう",
    "meaning": "the form of a Buddhist priest, priestly attire"
  },
  {
    "question": "信楽焼",
    "answer": "しがらきやき",
    "meaning": "Shigaraki ware"
  },
  {
    "question": "生起",
    "answer": "せいき",
    "meaning": "occurrence, taking place, happening"
  },
  {
    "question": "特赦",
    "answer": "とくしゃ",
    "meaning": "special pardon, (general) amnesty"
  },
  {
    "question": "監察医",
    "answer": "かんさつい",
    "meaning": "medical coroner, medical examiner"
  },
  {
    "question": "薬包紙",
    "answer": "やくほうし",
    "meaning": "paper for wrapping powdered medicine"
  },
  {
    "question": "搗く",
    "answer": "つく",
    "meaning": "to hull (rice, barley, etc.), to pound (rice), to polish (rice), to stamp (ore)"
  },
  {
    "question": "円座",
    "answer": "えんざ",
    "meaning": "sitting in circle, round straw mat"
  },
  {
    "question": "履",
    "answer": "くつ",
    "meaning": "shoe, shoes, boots, footwear, footgear"
  },
  {
    "question": "砲列",
    "answer": "ほうれつ",
    "meaning": "battery (of artillery, cameras, etc.), barrage"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄木細工",
    "answer": "よせぎざいく",
    "meaning": "wooden mosaic work, parquetry, wooden mosaic (e.g. on a piece of furniture), marquetry, marqueterie"
  },
  {
    "question": "誘導路",
    "answer": "ゆうどうろ",
    "meaning": "taxiway"
  },
  {
    "question": "執り成す",
    "answer": "とりなす",
    "meaning": "to mediate, to intervene, to smooth"
  },
  {
    "question": "発行者",
    "answer": "はっこうしゃ",
    "meaning": "issuer, publisher"
  },
  {
    "question": "繁い",
    "answer": "しげい",
    "meaning": "frequent, densely packed, thick"
  },
  {
    "question": "筆算",
    "answer": "ひっさん",
    "meaning": "calculating on paper, writing and arithmetic"
  },
  {
    "question": "返書",
    "answer": "へんしょ",
    "meaning": "reply (to a letter), response, answer"
  },
  {
    "question": "巻毛",
    "answer": "まきげ",
    "meaning": "curl, curly hair, ringlet"
  },
  {
    "question": "豪い",
    "answer": "えらい",
    "meaning": "great, excellent, admirable, remarkable, distinguished, important, celebrated, famous, eminent, very"
  },
  {
    "question": "外交使節",
    "answer": "がいこうしせつ",
    "meaning": "diplomat"
  },
  {
    "question": "性悪説",
    "answer": "せいあくせつ",
    "meaning": "cynicism (of mankind), belief that human nature is fundamentally evil"
  },
  {
    "question": "熱気球",
    "answer": "ねつききゅう,ねっききゅう",
    "meaning": "hot-air balloon"
  },
  {
    "question": "閲",
    "answer": "えつ",
    "meaning": "inspection (esp. of a document), stamp of approval (for a document)"
  },
  {
    "question": "我執",
    "answer": "がしゅう",
    "meaning": "egotism, obstinacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "秋田犬",
    "answer": "あきたけん,あきたいぬ",
    "meaning": "Akita (breed of dog)"
  },
  {
    "question": "濁り酒",
    "answer": "にごりざけ",
    "meaning": "unrefined sake, unfiltered sake, cloudy sake"
  },
  {
    "question": "禿鷹",
    "answer": "はげたか",
    "meaning": "vulture, condor"
  },
  {
    "question": "階段室",
    "answer": "かいだんしつ",
    "meaning": "stairwell, stair hall, staircase"
  },
  {
    "question": "伊勢神宮",
    "answer": "いせじんぐう",
    "meaning": "Ise Grand Shrine"
  },
  {
    "question": "親機",
    "answer": "おやき",
    "meaning": "base unit, main telephone (esp. when there are extensions)"
  },
  {
    "question": "頸木",
    "answer": "くびき",
    "meaning": "yoke, constraints, oppression"
  },
  {
    "question": "貴下",
    "answer": "きか",
    "meaning": "you"
  },
  {
    "question": "塩鮭",
    "answer": "しおざけ",
    "meaning": "salted salmon"
  },
  {
    "question": "閲兵",
    "answer": "えっぺい",
    "meaning": "parade, review (of troops)"
  },
  {
    "question": "尤",
    "answer": "ゆう",
    "meaning": "superb, outstanding"
  },
  {
    "question": "帝釈天",
    "answer": "たいしゃくてん",
    "meaning": "Śakra (Deva), Shakra, Indra, Shakra Devanam Indra, the king of heaven in Hindu mythology"
  },
  {
    "question": "教化",
    "answer": "きょうか,きょうけ,きょうげ",
    "meaning": "education, enlightenment, civilization, civilisation, indoctrination, guidance, teaching people and"
  },
  {
    "question": "暁闇",
    "answer": "あかつきやみ,あかときやみ,ぎょうあん",
    "meaning": "moonless dawn, dark before dawn"
  },
  {
    "question": "橋桁",
    "answer": "はしげた",
    "meaning": "bridge girder"
  },
  {
    "question": "天下太平",
    "answer": "てんかたいへい",
    "meaning": "peace and tranquillity, halcyon times of peace, peaceful world"
  },
  {
    "question": "原版",
    "answer": "げんぱん,げんばん",
    "meaning": "form (printing), forme, typesetting plate, original plate, original edition (of a publication)"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑役",
    "answer": "ざつえき",
    "meaning": "chore, odd job"
  },
  {
    "question": "楽屋裏",
    "answer": "がくやうら",
    "meaning": "dressing room, green room, backstage, inside story, confidential talk, hidden circumstances"
  },
  {
    "question": "守旧",
    "answer": "しゅきゅう",
    "meaning": "conservatism"
  },
  {
    "question": "決まり手",
    "answer": "きまりて",
    "meaning": "clincher, winning technique, official winning technique"
  },
  {
    "question": "謀叛",
    "answer": "むほん,ぼうはん",
    "meaning": "rebellion, uprising, insurrection, treason"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎬",
    "answer": "しのぎ",
    "meaning": "ridge on the side of a sword blade, ridged pattern"
  },
  {
    "question": "整数",
    "answer": "せいすう",
    "meaning": "integer"
  },
  {
    "question": "断水",
    "answer": "だんすい",
    "meaning": "suspension of water supply, water outage"
  },
  {
    "question": "博士課程",
    "answer": "はくしかてい,はかせかてい",
    "meaning": "doctoral course"
  },
  {
    "question": "弱卒",
    "answer": "じゃくそつ",
    "meaning": "cowardly soldier"
  },
  {
    "question": "辞儀",
    "answer": "じぎ,じんぎ",
    "meaning": "(bowing and) greeting, declining, refusing"
  },
  {
    "question": "閉校",
    "answer": "へいこう",
    "meaning": "closing a school"
  },
  {
    "question": "噴火口",
    "answer": "ふんかこう",
    "meaning": "(volcanic) crater"
  },
  {
    "question": "眼底",
    "answer": "がんてい",
    "meaning": "fundus of the eye"
  },
  {
    "question": "興趣",
    "answer": "きょうしゅ",
    "meaning": "interest (in something)"
  },
  {
    "question": "流鏑馬",
    "answer": "やぶさめ",
    "meaning": "horseback archery"
  },
  {
    "question": "称揚",
    "answer": "しょうよう",
    "meaning": "praise, admiration, exalting, extolling"
  },
  {
    "question": "昆布巻き",
    "answer": "こぶまき,こんぶまき",
    "meaning": "type of food (sliced dried herring or other fish wrapped in kombu seaweed and boiled)"
  },
  {
    "question": "筆名",
    "answer": "ひつめい",
    "meaning": "alias, pseudonym, pen name, nom de plume"
  },
  {
    "question": "骨組",
    "answer": "ほねぐみ",
    "meaning": "skeletal frame, skeleton, build, physique, framework, frame, structure, outline"
  },
  {
    "question": "小倅",
    "answer": "こせがれ",
    "meaning": "one's son, you little bastard, you little brat"
  },
  {
    "question": "臣籍",
    "answer": "しんせき",
    "meaning": "status of a subject"
  },
  {
    "question": "状勢",
    "answer": "じょうせい",
    "meaning": "state of things, state of affairs, condition, situation, circumstances"
  },
  {
    "question": "言行",
    "answer": "げんこう",
    "meaning": "speech and behaviour (behavior)"
  },
  {
    "question": "警報器",
    "answer": "けいほうき",
    "meaning": "alarm (fire, burglar, railroad-crossing, etc.), sensor"
  },
  {
    "question": "規格品",
    "answer": "きかくひん",
    "meaning": "standardized article or goods, standardised article or goods"
  },
  {
    "question": "無税",
    "answer": "むぜい",
    "meaning": "duty-free, tax-free"
  },
  {
    "question": "腹巻",
    "answer": "はらまき",
    "meaning": "haramaki, bellyband, stomach band, stomach covering (worn for warmth), torso armour that opens at th"
  },
  {
    "question": "列伝",
    "answer": "れつでん",
    "meaning": "series of biographies"
  },
  {
    "question": "国際連合",
    "answer": "こくさいれんごう",
    "meaning": "United Nations"
  },
  {
    "question": "圧制",
    "answer": "あっせい",
    "meaning": "oppression, tyranny, despotism"
  },
  {
    "question": "釣り船",
    "answer": "つりぶね,つりふね",
    "meaning": "fishing boat, boat-shaped hanging flower vase"
  },
  {
    "question": "繻子",
    "answer": "しゅす",
    "meaning": "satin"
  },
  {
    "question": "青物",
    "answer": "あおもの",
    "meaning": "vegetables, (edible) greens, blueback (any fish with a bluish back, such as the Japanese sardine)"
  },
  {
    "question": "廃物",
    "answer": "はいぶつ",
    "meaning": "scrap, junk, waste material"
  },
  {
    "question": "貸付",
    "answer": "かしつけ",
    "meaning": "loan"
  },
  {
    "question": "大見出し",
    "answer": "おおみだし",
    "meaning": "banner headline"
  },
  {
    "question": "試写",
    "answer": "ししゃ",
    "meaning": "preview, private showing"
  },
  {
    "question": "舞台稽古",
    "answer": "ぶたいげいこ",
    "meaning": "dress rehearsal"
  },
  {
    "question": "為さる",
    "answer": "なさる",
    "meaning": "to do"
  },
  {
    "question": "温む",
    "answer": "ぬるむ",
    "meaning": "to become lukewarm, to become tepid"
  },
  {
    "question": "牽強付会",
    "answer": "けんきょうふかい",
    "meaning": "farfetched (argument, opinion), forced (sense, view), strained (interpretation), distorted"
  },
  {
    "question": "妖婦",
    "answer": "ようふ",
    "meaning": "enchantress, seductress, vamp"
  },
  {
    "question": "否応無く",
    "answer": "いやおうなく",
    "meaning": "whether one wants to or not, without choice"
  },
  {
    "question": "肺病",
    "answer": "はいびょう",
    "meaning": "lung disease, chest trouble, pulmonary tuberculosis"
  },
  {
    "question": "復元力",
    "answer": "ふくげんりょく",
    "meaning": "righting moment, restoring force, stability"
  },
  {
    "question": "統轄",
    "answer": "とうかつ",
    "meaning": "unification, bringing together, generalization, control, supervision"
  },
  {
    "question": "横飛び",
    "answer": "よことび",
    "meaning": "jumping sideways, flying sideways, running hurriedly (with one's body bent forward)"
  },
  {
    "question": "長期記憶",
    "answer": "ちょうききおく",
    "meaning": "long-term memory"
  },
  {
    "question": "大箱",
    "answer": "おおばこ",
    "meaning": "large box, chest"
  },
  {
    "question": "美人薄命",
    "answer": "びじんはくめい",
    "meaning": "beauty and fortune seldom go together, the beautiful die young"
  },
  {
    "question": "邪魔物",
    "answer": "じゃまもの",
    "meaning": "obstacle, hindrance, impediment, obstruction, nuisance, bore, burden"
  },
  {
    "question": "不連続",
    "answer": "ふれんぞく",
    "meaning": "discontinuity"
  },
  {
    "question": "骨壺",
    "answer": "こつつぼ",
    "meaning": "funerary urn, cinerary urn, burial urn, cremation urn"
  },
  {
    "question": "品質管理",
    "answer": "ひんしつかんり",
    "meaning": "quality control"
  },
  {
    "question": "立脚",
    "answer": "りっきゃく",
    "meaning": "being based on"
  },
  {
    "question": "保険料",
    "answer": "ほけんりょう",
    "meaning": "insurance premium"
  },
  {
    "question": "早い事",
    "answer": "はやいこと",
    "meaning": "quickly"
  },
  {
    "question": "損切り",
    "answer": "そんぎり",
    "meaning": "loss-cutting, cutting one's losses"
  },
  {
    "question": "出合い",
    "answer": "であい",
    "meaning": "meeting, rendezvous, encounter, confluence"
  },
  {
    "question": "小玉",
    "answer": "こだま",
    "meaning": "small ball, globule, bead, small vegetable or piece of fruit"
  },
  {
    "question": "年賀",
    "answer": "ねんが",
    "meaning": "New Year's greetings, New Year's call, New Year's gift"
  },
  {
    "question": "忠臣蔵",
    "answer": "ちゅうしんぐら",
    "meaning": "performance or narrative based on the story of the Forty-seven Rōnin (esp. the Kanadehon Chūshingura"
  },
  {
    "question": "以北",
    "answer": "いほく",
    "meaning": "north of, and northward"
  },
  {
    "question": "轢死",
    "answer": "れきし",
    "meaning": "death by being run over"
  },
  {
    "question": "須く",
    "answer": "すべからく",
    "meaning": "absolutely (ought to), by all means, all, entirely"
  },
  {
    "question": "小豆色",
    "answer": "あずきいろ",
    "meaning": "reddish-brown"
  },
  {
    "question": "有価証券",
    "answer": "ゆうかしょうけん",
    "meaning": "marketable securities, stocks and bonds"
  },
  {
    "question": "一升",
    "answer": "いっしょう,ひとます",
    "meaning": "unit of old Japanese liquid measurement, 1800 cc, one square on a grid, one cell of a grid"
  },
  {
    "question": "不器量",
    "answer": "ふきりょう,ぶきりょう",
    "meaning": "ugliness, homeliness, lack of ability, incompetence"
  },
  {
    "question": "含意",
    "answer": "がんい",
    "meaning": "implication, connotation, (logical) implication, material conditional, material consequence"
  },
  {
    "question": "初動捜査",
    "answer": "しょどうそうさ",
    "meaning": "initial investigation (by police)"
  },
  {
    "question": "沙羅双樹",
    "answer": "さらそうじゅ,しゃらそうじゅ",
    "meaning": "sal (tree) (Shorea robusta), saul, Japanese stewartia (Stewartia pseudocamellia)"
  },
  {
    "question": "着火剤",
    "answer": "ちゃっかざい",
    "meaning": "firelighter"
  },
  {
    "question": "身贔屓",
    "answer": "みびいき",
    "meaning": "favoritism (towards relatives), favouritism, nepotism"
  },
  {
    "question": "透け感",
    "answer": "すけかん",
    "meaning": "see-through sensation (for clothing), gauziness"
  },
  {
    "question": "数知れぬ",
    "answer": "かずしれぬ",
    "meaning": "countless, innumerable"
  },
  {
    "question": "冶金",
    "answer": "やきん",
    "meaning": "metallurgy"
  },
  {
    "question": "学習機能",
    "answer": "がくしゅうきのう",
    "meaning": "learning function"
  },
  {
    "question": "交通違反",
    "answer": "こうつういはん",
    "meaning": "traffic violation"
  },
  {
    "question": "拾い読み",
    "answer": "ひろいよみ",
    "meaning": "reading (the parts one is interested in), reading here and there, skimming through, browsing, readin"
  },
  {
    "question": "軟らか",
    "answer": "やわらか",
    "meaning": "soft, tender, limp, subdued (colour or light) (color), gentle, meek"
  },
  {
    "question": "首謀",
    "answer": "しゅぼう",
    "meaning": "plotting, planning (crime, intrigue), ringleader, mastermind, leader (of a plot)"
  },
  {
    "question": "折衷",
    "answer": "せっちゅう",
    "meaning": "compromise, cross, blending, eclecticism"
  },
  {
    "question": "帰港",
    "answer": "きこう",
    "meaning": "returning to port"
  },
  {
    "question": "投宿",
    "answer": "とうしゅく",
    "meaning": "lodging, putting up at a hotel"
  },
  {
    "question": "塩昆布",
    "answer": "しおこんぶ",
    "meaning": "thin strips of kombu cooked in soy sauce, etc. then dried"
  },
  {
    "question": "収集癖",
    "answer": "しゅうしゅうへき",
    "meaning": "collecting mania, mania for collecting, collectionism"
  },
  {
    "question": "矢羽根",
    "answer": "やばね",
    "meaning": "arrow feathers"
  },
  {
    "question": "字余り",
    "answer": "じあまり",
    "meaning": "hypermeter, excess syllables in haiku, waka, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "術無い",
    "answer": "じゅつない",
    "meaning": "at a loss for what to do, at one's wits' end, having no choice"
  },
  {
    "question": "廃液",
    "answer": "はいえき",
    "meaning": "waste liquid"
  },
  {
    "question": "毒舌家",
    "answer": "どくぜつか",
    "meaning": "person with a sharp tongue"
  },
  {
    "question": "紋所",
    "answer": "もんどころ",
    "meaning": "family crest"
  },
  {
    "question": "乱れ髪",
    "answer": "みだれがみ",
    "meaning": "disheveled hair, unravelled hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "伏せ字",
    "answer": "ふせじ",
    "meaning": "symbol used in place of a censored word (e.g. blank, circle, X, asterisk), turn (in set-type proofin"
  },
  {
    "question": "居住権",
    "answer": "きょじゅうけん",
    "meaning": "right of residence (i.e. right to go on leasing a house, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "掌大",
    "answer": "しょうだい",
    "meaning": "small, tiny, size of a palm"
  },
  {
    "question": "心尽くし",
    "answer": "こころづくし,こころずくし",
    "meaning": "kindness, consideration"
  },
  {
    "question": "早生まれ",
    "answer": "はやうまれ",
    "meaning": "being born between January 1 and April 1 (school entrance date)"
  },
  {
    "question": "狐狸",
    "answer": "こり",
    "meaning": "foxes and tanuki, sly fellow, deceiver"
  },
  {
    "question": "同社",
    "answer": "どうしゃ",
    "meaning": "the same firm"
  },
  {
    "question": "社風",
    "answer": "しゃふう",
    "meaning": "corporate culture, company climate or spirit, the way a company does things"
  },
  {
    "question": "刑事罰",
    "answer": "けいじばつ",
    "meaning": "criminal punishment, criminal penalty"
  },
  {
    "question": "無性",
    "answer": "むせい",
    "meaning": "asexual"
  },
  {
    "question": "停留",
    "answer": "ていりゅう",
    "meaning": "stop, halt"
  },
  {
    "question": "物狂い",
    "answer": "ものぐるい",
    "meaning": "insanity, an insane person"
  },
  {
    "question": "民度",
    "answer": "みんど",
    "meaning": "cultural standard (of the people), moral standard, cultural level, social manners, standard of livin"
  },
  {
    "question": "前貸し",
    "answer": "まえがし",
    "meaning": "advance payment"
  },
  {
    "question": "著す",
    "answer": "あらわす",
    "meaning": "to write, to publish"
  },
  {
    "question": "天下取り",
    "answer": "てんかとり",
    "meaning": "rule over the whole country"
  },
  {
    "question": "文句無し",
    "answer": "もんくなし",
    "meaning": "undisputed, entirely, perfect"
  },
  {
    "question": "意義深い",
    "answer": "いぎぶかい",
    "meaning": "significant, important"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕舞",
    "answer": "しまい,じまい",
    "meaning": "end, close, finish, termination, noh dance in plain clothes, ending, quitting, closing, ending befor"
  },
  {
    "question": "追い払い",
    "answer": "おいばらい",
    "meaning": "supplementary payment"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇癖",
    "answer": "きへき",
    "meaning": "strange habit"
  },
  {
    "question": "新進",
    "answer": "しんしん",
    "meaning": "rising, up-and-coming"
  },
  {
    "question": "通俗的",
    "answer": "つうぞくてき",
    "meaning": "popular, common, commonplace"
  },
  {
    "question": "自賛",
    "answer": "じさん",
    "meaning": "self-praise, praising oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "気忙しい",
    "answer": "きぜわしい",
    "meaning": "restless, fidgety, fussy"
  },
  {
    "question": "服す",
    "answer": "ふくす",
    "meaning": "to obey, to submit to, to yield to, to accept, to abide by, to serve (in the army, a prison sentence"
  },
  {
    "question": "戸建て",
    "answer": "こだて",
    "meaning": "(separate) house, detached house"
  },
  {
    "question": "読み応え",
    "answer": "よみごたえ",
    "meaning": "worthwhile reading, substantial reading"
  },
  {
    "question": "早技",
    "answer": "はやわざ",
    "meaning": "quick work, (clever) feat"
  },
  {
    "question": "禁固",
    "answer": "きんこ",
    "meaning": "imprisonment (without forced labour), incarceration, confinement"
  },
  {
    "question": "修飾語",
    "answer": "しゅうしょくご",
    "meaning": "modifier"
  },
  {
    "question": "数の子",
    "answer": "かずのこ",
    "meaning": "herring roe"
  },
  {
    "question": "有形",
    "answer": "ゆうけい",
    "meaning": "material, tangible, concrete"
  },
  {
    "question": "慌て者",
    "answer": "あわてもの",
    "meaning": "scatterbrain, absent-minded person, careless person, thoughtless person, rash person, hasty person"
  },
  {
    "question": "移り",
    "answer": "うつり",
    "meaning": "change, transition, return present"
  },
  {
    "question": "藍玉",
    "answer": "あいだま",
    "meaning": "ball of dried, ground, fermented dyer's knotweed leaves"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤熊",
    "answer": "あかぐま,しゃぐま",
    "meaning": "brown bear (esp. the Ussuri brown bear, Ursus arctos lasiotus), yak hair dyed red, red hair, frizzle"
  },
  {
    "question": "久住",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "上船",
    "answer": "じょうせん",
    "meaning": "embarking (a ship), embarkation, boarding"
  },
  {
    "question": "時宗",
    "answer": "じしゅう",
    "meaning": "Jishū sect (of Buddhism)"
  },
  {
    "question": "正則",
    "answer": "せいそく",
    "meaning": "correct, proper, formal, regular, systematic, normal, invertible (matrix), holomorphic"
  },
  {
    "question": "海星",
    "answer": "ひとで",
    "meaning": "starfish, sea star, asteroid, any echinoderm of the class Asteroidea, northern Pacific seastar (Aste"
  },
  {
    "question": "富家",
    "answer": "ふか",
    "meaning": "wealthy family"
  },
  {
    "question": "尹",
    "answer": "いん",
    "meaning": "director (of the ritsuryo-period Imperial Prosecuting and Investigating Office)"
  },
  {
    "question": "今宮",
    "answer": "いまみや",
    "meaning": "newly born imperial prince, newly constructed (branch) shrine"
  },
  {
    "question": "弥勒",
    "answer": "みろく",
    "meaning": "Maitreya (Bodhisattva), Miroku"
  },
  {
    "question": "護摩壇",
    "answer": "ごまだん",
    "meaning": "homa-mandala (fire altar)"
  },
  {
    "question": "材木屋",
    "answer": "ざいもくや",
    "meaning": "lumber dealer"
  },
  {
    "question": "五稜郭",
    "answer": "ごりょうかく",
    "meaning": "five-sided fortification"
  },
  {
    "question": "水行",
    "answer": "みずぎょう,すいぎょう",
    "meaning": "cold-water ablutions"
  },
  {
    "question": "宮内省",
    "answer": "くないしょう",
    "meaning": "Department of the Imperial Household"
  },
  {
    "question": "操車場",
    "answer": "そうしゃじょう",
    "meaning": "switchyard"
  },
  {
    "question": "窮極",
    "answer": "きゅうきょく",
    "meaning": "ultimate, final, last, eventual"
  },
  {
    "question": "抗原",
    "answer": "こうげん",
    "meaning": "antigen"
  },
  {
    "question": "反陽子",
    "answer": "はんようし",
    "meaning": "antiproton"
  },
  {
    "question": "軽巡洋艦",
    "answer": "けいじゅんようかん",
    "meaning": "light cruiser"
  },
  {
    "question": "石塔",
    "answer": "せきとう",
    "meaning": "stone monument or pagoda"
  },
  {
    "question": "肥前",
    "answer": "ひぜん",
    "meaning": "Hizen (former province located in present-day Saga and Nagasaki prefectures, excluding Tsushima and"
  },
  {
    "question": "ゴムの木",
    "answer": "ゴムのき",
    "meaning": "rubber tree"
  },
  {
    "question": "緑玉",
    "answer": "りょくぎょく",
    "meaning": "emerald"
  },
  {
    "question": "関八州",
    "answer": "かんはっしゅう",
    "meaning": "the eight Edo-period provinces of Kanto (Sagami, Musashi, Awa, Kazusa, Shimousa, Hitachi, Kouzuke an"
  },
  {
    "question": "一下",
    "answer": "いっか",
    "meaning": "something handed down (usu. an order)"
  },
  {
    "question": "寂静",
    "answer": "じゃくじょう,せきせい",
    "meaning": "calmness, stillness, tranquility, calmness of the heart, enlightenment"
  },
  {
    "question": "高麗",
    "answer": "こうらい,こま",
    "meaning": "Goryeo (dynasty of Korea; 918-1392 CE), Korea (esp. the Goguryeo kingdom or the Goryeo dynasty)"
  },
  {
    "question": "幻灯機",
    "answer": "げんとうき",
    "meaning": "magic lantern, slide projector"
  },
  {
    "question": "崖道",
    "answer": "がけみち",
    "meaning": "path along a cliff"
  },
  {
    "question": "鰆",
    "answer": "さわら",
    "meaning": "Japanese Spanish mackerel (Scomberomorus niphonius)"
  },
  {
    "question": "反粒子",
    "answer": "はんりゅうし",
    "meaning": "antiparticle"
  },
  {
    "question": "利回り",
    "answer": "りまわり",
    "meaning": "interest, (investment) yield, profits"
  },
  {
    "question": "逐う",
    "answer": "おう",
    "meaning": "to chase, to run after, to pursue, to follow after, to follow (a set order, a trend, etc.), to drive"
  },
  {
    "question": "男女共学",
    "answer": "だんじょきょうがく",
    "meaning": "co-education, mixed education"
  },
  {
    "question": "老馬",
    "answer": "ろうば",
    "meaning": "old horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "ギャル男",
    "answer": "ギャルお",
    "meaning": "(young) man adhering to a masculine version of gyaru fashion (usually marked by hair dyed brown or b"
  },
  {
    "question": "自治都市",
    "answer": "じちとし",
    "meaning": "commune (of medieval Europe), autonomous city"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠江",
    "answer": "とおとうみ",
    "meaning": "Tōtōmi (former province located in the west of present-day Shizuoka Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "靖国",
    "answer": "せいこく,やすくに",
    "meaning": "pacifying the nation, Yasukuni (Shrine)"
  },
  {
    "question": "儀典",
    "answer": "ぎてん",
    "meaning": "ceremony, rite, ritual, service"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き攣り",
    "answer": "ひきつり",
    "meaning": "scar, spasm, twitch, cramp"
  },
  {
    "question": "鳳仙花",
    "answer": "ほうせんか",
    "meaning": "(garden) balsam, Impatiens balsamina"
  },
  {
    "question": "刑死",
    "answer": "けいし",
    "meaning": "execution, death by execution"
  },
  {
    "question": "能楽",
    "answer": "のうがく",
    "meaning": "noh play"
  },
  {
    "question": "謹直",
    "answer": "きんちょく",
    "meaning": "conscientious, scrupulous"
  },
  {
    "question": "老臣",
    "answer": "ろうしん",
    "meaning": "old or key retainer"
  },
  {
    "question": "霜月",
    "answer": "しもつき,そうげつ",
    "meaning": "eleventh month of the lunar calendar"
  },
  {
    "question": "上弦",
    "answer": "じょうげん",
    "meaning": "1st quarter of moon, crescent moon"
  },
  {
    "question": "棚田",
    "answer": "たなだ",
    "meaning": "terraced rice-fields"
  },
  {
    "question": "掠う",
    "answer": "さらう",
    "meaning": "to carry off, to run away with, to sweep away, to snatch, to kidnap, to abduct, to take entirely for"
  },
  {
    "question": "炸",
    "answer": "ザー",
    "meaning": "deep-fried"
  },
  {
    "question": "草紙",
    "answer": "そうし",
    "meaning": "written work (esp. a bound text, as opposed to a scroll), a text written entirely in kana, graphic n"
  },
  {
    "question": "用船",
    "answer": "ようせん",
    "meaning": "chartered ship, chartering or hiring a vessel"
  },
  {
    "question": "登り口",
    "answer": "のぼりぐち,のぼりくち",
    "meaning": "starting point for an ascent (mountain, stairs, etc.), base (of mountain, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "外来患者",
    "answer": "がいらいかんじゃ",
    "meaning": "outpatients"
  },
  {
    "question": "教授会",
    "answer": "きょうじゅかい",
    "meaning": "faculty meeting"
  },
  {
    "question": "書評",
    "answer": "しょひょう",
    "meaning": "book review"
  },
  {
    "question": "督戦",
    "answer": "とくせん",
    "meaning": "urging soldiers to fight more vigorously"
  },
  {
    "question": "脹らむ",
    "answer": "ふくらむ",
    "meaning": "to expand, to swell (out), to get big, to become inflated"
  },
  {
    "question": "遁甲",
    "answer": "とんこう",
    "meaning": "type of astrology"
  },
  {
    "question": "点じる",
    "answer": "てんじる",
    "meaning": "to drop, to light, to kindle, to make tea"
  },
  {
    "question": "測位",
    "answer": "そくい",
    "meaning": "positioning, measurement of position"
  },
  {
    "question": "豚しゃぶ",
    "answer": "ぶたしゃぶ",
    "meaning": "pork shabu-shabu"
  },
  {
    "question": "筆写",
    "answer": "ひっしゃ",
    "meaning": "copying (by hand), transcribing"
  },
  {
    "question": "邦楽",
    "answer": "ほうがく",
    "meaning": "Japanese music (esp. traditional Japanese music)"
  },
  {
    "question": "門徒",
    "answer": "もんと",
    "meaning": "follower (of religion; esp. Jōdo Shinshū practitioners), believer"
  },
  {
    "question": "相似形",
    "answer": "そうじけい",
    "meaning": "similar figures (in geometry)"
  },
  {
    "question": "荷役",
    "answer": "にえき,にやく",
    "meaning": "handling cargo, loading and unloading"
  },
  {
    "question": "細片",
    "answer": "さいへん",
    "meaning": "small piece, fragment, chip, splinter, strip, shred"
  },
  {
    "question": "民族主義",
    "answer": "みんぞくしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "nationalism"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼菓子",
    "answer": "やきがし",
    "meaning": "baked sweets"
  },
  {
    "question": "命令文",
    "answer": "めいれいぶん",
    "meaning": "imperative sentence, imperative statement"
  },
  {
    "question": "存立",
    "answer": "そんりつ",
    "meaning": "existence, subsistence"
  },
  {
    "question": "稚い",
    "answer": "いとけない",
    "meaning": "very young, little"
  },
  {
    "question": "自然薯",
    "answer": "じねんじょ",
    "meaning": "Japanese yam (Dioscorea japonica)"
  },
  {
    "question": "梵字",
    "answer": "ぼんじ",
    "meaning": "script used to write Sanskrit (esp. Siddham)"
  },
  {
    "question": "新聞広告",
    "answer": "しんぶんこうこく",
    "meaning": "newspaper advertisement"
  },
  {
    "question": "下穿き",
    "answer": "したばき",
    "meaning": "undershorts, underpants"
  },
  {
    "question": "奔出",
    "answer": "ほんしゅつ",
    "meaning": "gushing out"
  },
  {
    "question": "閑話",
    "answer": "かんわ",
    "meaning": "quiet conversation, gossiping, idle talk"
  },
  {
    "question": "手鍋",
    "answer": "てなべ",
    "meaning": "pan"
  },
  {
    "question": "鑑定人",
    "answer": "かんていにん",
    "meaning": "judge, appraiser"
  },
  {
    "question": "素描",
    "answer": "そびょう,すがき",
    "meaning": "drawing, sketch, outline, summary, synopsis, uncolored sketch, line sketch, rough sketch"
  },
  {
    "question": "催淫剤",
    "answer": "さいいんざい",
    "meaning": "aphrodisiac"
  },
  {
    "question": "嫡流",
    "answer": "ちゃくりゅう",
    "meaning": "lineage of eldest son"
  },
  {
    "question": "式服",
    "answer": "しきふく",
    "meaning": "ceremonial dress"
  },
  {
    "question": "尉官",
    "answer": "いかん",
    "meaning": "officer below the rank of major, company officer"
  },
  {
    "question": "麦飯",
    "answer": "むぎめし,ばくはん,むぎいい",
    "meaning": "boiled barley and rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "慰霊祭",
    "answer": "いれいさい",
    "meaning": "memorial service"
  },
  {
    "question": "教則本",
    "answer": "きょうそくぼん",
    "meaning": "manual, practice book"
  },
  {
    "question": "事務総長",
    "answer": "じむそうちょう",
    "meaning": "secretary-general, director"
  },
  {
    "question": "五十日",
    "answer": "ごとおび,いか",
    "meaning": "days of the month ending in 5 or 0 (when payments are often due), fiftieth day after the birth of a"
  },
  {
    "question": "浮き島",
    "answer": "うきしま,うきじま",
    "meaning": "floating mass (of waterweeds, ice, etc.), floating island (mirage)"
  },
  {
    "question": "天王星",
    "answer": "てんのうせい,てんおうせい",
    "meaning": "Uranus (planet)"
  },
  {
    "question": "雪下ろし",
    "answer": "ゆきおろし",
    "meaning": "wind blowing snow down a mountain, removing snow from the roof of a house"
  },
  {
    "question": "公金",
    "answer": "こうきん",
    "meaning": "public funds"
  },
  {
    "question": "腹中",
    "answer": "ふくちゅう",
    "meaning": "within one, at heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "週番",
    "answer": "しゅうばん",
    "meaning": "weekly duty"
  },
  {
    "question": "曲り角",
    "answer": "まがりかど",
    "meaning": "street corner, road turn, bend in the road, turning point, watershed"
  },
  {
    "question": "味覚障害",
    "answer": "みかくしょうがい",
    "meaning": "dysgeusia, taste disorder"
  },
  {
    "question": "逼塞",
    "answer": "ひっそく",
    "meaning": "being blocked (and contained), reduced circumstances"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝正月",
    "answer": "ねしょうがつ",
    "meaning": "staying at home during the New Year's holiday"
  },
  {
    "question": "同位体",
    "answer": "どういたい",
    "meaning": "isotope"
  },
  {
    "question": "太陽風",
    "answer": "たいようふう",
    "meaning": "solar wind"
  },
  {
    "question": "換言",
    "answer": "かんげん",
    "meaning": "saying in other words, putting (something) another way"
  },
  {
    "question": "襟章",
    "answer": "えりしょう",
    "meaning": "lapel badge, collar badge"
  },
  {
    "question": "艱難",
    "answer": "かんなん",
    "meaning": "hardships, privations, difficulties"
  },
  {
    "question": "前身頃",
    "answer": "まえみごろ",
    "meaning": "front (of a piece of traditional Japanese clothing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "アヒル口",
    "answer": "アヒルぐち,アヒルくち",
    "meaning": "duck face, duck lips, facial expression where the lips are pursed and corners of the mouth raised"
  },
  {
    "question": "隣県",
    "answer": "りんけん",
    "meaning": "neighboring prefecture, adjacent prefecture"
  },
  {
    "question": "上せる",
    "answer": "のぼせる",
    "meaning": "to raise, to record, to bring up (a matter), to serve (food), to send some on out"
  },
  {
    "question": "滅私",
    "answer": "めっし",
    "meaning": "selflessness, being unselfish"
  },
  {
    "question": "画布",
    "answer": "がふ",
    "meaning": "(oil painting) canvas"
  },
  {
    "question": "尚武",
    "answer": "しょうぶ",
    "meaning": "militarism, warlike spirit"
  },
  {
    "question": "春野菜",
    "answer": "はるやさい",
    "meaning": "spring vegetables"
  },
  {
    "question": "装幀",
    "answer": "そうてい",
    "meaning": "binding (of a book), design (of a book cover)"
  },
  {
    "question": "減ずる",
    "answer": "げんずる",
    "meaning": "to decrease, to be reduced, to grow less, to abate, to reduce, to lessen, to cut down, to mitigate,"
  },
  {
    "question": "謂",
    "answer": "いい",
    "meaning": "what was said, what it means, origin of a story (or tradition, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "位相空間",
    "answer": "いそうくうかん",
    "meaning": "phase space, topological space"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会悪",
    "answer": "しゃかいあく",
    "meaning": "social ills"
  },
  {
    "question": "混ざり物",
    "answer": "まざりもの",
    "meaning": "impurity"
  },
  {
    "question": "沈澱",
    "answer": "ちんでん",
    "meaning": "precipitation, deposition, settlement (e.g. of sediment)"
  },
  {
    "question": "小股",
    "answer": "こまた",
    "meaning": "short steps, mincing stride, crotch, groin, thigh"
  },
  {
    "question": "衛星都市",
    "answer": "えいせいとし",
    "meaning": "satellite city, satellite town"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿縁",
    "answer": "しゅくえん",
    "meaning": "destiny, fate, karma"
  },
  {
    "question": "明くる朝",
    "answer": "あくるあさ,あくるあした",
    "meaning": "next morning, following morning"
  },
  {
    "question": "敗血症",
    "answer": "はいけつしょう",
    "meaning": "blood poisoning, septicemia, sepsis"
  },
  {
    "question": "四海",
    "answer": "しかい",
    "meaning": "the whole world, the seven seas"
  },
  {
    "question": "早い所",
    "answer": "はやいとこ,はやいところ",
    "meaning": "promptly, quickly"
  },
  {
    "question": "盆暗",
    "answer": "ぼんくら",
    "meaning": "stupidity, idiocy, blockhead, idiot, dimwit, mediocrity"
  },
  {
    "question": "生餌",
    "answer": "いきえ",
    "meaning": "live bait"
  },
  {
    "question": "月食",
    "answer": "げっしょく",
    "meaning": "lunar eclipse"
  },
  {
    "question": "術策",
    "answer": "じゅっさく",
    "meaning": "artifice, intrigue"
  },
  {
    "question": "卒園",
    "answer": "そつえん",
    "meaning": "finishing kindergarten, graduating from kindergarten"
  },
  {
    "question": "馬子",
    "answer": "まご",
    "meaning": "packhorse driver"
  },
  {
    "question": "果せる",
    "answer": "おおせる",
    "meaning": "to succeed in doing, to manage to do, to finish doing"
  },
  {
    "question": "遣り合う",
    "answer": "やりあう",
    "meaning": "to compete with, to argue with, to quarrel"
  },
  {
    "question": "民俗",
    "answer": "みんぞく",
    "meaning": "folk customs, folkways, ethnic customs"
  },
  {
    "question": "千日",
    "answer": "せんにち",
    "meaning": "one thousand days"
  },
  {
    "question": "払底",
    "answer": "ふってい",
    "meaning": "shortage, scarcity, dearth, famine"
  },
  {
    "question": "近似値",
    "answer": "きんじち",
    "meaning": "approximate value, approximation"
  },
  {
    "question": "疑問文",
    "answer": "ぎもんぶん",
    "meaning": "interrogative sentence"
  },
  {
    "question": "四十八手",
    "answer": "しじゅうはって",
    "meaning": "the 48 basic techniques, every trick in the book, the 48 basic sexual positions"
  },
  {
    "question": "不調和",
    "answer": "ふちょうわ",
    "meaning": "disharmony, discord, dissonance, incongruity"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄輪",
    "answer": "かなわ,てつりん",
    "meaning": "metal ring, metal hoop, metal band, trivet, train wheel, train"
  },
  {
    "question": "印画紙",
    "answer": "いんがし",
    "meaning": "(photographic) printing paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "本試験",
    "answer": "ほんしけん",
    "meaning": "final examination"
  },
  {
    "question": "湯冷まし",
    "answer": "ゆざまし",
    "meaning": "boiled water which has cooled"
  },
  {
    "question": "手鞠",
    "answer": "てまり",
    "meaning": "traditional Japanese handball game"
  },
  {
    "question": "金文字",
    "answer": "きんもじ",
    "meaning": "gold or gilt letters"
  },
  {
    "question": "葉音",
    "answer": "はおと",
    "meaning": "sound of rustling leaves"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪戯書き",
    "answer": "いたずらがき",
    "meaning": "scribbling, doodling, graffiti"
  },
  {
    "question": "平等主義",
    "answer": "びょうどうしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "principle of equality"
  },
  {
    "question": "護岸",
    "answer": "ごがん",
    "meaning": "river dike"
  },
  {
    "question": "一浪",
    "answer": "いちろう",
    "meaning": "failing college entrance exams and retaking them a year later"
  },
  {
    "question": "魚座",
    "answer": "うおざ",
    "meaning": "Pisces (constellation), the Fish, the Fishes, fishmongers' guild"
  },
  {
    "question": "刺傷",
    "answer": "さしきず,ししょう",
    "meaning": "stab wound, puncture wound, bite (e.g. from a insect), sting, prick, stab"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛋白",
    "answer": "たんぱく",
    "meaning": "protein, egg white, albumen, albumin"
  },
  {
    "question": "在来線",
    "answer": "ざいらいせん",
    "meaning": "conventional train line (esp. non-Shinkansen)"
  },
  {
    "question": "落伍",
    "answer": "らくご",
    "meaning": "straggling, falling behind, being left behind, dropping out, falling behind the ranks, falling out o"
  },
  {
    "question": "沈滞",
    "answer": "ちんたい",
    "meaning": "stagnation, inactivity"
  },
  {
    "question": "目眩く",
    "answer": "めくるめく",
    "meaning": "to dazzle, to blind"
  },
  {
    "question": "単三",
    "answer": "たんさん",
    "meaning": "AA battery, AA cell"
  },
  {
    "question": "懲戒処分",
    "answer": "ちょうかいしょぶん",
    "meaning": "disciplinary measures, (judicial) sanctions"
  },
  {
    "question": "浅手",
    "answer": "あさで",
    "meaning": "slight wound, minor wound"
  },
  {
    "question": "ど突く",
    "answer": "どつく,どづく",
    "meaning": "to jab, to hit, to punch"
  },
  {
    "question": "野次る",
    "answer": "やじる",
    "meaning": "to jeer (at), to hoot, to boo, to catcall, to heckle"
  },
  {
    "question": "一国一城",
    "answer": "いっこくいちじょう",
    "meaning": "(possession of) one feudal domain and one castle, being independent (acting without compromise or as"
  },
  {
    "question": "深慮遠謀",
    "answer": "しんりょえんぼう",
    "meaning": "deep design and forethought, a farsighted and deeply-laid plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "縁飾り",
    "answer": "ふちかざり",
    "meaning": "edging, frill"
  },
  {
    "question": "梃子摺る",
    "answer": "てこずる",
    "meaning": "to have much trouble, to have a hard time, to not know how to handle"
  },
  {
    "question": "死の舞踏",
    "answer": "しのぶとう",
    "meaning": "dance of death, danse macabre"
  },
  {
    "question": "容色",
    "answer": "ようしょく",
    "meaning": "looks, features, beauty"
  },
  {
    "question": "感染経路",
    "answer": "かんせんけいろ",
    "meaning": "infection route, source of infection"
  },
  {
    "question": "地域社会",
    "answer": "ちいきしゃかい",
    "meaning": "regional community"
  },
  {
    "question": "低調",
    "answer": "ていちょう",
    "meaning": "inactive, slow, sluggish, slack, low tone, undertone, dullness, (market) weakness"
  },
  {
    "question": "梅肉",
    "answer": "ばいにく",
    "meaning": "shredded dried plum, plum pulp"
  },
  {
    "question": "居合抜き",
    "answer": "いあいぬき",
    "meaning": "iai, art of drawing one's sword, cutting down one's opponent and sheathing the sword afterwards, iai"
  },
  {
    "question": "小人数",
    "answer": "こにんずう,こにんず",
    "meaning": "small number of people"
  },
  {
    "question": "読後感",
    "answer": "どくごかん",
    "meaning": "one's impressions after reading a book"
  },
  {
    "question": "疲れ目",
    "answer": "つかれめ",
    "meaning": "eye strain"
  },
  {
    "question": "歓心",
    "answer": "かんしん",
    "meaning": "favour, favor"
  },
  {
    "question": "見え難い",
    "answer": "みえにくい",
    "meaning": "hard to see, obscured"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄日",
    "answer": "うすび",
    "meaning": "soft light"
  },
  {
    "question": "込み込み",
    "answer": "こみこみ",
    "meaning": "tax and service charge included, all-inclusive, with everything included"
  },
  {
    "question": "虫唾",
    "answer": "むしず",
    "meaning": "heartburn, strong sense of disgust"
  },
  {
    "question": "話し振り",
    "answer": "はなしぶり",
    "meaning": "one's way of talking"
  },
  {
    "question": "正比例",
    "answer": "せいひれい",
    "meaning": "direct proportion, direct ratio"
  },
  {
    "question": "戯れ事",
    "answer": "ざれごと,たわむれごと",
    "meaning": "wanton sporting"
  },
  {
    "question": "静物画",
    "answer": "せいぶつが",
    "meaning": "still life (painting, drawing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "急募",
    "answer": "きゅうぼ",
    "meaning": "hurried recruitment, urgent recruitment"
  },
  {
    "question": "客待ち",
    "answer": "きゃくまち",
    "meaning": "waiting for customers"
  },
  {
    "question": "教育学部",
    "answer": "きょういくがくぶ",
    "meaning": "faculty of education"
  },
  {
    "question": "躁状態",
    "answer": "そうじょうたい",
    "meaning": "manic state"
  },
  {
    "question": "簡素化",
    "answer": "かんそか",
    "meaning": "simplification"
  },
  {
    "question": "名文",
    "answer": "めいぶん",
    "meaning": "famous literary composition"
  },
  {
    "question": "問題作",
    "answer": "もんだいさく",
    "meaning": "controversial work (art, literature, etc.), work that caused public criticism, work of art dealing w"
  },
  {
    "question": "片一方",
    "answer": "かたいっぽう,かたっぽ",
    "meaning": "one side, one of a pair"
  },
  {
    "question": "食性",
    "answer": "しょくせい",
    "meaning": "feeding habit (e.g. of an animal), feeding habitat"
  },
  {
    "question": "誘拐罪",
    "answer": "ゆうかいざい",
    "meaning": "(the crime of) kidnapping (kidnaping)"
  },
  {
    "question": "如何で",
    "answer": "いかで",
    "meaning": "how"
  },
  {
    "question": "大風呂敷",
    "answer": "おおぶろしき",
    "meaning": "large furoshiki, big talk, vain boasting or bluster, blowing one's own trumpet, rodomontade"
  },
  {
    "question": "早引き",
    "answer": "はやびき",
    "meaning": "leaving work (office, school) early"
  },
  {
    "question": "既成概念",
    "answer": "きせいがいねん",
    "meaning": "stereotype, preconceived idea, preconceived notion"
  },
  {
    "question": "元素記号",
    "answer": "げんそきごう",
    "meaning": "chemical symbol (i.e. H for hydrogen, O for oxygen, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "取扱い",
    "answer": "とりあつかい",
    "meaning": "treatment, service, handling, management"
  },
  {
    "question": "白み",
    "answer": "しろみ",
    "meaning": "whiteness"
  },
  {
    "question": "承伏",
    "answer": "しょうふく",
    "meaning": "accepting, consenting, agreeing, submission, compliance, agreement, consent"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝冷え",
    "answer": "ねびえ",
    "meaning": "indisposition (e.g. a cold) caused by getting chilled while sleeping"
  },
  {
    "question": "堕す",
    "answer": "だす",
    "meaning": "to degenerate, to lapse into"
  },
  {
    "question": "七分袖",
    "answer": "しちぶそで",
    "meaning": "three-quarter sleeves"
  },
  {
    "question": "形式張る",
    "answer": "けいしきばる",
    "meaning": "to be formal, to be ceremonious, to stand on ceremony"
  },
  {
    "question": "不経済",
    "answer": "ふけいざい",
    "meaning": "poor economy, waste"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き返し",
    "answer": "ひきかえし",
    "meaning": "turning back"
  },
  {
    "question": "首っ引き",
    "answer": "くびっぴき",
    "meaning": "making constant reference to"
  },
  {
    "question": "陸続き",
    "answer": "りくつづき",
    "meaning": "being joined by land"
  },
  {
    "question": "片っ端",
    "answer": "かたっぱし",
    "meaning": "one edge, one end, one side"
  },
  {
    "question": "在中",
    "answer": "ざいちゅう",
    "meaning": "(contained) within"
  },
  {
    "question": "素っ",
    "answer": "すっ",
    "meaning": "most, much, greatly"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り切る",
    "answer": "とりきる",
    "meaning": "to take completely, to deplete, to block off, to isolate"
  },
  {
    "question": "下降線",
    "answer": "かこうせん",
    "meaning": "downward curve"
  },
  {
    "question": "固持",
    "answer": "こじ",
    "meaning": "adherence (to one's beliefs) (positive nuance), persistence, sticking to one's guns, standing one's"
  },
  {
    "question": "豚に真珠",
    "answer": "ぶたにしんじゅ",
    "meaning": "(cast) pearls before swine"
  },
  {
    "question": "遅らす",
    "answer": "おくらす",
    "meaning": "to delay, to postpone, to slow down, to retard"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶にする",
    "answer": "ちゃにする",
    "meaning": "to make fun of, to look down on, to make light of, to take a tea break, to rest"
  },
  {
    "question": "精読",
    "answer": "せいどく",
    "meaning": "intensive reading, conning"
  },
  {
    "question": "神祇省",
    "answer": "じんぎしょう",
    "meaning": "Ministry of Divinities (1871-1872)"
  },
  {
    "question": "箏曲",
    "answer": "そうきょく",
    "meaning": "koto music"
  },
  {
    "question": "旧大陸",
    "answer": "きゅうたいりく",
    "meaning": "Old World (i.e., Asia, Africa, Europe)"
  },
  {
    "question": "余接",
    "answer": "よせつ",
    "meaning": "cotangent"
  },
  {
    "question": "限局",
    "answer": "げんきょく",
    "meaning": "restriction, localization"
  },
  {
    "question": "宗匠",
    "answer": "そうしょう",
    "meaning": "master, teacher"
  },
  {
    "question": "斎宮",
    "answer": "さいぐう",
    "meaning": "the ancient imperial princesses serving at the Ise shrine"
  },
  {
    "question": "土橋",
    "answer": "どばし,つちばし",
    "meaning": "earthen bridge"
  },
  {
    "question": "挿抜",
    "answer": "そうばつ",
    "meaning": "insertion-extraction, add-remove, swapping (e.g. plugs)"
  },
  {
    "question": "洛陽",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "営林署",
    "answer": "えいりんしょ",
    "meaning": "forest service field office"
  },
  {
    "question": "水耕",
    "answer": "すいこう",
    "meaning": "hydroponics"
  },
  {
    "question": "笈",
    "answer": "おい,きゅう",
    "meaning": "wooden box carried on one's back to store items for a pilgrimage, box carried on one's back to store"
  },
  {
    "question": "落車",
    "answer": "らくしゃ",
    "meaning": "falling from bicycle, motorcycle, etc. while driving (esp. in a race)"
  },
  {
    "question": "兇暴",
    "answer": "きょうぼう",
    "meaning": "ferocious, brutal, atrocious, savage, barbarous"
  },
  {
    "question": "快絶",
    "answer": "かいぜつ",
    "meaning": "splendid"
  },
  {
    "question": "電界",
    "answer": "でんかい",
    "meaning": "electric field"
  },
  {
    "question": "刀狩",
    "answer": "かたながり",
    "meaning": "sword hunt, sword confiscation"
  },
  {
    "question": "転部",
    "answer": "てんぶ",
    "meaning": "changing post (department, club, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "現生",
    "answer": "げんなま,げんしょう,げんせい",
    "meaning": "cold cash, hard cash, present world, living in the present"
  },
  {
    "question": "白水",
    "answer": "しろみず",
    "meaning": "color of water after washing rice (colour)"
  },
  {
    "question": "論理学",
    "answer": "ろんりがく",
    "meaning": "(study of) logic"
  },
  {
    "question": "代将",
    "answer": "だいしょう",
    "meaning": "brigadier general, commodore"
  },
  {
    "question": "川瀬",
    "answer": "かわせ",
    "meaning": "rapids, shallows of a river"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪妻",
    "answer": "あくさい",
    "meaning": "bad wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "釜山",
    "answer": "プサン,ふざん",
    "meaning": "Busan (South Korea), Pusan"
  },
  {
    "question": "塡める",
    "answer": "はめる",
    "meaning": "to insert, to put in (such that there is a snug fit), to button, to put on (something that envelops,"
  },
  {
    "question": "糠漬け",
    "answer": "ぬかづけ",
    "meaning": "pickles made in brine and fermented rice bran (esp. vegetables, also meat, fish, eggs, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "稟議",
    "answer": "りんぎ,ひんぎ",
    "meaning": "reaching a decision by using a circular letter, reaching a decision via a document circulated to all"
  },
  {
    "question": "三門",
    "answer": "さんもん",
    "meaning": "large triple gate to temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "濡れ縁",
    "answer": "ぬれえん",
    "meaning": "open verandah, open veranda"
  },
  {
    "question": "無想",
    "answer": "むそう",
    "meaning": "a blank mind"
  },
  {
    "question": "鰊",
    "answer": "にしん,かど",
    "meaning": "Pacific herring (Clupea pallasii)"
  },
  {
    "question": "入内",
    "answer": "じゅだい",
    "meaning": "imperial bridal party's entry into the court"
  },
  {
    "question": "永劫回帰",
    "answer": "えいごうかいき",
    "meaning": "eternal recurrence, eternal return"
  },
  {
    "question": "水陸",
    "answer": "すいりく",
    "meaning": "land and water"
  },
  {
    "question": "青柳",
    "answer": "あおやぎ,あおやなぎ",
    "meaning": "green willow (i.e. one that has budded), meat of the trough shell (Mactra chinensis)"
  },
  {
    "question": "火山ガス",
    "answer": "かざんガス",
    "meaning": "volcanic gas"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄土",
    "answer": "おうど,こうど",
    "meaning": "loess, yellow ochre, yellow ocher, Hades, hell, underworld, world of the dead"
  },
  {
    "question": "忘れ難い",
    "answer": "わすれがたい",
    "meaning": "unforgettable, memorable"
  },
  {
    "question": "参事",
    "answer": "さんじ",
    "meaning": "secretary, councillor, councilor"
  },
  {
    "question": "照応",
    "answer": "しょうおう",
    "meaning": "correspondence, being in accordance with, anaphora"
  },
  {
    "question": "潟",
    "answer": "かた",
    "meaning": "lagoon"
  },
  {
    "question": "家作",
    "answer": "かさく",
    "meaning": "house for rent, house to let, building a house, built house"
  },
  {
    "question": "労咳",
    "answer": "ろうがい",
    "meaning": "pulmonary tuberculosis (in traditional Chinese medicine)"
  },
  {
    "question": "電磁気",
    "answer": "でんじき",
    "meaning": "electromagnetism"
  },
  {
    "question": "保育器",
    "answer": "ほいくき",
    "meaning": "incubator"
  },
  {
    "question": "街道筋",
    "answer": "かいどうすじ",
    "meaning": "highway route (Edo period), main route"
  },
  {
    "question": "潜水服",
    "answer": "せんすいふく",
    "meaning": "diving suit"
  },
  {
    "question": "暴飲",
    "answer": "ぼういん",
    "meaning": "heavy drinking"
  },
  {
    "question": "リア友",
    "answer": "リアとも",
    "meaning": "real-life friend (as opposed to online friend)"
  },
  {
    "question": "集荷",
    "answer": "しゅうか",
    "meaning": "collection of cargo (esp. produce, etc.), cargo booking"
  },
  {
    "question": "積木",
    "answer": "つみき",
    "meaning": "wooden building blocks, wooden bricks, playing with building blocks, piled timber, piling up wood"
  },
  {
    "question": "雪花",
    "answer": "ゆきばな,せっか",
    "meaning": "snowflake"
  },
  {
    "question": "詰将棋",
    "answer": "つめしょうぎ",
    "meaning": "chess problem, composed shogi problem"
  },
  {
    "question": "大領",
    "answer": "だいりょう,たいりょう,おおくび",
    "meaning": "director of a district (ritsuryo system), gusset, front collar of a kimono"
  },
  {
    "question": "創部",
    "answer": "そうぶ",
    "meaning": "establishing a club (at a school, college, etc.), establishing a division (in a company)"
  },
  {
    "question": "畜舎",
    "answer": "ちくしゃ",
    "meaning": "cattle shed, barn"
  },
  {
    "question": "雌性",
    "answer": "しせい",
    "meaning": "female"
  },
  {
    "question": "防衛費",
    "answer": "ぼうえいひ",
    "meaning": "defense costs, defence costs, ERA"
  },
  {
    "question": "株分け",
    "answer": "かぶわけ",
    "meaning": "root division"
  },
  {
    "question": "裳裾",
    "answer": "もすそ",
    "meaning": "cuff (of pants), hem (of skirt), train (of dress), foot (of mountain)"
  },
  {
    "question": "兇器",
    "answer": "きょうき",
    "meaning": "dangerous weapon, lethal weapon, deadly weapon, murder weapon"
  },
  {
    "question": "坊様",
    "answer": "ぼんさま",
    "meaning": "monk, priest, boy"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶滅種",
    "answer": "ぜつめつしゅ",
    "meaning": "extinct species"
  },
  {
    "question": "影像",
    "answer": "えいぞう",
    "meaning": "silhouette"
  },
  {
    "question": "看做す",
    "answer": "みなす",
    "meaning": "to consider as, to regard (as equivalent), to deem (as), to equate"
  },
  {
    "question": "打ち拉ぐ",
    "answer": "うちひしぐ",
    "meaning": "to crush (with the weight of misfortune)"
  },
  {
    "question": "弥勒菩薩",
    "answer": "みろくぼさつ",
    "meaning": "Maitreya (Bodhisattva), Miroku"
  },
  {
    "question": "一男",
    "answer": "いちなん",
    "meaning": "boy, eldest son"
  },
  {
    "question": "初演",
    "answer": "しょえん",
    "meaning": "first performance"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒸籠",
    "answer": "せいろ,せいろう,チョンロン",
    "meaning": "bamboo steamer, steaming basket, wooden frame holder with reed base used to steam food over a pot, s"
  },
  {
    "question": "管弦楽",
    "answer": "かんげんがく",
    "meaning": "orchestral music"
  },
  {
    "question": "羽織袴",
    "answer": "はおりはかま",
    "meaning": "haori and hakama (Japanese male formal attire)"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓄光",
    "answer": "ちっこう,ちくこう",
    "meaning": "phosphorescence, luminescence"
  },
  {
    "question": "食紅",
    "answer": "しょくべに",
    "meaning": "red food coloring, red food colouring"
  },
  {
    "question": "遊行",
    "answer": "ゆうこう,ゆぎょう",
    "meaning": "gadding around, gallivanting, tour, wandering, walking aimlessly, pilgrimage, travelling around (by"
  },
  {
    "question": "賽子",
    "answer": "さいころ",
    "meaning": "dice, die"
  },
  {
    "question": "道化芝居",
    "answer": "どうけしばい",
    "meaning": "farce, low comedy"
  },
  {
    "question": "預かり所",
    "answer": "あずかりじょ,あずかりしょ",
    "meaning": "cloakroom, parcel room"
  },
  {
    "question": "框",
    "answer": "わく,かまち",
    "meaning": "frame, framework, border, box, limit, restriction, quota, category, bracket, class, (broadcasting) s"
  },
  {
    "question": "満腔",
    "answer": "まんこう,まんくう",
    "meaning": "heartfelt, sincere, wholehearted"
  },
  {
    "question": "輝度",
    "answer": "きど",
    "meaning": "brightness, clearness, luminance"
  },
  {
    "question": "母御",
    "answer": "ははご",
    "meaning": "mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "嘲罵",
    "answer": "ちょうば",
    "meaning": "(verbal) abuse, insulting remark, taunt"
  },
  {
    "question": "子等",
    "answer": "こら",
    "meaning": "children"
  },
  {
    "question": "両前",
    "answer": "りょうまえ",
    "meaning": "double-breasted"
  },
  {
    "question": "投げ銭",
    "answer": "なげせん,なげぜに",
    "meaning": "tossed coin (to a street performer or beggar)"
  },
  {
    "question": "酒器",
    "answer": "しゅき",
    "meaning": "utensil used for serving or drinking sake, sake drinking set"
  },
  {
    "question": "大阪弁",
    "answer": "おおさかべん",
    "meaning": "Ōsaka dialect"
  },
  {
    "question": "肝硬変",
    "answer": "かんこうへん",
    "meaning": "cirrhosis of the liver"
  },
  {
    "question": "脚絆",
    "answer": "きゃはん",
    "meaning": "gaiters, leggings, puttees"
  },
  {
    "question": "延伸",
    "answer": "えんしん",
    "meaning": "stretching, extension, elongation"
  },
  {
    "question": "演芸",
    "answer": "えんげい",
    "meaning": "entertainment, performance"
  },
  {
    "question": "欲得",
    "answer": "よくとく",
    "meaning": "selfishness, self-interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "硝酸",
    "answer": "しょうさん",
    "meaning": "nitric acid"
  },
  {
    "question": "態と",
    "answer": "わざと",
    "meaning": "on purpose, deliberately, intentionally"
  },
  {
    "question": "酸性雨",
    "answer": "さんせいう",
    "meaning": "acid rain"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄片",
    "answer": "はくへん",
    "meaning": "flake, lamella (of bone), foil (of metal), flat, thin slice of a material"
  },
  {
    "question": "海の日",
    "answer": "うみのひ",
    "meaning": "Marine Day (national holiday; 3rd Monday of July)"
  },
  {
    "question": "恒常性",
    "answer": "こうじょうせい",
    "meaning": "homeostasis, homoeostasis, constancy"
  },
  {
    "question": "金輪",
    "answer": "かなわ,こんりん",
    "meaning": "metal ring, metal hoop, metal band, trivet, gold wheel (highest of the three layered wheels that sup"
  },
  {
    "question": "修養",
    "answer": "しゅうよう",
    "meaning": "self-improvement, (mental) training, self-discipline, cultivation"
  },
  {
    "question": "造営",
    "answer": "ぞうえい",
    "meaning": "building (a temple, palace, etc.), construction, erection"
  },
  {
    "question": "心筋",
    "answer": "しんきん",
    "meaning": "heart muscle, myocardium"
  },
  {
    "question": "能動",
    "answer": "のうどう",
    "meaning": "activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "狭心症",
    "answer": "きょうしんしょう",
    "meaning": "heart attack, angina pectoris"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉦",
    "answer": "かね,しょう",
    "meaning": "gong, handbell"
  },
  {
    "question": "来季",
    "answer": "らいき",
    "meaning": "next season (esp. in sports), next year"
  },
  {
    "question": "売国",
    "answer": "ばいこく",
    "meaning": "selling out one's country, betraying one's country, treason"
  },
  {
    "question": "消え残る",
    "answer": "きえのこる",
    "meaning": "to remain unextinguished, to survive"
  },
  {
    "question": "国花",
    "answer": "こっか",
    "meaning": "national flower"
  },
  {
    "question": "防虫",
    "answer": "ぼうちゅう",
    "meaning": "protection from insects, insect repellence"
  },
  {
    "question": "硫化水素",
    "answer": "りゅうかすいそ",
    "meaning": "hydrogen sulphide, hydrogen sulfide, sulphuretted hydrogen, sulfuretted hydrogen"
  },
  {
    "question": "転籍",
    "answer": "てんせき",
    "meaning": "transfer of permanent domicile (as recorded in the family register), transfer of school register"
  },
  {
    "question": "全粒粉",
    "answer": "ぜんりゅうふん",
    "meaning": "whole wheat flour"
  },
  {
    "question": "廃案",
    "answer": "はいあん",
    "meaning": "rejected bill (project)"
  },
  {
    "question": "破却",
    "answer": "はきゃく",
    "meaning": "complete destruction, demolition"
  },
  {
    "question": "文部省",
    "answer": "もんぶしょう",
    "meaning": "Ministry of Education, Science and Culture (1871-2001)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鶏冠",
    "answer": "とさか,けいかん",
    "meaning": "cockscomb, crest"
  },
  {
    "question": "家裁",
    "answer": "かさい",
    "meaning": "family court"
  },
  {
    "question": "讃美",
    "answer": "さんび",
    "meaning": "praise, glorification, extolment"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍費",
    "answer": "ぐんぴ",
    "meaning": "war funds, war expenditures"
  },
  {
    "question": "貪婪",
    "answer": "たんらん,どんらん",
    "meaning": "covetousness, greed"
  },
  {
    "question": "本立て",
    "answer": "ほんたて",
    "meaning": "bookends"
  },
  {
    "question": "腐る程",
    "answer": "くさるほど",
    "meaning": "more than one can possibly use, countless (e.g. examples), (money) to burn, rolling in (cash)"
  },
  {
    "question": "寸鉄",
    "answer": "すんてつ",
    "meaning": "short blade, small weapon, epigram, pithy saying"
  },
  {
    "question": "食育",
    "answer": "しょくいく",
    "meaning": "dietary education, nutrition education, food education"
  },
  {
    "question": "戒名",
    "answer": "かいみょう",
    "meaning": "posthumous Buddhist name"
  },
  {
    "question": "柔毛",
    "answer": "じゅうもう",
    "meaning": "soft hair, villus (intestinal)"
  },
  {
    "question": "序盤戦",
    "answer": "じょばんせん",
    "meaning": "early stages (of a game), opening phase"
  },
  {
    "question": "涙雨",
    "answer": "なみだあめ",
    "meaning": "light rain, rain falling at a time of sadness"
  },
  {
    "question": "飯炊き",
    "answer": "めしたき",
    "meaning": "cooking rice, kitchenmaid, cook"
  },
  {
    "question": "撚る",
    "answer": "ひねる,よる",
    "meaning": "to twist, to wrench, to turn (a switch on or off, etc.), to wring (a neck), to puzzle over, to defea"
  },
  {
    "question": "価値判断",
    "answer": "かちはんだん",
    "meaning": "value judgement, value judgment"
  },
  {
    "question": "拠出",
    "answer": "きょしゅつ",
    "meaning": "donation, contribution"
  },
  {
    "question": "家並",
    "answer": "いえなみ,やなみ",
    "meaning": "row of houses, each house, every house, every door"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨模様",
    "answer": "あまもよう,あめもよう",
    "meaning": "signs of rain, threat of rain"
  },
  {
    "question": "捩じ込む",
    "answer": "ねじこむ",
    "meaning": "to screw in, to thrust into, to push into, to shove into, to squeeze in (e.g. meeting), to protest ("
  },
  {
    "question": "仕切り板",
    "answer": "しきりいた",
    "meaning": "partition board, plank used as a partition, board used in a ship to prevent the cargo from moving ar"
  },
  {
    "question": "上半期",
    "answer": "かみはんき",
    "meaning": "first half of the year, first half of the fiscal year"
  },
  {
    "question": "撓う",
    "answer": "しなう",
    "meaning": "to bend, to warp, to yield, to be supple (e.g. bamboo, body), to be flexible, to be pliant"
  },
  {
    "question": "金歯",
    "answer": "きんば",
    "meaning": "gold tooth"
  },
  {
    "question": "物臭",
    "answer": "ものぐさ",
    "meaning": "laziness, lazy person"
  },
  {
    "question": "鈍ら",
    "answer": "なまくら",
    "meaning": "blunt (e.g. sword), dull, lazy, cowardly, good for nothing"
  },
  {
    "question": "除草",
    "answer": "じょそう",
    "meaning": "weeding"
  },
  {
    "question": "編み棒",
    "answer": "あみぼう",
    "meaning": "knitting needle"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち飲み",
    "answer": "たちのみ",
    "meaning": "drinking while standing"
  },
  {
    "question": "弧状",
    "answer": "こじょう",
    "meaning": "arc shape, crescent shape"
  },
  {
    "question": "各紙",
    "answer": "かくし",
    "meaning": "every newspaper"
  },
  {
    "question": "節減",
    "answer": "せつげん",
    "meaning": "retrenchment, curtailment, economy"
  },
  {
    "question": "冠水",
    "answer": "かんすい",
    "meaning": "being covered with water (i.e. in a flood), being submerged, being inundated, flooding"
  },
  {
    "question": "廉価",
    "answer": "れんか",
    "meaning": "low price, moderate price"
  },
  {
    "question": "不如意",
    "answer": "ふにょい",
    "meaning": "contrary to one's wishes, gone awry, gone amiss, short of money, in financial difficulty"
  },
  {
    "question": "適所",
    "answer": "てきしょ",
    "meaning": "right place, right position, right post"
  },
  {
    "question": "御曹子",
    "answer": "おんぞうし",
    "meaning": "son of a distinguished family, son of a noble"
  },
  {
    "question": "路上生活",
    "answer": "ろじょうせいかつ",
    "meaning": "living on the street, life on the streets, homelessness"
  },
  {
    "question": "母性愛",
    "answer": "ぼせいあい",
    "meaning": "maternal love"
  },
  {
    "question": "外人部隊",
    "answer": "がいじんぶたい",
    "meaning": "Foreign Legion"
  },
  {
    "question": "細緻",
    "answer": "さいち",
    "meaning": "minute, meticulous"
  },
  {
    "question": "古道具",
    "answer": "ふるどうぐ,こどうぐ",
    "meaning": "old furniture, curios, secondhand goods"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶飯事",
    "answer": "さはんじ",
    "meaning": "commonly occurring thing, commonplace event, bread and butter item"
  },
  {
    "question": "七変化",
    "answer": "しちへんげ",
    "meaning": "lantana (plant, flower), hydrangea (Hydrangea macrophylla), kabuki dance in which the dancer quickly"
  },
  {
    "question": "点線",
    "answer": "てんせん",
    "meaning": "dotted line, perforated line"
  },
  {
    "question": "弓形",
    "answer": "ゆみなり,ゆみがた,きゅうけい",
    "meaning": "bow shape, arc, arch, segment (of a circle)"
  },
  {
    "question": "古豪",
    "answer": "こごう",
    "meaning": "veteran, old-timer, man of experience"
  },
  {
    "question": "合成写真",
    "answer": "ごうせいしゃしん",
    "meaning": "composite or montage photograph"
  },
  {
    "question": "錬磨",
    "answer": "れんま",
    "meaning": "training, practice, practising, cultivation"
  },
  {
    "question": "乃至",
    "answer": "ないし",
    "meaning": "from ... to, between ... and, or"
  },
  {
    "question": "満天下",
    "answer": "まんてんか",
    "meaning": "all over the world"
  },
  {
    "question": "防腐剤",
    "answer": "ぼうふざい",
    "meaning": "antiseptic, preservative"
  },
  {
    "question": "基礎代謝",
    "answer": "きそたいしゃ",
    "meaning": "basal metabolism"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会の窓",
    "answer": "しゃかいのまど",
    "meaning": "trouser zipper (mainly for males), fly"
  },
  {
    "question": "発起",
    "answer": "ほっき,はっき",
    "meaning": "proposal, promotion, spiritual awakening, resolution"
  },
  {
    "question": "落し",
    "answer": "おとし",
    "meaning": "dropping, losing, missing item, something one forgot to write down, trap, wooden protrusion from a J"
  },
  {
    "question": "罪過",
    "answer": "ざいか",
    "meaning": "offence, offense, fault"
  },
  {
    "question": "暖冬",
    "answer": "だんとう",
    "meaning": "mild winter, warm winter"
  },
  {
    "question": "待ち惚け",
    "answer": "まちぼうけ",
    "meaning": "waiting in vain"
  },
  {
    "question": "不順",
    "answer": "ふじゅん",
    "meaning": "irregular, unseasonable, changeable, unsettled, abnormal"
  },
  {
    "question": "和製",
    "answer": "わせい",
    "meaning": "Japanese-made"
  },
  {
    "question": "咽頭",
    "answer": "いんとう",
    "meaning": "pharynx"
  },
  {
    "question": "返杯",
    "answer": "へんぱい",
    "meaning": "offering a cup (of sake) in return"
  },
  {
    "question": "消散",
    "answer": "しょうさん",
    "meaning": "evaporation, dispersion, dissipation"
  },
  {
    "question": "英検",
    "answer": "えいけん",
    "meaning": "English proficiency test (esp. the STEP test)"
  },
  {
    "question": "誂え",
    "answer": "あつらえ",
    "meaning": "order, article ordered"
  },
  {
    "question": "側部",
    "answer": "そくぶ",
    "meaning": "the side"
  },
  {
    "question": "仏前",
    "answer": "ぶつぜん",
    "meaning": "(before a) Buddhist altar, before the Buddha, offering placed on a Buddhist altar, incense money, co"
  },
  {
    "question": "常緑",
    "answer": "じょうりょく",
    "meaning": "evergreen"
  },
  {
    "question": "とろ火",
    "answer": "とろび",
    "meaning": "low flame (heat, gas)"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍楽隊",
    "answer": "ぐんがくたい",
    "meaning": "military or naval band"
  },
  {
    "question": "首を括る",
    "answer": "くびをくくる",
    "meaning": "to hang oneself, to strangle oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "無期延期",
    "answer": "むきえんき",
    "meaning": "indefinite postponement"
  },
  {
    "question": "半焼",
    "answer": "はんしょう",
    "meaning": "partial destruction by fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "不随意",
    "answer": "ふずいい",
    "meaning": "involuntary"
  },
  {
    "question": "肺結核",
    "answer": "はいけっかく",
    "meaning": "pulmonary tuberculosis, consumption"
  },
  {
    "question": "御馳走様",
    "answer": "ごちそうさま",
    "meaning": "thank you (for the meal), that was a delicious meal, thank you (for displaying lovey-dovey behaviour"
  },
  {
    "question": "明朝体",
    "answer": "みんちょうたい",
    "meaning": "Ming (typeface), Minchō"
  },
  {
    "question": "近視眼的",
    "answer": "きんしがんてき",
    "meaning": "myopic, short-sighted"
  },
  {
    "question": "目が高い",
    "answer": "めがたかい",
    "meaning": "having an expert eye, having a discerning eye"
  },
  {
    "question": "遣り甲斐",
    "answer": "やりがい",
    "meaning": "being worth doing"
  },
  {
    "question": "粒揃い",
    "answer": "つぶぞろい",
    "meaning": "uniform excellence"
  },
  {
    "question": "敗る",
    "answer": "やぶる",
    "meaning": "to defeat, to beat"
  },
  {
    "question": "掘り込む",
    "answer": "ほりこむ",
    "meaning": "to dig into"
  },
  {
    "question": "往々",
    "answer": "おうおう",
    "meaning": "sometimes, often"
  },
  {
    "question": "人待ち",
    "answer": "ひとまち",
    "meaning": "waiting for someone to arrive"
  },
  {
    "question": "盛衰",
    "answer": "せいすい",
    "meaning": "rise and fall, ups and downs, welfare, vicissitudes"
  },
  {
    "question": "防虫剤",
    "answer": "ぼうちゅうざい",
    "meaning": "insect repellent"
  },
  {
    "question": "葺く",
    "answer": "ふく",
    "meaning": "to roof (a house with some material), to thatch, to shingle, to tile"
  },
  {
    "question": "恣意",
    "answer": "しい",
    "meaning": "arbitrariness"
  },
  {
    "question": "三文小説",
    "answer": "さんもんしょうせつ",
    "meaning": "dime novel"
  },
  {
    "question": "地固め",
    "answer": "じがため",
    "meaning": "ground leveling, ground levelling, groundwork, laying foundations"
  },
  {
    "question": "路頭",
    "answer": "ろとう",
    "meaning": "roadside, wayside"
  },
  {
    "question": "小菊",
    "answer": "こぎく",
    "meaning": "small chrysanthemum, small low grade piece of Japanese paper used as a kettle rest or as a tissue, p"
  },
  {
    "question": "岩室",
    "answer": "いわむろ",
    "meaning": "cave"
  },
  {
    "question": "銅鐸",
    "answer": "どうたく",
    "meaning": "bell-shaped bronze vessel of Yayoi period"
  },
  {
    "question": "大禍時",
    "answer": "おおまがとき",
    "meaning": "twilight, time for disasters (similar to 'the witching hour' but not midnight)"
  },
  {
    "question": "島守",
    "answer": "とうしゅ,しまもり",
    "meaning": "island chief"
  },
  {
    "question": "観音堂",
    "answer": "かんのんどう",
    "meaning": "temple dedicated to Kannon"
  },
  {
    "question": "将星",
    "answer": "しょうせい",
    "meaning": "commander"
  },
  {
    "question": "天機",
    "answer": "てんき",
    "meaning": "secret of nature, profound secret, disposition, character, nature, emperor's health, emperor's well-"
  },
  {
    "question": "内侍",
    "answer": "ないし,ないじ",
    "meaning": "maid of honor, maid of honour"
  },
  {
    "question": "南都",
    "answer": "なんと",
    "meaning": "Nara, Kongōbu-ji"
  },
  {
    "question": "八咫",
    "answer": "やあた,やた",
    "meaning": "eight ata (approx. 144 cm), large, long"
  },
  {
    "question": "本科",
    "answer": "ほんか",
    "meaning": "regular course, this lesson"
  },
  {
    "question": "国際警察",
    "answer": "こくさいけいさつ",
    "meaning": "international police"
  },
  {
    "question": "公証人",
    "answer": "こうしょうにん",
    "meaning": "notary public, notary, public notary"
  },
  {
    "question": "廬",
    "answer": "いおり,いお,ろ",
    "meaning": "hermitage, retreat, small house, thatched hut"
  },
  {
    "question": "中道",
    "answer": "ちゅうどう,なかみち",
    "meaning": "middle of the road, centrism, moderation, golden mean, the middle (of what one is doing), half-way,"
  },
  {
    "question": "論理回路",
    "answer": "ろんりかいろ",
    "meaning": "logic device, logic circuit"
  },
  {
    "question": "槙",
    "answer": "まき",
    "meaning": "yew plum pine (Podocarpus macrophyllus)"
  },
  {
    "question": "霊草",
    "answer": "れいそう",
    "meaning": "miracle herb, sacred herb, herb with mysterious powers"
  },
  {
    "question": "数寄者",
    "answer": "すきしゃ",
    "meaning": "man of refined tastes, refined person, tea ceremony master, lewd man, lecher"
  },
  {
    "question": "円蓋",
    "answer": "えんがい",
    "meaning": "cupola, dome, vault"
  },
  {
    "question": "雀斑",
    "answer": "そばかす",
    "meaning": "freckles"
  },
  {
    "question": "青田",
    "answer": "あおた",
    "meaning": "green paddy"
  },
  {
    "question": "句点",
    "answer": "くてん",
    "meaning": "period, full stop"
  },
  {
    "question": "国際連盟",
    "answer": "こくさいれんめい",
    "meaning": "League of Nations"
  },
  {
    "question": "沙漠",
    "answer": "さばく",
    "meaning": "desert"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤木",
    "answer": "あかぎ",
    "meaning": "bishop wood (Bischofia javanica), barked tree, red tree"
  },
  {
    "question": "供犠",
    "answer": "くぎ",
    "meaning": "sacrifice, sacrificial animal"
  },
  {
    "question": "共和党",
    "answer": "きょうわとう",
    "meaning": "Republican Party"
  },
  {
    "question": "九州地方",
    "answer": "きゅうしゅうちほう",
    "meaning": "Kyushu region (sometimes incl. the Nansei Islands)"
  },
  {
    "question": "振付",
    "answer": "ふりつけ",
    "meaning": "choreography, dance composition, dance coaching"
  },
  {
    "question": "不分明",
    "answer": "ふぶんめい",
    "meaning": "obscure, vague"
  },
  {
    "question": "燎原",
    "answer": "りょうげん",
    "meaning": "agricultural burning, setting a field ablaze"
  },
  {
    "question": "図像",
    "answer": "ずぞう",
    "meaning": "icon, simple ink drawing (of a buddha, mandala, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "山津波",
    "answer": "やまつなみ",
    "meaning": "landslide"
  },
  {
    "question": "刀狩り",
    "answer": "かたながり",
    "meaning": "sword hunt, sword confiscation"
  },
  {
    "question": "首座",
    "answer": "しゅざ",
    "meaning": "seat of honor, seat of honour, head of the table, head"
  },
  {
    "question": "媒質",
    "answer": "ばいしつ",
    "meaning": "medium (for carrying energy waves), transmission medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "戎",
    "answer": "えびす",
    "meaning": "peoples formerly of northern Japan with distinct language and culture (i.e. the Ainu), provincial (i"
  },
  {
    "question": "修験道",
    "answer": "しゅげんどう",
    "meaning": "Shugendō, Japanese mountain asceticism incorporating Shinto and Buddhist concepts"
  },
  {
    "question": "下弦",
    "answer": "かげん",
    "meaning": "(moon's) last quarter"
  },
  {
    "question": "花房",
    "answer": "はなぶさ,かぼう",
    "meaning": "calyx, corolla"
  },
  {
    "question": "検地",
    "answer": "けんち",
    "meaning": "land survey, cadastral survey"
  },
  {
    "question": "亜麻",
    "answer": "あま",
    "meaning": "flax (Linum usitatissimum), linseed"
  },
  {
    "question": "塩田",
    "answer": "えんでん",
    "meaning": "saltpan, field for drying salt"
  },
  {
    "question": "文理",
    "answer": "ぶんり",
    "meaning": "literature and science, context, (line of) reasoning"
  },
  {
    "question": "樅",
    "answer": "もみ",
    "meaning": "Japanese fir (Abies firma), momi fir"
  },
  {
    "question": "水甕",
    "answer": "みずがめ",
    "meaning": "water jug"
  },
  {
    "question": "銅銭",
    "answer": "どうせん",
    "meaning": "copper coin"
  },
  {
    "question": "功臣",
    "answer": "こうしん",
    "meaning": "meritorious retainer"
  },
  {
    "question": "打数",
    "answer": "だすう",
    "meaning": "times at bat"
  },
  {
    "question": "幻妖",
    "answer": "げんよう",
    "meaning": "confusing people, magic, ghost, monster, etc., the true identity of which is unknown"
  },
  {
    "question": "目指し",
    "answer": "めざし",
    "meaning": "aim, goal, purpose, look, eyes, expression of eyes"
  },
  {
    "question": "輪作",
    "answer": "りんさく",
    "meaning": "rotation of crops"
  },
  {
    "question": "双手",
    "answer": "もろて,もろで,そうしゅ",
    "meaning": "both hands"
  },
  {
    "question": "深宇宙",
    "answer": "しんうちゅう",
    "meaning": "deep space"
  },
  {
    "question": "領事",
    "answer": "りょうじ",
    "meaning": "consul"
  },
  {
    "question": "行き逢う",
    "answer": "いきあう,ゆきあう",
    "meaning": "to meet somebody by chance, to happen upon"
  },
  {
    "question": "懼れる",
    "answer": "おそれる",
    "meaning": "to fear, to be afraid of"
  },
  {
    "question": "卵酒",
    "answer": "たまござけ",
    "meaning": "eggnog (made with sake)"
  },
  {
    "question": "連ドラ",
    "answer": "れんドラ",
    "meaning": "drama serial"
  },
  {
    "question": "二強",
    "answer": "にきょう",
    "meaning": "top two"
  },
  {
    "question": "逗子",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "蕗",
    "answer": "ふき,ふふき",
    "meaning": "giant butterbur (Petasites japonicus), Japanese sweet coltsfoot"
  },
  {
    "question": "御母",
    "answer": "おかあ,みおも",
    "meaning": "mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "蔓薔薇",
    "answer": "つるばら",
    "meaning": "climbing rose, rambling rose"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き綱",
    "answer": "ひきづな",
    "meaning": "tow rope, bell rope, dog lead, lanyard, sash cord"
  },
  {
    "question": "大時化",
    "answer": "おおしけ",
    "meaning": "very stormy weather (at sea), very poor catch of fish (due to stormy seas)"
  },
  {
    "question": "金属性",
    "answer": "きんぞくせい",
    "meaning": "metallic quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "静かの海",
    "answer": "しずかのうみ",
    "meaning": "Mare Tranquillitatis (lunar mare), Sea of Tranquility"
  },
  {
    "question": "長駆",
    "answer": "ちょうく",
    "meaning": "a long march"
  },
  {
    "question": "見台",
    "answer": "けんだい",
    "meaning": "bookrest, bookholder"
  },
  {
    "question": "正真",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "給電",
    "answer": "きゅうでん",
    "meaning": "supplying electricity"
  },
  {
    "question": "阿弥陀",
    "answer": "あみだ",
    "meaning": "Amitabha (Buddha), Amida, ghostleg lottery, ladder lottery, lottery in which participants trace a li"
  },
  {
    "question": "帝大",
    "answer": "ていだい",
    "meaning": "(former) imperial university"
  },
  {
    "question": "井戸掘り",
    "answer": "いどほり",
    "meaning": "well digging, well digger"
  },
  {
    "question": "間欠的",
    "answer": "かんけつてき",
    "meaning": "intermittent"
  },
  {
    "question": "用人",
    "answer": "ようにん",
    "meaning": "manager, steward, factotum, person next in rank to the chief retainers and in charge of general mana"
  },
  {
    "question": "魁偉",
    "answer": "かいい",
    "meaning": "brawny, muscular, impressive, gigantic"
  },
  {
    "question": "臨死",
    "answer": "りんし",
    "meaning": "near-death, close to death"
  },
  {
    "question": "月色",
    "answer": "げっしょく",
    "meaning": "moonlight"
  },
  {
    "question": "抜け作",
    "answer": "ぬけさく",
    "meaning": "fool, blockhead"
  },
  {
    "question": "燥ぐ",
    "answer": "はしゃぐ",
    "meaning": "to make merry, to frolic, to be in high spirits"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹輪",
    "answer": "ちくわ",
    "meaning": "chikuwa, tube-shaped fish paste cake"
  },
  {
    "question": "流体力学",
    "answer": "りゅうたいりきがく",
    "meaning": "fluid mechanics, fluid dynamics, hydrodynamics"
  },
  {
    "question": "請い",
    "answer": "こい",
    "meaning": "request, entreaty"
  },
  {
    "question": "藁半紙",
    "answer": "わらばんし",
    "meaning": "straw paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "叡知",
    "answer": "えいち",
    "meaning": "wisdom, intelligence, intellect"
  },
  {
    "question": "横臥",
    "answer": "おうが",
    "meaning": "lying on one's side"
  },
  {
    "question": "韻律",
    "answer": "いんりつ",
    "meaning": "metre (of a poem), meter, rhythm, prosody"
  },
  {
    "question": "厄落とし",
    "answer": "やくおとし",
    "meaning": "escape from evil, exorcism"
  },
  {
    "question": "手筋",
    "answer": "てすじ",
    "meaning": "lines of the palm, aptitude, handwriting, apt move (in a go or shogi game), standard method"
  },
  {
    "question": "製剤",
    "answer": "せいざい",
    "meaning": "formulation (of pharmaceuticals), preparation, pharmaceutical production"
  },
  {
    "question": "カノン砲",
    "answer": "カノンほう",
    "meaning": "cannon (esp. high-velocity artillery)"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒙古斑",
    "answer": "もうこはん",
    "meaning": "Mongolian spot, Mongolian blue spot, congenital dermal melanocytosis"
  },
  {
    "question": "天翔る",
    "answer": "あまがける,あまかける",
    "meaning": "to soar (esp. of spirits and gods)"
  },
  {
    "question": "詩情",
    "answer": "しじょう",
    "meaning": "poetic sentiment, poetic interest, poetic inspiration"
  },
  {
    "question": "参詣",
    "answer": "さんけい",
    "meaning": "visit to a temple or shrine, worship, pilgrimage"
  },
  {
    "question": "諮問",
    "answer": "しもん",
    "meaning": "consultation, question, enquiry, inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "海魚",
    "answer": "かいぎょ",
    "meaning": "ocean fish, saltwater fish"
  },
  {
    "question": "大枝",
    "answer": "おおえだ",
    "meaning": "large branch"
  },
  {
    "question": "短波",
    "answer": "たんぱ",
    "meaning": "short wave"
  },
  {
    "question": "枕辺",
    "answer": "まくらべ",
    "meaning": "bedside"
  },
  {
    "question": "死亡届",
    "answer": "しぼうとどけ",
    "meaning": "report of death, notification of a death"
  },
  {
    "question": "溶融",
    "answer": "ようゆう",
    "meaning": "melting, fusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "紐帯",
    "answer": "ちゅうたい",
    "meaning": "important connection, important social foundation, close relation, tight relationship, intimate rela"
  },
  {
    "question": "切創",
    "answer": "せっそう",
    "meaning": "cut wound, incised wound, knife wound"
  },
  {
    "question": "差し歯",
    "answer": "さしば",
    "meaning": "post crown, dowel crown, false tooth, 'tooth' on a geta clog"
  },
  {
    "question": "爪先立つ",
    "answer": "つまさきだつ",
    "meaning": "to stand on tiptoes"
  },
  {
    "question": "宜い",
    "answer": "よい,えい",
    "meaning": "good, excellent, fine, nice, pleasant, agreeable, sufficient, enough, ready, prepared, profitable (d"
  },
  {
    "question": "火玉",
    "answer": "ひだま",
    "meaning": "falling star, fireball"
  },
  {
    "question": "心気",
    "answer": "しんき",
    "meaning": "mentality, mood, sentiment, feelings, fretfulness, tedium, irritation"
  },
  {
    "question": "渦状",
    "answer": "かじょう",
    "meaning": "spiral"
  },
  {
    "question": "掲揚",
    "answer": "けいよう",
    "meaning": "hoisting (e.g. a flag), raising, flying, putting up"
  },
  {
    "question": "女部屋",
    "answer": "おんなべや",
    "meaning": "room for female servants, room where there are women, jail for women"
  },
  {
    "question": "太平楽",
    "answer": "たいへいらく",
    "meaning": "happy-go-lucky"
  },
  {
    "question": "通風",
    "answer": "つうふう",
    "meaning": "ventilation, draft, airing"
  },
  {
    "question": "無精卵",
    "answer": "むせいらん",
    "meaning": "wind egg, unfertilized egg, unfertilised egg"
  },
  {
    "question": "広漠",
    "answer": "こうばく",
    "meaning": "vast, wide, boundless"
  },
  {
    "question": "製粉",
    "answer": "せいふん",
    "meaning": "milling, grinding into flour"
  },
  {
    "question": "養鶏",
    "answer": "ようけい",
    "meaning": "poultry raising, poultry farming, chicken farming"
  },
  {
    "question": "低血糖",
    "answer": "ていけっとう",
    "meaning": "low blood sugar, hypoglycemia"
  },
  {
    "question": "笏",
    "answer": "しゃく",
    "meaning": "shaku (flat wooden or ivory baton carried in the right hand when in ceremonial imperial or Shinto ga"
  },
  {
    "question": "途上国",
    "answer": "とじょうこく",
    "meaning": "developing country"
  },
  {
    "question": "哀感",
    "answer": "あいかん",
    "meaning": "pathos"
  },
  {
    "question": "失業率",
    "answer": "しつぎょうりつ",
    "meaning": "unemployment rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "畦",
    "answer": "あぜ,うね",
    "meaning": "ridge of earth between rice fields, ridge between grooves in threshold or lintel, footpath between r"
  },
  {
    "question": "拝す",
    "answer": "はいす",
    "meaning": "to bow, to worship, to receive, to see"
  },
  {
    "question": "学派",
    "answer": "がくは",
    "meaning": "school, sect"
  },
  {
    "question": "事業者",
    "answer": "じぎょうしゃ",
    "meaning": "business person, operator, carrier (telecommunications, transport, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "知育",
    "answer": "ちいく",
    "meaning": "intellectual training"
  },
  {
    "question": "経済政策",
    "answer": "けいざいせいさく",
    "meaning": "economic policy"
  },
  {
    "question": "同年輩",
    "answer": "どうねんぱい",
    "meaning": "persons of the same age"
  },
  {
    "question": "木端",
    "answer": "こっぱ,こば",
    "meaning": "wood chip, splinter, worthless thing, worthless person, thin shingles"
  },
  {
    "question": "等量",
    "answer": "とうりょう",
    "meaning": "equal amount, same quantity"
  },
  {
    "question": "漂白剤",
    "answer": "ひょうはくざい",
    "meaning": "bleaching agent, bleach"
  },
  {
    "question": "晩春",
    "answer": "ばんしゅん",
    "meaning": "late spring, third month of the lunar calendar"
  },
  {
    "question": "差し止め",
    "answer": "さしとめ",
    "meaning": "prohibition, ban, suspension"
  },
  {
    "question": "下水管",
    "answer": "げすいかん",
    "meaning": "sewer pipe"
  },
  {
    "question": "忠勇",
    "answer": "ちゅうゆう",
    "meaning": "loyalty and bravery"
  },
  {
    "question": "祝祭日",
    "answer": "しゅくさいじつ",
    "meaning": "national holiday"
  },
  {
    "question": "酒焼け",
    "answer": "さけやけ,さかやけ",
    "meaning": "facial flushing, drink-reddened face, having a hoarse voice after drinking, raspiness caused by over"
  },
  {
    "question": "外遊び",
    "answer": "そとあそび",
    "meaning": "playing outside"
  },
  {
    "question": "芥子",
    "answer": "からし,けし",
    "meaning": "mustard, opium poppy (Papaver somniferum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き波",
    "answer": "ひきなみ",
    "meaning": "backwash, rip current, undertow, stern wave, drawback (of a tsunami, i.e. when a wave trough reaches"
  },
  {
    "question": "単線",
    "answer": "たんせん",
    "meaning": "single track (railway), single line, solid wire, solid-core wire, single-strand wire"
  },
  {
    "question": "理屈屋",
    "answer": "りくつや",
    "meaning": "quibbler"
  },
  {
    "question": "皮張り",
    "answer": "かわばり",
    "meaning": "leather-covered"
  },
  {
    "question": "暗中",
    "answer": "あんちゅう",
    "meaning": "in the dark"
  },
  {
    "question": "列する",
    "answer": "れっする",
    "meaning": "to line up with, to be a member of, to rank with, to attend, to take part in"
  },
  {
    "question": "無課金",
    "answer": "むかきん",
    "meaning": "free-to-play, without paying"
  },
  {
    "question": "近縁",
    "answer": "きんえん",
    "meaning": "close relation (association)"
  },
  {
    "question": "識字",
    "answer": "しきじ",
    "meaning": "literacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛護",
    "answer": "あいご",
    "meaning": "protection, tender care"
  },
  {
    "question": "空っ風",
    "answer": "からっかぜ",
    "meaning": "cold, strong, dry wind"
  },
  {
    "question": "繙く",
    "answer": "ひもとく",
    "meaning": "to read (a book), to open (a book) to read, to unravel (e.g. a mystery), to discover (the truth)"
  },
  {
    "question": "狂想曲",
    "answer": "きょうそうきょく",
    "meaning": "capriccio"
  },
  {
    "question": "静的",
    "answer": "せいてき",
    "meaning": "static"
  },
  {
    "question": "洒落者",
    "answer": "しゃれもの",
    "meaning": "dandy, fop"
  },
  {
    "question": "登坂",
    "answer": "とうはん,とはん",
    "meaning": "climbing a slope (hill), ascending a hill"
  },
  {
    "question": "鰤",
    "answer": "ぶり",
    "meaning": "Japanese amberjack (species of yellowtail, Seriola quinqueradiata)"
  },
  {
    "question": "意趣",
    "answer": "いしゅ",
    "meaning": "grudge, malice, spite, intention, disposition, obstinacy, reason, revenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "重罰",
    "answer": "じゅうばつ",
    "meaning": "heavy punishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "送信機",
    "answer": "そうしんき",
    "meaning": "transmitter (device)"
  },
  {
    "question": "補整",
    "answer": "ほせい",
    "meaning": "adjust (by supplementing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "妬心",
    "answer": "としん",
    "meaning": "jealousy"
  },
  {
    "question": "無担保",
    "answer": "むたんぽ",
    "meaning": "unsecured (loan)"
  },
  {
    "question": "入管",
    "answer": "にゅうかん",
    "meaning": "Immigration Bureau"
  },
  {
    "question": "文壇",
    "answer": "ぶんだん",
    "meaning": "literary world, literary circles"
  },
  {
    "question": "亦",
    "answer": "また",
    "meaning": "again, once more, once again, another time, some other time, also, too, as well, likewise, on the ot"
  },
  {
    "question": "死活",
    "answer": "しかつ",
    "meaning": "life and death, life or death"
  },
  {
    "question": "場馴れ",
    "answer": "ばなれ",
    "meaning": "experience, being accustomed (to something), poise in a critical situation"
  },
  {
    "question": "射手座",
    "answer": "いてざ",
    "meaning": "Sagittarius (constellation), the Archer"
  },
  {
    "question": "配当金",
    "answer": "はいとうきん",
    "meaning": "dividend"
  },
  {
    "question": "所要",
    "answer": "しょよう",
    "meaning": "required, needed, necessary"
  },
  {
    "question": "球児",
    "answer": "きゅうじ",
    "meaning": "baseball-playing teenager, high-school baseball player"
  },
  {
    "question": "酸素吸入",
    "answer": "さんそきゅうにゅう",
    "meaning": "oxygen inhalation"
  },
  {
    "question": "自由裁量",
    "answer": "じゆうさいりょう",
    "meaning": "latitude, (at one's) discretion, discretionary powers, a free hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "赫々",
    "answer": "かくかく,かっかく",
    "meaning": "brilliant, bright, glorious"
  },
  {
    "question": "蟻塚",
    "answer": "ありづか",
    "meaning": "anthill"
  },
  {
    "question": "買い換え",
    "answer": "かいかえ",
    "meaning": "buying a replacement, replacing by buying something new"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤味噌",
    "answer": "あかみそ",
    "meaning": "dark-brown miso paste"
  },
  {
    "question": "当たり年",
    "answer": "あたりどし",
    "meaning": "good year, lucky year, bumper year, banner year"
  },
  {
    "question": "報恩",
    "answer": "ほうおん",
    "meaning": "repaying a kindness, gratitude"
  },
  {
    "question": "身軽い",
    "answer": "みがるい",
    "meaning": "nimble, light"
  },
  {
    "question": "化学肥料",
    "answer": "かがくひりょう",
    "meaning": "chemical fertilizer, chemical fertiliser"
  },
  {
    "question": "玄孫",
    "answer": "げんそん,やしゃご",
    "meaning": "great-great-grandchild, fourth-generation descendant"
  },
  {
    "question": "混信",
    "answer": "こんしん",
    "meaning": "jamming, interference, cross talk"
  },
  {
    "question": "正中",
    "answer": "せいちゅう,しょうなか,しょうちゅう",
    "meaning": "the exact middle, center of a noh stage, Shōchū era (1324.12.9-1326.4.26)"
  },
  {
    "question": "度忘れ",
    "answer": "どわすれ",
    "meaning": "lapse of memory, (something) slipping one's mind, forgetting for a moment something one knows well"
  },
  {
    "question": "依怙地",
    "answer": "いこじ,えこじ",
    "meaning": "obstinate, stubborn, obdurate, headstrong, willful, perverse"
  },
  {
    "question": "阿呆面",
    "answer": "あほうづら,あほづら",
    "meaning": "stupid face, foolish look on one's face"
  },
  {
    "question": "連絡帳",
    "answer": "れんらくちょう",
    "meaning": "correspondence notebook (e.g. between teacher and parents), contact notebook, communication notebook"
  },
  {
    "question": "運命論",
    "answer": "うんめいろん",
    "meaning": "fatalism"
  },
  {
    "question": "早出",
    "answer": "はやで",
    "meaning": "early arrival"
  },
  {
    "question": "切り合う",
    "answer": "きりあう",
    "meaning": "to fight with swords, to cross swords"
  },
  {
    "question": "好し",
    "answer": "よし,えし",
    "meaning": "good, excellent, fine, nice, pleasant, agreeable"
  },
  {
    "question": "締め出し",
    "answer": "しめだし",
    "meaning": "shutout, shutting out, lock-out, freeze-out"
  },
  {
    "question": "一本槍",
    "answer": "いっぽんやり",
    "meaning": "guiding principle, single-minded policy, one's sole talent, single spear"
  },
  {
    "question": "拝受",
    "answer": "はいじゅ",
    "meaning": "receiving (accepting)"
  },
  {
    "question": "流失",
    "answer": "りゅうしつ",
    "meaning": "being washed away"
  },
  {
    "question": "迎い",
    "answer": "むかい",
    "meaning": "meeting, greeting, welcome"
  },
  {
    "question": "中南米",
    "answer": "ちゅうなんべい",
    "meaning": "Central and South America"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷夏",
    "answer": "れいか",
    "meaning": "cool summer, cold summer, cooler-than-normal summer"
  },
  {
    "question": "互換",
    "answer": "ごかん",
    "meaning": "interchange, transposition, compatible (e.g. PC)"
  },
  {
    "question": "縺れ",
    "answer": "もつれ",
    "meaning": "tangle, entanglement, snarl, complication, difficulties, trouble, troubles, snag"
  },
  {
    "question": "濡れ羽色",
    "answer": "ぬればいろ",
    "meaning": "jet black"
  },
  {
    "question": "品行",
    "answer": "ひんこう",
    "meaning": "(moral) conduct, behaviour, behavior, deportment"
  },
  {
    "question": "算式",
    "answer": "さんしき",
    "meaning": "mathematical formula, numerical expression"
  },
  {
    "question": "組み替え",
    "answer": "くみかえ",
    "meaning": "rearrangement (of classes), recomposition, recombination, reclassification"
  },
  {
    "question": "女親",
    "answer": "おんなおや",
    "meaning": "mother, female parent"
  },
  {
    "question": "宗教学",
    "answer": "しゅうきょうがく",
    "meaning": "the study or science of religion, religious studies"
  },
  {
    "question": "芸が無い",
    "answer": "げいがない",
    "meaning": "lacking skill, uninspiring, unexciting, dull, unrefined, boring (from being too plain)"
  },
  {
    "question": "脅迫罪",
    "answer": "きょうはくざい",
    "meaning": "criminal intimidation"
  },
  {
    "question": "あ行",
    "answer": "あぎょう",
    "meaning": "the 'a' column of the Japanese syllabary table (a, i, u, e, o)"
  },
  {
    "question": "夭折",
    "answer": "ようせつ",
    "meaning": "premature death"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り零す",
    "answer": "とりこぼす",
    "meaning": "to lose an easy game, to suffer an unexpected defeat, to lose information"
  },
  {
    "question": "前段",
    "answer": "ぜんだん",
    "meaning": "preceding paragraph, first part"
  },
  {
    "question": "動態",
    "answer": "どうたい",
    "meaning": "movement, dynamic state"
  },
  {
    "question": "詰め切る",
    "answer": "つめきる",
    "meaning": "to be or remain always on hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "基本設計",
    "answer": "きほんせっけい",
    "meaning": "baseline design, preliminary design, basic design"
  },
  {
    "question": "経産婦",
    "answer": "けいさんぷ",
    "meaning": "woman who has given birth"
  },
  {
    "question": "大時代",
    "answer": "おおじだい,だいじだい",
    "meaning": "old-fashioned, antiquated, anachronistic"
  },
  {
    "question": "両性",
    "answer": "りょうせい",
    "meaning": "both sexes"
  },
  {
    "question": "弔意",
    "answer": "ちょうい",
    "meaning": "condolence, sympathy, mourning"
  },
  {
    "question": "昵懇",
    "answer": "じっこん",
    "meaning": "intimacy, familiarity, closeness"
  },
  {
    "question": "唐草模様",
    "answer": "からくさもよう",
    "meaning": "arabesque, scrollwork"
  },
  {
    "question": "回らす",
    "answer": "めぐらす",
    "meaning": "to enclose (with), to surround (with), to encircle, to turn (one's head, heel, etc.), to think over,"
  },
  {
    "question": "育休",
    "answer": "いくきゅう",
    "meaning": "childcare leave, leave taken after the compulsory maternity leave"
  },
  {
    "question": "咳止め",
    "answer": "せきどめ",
    "meaning": "cough medicine, cough syrup, cough lozenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "誤訳",
    "answer": "ごやく",
    "meaning": "mistranslation"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄地",
    "answer": "うすじ",
    "meaning": "thin cloth"
  },
  {
    "question": "男盛り",
    "answer": "おとこざかり",
    "meaning": "prime of manhood"
  },
  {
    "question": "口溶け",
    "answer": "くちどけ",
    "meaning": "melt-in-the-mouth feeling"
  },
  {
    "question": "旅の空",
    "answer": "たびのそら",
    "meaning": "away from home, while travelling"
  },
  {
    "question": "乾拭き",
    "answer": "からぶき",
    "meaning": "polishing with a dry cloth, wiping with a dry cloth"
  },
  {
    "question": "部屋干し",
    "answer": "へやぼし",
    "meaning": "indoor drying, hanging clothes to dry indoors"
  },
  {
    "question": "残額",
    "answer": "ざんがく",
    "meaning": "remaining amount, balance (of an account)"
  },
  {
    "question": "行動半径",
    "answer": "こうどうはんけい",
    "meaning": "radius of action, sphere of activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "越権",
    "answer": "えっけん",
    "meaning": "going beyond authority, unauthorized, unauthorised, ultra vires"
  },
  {
    "question": "静物",
    "answer": "せいぶつ",
    "meaning": "still object, object at rest, still life (painting, drawing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "順風",
    "answer": "じゅんぷう",
    "meaning": "favourable wind, favorable wind"
  },
  {
    "question": "涙顔",
    "answer": "なみだがお",
    "meaning": "tearful face, tear-stained face"
  },
  {
    "question": "鰻登り",
    "answer": "うなぎのぼり",
    "meaning": "rising rapidly (e.g. prices, popularity), soaring, skyrocketing, going through the roof"
  },
  {
    "question": "御立派",
    "answer": "ごりっぱ",
    "meaning": "splendid, fine, handsome, elegant, imposing, prominent, legal, legitimate"
  },
  {
    "question": "三鳥",
    "answer": "さんちょう",
    "meaning": "chicken, goose and pheasant, cuckoo, Japanese bush warbler and wagtail"
  },
  {
    "question": "藪から棒",
    "answer": "やぶからぼう",
    "meaning": "bolt from the blue, unforeseen event, complete surprise"
  },
  {
    "question": "腰が重い",
    "answer": "こしがおもい",
    "meaning": "slow to act, slow in starting work"
  },
  {
    "question": "休す",
    "answer": "きゅうす",
    "meaning": "to come to an end, to rest"
  },
  {
    "question": "迎え酒",
    "answer": "むかえざけ",
    "meaning": "hair of the dog, morning drink to get rid of a hangover"
  },
  {
    "question": "困り者",
    "answer": "こまりもの",
    "meaning": "good-for-nothing, scapegrace, nuisance, trouble"
  },
  {
    "question": "胸三寸",
    "answer": "むねさんずん",
    "meaning": "heart, mind, feelings"
  },
  {
    "question": "終始一貫",
    "answer": "しゅうしいっかん",
    "meaning": "consistently, unchangingly, throughout"
  },
  {
    "question": "新説",
    "answer": "しんせつ",
    "meaning": "new theory"
  },
  {
    "question": "多幸",
    "answer": "たこう",
    "meaning": "great happiness"
  },
  {
    "question": "山姫",
    "answer": "やまひめ",
    "meaning": "mountain goddess"
  },
  {
    "question": "飛驒",
    "answer": "ひだ",
    "meaning": "Hida (city, region of Gifu Prefecture, Edo-period province)"
  },
  {
    "question": "儺",
    "answer": "な",
    "meaning": "(ceremony of) driving out evil spirits"
  },
  {
    "question": "鶴亀",
    "answer": "つるかめ",
    "meaning": "crane and tortoise (symbol of longevity, artistic motif)"
  },
  {
    "question": "民権",
    "answer": "みんけん",
    "meaning": "civil rights"
  },
  {
    "question": "別当",
    "answer": "べっとう",
    "meaning": "groom, footman, stableman, equerry, steward, intendant, head of an institution, esp. religious, head"
  },
  {
    "question": "三題噺",
    "answer": "さんだいばなし",
    "meaning": "performing a rakugo story on the spot based on three topics given by the audience, impromptu rakugo"
  },
  {
    "question": "口器",
    "answer": "こうき",
    "meaning": "trophi (mouthparts of an insect, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "月虹",
    "answer": "げっこう",
    "meaning": "moonbow, lunar rainbow, whitish rainbow cast by moonlight, lunar bow, space rainbow"
  },
  {
    "question": "刈入れ",
    "answer": "かりいれ",
    "meaning": "harvest"
  },
  {
    "question": "異本",
    "answer": "いほん",
    "meaning": "variant edition (of a book), alternative version, different manuscript, strange book, rare book, uni"
  },
  {
    "question": "海南",
    "answer": "かいなん",
    "meaning": "island in the southern sea (esp. Shikoku)"
  },
  {
    "question": "門人",
    "answer": "もんじん",
    "meaning": "pupil, student, follower"
  },
  {
    "question": "不二",
    "answer": "ふじ,ふに",
    "meaning": "being two sides of the same coin, being the same (while appearing different), Very sincerely yours,"
  },
  {
    "question": "青雲",
    "answer": "せいうん",
    "meaning": "blue sky, erudition, detachment from the world, high rank"
  },
  {
    "question": "除染",
    "answer": "じょせん",
    "meaning": "decontamination (e.g. from chemical or radioactive contamination)"
  },
  {
    "question": "市庁",
    "answer": "しちょう",
    "meaning": "municipal office"
  },
  {
    "question": "庚",
    "answer": "かのえ,こう",
    "meaning": "7th in rank, seventh sign of the Chinese calendar"
  },
  {
    "question": "公論",
    "answer": "こうろん",
    "meaning": "public opinion, unbiased criticism, unbiassed criticism"
  },
  {
    "question": "水葬",
    "answer": "すいそう",
    "meaning": "burial at sea"
  },
  {
    "question": "貪食",
    "answer": "どんしょく",
    "meaning": "voracity, ravenousness"
  },
  {
    "question": "泰斗",
    "answer": "たいと",
    "meaning": "great authority, eminent person, luminary"
  },
  {
    "question": "黝い",
    "answer": "あおぐろい",
    "meaning": "black with hints of blue (as in a bruise), bluish black"
  },
  {
    "question": "墓掘り",
    "answer": "はかほり",
    "meaning": "gravedigger"
  },
  {
    "question": "振子",
    "answer": "ふりこ,しんし",
    "meaning": "pendulum"
  },
  {
    "question": "国父",
    "answer": "こくふ",
    "meaning": "father of one's country, father of the nation"
  },
  {
    "question": "智略",
    "answer": "ちりゃく",
    "meaning": "ingenuity, resourcefulness"
  },
  {
    "question": "環礁",
    "answer": "かんしょう",
    "meaning": "atoll, circular coral reef"
  },
  {
    "question": "佐久",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "巴",
    "answer": "ともえ,パ",
    "meaning": "tomoe, heraldic design composed of two or more interlocked comma-shaped figures, Pali language"
  },
  {
    "question": "裏番",
    "answer": "うらばん",
    "meaning": "secret leader of a group of juvenile delinquents, program in a competing timeslot (programme)"
  },
  {
    "question": "貨客船",
    "answer": "かきゃくせん,かかくせん",
    "meaning": "combined cargo and passenger ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "外商",
    "answer": "がいしょう",
    "meaning": "foreign merchant, foreign businessman, foreign company, foreign firm, out-of-store sales, calling on"
  },
  {
    "question": "後頭",
    "answer": "こうとう",
    "meaning": "back of the head, occiput"
  },
  {
    "question": "三才",
    "answer": "さんさい",
    "meaning": "the three powers: heaven, earth and man"
  },
  {
    "question": "防毒",
    "answer": "ぼうどく",
    "meaning": "gasproofing"
  },
  {
    "question": "起訴状",
    "answer": "きそじょう",
    "meaning": "(written) indictment"
  },
  {
    "question": "房事",
    "answer": "ぼうじ",
    "meaning": "sex, sexual intercourse, lovemaking"
  },
  {
    "question": "教会堂",
    "answer": "きょうかいどう",
    "meaning": "church, cathedral, chapel"
  },
  {
    "question": "車屋",
    "answer": "くるまや",
    "meaning": "small car dealership, auto repair shop selling cars, wheelwright, cartwright, rickshawman, rickshaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "兵営",
    "answer": "へいえい",
    "meaning": "barracks"
  },
  {
    "question": "進水式",
    "answer": "しんすいしき",
    "meaning": "launching ceremony, ceremonial ship launching"
  },
  {
    "question": "牡羊座",
    "answer": "おひつじざ",
    "meaning": "Aries (constellation), the Ram"
  },
  {
    "question": "抑留",
    "answer": "よくりゅう",
    "meaning": "internment, detainment, detention"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄附",
    "answer": "きふ",
    "meaning": "contribution, donation"
  },
  {
    "question": "温浴",
    "answer": "おんよく",
    "meaning": "hot bath, warm bath"
  },
  {
    "question": "研ぎ師",
    "answer": "とぎし",
    "meaning": "sharpener (of swords) and polisher (of mirrors)"
  },
  {
    "question": "光通信",
    "answer": "ひかりつうしん",
    "meaning": "light-wave communication"
  },
  {
    "question": "秋波",
    "answer": "しゅうは",
    "meaning": "amorous glance, wink"
  },
  {
    "question": "方正",
    "answer": "ほうせい",
    "meaning": "rectitude"
  },
  {
    "question": "募兵",
    "answer": "ぼへい",
    "meaning": "recruiting"
  },
  {
    "question": "市松人形",
    "answer": "いちまつにんぎょう",
    "meaning": "ichimatsu doll, traditional Japanese doll with a torso made of hardened sawdust"
  },
  {
    "question": "消防庁",
    "answer": "しょうぼうちょう",
    "meaning": "Fire and Disaster Management Agency (formerly: Fire Defense Agency) (Defence)"
  },
  {
    "question": "複利",
    "answer": "ふくり",
    "meaning": "compound interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "女郎屋",
    "answer": "じょろうや",
    "meaning": "brothel"
  },
  {
    "question": "前照灯",
    "answer": "ぜんしょうとう",
    "meaning": "headlights"
  },
  {
    "question": "社会体制",
    "answer": "しゃかいたいせい",
    "meaning": "social system"
  },
  {
    "question": "真鯛",
    "answer": "まだい",
    "meaning": "red sea bream (Pagrus major), Japanese sea bream, red tai, porgy"
  },
  {
    "question": "大潮",
    "answer": "おおしお",
    "meaning": "spring tide"
  },
  {
    "question": "半白",
    "answer": "はんぱく",
    "meaning": "grayish color, greyish colour, grizzled hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "内庭",
    "answer": "うちにわ,ないてい",
    "meaning": "inner court, quadrangle"
  },
  {
    "question": "下人",
    "answer": "げにん",
    "meaning": "low-rank person, menial"
  },
  {
    "question": "湾岸戦争",
    "answer": "わんがんせんそう",
    "meaning": "the Gulf War"
  },
  {
    "question": "野牛",
    "answer": "やぎゅう",
    "meaning": "buffalo"
  },
  {
    "question": "自走砲",
    "answer": "じそうほう",
    "meaning": "self-propelled artillery"
  },
  {
    "question": "河畔",
    "answer": "かはん",
    "meaning": "riverside"
  },
  {
    "question": "角形",
    "answer": "かくがた,かくけい,かっけい",
    "meaning": "square shape, oblong, rectangle, polygon, -gon, Japanese rectangular envelope (opening on the short"
  },
  {
    "question": "規格化",
    "answer": "きかくか",
    "meaning": "standardization, standardisation, normalization (e.g. in maths)"
  },
  {
    "question": "大蔵省",
    "answer": "おおくらしょう",
    "meaning": "Ministry of Finance (1869-2001), Ministry of the Treasury (under the ritsuryo system)"
  },
  {
    "question": "貢ぎ",
    "answer": "みつぎ",
    "meaning": "tribute"
  },
  {
    "question": "多国籍軍",
    "answer": "たこくせきぐん",
    "meaning": "multinational force"
  },
  {
    "question": "諸処",
    "answer": "しょしょ",
    "meaning": "here and there, everywhere"
  },
  {
    "question": "臂",
    "answer": "ひじ",
    "meaning": "elbow"
  },
  {
    "question": "撓める",
    "answer": "たわめる,ためる,いためる",
    "meaning": "to bend (a piece of wood, etc.), to bow, to bend, to train (e.g. a branch), to treat leather, sharks"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦塵",
    "answer": "せんじん",
    "meaning": "battle dust, the tumult of war"
  },
  {
    "question": "孫息子",
    "answer": "まごむすこ",
    "meaning": "grandson"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄瓶",
    "answer": "てつびん",
    "meaning": "iron kettle"
  },
  {
    "question": "青海苔",
    "answer": "あおのり",
    "meaning": "green laver (Enteromorpha), green dried seaweed, nori"
  },
  {
    "question": "火山帯",
    "answer": "かざんたい",
    "meaning": "volcanic belt, volcanic zone"
  },
  {
    "question": "蚤の市",
    "answer": "のみのいち",
    "meaning": "flea market"
  },
  {
    "question": "校訓",
    "answer": "こうくん",
    "meaning": "school precepts"
  },
  {
    "question": "中間層",
    "answer": "ちゅうかんそう",
    "meaning": "the middle class"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪筆",
    "answer": "あくひつ",
    "meaning": "poor handwriting"
  },
  {
    "question": "副都心",
    "answer": "ふくとしん",
    "meaning": "subcenter (of a large city) (subcentre), urban subcenter"
  },
  {
    "question": "通関",
    "answer": "つうかん",
    "meaning": "customs clearance"
  },
  {
    "question": "売上高",
    "answer": "うりあげだか",
    "meaning": "sales, amount sold, proceeds"
  },
  {
    "question": "霧中",
    "answer": "むちゅう",
    "meaning": "in the fog"
  },
  {
    "question": "声調",
    "answer": "せいちょう",
    "meaning": "tone (of voice), tone (e.g. in Chinese)"
  },
  {
    "question": "随筆",
    "answer": "ずいひつ",
    "meaning": "essays, miscellaneous writings, literary jottings"
  },
  {
    "question": "明くる",
    "answer": "あくる",
    "meaning": "next (day, morning, etc.), following"
  },
  {
    "question": "主幹",
    "answer": "しゅかん",
    "meaning": "chief editor, managing editor, manager, person in charge"
  },
  {
    "question": "胆石",
    "answer": "たんせき",
    "meaning": "gallstones"
  },
  {
    "question": "防風",
    "answer": "ぼうふう",
    "meaning": "protection against wind, Saposhnikovia divaricata (species of umbellifer used in Chinese medicine),"
  },
  {
    "question": "守役",
    "answer": "もりやく",
    "meaning": "nurse, nanny, guardian"
  },
  {
    "question": "御免蒙る",
    "answer": "ごめんこうむる",
    "meaning": "to receive permission, to leave (with someone's permission), to retire, to refuse, to beg off doing"
  },
  {
    "question": "艀",
    "answer": "はしけ",
    "meaning": "barge"
  },
  {
    "question": "送り状",
    "answer": "おくりじょう",
    "meaning": "invoice, consignment note, sender's copy, receipt of shipment"
  },
  {
    "question": "銅鏡",
    "answer": "どうきょう",
    "meaning": "bronze mirror"
  },
  {
    "question": "花代",
    "answer": "はなだい",
    "meaning": "price of a flower, fee for a geisha's companionship"
  },
  {
    "question": "大政奉還",
    "answer": "たいせいほうかん",
    "meaning": "restoration of imperial rule"
  },
  {
    "question": "罅割れ",
    "answer": "ひびわれ",
    "meaning": "crack, crevice, fissure"
  },
  {
    "question": "単音",
    "answer": "たんおん",
    "meaning": "single sound, monosyllable, phone, monotone (harmonica, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦時体制",
    "answer": "せんじたいせい",
    "meaning": "wartime regime, war footing"
  },
  {
    "question": "本署",
    "answer": "ほんしょ",
    "meaning": "police headquarters, main office, this office"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼集",
    "answer": "こしゅう",
    "meaning": "gathering (esp. troops), getting together, mustering"
  },
  {
    "question": "拉ぐ",
    "answer": "ひしぐ",
    "meaning": "to crush"
  },
  {
    "question": "付け毛",
    "answer": "つけげ",
    "meaning": "hairpiece, hair filler, artificial hair, wig"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑巾掛け",
    "answer": "ぞうきんがけ,ぞうきんかけ",
    "meaning": "cleaning with a cloth (floors, etc.), dirty work, low-level work, apprentice work"
  },
  {
    "question": "玄米茶",
    "answer": "げんまいちゃ",
    "meaning": "tea (with roasted rice)"
  },
  {
    "question": "佳き",
    "answer": "よき",
    "meaning": "goodness, good"
  },
  {
    "question": "渡し舟",
    "answer": "わたしぶね",
    "meaning": "ferry, ferryboat"
  },
  {
    "question": "冬虫夏草",
    "answer": "とうちゅうかそう,ふゆむしなつくさ",
    "meaning": "caterpillar fungus (esp. Cordyceps sinensis)"
  },
  {
    "question": "怨めしい",
    "answer": "うらめしい",
    "meaning": "reproachful, hateful, bitter"
  },
  {
    "question": "独居",
    "answer": "どっきょ",
    "meaning": "living alone, solitude, solitary life"
  },
  {
    "question": "権謀",
    "answer": "けんぼう",
    "meaning": "scheme, stratagem, ploy"
  },
  {
    "question": "釣り込む",
    "answer": "つりこむ",
    "meaning": "to take in, to attract"
  },
  {
    "question": "塵取り",
    "answer": "ちりとり",
    "meaning": "dustpan"
  },
  {
    "question": "失政",
    "answer": "しっせい",
    "meaning": "misgovernment"
  },
  {
    "question": "送り手",
    "answer": "おくりて",
    "meaning": "sender"
  },
  {
    "question": "方眼紙",
    "answer": "ほうがんし",
    "meaning": "graph paper, section paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "創建",
    "answer": "そうけん",
    "meaning": "establishment, foundation"
  },
  {
    "question": "筋金",
    "answer": "すじがね",
    "meaning": "a metal reinforcement"
  },
  {
    "question": "死屍",
    "answer": "しし",
    "meaning": "corpse"
  },
  {
    "question": "強肩",
    "answer": "きょうけん",
    "meaning": "strong throwing arm"
  },
  {
    "question": "蕎麦粉",
    "answer": "そばこ",
    "meaning": "buckwheat flour"
  },
  {
    "question": "仏道",
    "answer": "ぶつどう",
    "meaning": "Buddhism, Buddhist teachings"
  },
  {
    "question": "無才",
    "answer": "むさい",
    "meaning": "lacking talent or ability"
  },
  {
    "question": "多情",
    "answer": "たじょう",
    "meaning": "profligate, licentious, of loose morals, amorous, emotional, passionate, sentimental"
  },
  {
    "question": "書院",
    "answer": "しょいん",
    "meaning": "drawing room, study, publishing house, writing alcove"
  },
  {
    "question": "今以て",
    "answer": "いまもって",
    "meaning": "until now, still, yet, (not) yet, since"
  },
  {
    "question": "片袖",
    "answer": "かたそで",
    "meaning": "one sleeve"
  },
  {
    "question": "西洋料理",
    "answer": "せいようりょうり",
    "meaning": "Western food, Western-style food"
  },
  {
    "question": "磊落",
    "answer": "らいらく",
    "meaning": "open-hearted, free and easy, frank, not being bothered by unimportant things"
  },
  {
    "question": "善玉",
    "answer": "ぜんだま",
    "meaning": "good person"
  },
  {
    "question": "十両",
    "answer": "じゅうりょう",
    "meaning": "second highest division, wrestlers of the second highest division"
  },
  {
    "question": "強心剤",
    "answer": "きょうしんざい",
    "meaning": "cardiotonic drug"
  },
  {
    "question": "大願成就",
    "answer": "たいがんじょうじゅ,だいがんじょうじゅ",
    "meaning": "realization of a great ambition, realisation of a great ambition"
  },
  {
    "question": "縄文",
    "answer": "じょうもん",
    "meaning": "straw-rope pattern pressed into earthenware, Jōmon period (ca. 14000-1000 BCE)"
  },
  {
    "question": "根性焼き",
    "answer": "こんじょうやき",
    "meaning": "cigarette burn"
  },
  {
    "question": "川床",
    "answer": "かわどこ,かわゆか,ゆか",
    "meaning": "riverbed, raised platform on the bank of a river for enjoying the cool in summer"
  },
  {
    "question": "刳り貫く",
    "answer": "くりぬく",
    "meaning": "to gouge out, to excavate, to hollow, to bore, to drill, to carve (e.g. pumpkin)"
  },
  {
    "question": "和合",
    "answer": "わごう",
    "meaning": "harmony, concord, agreement, unity, union"
  },
  {
    "question": "育毛",
    "answer": "いくもう",
    "meaning": "hair restoration, new hair growth"
  },
  {
    "question": "大猟",
    "answer": "たいりょう",
    "meaning": "good bag (hunting)"
  },
  {
    "question": "高菜",
    "answer": "たかな",
    "meaning": "leaf mustard (Brassica juncea var. integrifolia), mustard greens"
  },
  {
    "question": "理非",
    "answer": "りひ",
    "meaning": "right and wrong"
  },
  {
    "question": "鑑識眼",
    "answer": "かんしきがん",
    "meaning": "discerning eye"
  },
  {
    "question": "難詰",
    "answer": "なんきつ",
    "meaning": "reprimand"
  },
  {
    "question": "非常召集",
    "answer": "ひじょうしょうしゅう",
    "meaning": "emergency summons"
  },
  {
    "question": "封建",
    "answer": "ほうけん",
    "meaning": "feudalistic"
  },
  {
    "question": "公民",
    "answer": "こうみん,おおみたから",
    "meaning": "citizen, freemen, imperial subjects, the people"
  },
  {
    "question": "汁粉",
    "answer": "しるこ",
    "meaning": "shiruko, sweet red-bean soup with mochi"
  },
  {
    "question": "電磁誘導",
    "answer": "でんじゆうどう",
    "meaning": "electromagnetic induction"
  },
  {
    "question": "胃カメラ",
    "answer": "いカメラ",
    "meaning": "endoscope, gastrocamera"
  },
  {
    "question": "中国茶",
    "answer": "ちゅうごくちゃ",
    "meaning": "Chinese tea"
  },
  {
    "question": "匹夫",
    "answer": "ひっぷ",
    "meaning": "(humble) man, coarse man, rustic"
  },
  {
    "question": "波浪",
    "answer": "はろう",
    "meaning": "waves, billows, surge"
  },
  {
    "question": "不沈",
    "answer": "ふちん",
    "meaning": "unsinkable"
  },
  {
    "question": "四つ這い",
    "answer": "よつばい",
    "meaning": "crawling on all fours, getting on one's hands and knees, falling flat"
  },
  {
    "question": "騒擾",
    "answer": "そうじょう",
    "meaning": "riot, disturbance"
  },
  {
    "question": "富貴",
    "answer": "ふうき,ふっき",
    "meaning": "riches and honours (honors), wealth and rank"
  },
  {
    "question": "法務局",
    "answer": "ほうむきょく",
    "meaning": "regional legal affairs bureau"
  },
  {
    "question": "然したる",
    "answer": "さしたる",
    "meaning": "(any) particular, special, material, perceptible, noticeable"
  },
  {
    "question": "生存権",
    "answer": "せいぞんけん",
    "meaning": "right to life"
  },
  {
    "question": "染み着く",
    "answer": "しみつく",
    "meaning": "to be indelibly stained or ingrained, to be dyed in deeply"
  },
  {
    "question": "建て増し",
    "answer": "たてまし",
    "meaning": "building addition or extension, an annex"
  },
  {
    "question": "宇宙論",
    "answer": "うちゅうろん",
    "meaning": "cosmology"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷却水",
    "answer": "れいきゃくすい",
    "meaning": "coolant"
  },
  {
    "question": "水菓子",
    "answer": "みずがし",
    "meaning": "jelly dessert, fruit"
  },
  {
    "question": "話法",
    "answer": "わほう",
    "meaning": "narration"
  },
  {
    "question": "同月",
    "answer": "どうげつ",
    "meaning": "the same month"
  },
  {
    "question": "譴責",
    "answer": "けんせき",
    "meaning": "reprimand, rebuke, censure, reproof"
  },
  {
    "question": "全店",
    "answer": "ぜんてん",
    "meaning": "the whole store"
  },
  {
    "question": "植込み",
    "answer": "うえこみ",
    "meaning": "thick growth of plants, plantation, shrubbery, thicket"
  },
  {
    "question": "原状",
    "answer": "げんじょう",
    "meaning": "original state"
  },
  {
    "question": "然る",
    "answer": "さる,しかる",
    "meaning": "a particular, a certain, that kind of, such a"
  },
  {
    "question": "満期",
    "answer": "まんき",
    "meaning": "expiration (of a term), maturity (e.g. investment), serving one's (full) time"
  },
  {
    "question": "穿ち過ぎ",
    "answer": "うがちすぎ",
    "meaning": "reading too much into things"
  },
  {
    "question": "水利",
    "answer": "すいり",
    "meaning": "utilization of water, water supply, irrigation, water transportation, navigability (e.g. of a river)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎮痛薬",
    "answer": "ちんつうやく",
    "meaning": "analgesic"
  },
  {
    "question": "豪儀",
    "answer": "ごうぎ,ごうき",
    "meaning": "great, grand, obstinate, stubborn"
  },
  {
    "question": "売名",
    "answer": "ばいめい",
    "meaning": "self-advertisement"
  },
  {
    "question": "有責",
    "answer": "ゆうせき",
    "meaning": "fault, responsibility, culpability"
  },
  {
    "question": "小間物屋",
    "answer": "こまものや",
    "meaning": "haberdashery, sundries store"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑感",
    "answer": "ざっかん",
    "meaning": "miscellaneous thoughts (on), miscellaneous impressions"
  },
  {
    "question": "卒塔婆",
    "answer": "そとば,そとうば",
    "meaning": "stupa, dagoba, wooden grave tablet"
  },
  {
    "question": "充つ",
    "answer": "みつ",
    "meaning": "to be full, to wax (e.g. moon), to rise (e.g. tide), to mature, to expire"
  },
  {
    "question": "枝葉末節",
    "answer": "しようまっせつ",
    "meaning": "unimportant details, inessentials"
  },
  {
    "question": "建設業",
    "answer": "けんせつぎょう",
    "meaning": "construction industry, construction business"
  },
  {
    "question": "ぼろ負け",
    "answer": "ぼろまけ",
    "meaning": "decisive defeat, rout, thrashing, losing big"
  },
  {
    "question": "人類愛",
    "answer": "じんるいあい",
    "meaning": "humanism, love for humanity"
  },
  {
    "question": "三角定規",
    "answer": "さんかくじょうぎ",
    "meaning": "triangles (used in mechanical drawing), set square"
  },
  {
    "question": "頭割り",
    "answer": "あたまわり",
    "meaning": "sharing equally (costs, profits, etc.), splitting equally"
  },
  {
    "question": "聾",
    "answer": "つんぼ,みみしい,ろう",
    "meaning": "deafness, deaf person"
  },
  {
    "question": "伝道",
    "answer": "でんどう",
    "meaning": "missionary work, proselytizing, preaching, evangelism"
  },
  {
    "question": "踏み板",
    "answer": "ふみいた",
    "meaning": "board (across a ditch, etc.), step, tread, footboard, running board, pedal (of an organ, etc.), trea"
  },
  {
    "question": "両利き",
    "answer": "りょうきき",
    "meaning": "ambidexter, ambidexterity"
  },
  {
    "question": "ガラス質",
    "answer": "ガラスしつ",
    "meaning": "glassy, vitreous"
  },
  {
    "question": "手綱捌き",
    "answer": "たづなさばき",
    "meaning": "(one's) handling of the reins, how well one controls things"
  },
  {
    "question": "色彩感覚",
    "answer": "しきさいかんかく",
    "meaning": "sense of color, sense of colour"
  },
  {
    "question": "半病人",
    "answer": "はんびょうにん",
    "meaning": "semi-invalid"
  },
  {
    "question": "国交断絶",
    "answer": "こっこうだんぜつ",
    "meaning": "breakup of diplomatic relations, diplomatic break"
  },
  {
    "question": "手妻",
    "answer": "てづま",
    "meaning": "sleight of hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "厚地",
    "answer": "あつじ",
    "meaning": "thick cloth"
  },
  {
    "question": "中産階級",
    "answer": "ちゅうさんかいきゅう",
    "meaning": "middle class, bourgeoisie"
  },
  {
    "question": "内省的",
    "answer": "ないせいてき",
    "meaning": "reflective, introspective"
  },
  {
    "question": "海産",
    "answer": "かいさん",
    "meaning": "marine product, marine (e.g. product, animal etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "逃げ水",
    "answer": "にげみず",
    "meaning": "mirage"
  },
  {
    "question": "理想家",
    "answer": "りそうか",
    "meaning": "idealist"
  },
  {
    "question": "肉食女子",
    "answer": "にくしょくじょし",
    "meaning": "carnivorous female, predatory woman, aggressive woman who takes the initiative in relationships with"
  },
  {
    "question": "水先案内",
    "answer": "みずさきあんない",
    "meaning": "pilotage, pilot"
  },
  {
    "question": "画角",
    "answer": "がかく",
    "meaning": "angle of view (photography)"
  },
  {
    "question": "やくざ者",
    "answer": "やくざもの",
    "meaning": "professional gambler, gangster, gang member, good-for-nothing, ne'er-do-well, hoodlum, ruffian"
  },
  {
    "question": "左寄り",
    "answer": "ひだりより",
    "meaning": "left of center (politically), left-leaning, tending to the left"
  },
  {
    "question": "逆毛",
    "answer": "さかげ",
    "meaning": "back-combed hair, puffed up hair, teased hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "背高",
    "answer": "せいたか",
    "meaning": "tallness, tall person"
  },
  {
    "question": "天然資源",
    "answer": "てんねんしげん",
    "meaning": "natural resources"
  },
  {
    "question": "才気煥発",
    "answer": "さいきかんぱつ",
    "meaning": "quick-witted, a flash of brilliance, great wisdom"
  },
  {
    "question": "断捨離",
    "answer": "だんしゃり",
    "meaning": "decluttering, clearing out past accumulation, minimalism"
  },
  {
    "question": "今夕",
    "answer": "こんせき,こんゆう",
    "meaning": "this evening, tonight"
  },
  {
    "question": "尻上がり",
    "answer": "しりあがり",
    "meaning": "rising intonation, upward inflection, rising (sales, tendency, etc.), getting better, improvement, f"
  },
  {
    "question": "仏陀",
    "answer": "ぶっだ,ぶつだ",
    "meaning": "Buddha"
  },
  {
    "question": "菜食主義",
    "answer": "さいしょくしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "vegetarianism"
  },
  {
    "question": "一両日",
    "answer": "いちりょうじつ",
    "meaning": "(a) day or two"
  },
  {
    "question": "肺呼吸",
    "answer": "はいこきゅう",
    "meaning": "pulmonary respiration"
  },
  {
    "question": "けち臭い",
    "answer": "けちくさい",
    "meaning": "mean, stingy"
  },
  {
    "question": "湿潤",
    "answer": "しつじゅん",
    "meaning": "damp, moist, humid"
  },
  {
    "question": "半音",
    "answer": "はんおん",
    "meaning": "semitone, half-tone"
  },
  {
    "question": "搦める",
    "answer": "からめる",
    "meaning": "to entwine, to twine around, to mix together, to coordinate (with), to arrest"
  },
  {
    "question": "蟷螂の斧",
    "answer": "とうろうのおの",
    "meaning": "courageous but doomed resistance"
  },
  {
    "question": "一次元",
    "answer": "いちじげん",
    "meaning": "one dimensional"
  },
  {
    "question": "自己顕示",
    "answer": "じこけんじ",
    "meaning": "making oneself conspicuous, pressing one's own cause"
  },
  {
    "question": "百害",
    "answer": "ひゃくがい",
    "meaning": "great damage"
  },
  {
    "question": "激ウマ",
    "answer": "げきウマ",
    "meaning": "seriously delicious, very skillful, proficient"
  },
  {
    "question": "外面的",
    "answer": "がいめんてき",
    "meaning": "external, superficial, outward, surface"
  },
  {
    "question": "重量挙げ",
    "answer": "じゅうりょうあげ",
    "meaning": "weight lifting"
  },
  {
    "question": "名著",
    "answer": "めいちょ",
    "meaning": "famous book, masterpiece (literary work)"
  },
  {
    "question": "三段跳び",
    "answer": "さんだんとび",
    "meaning": "triple jump, hop, step and jump"
  },
  {
    "question": "大部",
    "answer": "たいぶ,だいぶ",
    "meaning": "lengthy (of a book, etc.), voluminous, most (e.g. most part), greater, fairly, a good deal, much"
  },
  {
    "question": "塩茹で",
    "answer": "しおゆで",
    "meaning": "boiling with salt, boiling in salty water (e.g. vegetables)"
  },
  {
    "question": "並足",
    "answer": "なみあし",
    "meaning": "walking pace, slow march"
  },
  {
    "question": "基本給",
    "answer": "きほんきゅう",
    "meaning": "base pay"
  },
  {
    "question": "幸せ太り",
    "answer": "しあわせぶとり",
    "meaning": "putting on weight from the good (married) life"
  },
  {
    "question": "連夜",
    "answer": "れんや",
    "meaning": "every evening, night after night"
  },
  {
    "question": "大入り",
    "answer": "おおいり",
    "meaning": "large attendance, full house, capacity audience"
  },
  {
    "question": "糊口",
    "answer": "ここう",
    "meaning": "bare livelihood, subsistence"
  },
  {
    "question": "移り行く",
    "answer": "うつりゆく",
    "meaning": "to change, to shift, to come and go"
  },
  {
    "question": "胸回り",
    "answer": "むねまわり",
    "meaning": "chest measurement, bust measurement"
  },
  {
    "question": "親の欲目",
    "answer": "おやのよくめ",
    "meaning": "parents' partiality for their children, parents overvaluing their children"
  },
  {
    "question": "樟",
    "answer": "くすのき,くす",
    "meaning": "camphor tree (Cinnamomum camphora), camphorwood, camphor laurel"
  },
  {
    "question": "羅国",
    "answer": "らこく",
    "meaning": "incense variety used in kōdō (orig. from Thailand)"
  },
  {
    "question": "星宿",
    "answer": "せいしゅく,ほとおりぼし,ほとほりぼし",
    "meaning": "constellation, mansion (any of the Chinese constellations used to divide the ecliptic into 28 positi"
  },
  {
    "question": "白道",
    "answer": "はくどう",
    "meaning": "moon's path"
  },
  {
    "question": "純利",
    "answer": "じゅんり",
    "meaning": "net profit"
  },
  {
    "question": "躑躅",
    "answer": "つつじ,てきちょく",
    "meaning": "azalea (Rhododendron spp.), hesitation, indecision, vacillation, wavering"
  },
  {
    "question": "尾花",
    "answer": "おばな",
    "meaning": "(ear of) Japanese pampas grass"
  },
  {
    "question": "神宮寺",
    "answer": "じんぐうじ",
    "meaning": "Buddhist temple within a Shinto shrine, temple attached to a shrine"
  },
  {
    "question": "陰暦",
    "answer": "いんれき",
    "meaning": "lunar calendar"
  },
  {
    "question": "天狗道",
    "answer": "てんぐどう",
    "meaning": "world of the tengu, hell of the long-nosed goblins"
  },
  {
    "question": "朝凪",
    "answer": "あさなぎ",
    "meaning": "morning calm (over the ocean)"
  },
  {
    "question": "焙烙",
    "answer": "ほうろく,ほうらく",
    "meaning": "earthenware baking pan, parching pan, form of punishment in which a person is forced to walk on an o"
  },
  {
    "question": "隠れ処",
    "answer": "かくれが",
    "meaning": "hiding place, hideout, refuge, retreat, hideaway"
  },
  {
    "question": "張形",
    "answer": "はりかた,はりがた",
    "meaning": "penis-shaped device, traditionally made of horn, shell or papier mache, dildo"
  },
  {
    "question": "原紙",
    "answer": "げんし",
    "meaning": "stencil, template, silkworm egg sheet"
  },
  {
    "question": "無重量",
    "answer": "むじゅうりょう",
    "meaning": "weightlessness, zero gravity"
  },
  {
    "question": "永禄",
    "answer": "えいろく",
    "meaning": "Eiroku era (1558.2.28-1570.4.23)"
  },
  {
    "question": "御話",
    "answer": "おはなし",
    "meaning": "story, tale"
  },
  {
    "question": "真言宗",
    "answer": "しんごんしゅう",
    "meaning": "Shingon sect (of Buddhism)"
  },
  {
    "question": "郵政",
    "answer": "ゆうせい",
    "meaning": "postal system"
  },
  {
    "question": "阿片窟",
    "answer": "あへんくつ",
    "meaning": "opium den"
  },
  {
    "question": "寛治",
    "answer": "かんじ",
    "meaning": "Kanji era (1087.4.7-1094.12.15)"
  },
  {
    "question": "倉敷",
    "answer": "くらしき",
    "meaning": "storage charges"
  },
  {
    "question": "正典",
    "answer": "せいてん",
    "meaning": "canon (i.e. the Biblical canon)"
  },
  {
    "question": "首斬り",
    "answer": "くびきり",
    "meaning": "decapitation, beheading, firings, dismissals, layoffs, downsizing, small samurai sword used for deca"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪相",
    "answer": "あくそう",
    "meaning": "evil countenance"
  },
  {
    "question": "情火",
    "answer": "じょうか",
    "meaning": "passion (of love)"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍衣",
    "answer": "ぐんい",
    "meaning": "military clothes"
  },
  {
    "question": "仙境",
    "answer": "せんきょう",
    "meaning": "fairyland, enchanted land"
  },
  {
    "question": "観艦式",
    "answer": "かんかんしき",
    "meaning": "naval review"
  },
  {
    "question": "海浜",
    "answer": "かいひん",
    "meaning": "seashore, seaside, beach"
  },
  {
    "question": "菰",
    "answer": "こも",
    "meaning": "woven straw mat (orig. made of wild rice leaves), beggar, Manchurian wild rice (Zizania latifolia)"
  },
  {
    "question": "老僧",
    "answer": "ろうそう",
    "meaning": "elderly priest"
  },
  {
    "question": "海砂",
    "answer": "かいさ",
    "meaning": "sea sand (sand collected from the ocean floor, as opposed to that which is used as an ingredient in"
  },
  {
    "question": "警務",
    "answer": "けいむ",
    "meaning": "police affairs, military police"
  },
  {
    "question": "編み笠",
    "answer": "あみがさ",
    "meaning": "braided hat"
  },
  {
    "question": "偽典",
    "answer": "ぎてん",
    "meaning": "pseudepigrapha"
  },
  {
    "question": "幽冥",
    "answer": "ゆうめい",
    "meaning": "semidarkness, deep and strange, hades, the present and the other world, dark and light"
  },
  {
    "question": "振替",
    "answer": "ふりかえ",
    "meaning": "transfer, switching over, change, money transfer (usu. between accounts held by the same person), po"
  },
  {
    "question": "双頭の鷲",
    "answer": "そうとうのわし",
    "meaning": "double-headed eagle (symbol of heraldry)"
  },
  {
    "question": "羹",
    "answer": "あつもの",
    "meaning": "broth made of fish and vegetables"
  },
  {
    "question": "可逆",
    "answer": "かぎゃく",
    "meaning": "reversible, invertible"
  },
  {
    "question": "深謀",
    "answer": "しんぼう",
    "meaning": "deliberate, careful, thoughtful, deeply laid plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "火山弾",
    "answer": "かざんだん",
    "meaning": "volcanic projectiles"
  },
  {
    "question": "三角柱",
    "answer": "さんかくちゅう",
    "meaning": "triangular prism"
  },
  {
    "question": "吸血蝙蝠",
    "answer": "きゅうけつこうもり",
    "meaning": "vampire bat"
  },
  {
    "question": "柏餅",
    "answer": "かしわもち",
    "meaning": "rice cakes wrapped in oak leaves"
  },
  {
    "question": "若侍",
    "answer": "わかざむらい",
    "meaning": "young samurai"
  },
  {
    "question": "朱印",
    "answer": "しゅいん",
    "meaning": "red seal"
  },
  {
    "question": "豊麗",
    "answer": "ほうれい",
    "meaning": "rich (design), beautiful, splendid"
  },
  {
    "question": "大円",
    "answer": "だいえん",
    "meaning": "large circle, great circle"
  },
  {
    "question": "血尿",
    "answer": "けつにょう",
    "meaning": "bloody urine, hematuria (haematuria)"
  },
  {
    "question": "兎角",
    "answer": "とかく",
    "meaning": "(doing) various things, (doing) this and that, being apt to, being prone to, tending to, at any rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "国学",
    "answer": "こくがく",
    "meaning": "study of (ancient) Japanese literature and culture, provincial school (under Japan's ritsuryo system"
  },
  {
    "question": "服属",
    "answer": "ふくぞく",
    "meaning": "a follower, yield allegiance to"
  },
  {
    "question": "吹き荒む",
    "answer": "ふきすさむ",
    "meaning": "to blow violently"
  },
  {
    "question": "牛脂",
    "answer": "ぎゅうし",
    "meaning": "beef tallow"
  },
  {
    "question": "退廷",
    "answer": "たいてい",
    "meaning": "leaving a court"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼き串",
    "answer": "やきぐし",
    "meaning": "skewer, spit"
  },
  {
    "question": "卵管",
    "answer": "らんかん",
    "meaning": "fallopian tube, oviduct"
  },
  {
    "question": "西南西",
    "answer": "せいなんせい",
    "meaning": "west-southwest"
  },
  {
    "question": "凡退",
    "answer": "ぼんたい",
    "meaning": "out in 1-2-3 order"
  },
  {
    "question": "桟敷",
    "answer": "さじき,さんじき",
    "meaning": "reviewing stand, box, gallery"
  },
  {
    "question": "生き神",
    "answer": "いきがみ",
    "meaning": "living god"
  },
  {
    "question": "感状",
    "answer": "かんじょう",
    "meaning": "letter of commendation"
  },
  {
    "question": "国税局",
    "answer": "こくぜいきょく",
    "meaning": "revenue office, taxation bureau"
  },
  {
    "question": "州境",
    "answer": "しゅうきょう",
    "meaning": "state boundary, provincial boundary"
  },
  {
    "question": "公卿",
    "answer": "くぎょう,こうけい,くげ",
    "meaning": "court noble, nobility, three lords and nine ministers (of the ancient Chinese government)"
  },
  {
    "question": "御辞儀",
    "answer": "おじぎ",
    "meaning": "bow, bowing"
  },
  {
    "question": "野点",
    "answer": "のだて",
    "meaning": "open-air tea ceremony, aristocrat taking a break during a trip in a palanquin, something standing in"
  },
  {
    "question": "還り",
    "answer": "かえり",
    "meaning": "return, coming back"
  },
  {
    "question": "御家人",
    "answer": "ごけにん",
    "meaning": "lower-ranking vassal in the Kamakura and Edo periods"
  },
  {
    "question": "随従",
    "answer": "ずいじゅう",
    "meaning": "following the lead of, playing second fiddle to, follower"
  },
  {
    "question": "衾",
    "answer": "ふすま",
    "meaning": "quilt, bedding"
  },
  {
    "question": "卓絶",
    "answer": "たくぜつ",
    "meaning": "excellence"
  },
  {
    "question": "誑す",
    "answer": "たらす",
    "meaning": "to cajole, to deceive, to seduce"
  },
  {
    "question": "運動家",
    "answer": "うんどうか",
    "meaning": "activist, campaigner, crusader (e.g. for women's rights), athlete, sporty person"
  },
  {
    "question": "日経",
    "answer": "にっけい",
    "meaning": "Nikkei (newspaper, share index)"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸盆",
    "answer": "まるぼん",
    "meaning": "round tray"
  },
  {
    "question": "附近",
    "answer": "ふきん",
    "meaning": "neighbourhood, neighborhood, vicinity, environs, approaching"
  },
  {
    "question": "幽谷",
    "answer": "ゆうこく",
    "meaning": "deep ravine, glen"
  },
  {
    "question": "元型",
    "answer": "げんけい",
    "meaning": "archetype"
  },
  {
    "question": "園庭",
    "answer": "えんてい",
    "meaning": "garden, kindergarten yard, playground"
  },
  {
    "question": "死命",
    "answer": "しめい",
    "meaning": "fate, life or death"
  },
  {
    "question": "射場",
    "answer": "しゃじょう,いば",
    "meaning": "archery range, archery ground, shooting range, firing range, shooting gallery, launch site (e.g. for"
  },
  {
    "question": "天台宗",
    "answer": "てんだいしゅう",
    "meaning": "Tendai sect (of Buddhism)"
  },
  {
    "question": "環境省",
    "answer": "かんきょうしょう",
    "meaning": "Ministry of the Environment"
  },
  {
    "question": "考古",
    "answer": "こうこ",
    "meaning": "study of antiquities, archeology"
  },
  {
    "question": "散髪屋",
    "answer": "さんぱつや",
    "meaning": "barber, barbershop, barber shop"
  },
  {
    "question": "掃滅",
    "answer": "そうめつ",
    "meaning": "wiping out, annihilation"
  },
  {
    "question": "忽",
    "answer": "こつ",
    "meaning": "one hundred-thousandth"
  },
  {
    "question": "招請",
    "answer": "しょうせい,しょうじょう,ちょうしょう",
    "meaning": "invitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "極微",
    "answer": "きょくび,ごくび",
    "meaning": "microscopic, infinitesimal"
  },
  {
    "question": "方途",
    "answer": "ほうと",
    "meaning": "way, means"
  },
  {
    "question": "奏法",
    "answer": "そうほう",
    "meaning": "playing (instrument), playing method, touch"
  },
  {
    "question": "境涯",
    "answer": "きょうがい",
    "meaning": "circumstances, one's situation or lot in life"
  },
  {
    "question": "魚河岸",
    "answer": "うおがし",
    "meaning": "riverside fish market"
  },
  {
    "question": "腥い",
    "answer": "なまぐさい",
    "meaning": "smelling of fish, fishy, smelling of blood, bloody, degenerate (of a monk), depraved, corrupt, falle"
  },
  {
    "question": "性情",
    "answer": "せいじょう",
    "meaning": "nature, disposition"
  },
  {
    "question": "恬淡",
    "answer": "てんたん",
    "meaning": "disinterested, unselfish, indifferent, unavaricious"
  },
  {
    "question": "香の物",
    "answer": "こうのもの",
    "meaning": "pickled vegetables"
  },
  {
    "question": "半金",
    "answer": "はんきん",
    "meaning": "half the amount"
  },
  {
    "question": "廃位",
    "answer": "はいい",
    "meaning": "dethronement"
  },
  {
    "question": "蹌踉",
    "answer": "そうろう",
    "meaning": "tottering, staggering, reeling"
  },
  {
    "question": "騎行",
    "answer": "きこう",
    "meaning": "horseback riding"
  },
  {
    "question": "懐手",
    "answer": "ふところで",
    "meaning": "with hands in pockets, idleness"
  },
  {
    "question": "小羊",
    "answer": "こひつじ",
    "meaning": "lamb"
  },
  {
    "question": "鑑別所",
    "answer": "かんべつしょ",
    "meaning": "juvenile classification home, juvenile detention facility"
  },
  {
    "question": "暈",
    "answer": "かさ,うん",
    "meaning": "halo (around the Sun, Moon, etc.), ring, corona"
  },
  {
    "question": "謎々",
    "answer": "なぞなぞ",
    "meaning": "riddle, puzzle, enigma"
  },
  {
    "question": "歌集",
    "answer": "かしゅう",
    "meaning": "collection of waka poems, anthology, songbook"
  },
  {
    "question": "他流",
    "answer": "たりゅう",
    "meaning": "another style, another school (of thought, karate, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "獅子頭",
    "answer": "ししがしら",
    "meaning": "lion mask, Japanese deer fern (Blechnum nipponicum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "装薬",
    "answer": "そうやく",
    "meaning": "charging with gunpowder, charge of gunpowder"
  },
  {
    "question": "論述",
    "answer": "ろんじゅつ",
    "meaning": "statement (of a carefully reasoned logical argument), dissertation, enunciation, setting forth"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤痢",
    "answer": "せきり",
    "meaning": "dysentery"
  },
  {
    "question": "病変",
    "answer": "びょうへん",
    "meaning": "lesion, pathological change"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜討ち",
    "answer": "ようち",
    "meaning": "night attack"
  },
  {
    "question": "探照灯",
    "answer": "たんしょうとう",
    "meaning": "searchlight"
  },
  {
    "question": "古酒",
    "answer": "こしゅ,ふるざけ",
    "meaning": "well-cured sake, last year's sake, old sake"
  },
  {
    "question": "一過",
    "answer": "いっか",
    "meaning": "passing (e.g. of a typhoon), going past"
  },
  {
    "question": "縫物",
    "answer": "ぬいもの",
    "meaning": "sewing, needlework, embroidery"
  },
  {
    "question": "百舌",
    "answer": "もず",
    "meaning": "shrike (any bird of family Laniidae), bull-headed shrike (Lanius bucephalus), butcher bird"
  },
  {
    "question": "撫で切り",
    "answer": "なでぎり",
    "meaning": "clean sweep, killing several with one sword sweep"
  },
  {
    "question": "流離",
    "answer": "さすらい,りゅうり",
    "meaning": "wandering (e.g. bird, exile, lifestyle), wandering alone in a strange country"
  },
  {
    "question": "潰瘍",
    "answer": "かいよう",
    "meaning": "ulcer"
  },
  {
    "question": "決勝点",
    "answer": "けっしょうてん",
    "meaning": "winning point, winning goal, game point (tennis, etc.), finishing line"
  },
  {
    "question": "政治団体",
    "answer": "せいじだんたい",
    "meaning": "political organization, political organisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "浄水場",
    "answer": "じょうすいじょう",
    "meaning": "water purification (filtering) plant"
  },
  {
    "question": "草刈り鎌",
    "answer": "くさかりがま",
    "meaning": "grass sickle"
  },
  {
    "question": "万両",
    "answer": "まんりょう",
    "meaning": "Ardisia crenata, coralberry"
  },
  {
    "question": "和綴じ",
    "answer": "わとじ",
    "meaning": "Japanese-style bookbinding"
  },
  {
    "question": "漁獲",
    "answer": "ぎょかく",
    "meaning": "fishing, catch, haul"
  },
  {
    "question": "霧笛",
    "answer": "むてき",
    "meaning": "foghorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "立花",
    "answer": "りっか",
    "meaning": "rikka, formal style of ikebana"
  },
  {
    "question": "八頭身",
    "answer": "はっとうしん",
    "meaning": "beautiful well-proportioned woman (body 8 times longer than head)"
  },
  {
    "question": "来園",
    "answer": "らいえん",
    "meaning": "visit to a park (kindergarten, zoo, etc.), coming to a park"
  },
  {
    "question": "七回忌",
    "answer": "しちかいき",
    "meaning": "sixth anniversary of a death"
  },
  {
    "question": "屹然",
    "answer": "きつぜん",
    "meaning": "towering, lofty, standing out without the influence of others, in splendid isolation"
  },
  {
    "question": "手配り",
    "answer": "てくばり",
    "meaning": "arrangements, preparations"
  },
  {
    "question": "文学青年",
    "answer": "ぶんがくせいねん",
    "meaning": "young literary enthusiast"
  },
  {
    "question": "酷寒",
    "answer": "こっかん,こくかん",
    "meaning": "severe cold, intense cold, bitter cold"
  },
  {
    "question": "罷り越す",
    "answer": "まかりこす",
    "meaning": "to go to, to visit, to call on"
  },
  {
    "question": "亡父",
    "answer": "ぼうふ",
    "meaning": "deceased father, late father"
  },
  {
    "question": "黙示",
    "answer": "もくし",
    "meaning": "revelation, apocalypse"
  },
  {
    "question": "鞴",
    "answer": "ふいご",
    "meaning": "(pair of) bellows"
  },
  {
    "question": "公衆衛生",
    "answer": "こうしゅうえいせい",
    "meaning": "sanitation, public health"
  },
  {
    "question": "国内線",
    "answer": "こくないせん",
    "meaning": "domestic air route, domestic airline (company)"
  },
  {
    "question": "器機",
    "answer": "きき",
    "meaning": "device, equipment, machinery, apparatus"
  },
  {
    "question": "原資",
    "answer": "げんし",
    "meaning": "capital, principal"
  },
  {
    "question": "空気抜き",
    "answer": "くうきぬき",
    "meaning": "ventilator"
  },
  {
    "question": "選外",
    "answer": "せんがい",
    "meaning": "unselected"
  },
  {
    "question": "国務長官",
    "answer": "こくむちょうかん",
    "meaning": "Secretary of State"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍事裁判",
    "answer": "ぐんじさいばん",
    "meaning": "court-martial"
  },
  {
    "question": "矢鱈",
    "answer": "やたら",
    "meaning": "indiscriminately, blindly, at random, recklessly, thoughtlessly, excessively, profusely, indiscrimin"
  },
  {
    "question": "雪空",
    "answer": "ゆきぞら",
    "meaning": "snow-laden sky"
  },
  {
    "question": "牽制球",
    "answer": "けんせいきゅう",
    "meaning": "pickoff attempt, throw to check a runner"
  },
  {
    "question": "枠組",
    "answer": "わくぐみ",
    "meaning": "frame, framework, outline"
  },
  {
    "question": "課目",
    "answer": "かもく",
    "meaning": "(school) subject, curriculum, course"
  },
  {
    "question": "合唱曲",
    "answer": "がっしょうきょく",
    "meaning": "chorus"
  },
  {
    "question": "白滝",
    "answer": "しらたき",
    "meaning": "shirataki noodles, white noodles made from konjak starch, often used in sukiyaki, waterfall resembli"
  },
  {
    "question": "時代考証",
    "answer": "じだいこうしょう",
    "meaning": "background research, research into the period"
  },
  {
    "question": "ボクっ娘",
    "answer": "ボクっこ",
    "meaning": "young woman who uses the first person pronoun 'boku'"
  },
  {
    "question": "若白髪",
    "answer": "わかしらが",
    "meaning": "prematurely gray hair, prematurely grey hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "独言",
    "answer": "どくげん",
    "meaning": "talking to oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "精神修養",
    "answer": "せいしんしゅうよう",
    "meaning": "moral (spiritual) improvement, practice mental training, cultivate one's mind (soul)"
  },
  {
    "question": "売り出し",
    "answer": "うりだし",
    "meaning": "(bargain) sale"
  },
  {
    "question": "弁護士会",
    "answer": "べんごしかい",
    "meaning": "bar association"
  },
  {
    "question": "商戦",
    "answer": "しょうせん",
    "meaning": "sales battle, business competition"
  },
  {
    "question": "弾き手",
    "answer": "ひきて",
    "meaning": "performer or player (of an instrument)"
  },
  {
    "question": "速度計",
    "answer": "そくどけい",
    "meaning": "speedometer"
  },
  {
    "question": "牛革",
    "answer": "ぎゅうかわ,うしがわ",
    "meaning": "cowhide, oxhide"
  },
  {
    "question": "禽獣",
    "answer": "きんじゅう",
    "meaning": "birds and animals"
  },
  {
    "question": "無辺",
    "answer": "むへん",
    "meaning": "infinite, boundless"
  },
  {
    "question": "提議",
    "answer": "ていぎ",
    "meaning": "proposal, motion"
  },
  {
    "question": "拒食症",
    "answer": "きょしょくしょう",
    "meaning": "anorexia"
  },
  {
    "question": "家猫",
    "answer": "いえねこ",
    "meaning": "domesticated cat"
  },
  {
    "question": "獄死",
    "answer": "ごくし",
    "meaning": "death in jail, death in prison"
  },
  {
    "question": "苦界",
    "answer": "くがい",
    "meaning": "world of suffering, life of prostitution"
  },
  {
    "question": "処置無し",
    "answer": "しょちなし",
    "meaning": "hopeless, unworkable"
  },
  {
    "question": "投法",
    "answer": "とうほう",
    "meaning": "way of throwing (esp. in baseball), throwing technique, pitching technique"
  },
  {
    "question": "電子辞書",
    "answer": "でんしじしょ",
    "meaning": "electronic dictionary"
  },
  {
    "question": "題字",
    "answer": "だいじ",
    "meaning": "title lettering"
  },
  {
    "question": "国情",
    "answer": "こくじょう",
    "meaning": "conditions of a country"
  },
  {
    "question": "唾吐く",
    "answer": "つばく,つはく",
    "meaning": "to spit"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓮根",
    "answer": "れんこん,はすね",
    "meaning": "lotus root"
  },
  {
    "question": "大検",
    "answer": "だいけん",
    "meaning": "University Entrance Qualification Examination (establishes the equivalent of high-school graduation"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠戚",
    "answer": "えんせき",
    "meaning": "distant relative"
  },
  {
    "question": "写実",
    "answer": "しゃじつ",
    "meaning": "realism, depicting realistically, representing accurately"
  },
  {
    "question": "充当",
    "answer": "じゅうとう",
    "meaning": "allocation, appropriation"
  },
  {
    "question": "関取",
    "answer": "せきとり",
    "meaning": "ranking wrestler in the makuuchi (senior-grade) or juryo (junior-grade) divisions"
  },
  {
    "question": "渡し賃",
    "answer": "わたしちん",
    "meaning": "ferriage"
  },
  {
    "question": "軟質",
    "answer": "なんしつ",
    "meaning": "softness"
  },
  {
    "question": "小脳",
    "answer": "しょうのう",
    "meaning": "cerebellum"
  },
  {
    "question": "広背筋",
    "answer": "こうはいきん",
    "meaning": "latissimus dorsi muscle"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤紙",
    "answer": "あかがみ",
    "meaning": "draft papers, call-up notice, red paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "雑居",
    "answer": "ざっきょ",
    "meaning": "living together, mixed residence, sharing living quarters, multi-tenant, community"
  },
  {
    "question": "円グラフ",
    "answer": "えんグラフ",
    "meaning": "pie graph, pie chart"
  },
  {
    "question": "嵌め殺し",
    "answer": "はめごろし,はめころし",
    "meaning": "fixed fitting (esp. window)"
  },
  {
    "question": "入射角",
    "answer": "にゅうしゃかく",
    "meaning": "angle of incidence"
  },
  {
    "question": "電熱",
    "answer": "でんねつ",
    "meaning": "electric heat"
  },
  {
    "question": "盲人",
    "answer": "もうじん",
    "meaning": "blind person"
  },
  {
    "question": "老化現象",
    "answer": "ろうかげんしょう",
    "meaning": "aging process, ageing process"
  },
  {
    "question": "螺鈿",
    "answer": "らでん",
    "meaning": "mother-of-pearl"
  },
  {
    "question": "正負",
    "answer": "せいふ",
    "meaning": "positive and negative, +-, plus and minus"
  },
  {
    "question": "大商い",
    "answer": "おおあきない",
    "meaning": "heavy turnover (trading)"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼鳥",
    "answer": "やきとり",
    "meaning": "yakitori, chicken pieces (or sometimes beef or pork offal) grilled on a skewer, grilled and skewered"
  },
  {
    "question": "鹿狩り",
    "answer": "ししがり",
    "meaning": "hunting (of animals such as boar, deer, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "専門教育",
    "answer": "せんもんきょういく",
    "meaning": "technical training, professional education"
  },
  {
    "question": "超伝導",
    "answer": "ちょうでんどう",
    "meaning": "superconductivity, super-conductivity"
  },
  {
    "question": "音読み",
    "answer": "おんよみ",
    "meaning": "on reading, on'yomi, Chinese-derived reading of a kanji"
  },
  {
    "question": "長尺",
    "answer": "ちょうじゃく,ちょうしゃく",
    "meaning": "long (esp. of photographic film), lengthy"
  },
  {
    "question": "防臭",
    "answer": "ぼうしゅう",
    "meaning": "odor-resistant, odour-resistant"
  },
  {
    "question": "豪速球",
    "answer": "ごうそっきゅう",
    "meaning": "blazing fastball"
  },
  {
    "question": "航空便",
    "answer": "こうくうびん",
    "meaning": "airmail, air mail, air service, air transport (of goods)"
  },
  {
    "question": "前奏曲",
    "answer": "ぜんそうきょく",
    "meaning": "prelude, overture"
  },
  {
    "question": "無駄毛",
    "answer": "むだげ",
    "meaning": "unwanted hair, superfluous hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "好球",
    "answer": "こうきゅう",
    "meaning": "good pitch (to hit), easy pitch"
  },
  {
    "question": "顎骨",
    "answer": "がっこつ,がくこつ,あごぼね",
    "meaning": "jawbone, mandible"
  },
  {
    "question": "求職",
    "answer": "きゅうしょく",
    "meaning": "job hunting, seeking employment"
  },
  {
    "question": "国威",
    "answer": "こくい",
    "meaning": "national prestige"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹竿",
    "answer": "たけざお",
    "meaning": "bamboo pole"
  },
  {
    "question": "振り替え",
    "answer": "ふりかえ",
    "meaning": "transfer, switching over, change, money transfer (usu. between accounts held by the same person), po"
  },
  {
    "question": "虚仮",
    "answer": "こけ",
    "meaning": "folly, fool"
  },
  {
    "question": "丹誠",
    "answer": "たんせい",
    "meaning": "working earnestly, sincerity, diligence, effort, pains"
  },
  {
    "question": "勝ち残り",
    "answer": "かちのこり",
    "meaning": "winning wrestler who remains ringside in case his involvement is needed in pre-bout rituals"
  },
  {
    "question": "人類学",
    "answer": "じんるいがく",
    "meaning": "anthropology"
  },
  {
    "question": "座談会",
    "answer": "ざだんかい",
    "meaning": "symposium, round-table discussion"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち寄り",
    "answer": "もちより",
    "meaning": "potluck"
  },
  {
    "question": "結審",
    "answer": "けっしん",
    "meaning": "conclusion of trial (hearing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "当選確実",
    "answer": "とうせんかくじつ",
    "meaning": "being projected to win, being certain to be elected, being sure of being elected"
  },
  {
    "question": "多妻",
    "answer": "たさい",
    "meaning": "polygamy, polygyny"
  },
  {
    "question": "空言",
    "answer": "そらごと,くうげん,むなこと",
    "meaning": "falsehood, lie"
  },
  {
    "question": "当意即妙",
    "answer": "とういそくみょう",
    "meaning": "ready wit"
  },
  {
    "question": "晒し首",
    "answer": "さらしくび",
    "meaning": "criminal's head on public display, displaying a beheaded head, beheaded head"
  },
  {
    "question": "付添い",
    "answer": "つきそい",
    "meaning": "attendance (on), chaperonage, attendant, escort, entourage, chaperon, retinue"
  },
  {
    "question": "四周",
    "answer": "ししゅう",
    "meaning": "periphery, circumference"
  },
  {
    "question": "浮腫む",
    "answer": "むくむ",
    "meaning": "to swell, to become swollen, to become puffy (e.g. face from lack of sleep), to become bloated (esp."
  },
  {
    "question": "体操座り",
    "answer": "たいそうずわり,たいそうすわり",
    "meaning": "sitting on the floor grasping one's knees (as in a gym class)"
  },
  {
    "question": "東海地方",
    "answer": "とうかいちほう",
    "meaning": "Tokai region of Honshu (incl. Aichi, Shizuoka, Mie and southern Gifu prefectures)"
  },
  {
    "question": "役付き",
    "answer": "やくづき,やくつき",
    "meaning": "holding a position of responsibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "凍みる",
    "answer": "しみる",
    "meaning": "to freeze, to be frozen over, to congeal"
  },
  {
    "question": "美容整形",
    "answer": "びようせいけい",
    "meaning": "cosmetic surgery"
  },
  {
    "question": "一利",
    "answer": "いちり",
    "meaning": "one advantage"
  },
  {
    "question": "充てがう",
    "answer": "あてがう",
    "meaning": "to allot, to allocate, to supply with, to furnish, to fit to, to fasten to, to apply to"
  },
  {
    "question": "出金",
    "answer": "しゅっきん",
    "meaning": "withdrawal (of money), payment, contribution, investment, financing"
  },
  {
    "question": "遺族年金",
    "answer": "いぞくねんきん",
    "meaning": "survivor's pension or annuity"
  },
  {
    "question": "似顔",
    "answer": "にがお",
    "meaning": "portrait, likeness"
  },
  {
    "question": "誤答",
    "answer": "ごとう",
    "meaning": "mistaken answer or response"
  },
  {
    "question": "無為無策",
    "answer": "むいむさく",
    "meaning": "do-nothing, plan-nothing (government, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "物は相談",
    "answer": "ものはそうだん",
    "meaning": "a wise man is he who listens to counsel, a worry shared is a worry halved, I've got something to ask"
  },
  {
    "question": "異常性欲",
    "answer": "いじょうせいよく",
    "meaning": "sexual abnormality"
  },
  {
    "question": "多色",
    "answer": "たしょく",
    "meaning": "many colors, many colours"
  },
  {
    "question": "名を成す",
    "answer": "なをなす",
    "meaning": "to become famous, to make a name for oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "番宣",
    "answer": "ばんせん",
    "meaning": "promo, advertising for a program (TV, radio, etc.), program publicity"
  },
  {
    "question": "検算",
    "answer": "けんざん",
    "meaning": "verification of accounts, checking figures, arithmetic check"
  },
  {
    "question": "販売促進",
    "answer": "はんばいそくしん",
    "meaning": "sales promotion"
  },
  {
    "question": "自家中毒",
    "answer": "じかちゅうどく",
    "meaning": "autotoxemia"
  },
  {
    "question": "内巻き",
    "answer": "うちまき",
    "meaning": "curling inwards (esp. the tips of one's hair)"
  },
  {
    "question": "強圧的",
    "answer": "きょうあつてき",
    "meaning": "high-handed, strong-armed, oppressive, overbearing, coercive"
  },
  {
    "question": "貰い泣き",
    "answer": "もらいなき",
    "meaning": "crying in sympathy, infectious crying"
  },
  {
    "question": "心無し",
    "answer": "こころなし",
    "meaning": "lacking in prudence, lacking in judgement"
  },
  {
    "question": "害毒",
    "answer": "がいどく",
    "meaning": "harm, injury, mischief, poison, virus"
  },
  {
    "question": "解き放す",
    "answer": "ときはなす",
    "meaning": "to liberate, to set free"
  },
  {
    "question": "開き戸",
    "answer": "ひらきど",
    "meaning": "(hinged) door"
  },
  {
    "question": "竜虎",
    "answer": "りゅうこ,りょうこ",
    "meaning": "dragon and tiger, two mighty rivals"
  },
  {
    "question": "水芸",
    "answer": "みずげい",
    "meaning": "tricks with water"
  },
  {
    "question": "岩間",
    "answer": "いわま",
    "meaning": "among rocks"
  },
  {
    "question": "冬野菜",
    "answer": "ふゆやさい",
    "meaning": "winter vegetables"
  },
  {
    "question": "一日置き",
    "answer": "いちにちおき",
    "meaning": "every other day"
  },
  {
    "question": "人道主義",
    "answer": "じんどうしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "humanism, humanitarianism"
  },
  {
    "question": "峠を越す",
    "answer": "とうげをこす",
    "meaning": "to pass the peak (of something), to get through the most difficult part, to be over the worst (e.g."
  },
  {
    "question": "国立公園",
    "answer": "こくりつこうえん",
    "meaning": "national park"
  },
  {
    "question": "擦り合い",
    "answer": "なすりあい",
    "meaning": "recrimination"
  },
  {
    "question": "虎児",
    "answer": "こじ",
    "meaning": "tiger cub"
  },
  {
    "question": "一粒種",
    "answer": "ひとつぶだね",
    "meaning": "only child"
  },
  {
    "question": "半同棲",
    "answer": "はんどうせい",
    "meaning": "almost living together, spending most nights with one's partner"
  },
  {
    "question": "召し出す",
    "answer": "めしだす",
    "meaning": "to call out, to summon"
  },
  {
    "question": "業界用語",
    "answer": "ぎょうかいようご",
    "meaning": "industry terminology, professional jargon, buzzword"
  },
  {
    "question": "自浄",
    "answer": "じじょう",
    "meaning": "self-purification, self-cleansing"
  },
  {
    "question": "在職",
    "answer": "ざいしょく",
    "meaning": "being in office"
  },
  {
    "question": "気化熱",
    "answer": "きかねつ",
    "meaning": "vaporization heat, vaporisation heat"
  },
  {
    "question": "全社",
    "answer": "ぜんしゃ",
    "meaning": "whole company, all the companies"
  },
  {
    "question": "聞き辛い",
    "answer": "ききづらい",
    "meaning": "difficult to hear, difficult to ask"
  },
  {
    "question": "開栓",
    "answer": "かいせん",
    "meaning": "unstopping, uncorking, uncapping, opening, connecting (e.g. gas supply)"
  },
  {
    "question": "小ちゃい",
    "answer": "ちいちゃい",
    "meaning": "small, little, tiny"
  },
  {
    "question": "掃き出す",
    "answer": "はきだす",
    "meaning": "to release, to sweep out, to clean out"
  },
  {
    "question": "染髪",
    "answer": "せんぱつ",
    "meaning": "hair dyeing"
  },
  {
    "question": "那由他",
    "answer": "なゆた",
    "meaning": "an extremely great number (often said to be 100 million), 10^60 (or 10^72)"
  },
  {
    "question": "家宅",
    "answer": "かたく",
    "meaning": "domicile, premises"
  },
  {
    "question": "旅疲れ",
    "answer": "たびづかれ",
    "meaning": "weary from traveling (travelling)"
  },
  {
    "question": "倒置法",
    "answer": "とうちほう",
    "meaning": "inversion of the word order in a sentence, anastrophe"
  },
  {
    "question": "証人喚問",
    "answer": "しょうにんかんもん",
    "meaning": "summoning of a sworn witness (court, Diet), subpoena"
  },
  {
    "question": "頓死",
    "answer": "とんし",
    "meaning": "sudden death"
  },
  {
    "question": "行楽日和",
    "answer": "こうらくびより",
    "meaning": "ideal weather for an outing"
  },
  {
    "question": "天佑",
    "answer": "てんゆう",
    "meaning": "divine aid, divine grace, providential help"
  },
  {
    "question": "斯様",
    "answer": "かよう",
    "meaning": "in such a manner, like this"
  },
  {
    "question": "天の岩戸",
    "answer": "あまのいわと",
    "meaning": "Gate of the Celestial Rock Cave"
  },
  {
    "question": "急騰",
    "answer": "きゅうとう",
    "meaning": "sudden rise (in price), sharp rise, jump, surge"
  },
  {
    "question": "色好い",
    "answer": "いろよい",
    "meaning": "favorable, favourable, friendly, encouraging, vividly colored, vividly coloured"
  },
  {
    "question": "長ずる",
    "answer": "ちょうずる",
    "meaning": "to grow, to grow up, to be good at, to excel in"
  },
  {
    "question": "懇ろ",
    "answer": "ねんごろ,ねもころ",
    "meaning": "kind, courteous, hospitable, warmly respectful, intimate, becoming intimate, having an intimate rela"
  },
  {
    "question": "予熱",
    "answer": "よねつ",
    "meaning": "preheat (oven, etc.), warm up (engine, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "前途洋々",
    "answer": "ぜんとようよう",
    "meaning": "with a rosy future, offering promising prospects"
  },
  {
    "question": "窮乏",
    "answer": "きゅうぼう",
    "meaning": "poverty, destitution, privation, indigence, penury"
  },
  {
    "question": "絹地",
    "answer": "きぬじ",
    "meaning": "silk fabrics"
  },
  {
    "question": "総元締め",
    "answer": "そうもとじめ",
    "meaning": "general manager"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨後",
    "answer": "うご",
    "meaning": "after rain"
  },
  {
    "question": "ゴム紐",
    "answer": "ゴムひも",
    "meaning": "elastic, elastic cord, elastic band"
  },
  {
    "question": "送り出し",
    "answer": "おくりだし",
    "meaning": "pushing (propelling) (one's opponent) out of the ring from behind"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶代",
    "answer": "ちゃだい",
    "meaning": "a tip"
  },
  {
    "question": "持ち切る",
    "answer": "もちきる",
    "meaning": "to hold all the while, to talk about nothing but"
  },
  {
    "question": "物別れ",
    "answer": "ものわかれ",
    "meaning": "failure to reach agreement"
  },
  {
    "question": "掬い",
    "answer": "すくい",
    "meaning": "scooping"
  },
  {
    "question": "著莪",
    "answer": "しゃが",
    "meaning": "fringed iris (Iris japonica), Japanese iris"
  },
  {
    "question": "果菜",
    "answer": "かさい",
    "meaning": "fruits and vegetables"
  },
  {
    "question": "星虫",
    "answer": "ほしむし",
    "meaning": "peanut worm (any worm of phylum Sipuncula)"
  },
  {
    "question": "信天翁",
    "answer": "あほうどり,しんてんおう",
    "meaning": "albatross (esp. the short-tailed albatross, Phoebastria albatrus)"
  },
  {
    "question": "秘鍵",
    "answer": "ひけん",
    "meaning": "hidden mysteries, secret principle"
  },
  {
    "question": "郡長",
    "answer": "ぐんちょう",
    "meaning": "district headman, head county official"
  },
  {
    "question": "士民",
    "answer": "しみん",
    "meaning": "samurai and common people"
  },
  {
    "question": "金融庁",
    "answer": "きんゆうちょう",
    "meaning": "Financial Services Agency, FSA"
  },
  {
    "question": "薺",
    "answer": "なずな",
    "meaning": "shepherd's purse (Capsella bursa-pastoris)"
  },
  {
    "question": "本真",
    "answer": "ほんま",
    "meaning": "truth, reality"
  },
  {
    "question": "精機",
    "answer": "せいき",
    "meaning": "precision machinery, precision machine, precision tool, precision tools, precision equipment"
  },
  {
    "question": "宵月",
    "answer": "よいづき",
    "meaning": "evening moon, moon that can only be seen in the early hours of the night (esp. from the 2nd to the 7"
  },
  {
    "question": "西京",
    "answer": "さいきょう",
    "meaning": "western capital, Kyoto"
  },
  {
    "question": "碑石",
    "answer": "ひせき",
    "meaning": "stone monument"
  },
  {
    "question": "春雪",
    "answer": "しゅんせつ",
    "meaning": "spring snow"
  },
  {
    "question": "冥加",
    "answer": "みょうが",
    "meaning": "divine protection, divine blessing, providence, blessed, fortunate, lucky, monetary offering (to a t"
  },
  {
    "question": "常用漢字",
    "answer": "じょうようかんじ",
    "meaning": "kanji for common use, jōyō kanji, list of 2,136 kanji established in 2010, formerly a list of 1,945"
  },
  {
    "question": "大覚",
    "answer": "だいかく,だいがく",
    "meaning": "great awakening, great enlightening, greatly awakened person, understanding, comprehension"
  },
  {
    "question": "協和",
    "answer": "きょうわ",
    "meaning": "concord, harmony, concert"
  },
  {
    "question": "町営",
    "answer": "ちょうえい",
    "meaning": "town management, municipal management"
  },
  {
    "question": "銅版画",
    "answer": "どうはんが",
    "meaning": "copperplate engraving, etching"
  },
  {
    "question": "跋",
    "answer": "ばつ",
    "meaning": "epilogue, postscript, envoi"
  },
  {
    "question": "傭う",
    "answer": "やとう",
    "meaning": "to employ, to hire, to charter"
  },
  {
    "question": "白鳥座",
    "answer": "はくちょうざ",
    "meaning": "Cygnus (constellation), the Swan"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼名",
    "answer": "よびな",
    "meaning": "popular name, common name, given name"
  },
  {
    "question": "淵源",
    "answer": "えんげん",
    "meaning": "origin"
  },
  {
    "question": "樒",
    "answer": "しきみ,しきび",
    "meaning": "Japanese star anise (Illicium anisatum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "甘藷",
    "answer": "さつまいも,かんしょ",
    "meaning": "sweet potato (Ipomoea batatas)"
  },
  {
    "question": "小咄",
    "answer": "こばなし",
    "meaning": "anecdote, brief (comic) story"
  },
  {
    "question": "大鷹",
    "answer": "おおたか",
    "meaning": "northern goshawk (Accipiter gentilis), female hawk (or falcon), falconry (using a northern goshawk)"
  },
  {
    "question": "襲爵",
    "answer": "しゅうしゃく",
    "meaning": "succession to the peerage"
  },
  {
    "question": "新教徒",
    "answer": "しんきょうと",
    "meaning": "a Protestant"
  },
  {
    "question": "寮舎",
    "answer": "りょうしゃ",
    "meaning": "dormitory"
  },
  {
    "question": "足部",
    "answer": "そくぶ",
    "meaning": "foot region"
  },
  {
    "question": "風前",
    "answer": "ふうぜん",
    "meaning": "where the wind blows"
  },
  {
    "question": "都下",
    "answer": "とか",
    "meaning": "in the capital, in Tokyo"
  },
  {
    "question": "炯眼",
    "answer": "けいがん",
    "meaning": "penetrating eyes, insightfulness"
  },
  {
    "question": "兵曹長",
    "answer": "へいそうちょう",
    "meaning": "(Japanese Imperial Navy) chief warrant-officer"
  },
  {
    "question": "習志野",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "事業所",
    "answer": "じぎょうしょ",
    "meaning": "plant, enterprise place, office"
  },
  {
    "question": "民政",
    "answer": "みんせい",
    "meaning": "civil administration, civil government, politics focused on the promotion of public welfare"
  },
  {
    "question": "牽牛",
    "answer": "けんぎゅう",
    "meaning": "Altair (star in the constellation Aquila), Alpha Aquilae"
  },
  {
    "question": "騎射",
    "answer": "きしゃ",
    "meaning": "shooting on horseback, equestrian archery"
  },
  {
    "question": "南山",
    "answer": "なんざん",
    "meaning": "Mount Kōya (esp. Kongōbu-ji), southern mountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "奴婢",
    "answer": "ぬひ,どひ",
    "meaning": "slaves (lowest class in the ritsuryō system), bondservants, male and female servants, manservants an"
  },
  {
    "question": "虎狼",
    "answer": "ころう",
    "meaning": "tigers and wolves, cruel and greedy brute"
  },
  {
    "question": "久保田",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "陀羅尼",
    "answer": "だらに",
    "meaning": "dharani, spell, litany, Sanskrit multi-syllabic chant"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉱毒",
    "answer": "こうどく",
    "meaning": "mine pollution"
  },
  {
    "question": "摂津",
    "answer": "せっつ",
    "meaning": "Settsu (former province located in the northern and central parts of present-day Ōsaka and the south"
  },
  {
    "question": "船窓",
    "answer": "せんそう",
    "meaning": "porthole"
  },
  {
    "question": "架台",
    "answer": "かだい",
    "meaning": "stand, frame, abutment"
  },
  {
    "question": "美術学校",
    "answer": "びじゅつがっこう",
    "meaning": "art school"
  },
  {
    "question": "中入り",
    "answer": "なかいり",
    "meaning": "intermission during a performance (e.g. variety show, play, sumo, etc.), temporary departure of an a"
  },
  {
    "question": "尾籠",
    "answer": "びろう,おこ",
    "meaning": "indecent, indelicate, foolish thing, stupid thing, absurdity"
  },
  {
    "question": "烽火",
    "answer": "のろし,ほうか",
    "meaning": "beacon, skyrocket, signal fire, smoke signals, starting shot, starting signal"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪餓鬼",
    "answer": "わるがき",
    "meaning": "brat"
  },
  {
    "question": "手掌",
    "answer": "しゅしょう",
    "meaning": "palmar, palm"
  },
  {
    "question": "電離",
    "answer": "でんり",
    "meaning": "ionization, ionisation, electrolytic dissociation"
  },
  {
    "question": "膨脹",
    "answer": "ぼうちょう",
    "meaning": "expansion, swelling, increase, growth"
  },
  {
    "question": "稠密",
    "answer": "ちゅうみつ,ちょうみつ",
    "meaning": "dense, populous, crowded, thick"
  },
  {
    "question": "模式図",
    "answer": "もしきず",
    "meaning": "schematic diagram"
  },
  {
    "question": "入力装置",
    "answer": "にゅうりょくそうち",
    "meaning": "input unit, input device"
  },
  {
    "question": "ソフト帽",
    "answer": "ソフトぼう",
    "meaning": "felt hat"
  },
  {
    "question": "出帆",
    "answer": "しゅっぱん",
    "meaning": "setting sail, departure (from a port)"
  },
  {
    "question": "荷札",
    "answer": "にふだ",
    "meaning": "label, tag"
  },
  {
    "question": "火山島",
    "answer": "かざんとう",
    "meaning": "volcanic island"
  },
  {
    "question": "其々",
    "answer": "それぞれ,そそ",
    "meaning": "each, respectively, come on, hurry up, chop chop, yeah, that's right, exactly"
  },
  {
    "question": "補充兵",
    "answer": "ほじゅうへい",
    "meaning": "reservist, recruit"
  },
  {
    "question": "野手",
    "answer": "やしゅ",
    "meaning": "fielder"
  },
  {
    "question": "雄性",
    "answer": "ゆうせい",
    "meaning": "male characteristics, manliness"
  },
  {
    "question": "林檎酒",
    "answer": "りんごしゅ",
    "meaning": "apple cider (alcoholic)"
  },
  {
    "question": "万屋",
    "answer": "よろずや",
    "meaning": "general merchant, Jack of all trades"
  },
  {
    "question": "佩刀",
    "answer": "はいとう",
    "meaning": "wearing a sword, sword one is wearing"
  },
  {
    "question": "葉陰",
    "answer": "はかげ",
    "meaning": "shadow of a leaf or tree"
  },
  {
    "question": "樹間",
    "answer": "じゅかん",
    "meaning": "space between trees, gap between trees"
  },
  {
    "question": "賦",
    "answer": "ふ",
    "meaning": "poem, narrative (style of the Shi Jing), classical Chinese rhymed prose"
  },
  {
    "question": "二の丸",
    "answer": "にのまる",
    "meaning": "outer citadel"
  },
  {
    "question": "打ち続く",
    "answer": "うちつづく",
    "meaning": "to continue for a long time, to undergo a repeated series"
  },
  {
    "question": "香具師",
    "answer": "やし,こうぐし",
    "meaning": "stall-keeper (esp. at a festival), street vendor, hawker, seller of unreliable merchandise, faker, h"
  },
  {
    "question": "手掛り",
    "answer": "てがかり",
    "meaning": "clue, lead, key, trail, scent, track, handhold, hold"
  },
  {
    "question": "高度計",
    "answer": "こうどけい",
    "meaning": "altimeter"
  },
  {
    "question": "内界",
    "answer": "ないかい",
    "meaning": "inner world, inner sphere"
  },
  {
    "question": "天秤棒",
    "answer": "てんびんぼう",
    "meaning": "shoulder carrying pole"
  },
  {
    "question": "新巻",
    "answer": "あらまき",
    "meaning": "salted salmon, fish wrapped in (bamboo) leaves"
  },
  {
    "question": "弓取り",
    "answer": "ゆみとり",
    "meaning": "archer (esp. a samurai), (skilled) archer, bowman, dominion of a whole province by a military family"
  },
  {
    "question": "細雪",
    "answer": "ささめゆき",
    "meaning": "light snow fall, small snow flakes"
  },
  {
    "question": "紋付",
    "answer": "もんつき",
    "meaning": "clothing (e.g. kimono) decorated with one's family crest"
  },
  {
    "question": "名跡",
    "answer": "みょうせき,めいせき",
    "meaning": "family name, professional name, famous historic spot"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒風",
    "answer": "こくふう",
    "meaning": "sky-darkening dust storm"
  },
  {
    "question": "餅屋",
    "answer": "もちや",
    "meaning": "rice cake shop keeper, rice cake store (shop)"
  },
  {
    "question": "大駒",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "銀山",
    "answer": "ぎんざん",
    "meaning": "silver mine"
  },
  {
    "question": "埋み火",
    "answer": "うずみび",
    "meaning": "banked fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "在所",
    "answer": "ざいしょ",
    "meaning": "whereabouts, country, one's home village, one's residence"
  },
  {
    "question": "覆滅",
    "answer": "ふくめつ",
    "meaning": "ruination"
  },
  {
    "question": "終曲",
    "answer": "しゅうきょく",
    "meaning": "finale"
  },
  {
    "question": "稲田",
    "answer": "いなだ",
    "meaning": "paddy field, rice field"
  },
  {
    "question": "修羅の巷",
    "answer": "しゅらのちまた",
    "meaning": "scene of carnage"
  },
  {
    "question": "残雪",
    "answer": "ざんせつ",
    "meaning": "remaining snow, lingering snow"
  },
  {
    "question": "闘鶏",
    "answer": "とうけい",
    "meaning": "cockfight, fighting cock"
  },
  {
    "question": "顧問官",
    "answer": "こもんかん",
    "meaning": "councillor, councilor"
  },
  {
    "question": "誤配",
    "answer": "ごはい",
    "meaning": "misdelivery"
  },
  {
    "question": "南十字星",
    "answer": "みなみじゅうじせい",
    "meaning": "Southern Cross (asterism formed with the brightest four stars of the constellation Crux)"
  },
  {
    "question": "壊血病",
    "answer": "かいけつびょう",
    "meaning": "scurvy"
  },
  {
    "question": "兵学校",
    "answer": "へいがっこう",
    "meaning": "naval academy"
  },
  {
    "question": "語勢",
    "answer": "ごせい",
    "meaning": "emphasis (e.g. placed on a word), stress, tone (of voice)"
  },
  {
    "question": "受け口",
    "answer": "うけぐち,うけくち",
    "meaning": "mouth with a protruding lower lip and jaw, socket, receiving window, slot"
  },
  {
    "question": "本義",
    "answer": "ほんぎ",
    "meaning": "true meaning, underlying principle"
  },
  {
    "question": "検察庁",
    "answer": "けんさつちょう",
    "meaning": "Public Prosecutor's Office"
  },
  {
    "question": "新奇",
    "answer": "しんき",
    "meaning": "novel, original, new"
  },
  {
    "question": "狂女",
    "answer": "きょうじょ",
    "meaning": "madwoman"
  },
  {
    "question": "鮪",
    "answer": "まぐろ,しび",
    "meaning": "tuna (edible fish, Thunnus spp.), tunny, Pacific bluefin tuna (edible fish, Thunnus orientalis), dea"
  },
  {
    "question": "左派",
    "answer": "さは",
    "meaning": "left wing"
  },
  {
    "question": "敏速",
    "answer": "びんそく",
    "meaning": "quickness, agility, activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "勢子",
    "answer": "せこ",
    "meaning": "beater (on a hunt)"
  },
  {
    "question": "他宗",
    "answer": "たしゅう",
    "meaning": "another sect"
  },
  {
    "question": "家付き",
    "answer": "いえつき",
    "meaning": "attached or belonging to a house"
  },
  {
    "question": "仲買",
    "answer": "なかがい",
    "meaning": "brokerage"
  },
  {
    "question": "無冠",
    "answer": "むかん",
    "meaning": "uncrowned, without rank, having no championship wins, receiving no (major) awards"
  },
  {
    "question": "身廊",
    "answer": "しんろう",
    "meaning": "nave (of a church)"
  },
  {
    "question": "横跳び",
    "answer": "よことび",
    "meaning": "jumping sideways, flying sideways, running hurriedly (with one's body bent forward)"
  },
  {
    "question": "然して",
    "answer": "そして,しかして,さして",
    "meaning": "and, and then, thus, and now, and finally, (not) particularly, (not) especially, (not) very, (not) m"
  },
  {
    "question": "皆既日食",
    "answer": "かいきにっしょく",
    "meaning": "total solar eclipse"
  },
  {
    "question": "独行",
    "answer": "どっこう",
    "meaning": "going alone, self-reliance"
  },
  {
    "question": "占有権",
    "answer": "せんゆうけん",
    "meaning": "right of possession"
  },
  {
    "question": "縦棒",
    "answer": "たてぼう",
    "meaning": "vertical line, vertical bar, upright, note stem (music)"
  },
  {
    "question": "牛小屋",
    "answer": "うしごや",
    "meaning": "cow shed, cattle barn"
  },
  {
    "question": "春霞",
    "answer": "はるがすみ",
    "meaning": "springtime haze"
  },
  {
    "question": "献立表",
    "answer": "こんだてひょう",
    "meaning": "menu, list of meals (e.g. for the week)"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り入れ",
    "answer": "とりいれ",
    "meaning": "taking in, harvesting"
  },
  {
    "question": "共栄",
    "answer": "きょうえい",
    "meaning": "mutual prosperity"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓄電池",
    "answer": "ちくでんち",
    "meaning": "storage battery"
  },
  {
    "question": "隈取り",
    "answer": "くまどり",
    "meaning": "shading, (colour) gradation, kumadori, style of kabuki makeup used for violent roles"
  },
  {
    "question": "手弱女",
    "answer": "たおやめ,たわやめ",
    "meaning": "graceful young woman, sylph"
  },
  {
    "question": "上水",
    "answer": "じょうすい",
    "meaning": "water supply, tap water"
  },
  {
    "question": "恒常",
    "answer": "こうじょう",
    "meaning": "constancy, permanence"
  },
  {
    "question": "各省",
    "answer": "かくしょう",
    "meaning": "each ministry"
  },
  {
    "question": "転調",
    "answer": "てんちょう",
    "meaning": "change of key (during piece), modulation"
  },
  {
    "question": "殺人剣",
    "answer": "さつじんけん",
    "meaning": "life-taking sword, sword used to kill"
  },
  {
    "question": "讃歌",
    "answer": "さんか",
    "meaning": "song of praise, eulogy, paean, hymn"
  },
  {
    "question": "国際結婚",
    "answer": "こくさいけっこん",
    "meaning": "international marriage"
  },
  {
    "question": "情報弱者",
    "answer": "じょうほうじゃくしゃ",
    "meaning": "person with limited access to information (via the Internet, television, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "木管楽器",
    "answer": "もっかんがっき",
    "meaning": "woodwind instrument"
  },
  {
    "question": "対戦車砲",
    "answer": "たいせんしゃほう",
    "meaning": "antitank gun"
  },
  {
    "question": "鏝",
    "answer": "こて",
    "meaning": "flat-iron, soldering iron, crimper, curling tongs, trowel"
  },
  {
    "question": "難無く",
    "answer": "なんなく",
    "meaning": "easily"
  },
  {
    "question": "清新",
    "answer": "せいしん",
    "meaning": "fresh, new"
  },
  {
    "question": "出先機関",
    "answer": "でさききかん",
    "meaning": "branch office"
  },
  {
    "question": "水力発電",
    "answer": "すいりょくはつでん",
    "meaning": "hydroelectric power generation, water-power generation"
  },
  {
    "question": "寓意",
    "answer": "ぐうい",
    "meaning": "hidden meaning, symbolism, moral"
  },
  {
    "question": "尊名",
    "answer": "そんめい",
    "meaning": "your name"
  },
  {
    "question": "播く",
    "answer": "まく",
    "meaning": "to sow, to plant, to seed, to sprinkle (gold or silver powder on lacquerware)"
  },
  {
    "question": "密葬",
    "answer": "みっそう",
    "meaning": "private funeral, secret burial"
  },
  {
    "question": "白糸",
    "answer": "しらいと",
    "meaning": "white thread"
  },
  {
    "question": "礼式",
    "answer": "れいしき",
    "meaning": "etiquette, manners"
  },
  {
    "question": "己惚れ",
    "answer": "うぬぼれ",
    "meaning": "pretension, conceit, hubris"
  },
  {
    "question": "醸造酒",
    "answer": "じょうぞうしゅ",
    "meaning": "brewage, liquor"
  },
  {
    "question": "甍",
    "answer": "いらか",
    "meaning": "roof tile, tiled roof, objects crowded together (e.g. houses)"
  },
  {
    "question": "三面六臂",
    "answer": "さんめんろっぴ",
    "meaning": "rush of business, versatility, man who can do the work of many"
  },
  {
    "question": "聴き手",
    "answer": "ききて",
    "meaning": "hearer, listener, audience, interviewer, questioner"
  },
  {
    "question": "春を売る",
    "answer": "はるをうる",
    "meaning": "to be a prostitute, to work as a prostitute, to sell sexual services"
  },
  {
    "question": "敗訴",
    "answer": "はいそ",
    "meaning": "loss of a (legal) case"
  },
  {
    "question": "配水管",
    "answer": "はいすいかん",
    "meaning": "conduit (pipe), water pipe"
  },
  {
    "question": "本学",
    "answer": "ほんがく",
    "meaning": "this university, this educational establishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "副収入",
    "answer": "ふくしゅうにゅう",
    "meaning": "additional income"
  },
  {
    "question": "風変り",
    "answer": "ふうがわり",
    "meaning": "strange, eccentric"
  },
  {
    "question": "毒蛾",
    "answer": "どくが",
    "meaning": "poisonous moth"
  },
  {
    "question": "厚生",
    "answer": "こうせい",
    "meaning": "welfare, public welfare, social welfare, (former) Ministry of Health and Welfare"
  },
  {
    "question": "殆",
    "answer": "ほとほと",
    "meaning": "quite (usu. negative connotation), utterly, really"
  },
  {
    "question": "同意語",
    "answer": "どういご",
    "meaning": "synonym"
  },
  {
    "question": "閲する",
    "answer": "えっする,けみする",
    "meaning": "to inspect, to examine, to check, to elapse, to pass (time)"
  },
  {
    "question": "猛り立つ",
    "answer": "たけりたつ",
    "meaning": "to rage, to howl"
  },
  {
    "question": "末吉",
    "answer": "すえきち",
    "meaning": "good luck to come (omikuji fortune-telling result), future good luck"
  },
  {
    "question": "全市",
    "answer": "ぜんし",
    "meaning": "the whole city, all the cities, every city"
  },
  {
    "question": "接触感染",
    "answer": "せっしょくかんせん",
    "meaning": "infection through contact"
  },
  {
    "question": "罫線",
    "answer": "けいせん",
    "meaning": "ruled line, rule, chart, crease, score, border"
  },
  {
    "question": "追い抜き",
    "answer": "おいぬき",
    "meaning": "overtaking, passing, pursuit (event)"
  },
  {
    "question": "賤しい",
    "answer": "いやしい",
    "meaning": "lowborn, humble, lowly, vulgar, coarse, crude, mean, base, vile, shabby, greedy, gluttonous, avarici"
  },
  {
    "question": "無理押し",
    "answer": "むりおし",
    "meaning": "by force"
  },
  {
    "question": "肉筆",
    "answer": "にくひつ",
    "meaning": "one's own handwriting, autograph, as written with a brush"
  },
  {
    "question": "競艇",
    "answer": "きょうてい",
    "meaning": "boat race"
  },
  {
    "question": "土左衛門",
    "answer": "どざえもん",
    "meaning": "drowned body of a person"
  },
  {
    "question": "素っ首",
    "answer": "そっくび",
    "meaning": "head"
  },
  {
    "question": "指し",
    "answer": "さし",
    "meaning": "between (e.g. two people), face to face, hindrance, impediment, arrhythmic section of recitative in"
  },
  {
    "question": "萌黄色",
    "answer": "もえぎいろ",
    "meaning": "light green, yellowish-green"
  },
  {
    "question": "外履き",
    "answer": "そとばき",
    "meaning": "outdoor shoes, outdoor footwear"
  },
  {
    "question": "鬱病",
    "answer": "うつびょう",
    "meaning": "depression"
  },
  {
    "question": "広角",
    "answer": "こうかく",
    "meaning": "wide-angle"
  },
  {
    "question": "俯瞰図",
    "answer": "ふかんず",
    "meaning": "bird's-eye view, aerial view, overhead view"
  },
  {
    "question": "底意",
    "answer": "そこい",
    "meaning": "true intention, underlying motive"
  },
  {
    "question": "警察権",
    "answer": "けいさつけん",
    "meaning": "police powers"
  },
  {
    "question": "書き送る",
    "answer": "かきおくる",
    "meaning": "to write (to someone)"
  },
  {
    "question": "中等教育",
    "answer": "ちゅうとうきょういく",
    "meaning": "secondary education"
  },
  {
    "question": "牛蒡",
    "answer": "ごぼう,ごんぼ,うまふぶき",
    "meaning": "great burdock (Arctium lappa), gobo"
  },
  {
    "question": "助動詞",
    "answer": "じょどうし",
    "meaning": "inflecting dependent word (in Japanese), bound auxiliary, auxiliary verb (in languages other than Ja"
  },
  {
    "question": "人間工学",
    "answer": "にんげんこうがく",
    "meaning": "ergonomics, human factors, human engineering"
  },
  {
    "question": "初診",
    "answer": "しょしん",
    "meaning": "initial medical examination"
  },
  {
    "question": "紫檀",
    "answer": "したん",
    "meaning": "rosewood, red sandalwood"
  },
  {
    "question": "色数",
    "answer": "いろかず",
    "meaning": "number of colors"
  },
  {
    "question": "千々",
    "answer": "ちぢ",
    "meaning": "thousands, great number of, variety"
  },
  {
    "question": "手水舎",
    "answer": "てみずや,ちょうずや",
    "meaning": "place for ritual cleansing of hands and mouth with water when visiting shrines"
  },
  {
    "question": "振込み",
    "answer": "ふりこみ",
    "meaning": "payment made via bank deposit transfer, discarding a tile that becomes another player's winning tile"
  },
  {
    "question": "人文",
    "answer": "じんぶん,じんもん",
    "meaning": "humanity, civilization, civilisation, culture"
  },
  {
    "question": "落葉樹",
    "answer": "らくようじゅ",
    "meaning": "deciduous tree"
  },
  {
    "question": "梅雨前線",
    "answer": "ばいうぜんせん",
    "meaning": "seasonal rain front"
  },
  {
    "question": "連番",
    "answer": "れんばん",
    "meaning": "consecutive number, serial number"
  },
  {
    "question": "順延",
    "answer": "じゅんえん",
    "meaning": "postponement, moving to a later date"
  },
  {
    "question": "誇らか",
    "answer": "ほこらか",
    "meaning": "proud"
  },
  {
    "question": "合力",
    "answer": "ごうりょく,ごうりき,こうりょく",
    "meaning": "resultant force, assistance, help, donation, alms, almsgiving"
  },
  {
    "question": "剝ける",
    "answer": "むける",
    "meaning": "to peel off, to come off, to be taken off"
  },
  {
    "question": "狸親父",
    "answer": "たぬきおやじ",
    "meaning": "sly (cunning) old man"
  },
  {
    "question": "子音",
    "answer": "しいん,しおん",
    "meaning": "consonant"
  },
  {
    "question": "什器",
    "answer": "じゅうき",
    "meaning": "utensil, appliance, furniture"
  },
  {
    "question": "略図",
    "answer": "りゃくず",
    "meaning": "rough sketch, rough map"
  },
  {
    "question": "一問一答",
    "answer": "いちもんいっとう",
    "meaning": "answering question by question"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼き畑",
    "answer": "やきばた,やきはた,やきばたけ",
    "meaning": "land made arable by the slash-and-burn method, swidden, slash-and-burn farming"
  },
  {
    "question": "取次ぐ",
    "answer": "とりつぐ",
    "meaning": "to act as an agent for, to intermediate, to announce (someone's arrival), to answer (the door, the p"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒焼き",
    "answer": "くろやき",
    "meaning": "charring, something charred, traditional medicine made from charred ingredients"
  },
  {
    "question": "服喪",
    "answer": "ふくも",
    "meaning": "going into mourning"
  },
  {
    "question": "気取り屋",
    "answer": "きどりや",
    "meaning": "snob, affected person"
  },
  {
    "question": "土地鑑",
    "answer": "とちかん",
    "meaning": "familiarity with the land, locality or terrain (usually associated with knowing or feeling the local"
  },
  {
    "question": "定めし",
    "answer": "さだめし",
    "meaning": "surely"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪性腫瘍",
    "answer": "あくせいしゅよう",
    "meaning": "malignant tumor, malignant tumour"
  },
  {
    "question": "硬式",
    "answer": "こうしき",
    "meaning": "hard (esp. of hardball, tennis, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "山勘",
    "answer": "やまかん",
    "meaning": "guesswork, speculation, hunch"
  },
  {
    "question": "泥塗れ",
    "answer": "どろまみれ",
    "meaning": "muddy, mud-caked"
  },
  {
    "question": "腰の物",
    "answer": "こしのもの",
    "meaning": "sword worn on the hip, something worn on the hip (e.g. sword, pill box, money pouch)"
  },
  {
    "question": "快走",
    "answer": "かいそう",
    "meaning": "fast moving, fast running, fast sailing"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎖状",
    "answer": "さじょう",
    "meaning": "chainlike"
  },
  {
    "question": "一時金",
    "answer": "いちじきん",
    "meaning": "lump sum, bonus, one-off payment"
  },
  {
    "question": "商標",
    "answer": "しょうひょう",
    "meaning": "trademark"
  },
  {
    "question": "列記",
    "answer": "れっき",
    "meaning": "list, enumeration"
  },
  {
    "question": "成犬",
    "answer": "せいけん",
    "meaning": "adult dog, fully-grown dog, mature dog"
  },
  {
    "question": "罷り",
    "answer": "まかり",
    "meaning": "emphatic verbal prefix, humble verbal prefix"
  },
  {
    "question": "揉み出す",
    "answer": "もみだす",
    "meaning": "to squeeze out, to remove (dirt, stains, etc.) by washing and rubbing"
  },
  {
    "question": "役務",
    "answer": "えきむ",
    "meaning": "labor, labour, service"
  },
  {
    "question": "隔日",
    "answer": "かくじつ,かくにち",
    "meaning": "every other day, every second day"
  },
  {
    "question": "文意",
    "answer": "ぶんい",
    "meaning": "meaning of a sentence"
  },
  {
    "question": "朽ち木",
    "answer": "くちき",
    "meaning": "decayed tree, rotted tree, decayed wood, rotten wood, obscure, meaningless life (metaphor)"
  },
  {
    "question": "文学者",
    "answer": "ぶんがくしゃ",
    "meaning": "scholar of literature, literary person, man of letters, writer"
  },
  {
    "question": "苔生す",
    "answer": "こけむす",
    "meaning": "to become covered in moss, to be moss-covered, to have moss growing on itself, to become aged (e.g."
  },
  {
    "question": "浮かぬ顔",
    "answer": "うかぬかお",
    "meaning": "long face, looking dejected"
  },
  {
    "question": "視認性",
    "answer": "しにんせい",
    "meaning": "visibility, noticeability, perceptibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "抑え難い",
    "answer": "おさえがたい",
    "meaning": "uncontrollable, irrepressible"
  },
  {
    "question": "待ち合い",
    "answer": "まちあい",
    "meaning": "rendezvous, meeting, assignation, area where guests gather before the start of a tea ceremony, waiti"
  },
  {
    "question": "地産地消",
    "answer": "ちさんちしょう",
    "meaning": "local production for local consumption"
  },
  {
    "question": "記念受験",
    "answer": "きねんじゅけん",
    "meaning": "taking the entrance examination for a school without regard for one's chances of passing"
  },
  {
    "question": "世評",
    "answer": "せひょう",
    "meaning": "reputation, public opinion"
  },
  {
    "question": "殖やす",
    "answer": "ふやす",
    "meaning": "to increase, to add to, to augment"
  },
  {
    "question": "歩速",
    "answer": "ほそく",
    "meaning": "walking speed, walking pace"
  },
  {
    "question": "適齢",
    "answer": "てきれい",
    "meaning": "suitable age"
  },
  {
    "question": "道化者",
    "answer": "どうけもの",
    "meaning": "buffoon, jester"
  },
  {
    "question": "踏み破る",
    "answer": "ふみやぶる",
    "meaning": "to break by stepping on, to trample, to stomp on, to stamp through, to walk across, to travel on foo"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち番",
    "answer": "たちばん",
    "meaning": "standing watch, sentinel"
  },
  {
    "question": "黙視",
    "answer": "もくし",
    "meaning": "view without saying a word, tacit permission"
  },
  {
    "question": "鍵っ子",
    "answer": "かぎっこ",
    "meaning": "latchkey child"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き回し",
    "answer": "ひきまわし",
    "meaning": "taking someone around, guidance, parading a criminal through town before their execution (Edo period"
  },
  {
    "question": "三国一",
    "answer": "さんごくいち",
    "meaning": "unparalleled in Japan and China and India"
  },
  {
    "question": "動機付け",
    "answer": "どうきづけ",
    "meaning": "motivation"
  },
  {
    "question": "中間色",
    "answer": "ちゅうかんしょく",
    "meaning": "intermediate color, intermediate colour, neutral color or tint, neutral colour"
  },
  {
    "question": "血の道",
    "answer": "ちのみち",
    "meaning": "assorted (female) medical disorders, blood vessels"
  },
  {
    "question": "帷子",
    "answer": "かたびら",
    "meaning": "light, thin, single-layer kimono (esp. from hemp or raw silk, for summer use), shroud, burial clothe"
  },
  {
    "question": "外用",
    "answer": "がいよう",
    "meaning": "external use"
  },
  {
    "question": "早引け",
    "answer": "はやびけ",
    "meaning": "leaving work (office, school) early"
  },
  {
    "question": "奮迅",
    "answer": "ふんじん",
    "meaning": "impetuous dash forward"
  },
  {
    "question": "量り売り",
    "answer": "はかりうり",
    "meaning": "selling by measure, selling by weight, selling by volume"
  },
  {
    "question": "所帯持ち",
    "answer": "しょたいもち",
    "meaning": "married man or woman, housekeeping"
  },
  {
    "question": "設え",
    "answer": "しつらえ",
    "meaning": "equipment, installation, facilities, arrangements"
  },
  {
    "question": "無欠",
    "answer": "むけつ",
    "meaning": "flawlessness"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕出し",
    "answer": "しだし",
    "meaning": "food delivery service, catering, walk-on part (in a play or film), background actor, extra"
  },
  {
    "question": "半乾き",
    "answer": "はんかわき",
    "meaning": "half dry"
  },
  {
    "question": "尺骨",
    "answer": "しゃっこつ",
    "meaning": "the ulna"
  },
  {
    "question": "うるさ型",
    "answer": "うるさがた",
    "meaning": "fastidiousness, faultfinding, nit-picking"
  },
  {
    "question": "男一匹",
    "answer": "おとこいっぴき",
    "meaning": "shining example of a man"
  },
  {
    "question": "乾き物",
    "answer": "かわきもの",
    "meaning": "dry snacks (e.g. crackers, nuts, dried squid, esp. to go with drinks)"
  },
  {
    "question": "身分相応",
    "answer": "みぶんそうおう",
    "meaning": "appropriate to one's lot in life, within one's means, fitting to one's position, suitable to one's s"
  },
  {
    "question": "中編",
    "answer": "ちゅうへん",
    "meaning": "second part (of three), second volume, middle part, novelette, novella, short novel, long short stor"
  },
  {
    "question": "立国",
    "answer": "りっこく",
    "meaning": "founding of a nation"
  },
  {
    "question": "切目",
    "answer": "きりめ",
    "meaning": "cut, notch, end, conclusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "火付け役",
    "answer": "ひつけやく",
    "meaning": "instigator, originator, initiator, torch bearer, incendiary, agitator, troublemaker"
  },
  {
    "question": "勇退",
    "answer": "ゆうたい",
    "meaning": "bowing out, retiring voluntarily"
  },
  {
    "question": "西北西",
    "answer": "せいほくせい",
    "meaning": "west-northwest"
  },
  {
    "question": "常食",
    "answer": "じょうしょく",
    "meaning": "daily food, regular diet, staple food"
  },
  {
    "question": "相反",
    "answer": "そうはん",
    "meaning": "inversion, opposition, conflicting, repulsion, contradiction"
  },
  {
    "question": "光らす",
    "answer": "ひからす",
    "meaning": "to make something bright, to shine, to polish"
  },
  {
    "question": "偶",
    "answer": "たまたま,たま,ぐう",
    "meaning": "occasionally, once in a while, seldom, casually, unexpectedly, accidentally, by chance, occasional,"
  },
  {
    "question": "敬老",
    "answer": "けいろう",
    "meaning": "respect for the aged"
  },
  {
    "question": "連れ込み",
    "answer": "つれこみ",
    "meaning": "taking one's lover to a hotel"
  },
  {
    "question": "流々",
    "answer": "りゅうりゅう",
    "meaning": "workmanship, style"
  },
  {
    "question": "香子",
    "answer": "きょうす",
    "meaning": "lance"
  },
  {
    "question": "書字",
    "answer": "しょじ",
    "meaning": "written form"
  },
  {
    "question": "牆壁",
    "answer": "しょうへき",
    "meaning": "enclosing wall, boundary fence, obstacle, barrier"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜々",
    "answer": "よよ",
    "meaning": "every evening, night after night"
  },
  {
    "question": "多子",
    "answer": "たし",
    "meaning": "bearing many children, multiparity, multipariety, multiparousness, high birth rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "摸倣",
    "answer": "もほう",
    "meaning": "imitation, copying"
  },
  {
    "question": "明夜",
    "answer": "みょうや",
    "meaning": "tomorrow night"
  },
  {
    "question": "寒椿",
    "answer": "かんつばき",
    "meaning": "camellia-like plant native to China"
  },
  {
    "question": "宝貝",
    "answer": "たからがい",
    "meaning": "cowrie, cowry"
  },
  {
    "question": "錨泊",
    "answer": "びょうはく",
    "meaning": "anchorage"
  },
  {
    "question": "星章",
    "answer": "せいしょう",
    "meaning": "star (badge)"
  },
  {
    "question": "壱岐",
    "answer": "いき",
    "meaning": "Iki (former province located on Iki Island in present-day Nagasaki Prefecture), Iki (island)"
  },
  {
    "question": "皇祖",
    "answer": "こうそ,おおじのみこと",
    "meaning": "(divine, historical or legendary) founder of an empire, grandfather of the emperor"
  },
  {
    "question": "寸土",
    "answer": "すんど",
    "meaning": "an inch of land"
  },
  {
    "question": "内惑星",
    "answer": "ないわくせい",
    "meaning": "inner planet"
  },
  {
    "question": "内力",
    "answer": "ないりょく",
    "meaning": "internal stress"
  },
  {
    "question": "青砥",
    "answer": "あおと",
    "meaning": "medium-grade millstone"
  },
  {
    "question": "水絵",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "九十九折",
    "answer": "つづらおり",
    "meaning": "winding, meandering, sinuous, zigzag"
  },
  {
    "question": "華北",
    "answer": "かほく",
    "meaning": "North China"
  },
  {
    "question": "満艦飾",
    "answer": "まんかんしょく",
    "meaning": "dressed up, decked out"
  },
  {
    "question": "宣布",
    "answer": "せんぷ",
    "meaning": "proclamation, dissemination, promulgation"
  },
  {
    "question": "甲兵",
    "answer": "こうへい",
    "meaning": "arms, war, armed warrior"
  },
  {
    "question": "与太郎",
    "answer": "よたろう",
    "meaning": "slow witted fellow, counter-hero, liar, lie, nonsense, Yotaro (rakugo character)"
  },
  {
    "question": "成魚",
    "answer": "せいぎょ",
    "meaning": "adult fish"
  },
  {
    "question": "新嘗祭",
    "answer": "にいなめさい,しんじょうさい",
    "meaning": "ceremonial offering to the deities by the Emperor of newly-harvested rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "骨髄移植",
    "answer": "こつずいいしょく",
    "meaning": "marrow transplant"
  },
  {
    "question": "犬舎",
    "answer": "けんしゃ",
    "meaning": "kennel, doghouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "探題",
    "answer": "たんだい",
    "meaning": "local commissioner (Kamakura or Muromachi eras), draw to find the theme for poetry session, composin"
  },
  {
    "question": "教父",
    "answer": "きょうふ",
    "meaning": "godfather, sponsor, church fathers"
  },
  {
    "question": "張子",
    "answer": "はりこ",
    "meaning": "papier mâché, player who is not a dealer (in cards)"
  },
  {
    "question": "告発状",
    "answer": "こくはつじょう",
    "meaning": "bill of indictment"
  },
  {
    "question": "天水",
    "answer": "てんすい",
    "meaning": "rain water"
  },
  {
    "question": "巡洋戦艦",
    "answer": "じゅんようせんかん",
    "meaning": "battle cruiser, battlecruiser"
  },
  {
    "question": "地熱発電",
    "answer": "ちねつはつでん,じねつはつでん",
    "meaning": "geothermal electric power generation"
  },
  {
    "question": "暴風雪",
    "answer": "ぼうふうせつ",
    "meaning": "blizzard, snowstorm"
  },
  {
    "question": "風紋",
    "answer": "ふうもん",
    "meaning": "wind-wrought pattern on the sands"
  },
  {
    "question": "鳳雛",
    "answer": "ほうすう",
    "meaning": "gifted young person who shows much promise"
  },
  {
    "question": "金光",
    "answer": "きんこう",
    "meaning": "golden light"
  },
  {
    "question": "浬",
    "answer": "ノット,かいり",
    "meaning": "knot (nautical mile per hour), nautical mile"
  },
  {
    "question": "中宮",
    "answer": "ちゅうぐう",
    "meaning": "the empress, the empress dowager and the grand empress dowager, emperor's second consort, empress, p"
  },
  {
    "question": "殿舎",
    "answer": "でんしゃ",
    "meaning": "palace"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄道",
    "answer": "こうどう,おうどう",
    "meaning": "ecliptic"
  },
  {
    "question": "御中",
    "answer": "おなか,おんちゅう",
    "meaning": "belly, abdomen, stomach, and Company, Messrs, for the attention of ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "熨",
    "answer": "のし,ぬし",
    "meaning": "noshi, long thin strip of dried abalone in folded patterned paper, attached to a gift"
  },
  {
    "question": "紅毛",
    "answer": "こうもう",
    "meaning": "red hair, Westerner (esp., originally, the Dutch)"
  },
  {
    "question": "梯",
    "answer": "はしご,かけはし,はし",
    "meaning": "ladder, stairs, going to several places in succession (e.g. barhopping), suspension bridge, viaduct,"
  },
  {
    "question": "甜菜",
    "answer": "てんさい",
    "meaning": "sugar beet (Beta vulgaris)"
  },
  {
    "question": "手帖",
    "answer": "てちょう",
    "meaning": "notebook, memo pad, (pocket) diary, certificate, identification card"
  },
  {
    "question": "木本",
    "answer": "もくほん",
    "meaning": "tree, woody plant"
  },
  {
    "question": "舎監",
    "answer": "しゃかん",
    "meaning": "dormitory dean"
  },
  {
    "question": "蝦夷地",
    "answer": "えぞち",
    "meaning": "Yezo (northern part of Meiji-era Japan, esp. Hokkaido, but also Sakhalin and the Kuril Islands), Edo"
  },
  {
    "question": "疋",
    "answer": "ひき,き",
    "meaning": "counter for small animals, counter for rolls of cloth (two han in size), roll of cloth, counter for"
  },
  {
    "question": "立会演説",
    "answer": "たちあいえんぜつ",
    "meaning": "campaign speech"
  },
  {
    "question": "猫車",
    "answer": "ねこぐるま",
    "meaning": "wheelbarrow"
  },
  {
    "question": "新教",
    "answer": "しんきょう",
    "meaning": "Protestantism"
  },
  {
    "question": "燕麦",
    "answer": "えんばく,からすむぎ",
    "meaning": "wild oat (Avena fatua), wild oats, oat (Avena sativa), oats"
  },
  {
    "question": "収量",
    "answer": "しゅうりょう",
    "meaning": "yield, size of harvest"
  },
  {
    "question": "制球力",
    "answer": "せいきゅうりょく",
    "meaning": "(pitcher's) control"
  },
  {
    "question": "百合根",
    "answer": "ゆりね",
    "meaning": "lily bulb"
  },
  {
    "question": "転封",
    "answer": "てんぽう,てんぷう",
    "meaning": "forced relocation of a daimyo to a different domain by the Edo shogunate"
  },
  {
    "question": "方面隊",
    "answer": "ほうめんたい",
    "meaning": "army"
  },
  {
    "question": "大入道",
    "answer": "おおにゅうどう",
    "meaning": "large, bald-headed monster, giant, large, bald man, big baldy, large monk"
  },
  {
    "question": "高速鉄道",
    "answer": "こうそくてつどう",
    "meaning": "high-speed rail, rapid (rail) transit"
  },
  {
    "question": "漁具",
    "answer": "ぎょぐ",
    "meaning": "fishing tackle, fishing gear"
  },
  {
    "question": "一郭",
    "answer": "いっかく",
    "meaning": "one block, enclosure"
  },
  {
    "question": "主柱",
    "answer": "しゅちゅう",
    "meaning": "central pillar, principal post, backbone of a society or community"
  },
  {
    "question": "磁性",
    "answer": "じせい",
    "meaning": "magnetism"
  },
  {
    "question": "水上機",
    "answer": "すいじょうき",
    "meaning": "hydroplane, seaplane"
  },
  {
    "question": "京阪",
    "answer": "けいはん",
    "meaning": "Kyoto-Osaka, Kyoto and Osaka"
  },
  {
    "question": "分与",
    "answer": "ぶんよ",
    "meaning": "distribution, allocation, dispensation, impartation"
  },
  {
    "question": "禅僧",
    "answer": "ぜんそう",
    "meaning": "Zen priest"
  },
  {
    "question": "至誠",
    "answer": "しせい",
    "meaning": "sincerity, devotion"
  },
  {
    "question": "太刀魚",
    "answer": "たちうお",
    "meaning": "largehead hairtail (Trichiurus lepturus), scabbard fish, beltfish"
  },
  {
    "question": "超心理学",
    "answer": "ちょうしんりがく",
    "meaning": "parapsychology"
  },
  {
    "question": "国務大臣",
    "answer": "こくむだいじん",
    "meaning": "minister of state, cabinet minister (Japan)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鑑札",
    "answer": "かんさつ",
    "meaning": "licence, license, permit"
  },
  {
    "question": "瑞兆",
    "answer": "ずいちょう",
    "meaning": "auspicious sign, good omen"
  },
  {
    "question": "噓吐き",
    "answer": "うそつき",
    "meaning": "liar, fibber"
  },
  {
    "question": "八丈",
    "answer": "はちじょう",
    "meaning": "plain-woven silk cloth produced on Hachijo Island (sometimes striped)"
  },
  {
    "question": "湯口",
    "answer": "ゆぐち",
    "meaning": "hot-water tap, hot spring"
  },
  {
    "question": "千種",
    "answer": "ちぐさ,ちくさ",
    "meaning": "great variety of flowering plants, light greenish-blue, various"
  },
  {
    "question": "掩蔽",
    "answer": "えんぺい",
    "meaning": "cover, concealment, masking, screening, occultation"
  },
  {
    "question": "内陣",
    "answer": "ないじん",
    "meaning": "inner sanctum, inner temple, inner shrine, sanctuary, chancel"
  },
  {
    "question": "卯の花",
    "answer": "うのはな",
    "meaning": "bean curd lees, soybean pulp, refuse from tofu, deutzia, Deutzia crenata"
  },
  {
    "question": "八手",
    "answer": "やつで",
    "meaning": "fatsi (Fatsia japonica), paperplant, Japanese aralia"
  },
  {
    "question": "大業物",
    "answer": "おおわざもの",
    "meaning": "first-rate sword"
  },
  {
    "question": "生硬",
    "answer": "せいこう",
    "meaning": "crude, immature, unpolished"
  },
  {
    "question": "見馴れる",
    "answer": "みなれる",
    "meaning": "to become used to seeing, to be familiar with"
  },
  {
    "question": "綜合",
    "answer": "そうごう",
    "meaning": "synthesis, coordination, putting together, integration, composite, comprehensive"
  },
  {
    "question": "凡骨",
    "answer": "ぼんこつ",
    "meaning": "ordinary person"
  },
  {
    "question": "血膿",
    "answer": "ちうみ",
    "meaning": "bloody pus"
  },
  {
    "question": "発毛",
    "answer": "はつもう",
    "meaning": "new hair growth"
  },
  {
    "question": "托卵",
    "answer": "たくらん",
    "meaning": "brood parasitism (planting one's eggs in another bird's nest, as demonstrated by the cuckoo, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "友邦",
    "answer": "ゆうほう",
    "meaning": "friendly nation"
  },
  {
    "question": "少壮",
    "answer": "しょうそう",
    "meaning": "youth"
  },
  {
    "question": "熱感",
    "answer": "ねつかん",
    "meaning": "feverish"
  },
  {
    "question": "綜",
    "answer": "あぜ",
    "meaning": "warp controller (on a loom)"
  },
  {
    "question": "天雷",
    "answer": "てんらい",
    "meaning": "thunder"
  },
  {
    "question": "律動的",
    "answer": "りつどうてき",
    "meaning": "rhythmical"
  },
  {
    "question": "自然数",
    "answer": "しぜんすう",
    "meaning": "natural number, nonnegative integer"
  },
  {
    "question": "後端",
    "answer": "こうたん",
    "meaning": "(tail) end"
  },
  {
    "question": "司法書士",
    "answer": "しほうしょし",
    "meaning": "judicial scrivener, judicial clerk, person qualified to prepare legal documents, handle real-estate"
  },
  {
    "question": "輪舞曲",
    "answer": "りんぶきょく",
    "meaning": "rondo"
  },
  {
    "question": "食い道楽",
    "answer": "くいどうらく",
    "meaning": "gourmand, epicure"
  },
  {
    "question": "中等学校",
    "answer": "ちゅうとうがっこう",
    "meaning": "secondary school"
  },
  {
    "question": "大権",
    "answer": "たいけん",
    "meaning": "supreme authority"
  },
  {
    "question": "毒酒",
    "answer": "どくしゅ",
    "meaning": "poisoned sake, poisoned alcohol"
  },
  {
    "question": "妖異",
    "answer": "ようい",
    "meaning": "mysterious occurrence"
  },
  {
    "question": "中点",
    "answer": "ちゅうてん,なかてん",
    "meaning": "middle point, median point, middle dot (typographical symbol used between parallel terms, names in k"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍管区",
    "answer": "ぐんかんく",
    "meaning": "military district"
  },
  {
    "question": "胸乳",
    "answer": "むなち,むなぢ",
    "meaning": "breasts"
  },
  {
    "question": "露光",
    "answer": "ろこう",
    "meaning": "(photographic) exposure"
  },
  {
    "question": "羞じらい",
    "answer": "はじらい",
    "meaning": "shyness"
  },
  {
    "question": "失踪宣告",
    "answer": "しっそうせんこく",
    "meaning": "court decision declaring a missing person legally dead"
  },
  {
    "question": "完全試合",
    "answer": "かんぜんしあい,かんぜんじあい",
    "meaning": "perfect game"
  },
  {
    "question": "大蜥蜴",
    "answer": "おおとかげ",
    "meaning": "monitor lizard"
  },
  {
    "question": "失投",
    "answer": "しっとう",
    "meaning": "careless pitch"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜鷹",
    "answer": "よたか",
    "meaning": "grey nightjar (Caprimulgus indicus), nightjar (any bird of family Caprimulgidae), goatsucker, street"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉞",
    "answer": "まさかり",
    "meaning": "broadaxe, battle axe"
  },
  {
    "question": "煉瓦塀",
    "answer": "れんがべい",
    "meaning": "brick wall"
  },
  {
    "question": "手籠",
    "answer": "てかご",
    "meaning": "handbasket"
  },
  {
    "question": "秋季",
    "answer": "しゅうき",
    "meaning": "fall season, autumn season"
  },
  {
    "question": "精練",
    "answer": "せいれん",
    "meaning": "scouring, degumming, training, refining, refinement, smelting"
  },
  {
    "question": "情趣",
    "answer": "じょうしゅ",
    "meaning": "mood, sentiment, artistic effect"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉤鼻",
    "answer": "かぎばな,かぎはな",
    "meaning": "hooked nose"
  },
  {
    "question": "西域",
    "answer": "せいいき",
    "meaning": "western regions of China"
  },
  {
    "question": "塩害",
    "answer": "えんがい",
    "meaning": "salt damage (from seawater, sea air, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "害鳥",
    "answer": "がいちょう",
    "meaning": "vermin, injurious bird"
  },
  {
    "question": "陣太鼓",
    "answer": "じんだいこ",
    "meaning": "war drum"
  },
  {
    "question": "徳川幕府",
    "answer": "とくがわばくふ",
    "meaning": "Tokugawa shogunate (i.e. the Edo shogunate, 1603-1867)"
  },
  {
    "question": "山桜",
    "answer": "やまざくら",
    "meaning": "mountain cherry (Cerasus jamasakura)"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼き飯",
    "answer": "やきめし",
    "meaning": "fried rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "閊える",
    "answer": "つかえる,つっかえる",
    "meaning": "to stick, to get stuck, to get caught, to get jammed, to clog, to be unavailable, to be busy, to be"
  },
  {
    "question": "回文",
    "answer": "かいぶん",
    "meaning": "circular (document), circulating letter, palindrome"
  },
  {
    "question": "焚き上げ",
    "answer": "たきあげ",
    "meaning": "bonfire often in temple grounds, usu. of charms, talismans, New Year decorations, etc., ritual burni"
  },
  {
    "question": "沈潜",
    "answer": "ちんせん",
    "meaning": "sinking into deep thought, sinking to the depths, contemplation"
  },
  {
    "question": "遊説",
    "answer": "ゆうぜい",
    "meaning": "election tour, election campaign, stumping"
  },
  {
    "question": "痴愚",
    "answer": "ちぐ",
    "meaning": "imbecility, idiocy"
  },
  {
    "question": "市議",
    "answer": "しぎ",
    "meaning": "city councillor, city councilor, city assemblyman"
  },
  {
    "question": "携帯小説",
    "answer": "けいたいしょうせつ",
    "meaning": "cellphone novel"
  },
  {
    "question": "身心",
    "answer": "しんしん,しんじん",
    "meaning": "mind and body"
  },
  {
    "question": "裏ビデオ",
    "answer": "うらビデオ",
    "meaning": "black market adult video, black market adult film, bootleg video"
  },
  {
    "question": "電子工学",
    "answer": "でんしこうがく",
    "meaning": "electronic engineering, electronics"
  },
  {
    "question": "箇条",
    "answer": "かじょう",
    "meaning": "item, article, clause, section, point"
  },
  {
    "question": "油を絞る",
    "answer": "あぶらをしぼる",
    "meaning": "to chew out, to reprimand severely, to rake over the coals, to give a sound scolding, to tell someon"
  },
  {
    "question": "尻子玉",
    "answer": "しりこだま,しりごだま",
    "meaning": "mythical ball inside the anus that is sought after by kappa"
  },
  {
    "question": "鳴り物",
    "answer": "なりもの",
    "meaning": "musical instrument, music, accompaniment instruments used in kabuki (excluding the shamisen)"
  },
  {
    "question": "連結器",
    "answer": "れんけつき",
    "meaning": "connector, coupler"
  },
  {
    "question": "山椒魚",
    "answer": "さんしょううお",
    "meaning": "salamander (amphibian of the order Caudata)"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷感",
    "answer": "れいかん",
    "meaning": "cold feeling, psychroesthesia"
  },
  {
    "question": "禍禍しい",
    "answer": "まがまがしい",
    "meaning": "ominous, sinister, unlucky, ill-omened, annoying, appearing to be true, plausible"
  },
  {
    "question": "霞が関",
    "answer": "かすみがせき",
    "meaning": "Kasumigaseki, district of Tokyo where most of Japan's government ministry offices are located, gover"
  },
  {
    "question": "凶賊",
    "answer": "きょうぞく",
    "meaning": "villain"
  },
  {
    "question": "死都",
    "answer": "しと",
    "meaning": "dead city, ghost town"
  },
  {
    "question": "藁葺き",
    "answer": "わらぶき",
    "meaning": "straw-thatching, straw-thatched roof"
  },
  {
    "question": "伊達巻",
    "answer": "だてまき",
    "meaning": "(woman's) undersash, rolled omelette mixed with fish (paste) (omelet)"
  },
  {
    "question": "側女",
    "answer": "そばめ",
    "meaning": "mistress, kept woman, concubine, close female servant"
  },
  {
    "question": "陣立て",
    "answer": "じんだて",
    "meaning": "battle formation"
  },
  {
    "question": "露天掘り",
    "answer": "ろてんぼり",
    "meaning": "open-cut or open-air (strip) mining"
  },
  {
    "question": "資財",
    "answer": "しざい",
    "meaning": "property, assets, fortune"
  },
  {
    "question": "中部地方",
    "answer": "ちゅうぶちほう",
    "meaning": "Chūbu region (incl. Aichi, Nagano, Shizuoka, Niigata, Toyama, Ishikawa, Fukui, Yamanashi and Gifu pr"
  },
  {
    "question": "哮る",
    "answer": "たける",
    "meaning": "to roar, to howl"
  },
  {
    "question": "水羊羹",
    "answer": "みずようかん",
    "meaning": "mizu yōkan, soft adzuki-bean jelly"
  },
  {
    "question": "程好い",
    "answer": "ほどよい",
    "meaning": "moderate, proper, just right"
  },
  {
    "question": "金券",
    "answer": "きんけん",
    "meaning": "gold certificate, tradeable coupon redeemable for goods or services"
  },
  {
    "question": "訓話",
    "answer": "くんわ",
    "meaning": "exemplum, apologue"
  },
  {
    "question": "雛型",
    "answer": "ひながた",
    "meaning": "model, miniature, pattern, sample, specimen, prescribed form"
  },
  {
    "question": "製麺",
    "answer": "せいめん",
    "meaning": "noodle making"
  },
  {
    "question": "課員",
    "answer": "かいん",
    "meaning": "section staff"
  },
  {
    "question": "批准",
    "answer": "ひじゅん",
    "meaning": "ratification"
  },
  {
    "question": "重力崩壊",
    "answer": "じゅうりょくほうかい",
    "meaning": "gravitational collapse"
  },
  {
    "question": "プリン頭",
    "answer": "プリンあたま",
    "meaning": "black hair that has been dyed blond after the roots begin to grow in at the top giving an appearance"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄色",
    "answer": "うすいろ",
    "meaning": "pale color, pale colour"
  },
  {
    "question": "年利",
    "answer": "ねんり",
    "meaning": "annual interest rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "又貸し",
    "answer": "またがし,またかし",
    "meaning": "subleasing, subletting"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄銅",
    "answer": "おうどう,こうどう",
    "meaning": "brass"
  },
  {
    "question": "女流作家",
    "answer": "じょりゅうさっか",
    "meaning": "woman writer, lady writer, authoress"
  },
  {
    "question": "旧臣",
    "answer": "きゅうしん",
    "meaning": "old retainer"
  },
  {
    "question": "応諾",
    "answer": "おうだく",
    "meaning": "consent, compliance"
  },
  {
    "question": "光一",
    "answer": "ぴかいち",
    "meaning": "dealt hand consisting of one 20-point card and six 1-point cards, outstanding, standing out above th"
  },
  {
    "question": "新地",
    "answer": "さらち,しんち",
    "meaning": "empty lot, vacant plot of land, new (residential) area (esp. built on reclaimed land during the Edo"
  },
  {
    "question": "料簡",
    "answer": "りょうけん",
    "meaning": "idea, thought, intention, design, view, inclination, decision, motive, discretion, forgiveness, pard"
  },
  {
    "question": "非行少年",
    "answer": "ひこうしょうねん",
    "meaning": "juvenile delinquent"
  },
  {
    "question": "職掌",
    "answer": "しょくしょう",
    "meaning": "official duties, office, function"
  },
  {
    "question": "詳報",
    "answer": "しょうほう",
    "meaning": "detailed report, full report, details, particulars"
  },
  {
    "question": "手旗",
    "answer": "てばた",
    "meaning": "semaphore (hand) flag"
  },
  {
    "question": "売り値",
    "answer": "うりね",
    "meaning": "selling price"
  },
  {
    "question": "職業婦人",
    "answer": "しょくぎょうふじん",
    "meaning": "career woman"
  },
  {
    "question": "丸木",
    "answer": "まるき",
    "meaning": "log"
  },
  {
    "question": "強暴",
    "answer": "きょうぼう",
    "meaning": "brutality"
  },
  {
    "question": "多角",
    "answer": "たかく",
    "meaning": "many-sided, versatile, polygonal, diversified"
  },
  {
    "question": "切り目",
    "answer": "きりめ",
    "meaning": "cut, notch, end, conclusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "集配",
    "answer": "しゅうはい",
    "meaning": "collection and delivery"
  },
  {
    "question": "飾緒",
    "answer": "しょくしょ,しょくちょ",
    "meaning": "aiguillette (ornamental braided cord)"
  },
  {
    "question": "リンパ節",
    "answer": "リンパせつ",
    "meaning": "lymph node"
  },
  {
    "question": "天然自然",
    "answer": "てんねんしぜん",
    "meaning": "natural, naturally"
  },
  {
    "question": "独創",
    "answer": "どくそう",
    "meaning": "originality"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼓笛隊",
    "answer": "こてきたい",
    "meaning": "drum and fife band"
  },
  {
    "question": "獅子吼",
    "answer": "ししく",
    "meaning": "lion's roar, harangue"
  },
  {
    "question": "奉職",
    "answer": "ほうしょく",
    "meaning": "being in the service of, serving at, holding office"
  },
  {
    "question": "戦き",
    "answer": "おののき",
    "meaning": "shudder, shiver, agitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "概観",
    "answer": "がいかん",
    "meaning": "general view, outline"
  },
  {
    "question": "輪状",
    "answer": "りんじょう",
    "meaning": "ring-shaped, annular"
  },
  {
    "question": "狂躁",
    "answer": "きょうそう",
    "meaning": "mania, wild excitement"
  },
  {
    "question": "大社",
    "answer": "たいしゃ,おおやしろ",
    "meaning": "grand shrine, famous shrine, Izumo Grand Shrine"
  },
  {
    "question": "吉事",
    "answer": "きちじ,きつじ",
    "meaning": "auspicious event"
  },
  {
    "question": "受給",
    "answer": "じゅきゅう",
    "meaning": "receiving payments (pension, ration)"
  },
  {
    "question": "片輪",
    "answer": "かたわ",
    "meaning": "crippled, deformed, imperfect, incomplete, one wheel"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻炎",
    "answer": "びえん",
    "meaning": "rhinitis, coryza, nasal inflammation"
  },
  {
    "question": "末梢",
    "answer": "まっしょう",
    "meaning": "tip of a twig, tip, end, trifles, trivial matters, minor details"
  },
  {
    "question": "蒸着",
    "answer": "じょうちゃく",
    "meaning": "vacuum deposition"
  },
  {
    "question": "全図",
    "answer": "ぜんず",
    "meaning": "complete map, whole view"
  },
  {
    "question": "誕プレ",
    "answer": "たんプレ",
    "meaning": "birthday present"
  },
  {
    "question": "頭抜ける",
    "answer": "ずぬける",
    "meaning": "to tower above, to stand out"
  },
  {
    "question": "切株",
    "answer": "きりかぶ",
    "meaning": "stump, stubble"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍将",
    "answer": "ぐんしょう",
    "meaning": "army commander"
  },
  {
    "question": "新約聖書",
    "answer": "しんやくせいしょ",
    "meaning": "New Testament"
  },
  {
    "question": "落丁",
    "answer": "らくちょう",
    "meaning": "missing page"
  },
  {
    "question": "巻尺",
    "answer": "まきじゃく",
    "meaning": "tape measure"
  },
  {
    "question": "論客",
    "answer": "ろんきゃく,ろんかく",
    "meaning": "controversialist"
  },
  {
    "question": "肝入り",
    "answer": "きもいり",
    "meaning": "good offices, auspices, sponsorship, help, assistance, village official (during the Edo period)"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗客名簿",
    "answer": "じょうきゃくめいぼ",
    "meaning": "list of passengers, passenger manifest, passenger register"
  },
  {
    "question": "不人情",
    "answer": "ふにんじょう",
    "meaning": "unkindness, inhumanity, heartlessness"
  },
  {
    "question": "撥ね",
    "answer": "はね",
    "meaning": "(a) jump, splashes (usu. of mud), upward turn at the bottom (e.g. of a vertical stroke of a kanji or"
  },
  {
    "question": "封建社会",
    "answer": "ほうけんしゃかい",
    "meaning": "feudal society"
  },
  {
    "question": "稽古着",
    "answer": "けいこぎ",
    "meaning": "training clothes (judo, kendo, etc.), practice suit"
  },
  {
    "question": "海水魚",
    "answer": "かいすいぎょ",
    "meaning": "saltwater fish"
  },
  {
    "question": "鶉",
    "answer": "うずら",
    "meaning": "quail, Japanese quail (Coturnix japonica)"
  },
  {
    "question": "捨身",
    "answer": "すてみ,しゃしん",
    "meaning": "putting one's life on the line, giving everything one has got, acting out of desperation, renouncing"
  },
  {
    "question": "訪日",
    "answer": "ほうにち",
    "meaning": "visit to Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "取水",
    "answer": "しゅすい",
    "meaning": "drawing water from river or lake, water intake"
  },
  {
    "question": "全一",
    "answer": "ぜんいつ",
    "meaning": "perfect whole, unity"
  },
  {
    "question": "感冒",
    "answer": "かんぼう",
    "meaning": "cold (illness)"
  },
  {
    "question": "敷衍",
    "answer": "ふえん",
    "meaning": "expatiation, enlargement (e.g. on a point), elaboration, amplification, clear explanation, paraphras"
  },
  {
    "question": "圧搾空気",
    "answer": "あっさくくうき",
    "meaning": "compressed air"
  },
  {
    "question": "財産家",
    "answer": "ざいさんか",
    "meaning": "wealthy individual, person of wealth"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇禍",
    "answer": "きか",
    "meaning": "unforeseen misfortune"
  },
  {
    "question": "節句",
    "answer": "せっく",
    "meaning": "seasonal festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "封建制",
    "answer": "ほうけんせい",
    "meaning": "feudal system, feudalism"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤べこ",
    "answer": "あかべこ",
    "meaning": "toy from Fukushima prefecture in the shape of a red cow, also used as a talisman against smallpox"
  },
  {
    "question": "視覚野",
    "answer": "しかくや",
    "meaning": "visual area (of the brain), visual cortex"
  },
  {
    "question": "取っ組む",
    "answer": "とっくむ",
    "meaning": "to grapple with, to wrestle with, to engage in a bout, to be matched against, to tackle (e.g. a prob"
  },
  {
    "question": "薬事法",
    "answer": "やくじほう",
    "meaning": "(Japanese) Pharmaceutical Affairs Law"
  },
  {
    "question": "どら息子",
    "answer": "どらむすこ",
    "meaning": "lazy son, profligate son"
  },
  {
    "question": "通念",
    "answer": "つうねん",
    "meaning": "common idea, common wisdom, generally accepted idea"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄砂",
    "answer": "こうさ",
    "meaning": "yellow sand, yellow dust, Asian dust, dust carried on high winds from Mongolia, northern China, and"
  },
  {
    "question": "強健",
    "answer": "きょうけん",
    "meaning": "robust (health), strong (constitution), sturdy"
  },
  {
    "question": "上質紙",
    "answer": "じょうしつし",
    "meaning": "wood-free paper, woodfree paper, fine paper, free sheet paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "素気無い",
    "answer": "そっけない,すげない",
    "meaning": "cold, short, curt, blunt"
  },
  {
    "question": "謹聴",
    "answer": "きんちょう",
    "meaning": "listening attentively"
  },
  {
    "question": "讃辞",
    "answer": "さんじ",
    "meaning": "eulogy, compliment"
  },
  {
    "question": "閑寂",
    "answer": "かんじゃく",
    "meaning": "quiet, peaceful, tranquil"
  },
  {
    "question": "中国地方",
    "answer": "ちゅうごくちほう",
    "meaning": "Chūgoku region of western Honshu (incl. Okayama, Hiroshima, Shimane, Tottori and Yamaguchi prefectur"
  },
  {
    "question": "在来種",
    "answer": "ざいらいしゅ",
    "meaning": "native species"
  },
  {
    "question": "何分にも",
    "answer": "なにぶんにも",
    "meaning": "anyway, anyhow, at any rate, after all"
  },
  {
    "question": "銃後",
    "answer": "じゅうご",
    "meaning": "the homefront"
  },
  {
    "question": "犬と猿",
    "answer": "いぬとさる",
    "meaning": "cats and dogs (as an example of a bad relationship), dogs and monkeys"
  },
  {
    "question": "青光り",
    "answer": "あおびかり",
    "meaning": "bluish sheen, steel-blue sheen"
  },
  {
    "question": "政治献金",
    "answer": "せいじけんきん",
    "meaning": "political contributions"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻を折る",
    "answer": "はなをおる",
    "meaning": "to humble someone"
  },
  {
    "question": "梨の礫",
    "answer": "なしのつぶて",
    "meaning": "not getting a reply"
  },
  {
    "question": "円高",
    "answer": "えんだか",
    "meaning": "appreciation of the yen, strong yen, strengthening of the yen, high-valued yen, exchange in favor of"
  },
  {
    "question": "前文",
    "answer": "ぜんぶん",
    "meaning": "the above sentence, the foregoing remark, preamble (to a statute, constitution, etc.), opening part"
  },
  {
    "question": "和する",
    "answer": "わする",
    "meaning": "to get along, to add (one's own concordant voice, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "痩せ形",
    "answer": "やせがた",
    "meaning": "slender build, slender figure, leptosome, leptosomatic habit, waifish, leptosomaic, leptosomatic, ec"
  },
  {
    "question": "祝す",
    "answer": "しゅくす",
    "meaning": "to congratulate, to celebrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "手巻き",
    "answer": "てまき",
    "meaning": "rolling by hand (e.g. sushi roll, cigarette), winding by hand (e.g. watch), hand-rolled sushi (usu."
  },
  {
    "question": "惹起",
    "answer": "じゃっき",
    "meaning": "bringing about, cause, provocation"
  },
  {
    "question": "即身仏",
    "answer": "そくしんぶつ",
    "meaning": "monks who practise austerity to the point of death and mummification"
  },
  {
    "question": "国家財政",
    "answer": "こっかざいせい",
    "meaning": "national finance, central government finance"
  },
  {
    "question": "自叙伝",
    "answer": "じじょでん",
    "meaning": "autobiography"
  },
  {
    "question": "俗事",
    "answer": "ぞくじ",
    "meaning": "worldly affairs, everyday affairs, common cares, routine work, daily chores"
  },
  {
    "question": "訓告",
    "answer": "くんこく",
    "meaning": "reprimand, admonition"
  },
  {
    "question": "度を失う",
    "answer": "どをうしなう",
    "meaning": "to lose one's presence of mind, be flummoxed, to get flustered"
  },
  {
    "question": "享楽主義",
    "answer": "きょうらくしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "epicureanism, hedonism"
  },
  {
    "question": "辞意",
    "answer": "じい",
    "meaning": "intention to resign"
  },
  {
    "question": "筆力",
    "answer": "ひつりょく",
    "meaning": "strength of the brush stroke, power of the pen, ability to write"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼈甲",
    "answer": "べっこう",
    "meaning": "tortoiseshell (of the hawksbill turtle), bekko, tortoiseshell (esp. of the Chinese soft-shelled turt"
  },
  {
    "question": "巨編",
    "answer": "きょへん",
    "meaning": "extremely large-scale (literary) work, monster work, long film, epic"
  },
  {
    "question": "群像劇",
    "answer": "ぐんぞうげき",
    "meaning": "dramatic production with parallel storylines focusing on different characters, multiprotagonist stor"
  },
  {
    "question": "昂進",
    "answer": "こうしん",
    "meaning": "rising, exacerbated, exasperated, accelerated, aggravated"
  },
  {
    "question": "風雲児",
    "answer": "ふううんじ",
    "meaning": "lucky adventurer, adventurer who takes advantage of troubled times, soldier of fortune"
  },
  {
    "question": "深閑",
    "answer": "しんかん",
    "meaning": "silent, still, quiet, hushed"
  },
  {
    "question": "岩盤浴",
    "answer": "がんばんよく",
    "meaning": "stone sauna, facility where one rests on towels laid on a slab of heated natural rock"
  },
  {
    "question": "生兵法",
    "answer": "なまびょうほう",
    "meaning": "crude tactics, smattering of knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "要事",
    "answer": "ようじ",
    "meaning": "important matter, necessary thing, requirement"
  },
  {
    "question": "一軒屋",
    "answer": "いっけんや",
    "meaning": "detached house, single house, single building, isolated house, house in isolated location"
  },
  {
    "question": "相撲部屋",
    "answer": "すもうべや",
    "meaning": "stable"
  },
  {
    "question": "一朝",
    "answer": "いっちょう",
    "meaning": "temporarily, short period, once, one morning"
  },
  {
    "question": "特報",
    "answer": "とくほう",
    "meaning": "news flash"
  },
  {
    "question": "体良く",
    "answer": "ていよく",
    "meaning": "decently, gracefully, plausibly, politely, tactfully, discreetly"
  },
  {
    "question": "理想化",
    "answer": "りそうか",
    "meaning": "idealization, idealisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "作り声",
    "answer": "つくりごえ",
    "meaning": "feigned voice, unnatural voice"
  },
  {
    "question": "肉食性",
    "answer": "にくしょくせい",
    "meaning": "carnivorousness, carnivorous"
  },
  {
    "question": "億兆",
    "answer": "おくちょう",
    "meaning": "the people, multitude, masses"
  },
  {
    "question": "没年",
    "answer": "ぼつねん",
    "meaning": "year of a person's death, one's age at death"
  },
  {
    "question": "安手",
    "answer": "やすで",
    "meaning": "cheap kind"
  },
  {
    "question": "授かり物",
    "answer": "さずかりもの",
    "meaning": "boon, windfall, blessing"
  },
  {
    "question": "改題",
    "answer": "かいだい",
    "meaning": "changing a title"
  },
  {
    "question": "緩々",
    "answer": "ゆるゆる,かんかん",
    "meaning": "very loose, slowly, leisurely, looking cool and collect, with an air of perfect composure"
  },
  {
    "question": "休火山",
    "answer": "きゅうかざん",
    "meaning": "dormant volcano"
  },
  {
    "question": "私立学校",
    "answer": "しりつがっこう",
    "meaning": "private school, non-government school"
  },
  {
    "question": "革命児",
    "answer": "かくめいじ",
    "meaning": "revolutionary, child of the revolution, man of revolutionary temperament"
  },
  {
    "question": "尾骨",
    "answer": "びこつ",
    "meaning": "coccyx, tailbone"
  },
  {
    "question": "清拭",
    "answer": "せいしき,せいしょく",
    "meaning": "bed bath, sponge bath, blanket bath, toilet"
  },
  {
    "question": "飲茶",
    "answer": "ヤムチャ",
    "meaning": "yum cha, eating snacks (esp. dim sum) with tea"
  },
  {
    "question": "頼り無い",
    "answer": "たよりない",
    "meaning": "unreliable, undependable, indefinite, vague, helpless, forlorn, forsaken, worried, uneasy"
  },
  {
    "question": "泣き別れ",
    "answer": "なきわかれ",
    "meaning": "parting in tears, tearful parting, coming to grief, having to take a different tack, going separate"
  },
  {
    "question": "痛飲",
    "answer": "つういん",
    "meaning": "heavy drinking"
  },
  {
    "question": "火災保険",
    "answer": "かさいほけん",
    "meaning": "fire insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "温故知新",
    "answer": "おんこちしん",
    "meaning": "developing new ideas based on study of the past, learning from the past"
  },
  {
    "question": "割拠",
    "answer": "かっきょ",
    "meaning": "holding one's ground, defending local authority"
  },
  {
    "question": "杓子",
    "answer": "しゃくし",
    "meaning": "bamboo ladle"
  },
  {
    "question": "恐々",
    "answer": "きょうきょう,こわごわ",
    "meaning": "respect (epistolary usage), fearfully, timidly, cautiously, nervously"
  },
  {
    "question": "精出す",
    "answer": "せいだす",
    "meaning": "to exert oneself"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷やっと",
    "answer": "ひやっと",
    "meaning": "feeling a sudden chill, feeling a shiver, feeling sudden surprise (fright, horror, etc.), shuddering"
  },
  {
    "question": "表書き",
    "answer": "おもてがき",
    "meaning": "address (on envelope, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "必携",
    "answer": "ひっけい",
    "meaning": "handbook, manual, vade mecum, essential item, must-have"
  },
  {
    "question": "激賞",
    "answer": "げきしょう",
    "meaning": "enthusiastic praise"
  },
  {
    "question": "買い戻し",
    "answer": "かいもどし",
    "meaning": "repurchase, redemption"
  },
  {
    "question": "名人芸",
    "answer": "めいじんげい",
    "meaning": "masterful performance, virtuosity"
  },
  {
    "question": "自分史",
    "answer": "じぶんし",
    "meaning": "personal history"
  },
  {
    "question": "洋物",
    "answer": "ようもの",
    "meaning": "Western goods, Western things, imported goods"
  },
  {
    "question": "歩き詰め",
    "answer": "あるきづめ",
    "meaning": "walking without rest, walking continuously"
  },
  {
    "question": "図説",
    "answer": "ずせつ",
    "meaning": "illustration, diagram"
  },
  {
    "question": "好男子",
    "answer": "こうだんし",
    "meaning": "handsome man"
  },
  {
    "question": "縮れ",
    "answer": "ちぢれ",
    "meaning": "frizz, kink, crimp, curls (hair, noodles, leaves, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "心移り",
    "answer": "こころうつり",
    "meaning": "change of heart, fickleness"
  },
  {
    "question": "黴菌",
    "answer": "ばいきん",
    "meaning": "germ, germs, bacteria, mold, mould, something harmful, vermin"
  },
  {
    "question": "零れ",
    "answer": "こぼれ",
    "meaning": "spilling, spill, leavings, leftovers"
  },
  {
    "question": "存知",
    "answer": "ぞんち,ぞんじ",
    "meaning": "knowledge of, knowing"
  },
  {
    "question": "世知",
    "answer": "せち",
    "meaning": "worldly wisdom, gumption, stingy person"
  },
  {
    "question": "ガス管",
    "answer": "ガスかん",
    "meaning": "gas pipe, gas tube"
  },
  {
    "question": "下道",
    "answer": "したみち",
    "meaning": "non-highway road, toll-free road, local road, road shadowed by trees, mountain, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "キー局",
    "answer": "キーきょく",
    "meaning": "key station, flagship station, leading station of a broadcasting network"
  },
  {
    "question": "内張り",
    "answer": "うちばり",
    "meaning": "lining, ceiling, wainscoting, wainscotting"
  },
  {
    "question": "共有物",
    "answer": "きょうゆうぶつ",
    "meaning": "common property"
  },
  {
    "question": "名立たる",
    "answer": "なだたる",
    "meaning": "famous, notorious, noted"
  },
  {
    "question": "保存料",
    "answer": "ほぞんりょう",
    "meaning": "preservative"
  },
  {
    "question": "亢進",
    "answer": "こうしん",
    "meaning": "rising, exacerbated, exasperated, accelerated, aggravated"
  },
  {
    "question": "字数",
    "answer": "じすう",
    "meaning": "number of characters or letters"
  },
  {
    "question": "時季外れ",
    "answer": "じきはずれ",
    "meaning": "out of season, unseasonal"
  },
  {
    "question": "着回し",
    "answer": "きまわし",
    "meaning": "mixing and matching (clothes, accessories, etc.), wearing of an item of clothing in many different c"
  },
  {
    "question": "婦女",
    "answer": "ふじょ",
    "meaning": "woman, womankind"
  },
  {
    "question": "厄年",
    "answer": "やくどし",
    "meaning": "unlucky year, critical year, year (esp. age 25 and 42 for men, 19 and 33 for women) that is consider"
  },
  {
    "question": "ズボン下",
    "answer": "ズボンした",
    "meaning": "long johns, long underpants, long underwear"
  },
  {
    "question": "早逝",
    "answer": "そうせい",
    "meaning": "dying young, early death"
  },
  {
    "question": "対向",
    "answer": "たいこう",
    "meaning": "counter-, corresponding, face, opposite"
  },
  {
    "question": "選り取り",
    "answer": "よりどり",
    "meaning": "picking and choosing"
  },
  {
    "question": "公共料金",
    "answer": "こうきょうりょうきん",
    "meaning": "public utilities charge"
  },
  {
    "question": "甘苦",
    "answer": "かんく",
    "meaning": "sweetness and bitterness, joys and sorrows"
  },
  {
    "question": "因む",
    "answer": "ちなむ",
    "meaning": "to be associated (with), to be connected (with)"
  },
  {
    "question": "離れ技",
    "answer": "はなれわざ",
    "meaning": "stunt, feat"
  },
  {
    "question": "申込",
    "answer": "もうしこみ",
    "meaning": "application, entry, request, subscription, offer, proposal, overture, challenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "披瀝",
    "answer": "ひれき",
    "meaning": "expressing one's opinion, speaking one's mind, making known, revealing"
  },
  {
    "question": "目眩し",
    "answer": "めくらまし",
    "meaning": "smoke screen, dazzler, distraction, camouflage, deceptive means, magic, witchcraft, sleight of hand,"
  },
  {
    "question": "深掘り",
    "answer": "ふかぼり",
    "meaning": "digging deeply (below the surface), mining deep, probing deeply (issue, problem), investigating thor"
  },
  {
    "question": "見難い",
    "answer": "みにくい",
    "meaning": "hard to see, obscure, indistinct, illegible"
  },
  {
    "question": "客受け",
    "answer": "きゃくうけ",
    "meaning": "enjoying popularity among the customers"
  },
  {
    "question": "移り香",
    "answer": "うつりが",
    "meaning": "lingering scent"
  },
  {
    "question": "面を取る",
    "answer": "めんをとる",
    "meaning": "to plane off the corners"
  },
  {
    "question": "切傷",
    "answer": "きりきず",
    "meaning": "cut, gash, incision"
  },
  {
    "question": "英数字",
    "answer": "えいすうじ",
    "meaning": "alphanumeric character"
  },
  {
    "question": "急かせる",
    "answer": "せかせる",
    "meaning": "to hurry (up), to urge on, to press, to rush"
  },
  {
    "question": "重軽傷",
    "answer": "じゅうけいしょう",
    "meaning": "serious or slight injury, major and minor injuries"
  },
  {
    "question": "百聞",
    "answer": "ひゃくぶん",
    "meaning": "hearing many times"
  },
  {
    "question": "跡を濁す",
    "answer": "あとをにごす",
    "meaning": "to leave a bad impression behind"
  },
  {
    "question": "親船",
    "answer": "おやぶね",
    "meaning": "mother ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "京華",
    "answer": "けいか",
    "meaning": "capital, national capital"
  },
  {
    "question": "校倉",
    "answer": "あぜくら",
    "meaning": "ancient log storehouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "歌枕",
    "answer": "うたまくら",
    "meaning": "place that is often written about in waka poetry, oft-repeated descriptive epithets in poetry"
  },
  {
    "question": "老生",
    "answer": "ろうせい",
    "meaning": "elderly person, I, me"
  },
  {
    "question": "英連邦",
    "answer": "えいれんぽう",
    "meaning": "Commonwealth of Nations (formerly British Commonwealth)"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓋然",
    "answer": "がいぜん",
    "meaning": "probability"
  },
  {
    "question": "全人",
    "answer": "ぜんじん",
    "meaning": "saint, person well-balanced morally and intellectually"
  },
  {
    "question": "匈奴",
    "answer": "きょうど,フンヌ",
    "meaning": "Xiongnu, ancient Central Asian nomadic people often associated with the Huns"
  },
  {
    "question": "五大老",
    "answer": "ごたいろう",
    "meaning": "Council of Five Elders (committee of daimyo formed by Toyotomi Hideyoshi to rule Japan until his son"
  },
  {
    "question": "紅紫",
    "answer": "こうし,べにむらさき",
    "meaning": "crimson and purple, red-purple, magenta"
  },
  {
    "question": "薬用植物",
    "answer": "やくようしょくぶつ",
    "meaning": "medicinal plant, medicinal herb"
  },
  {
    "question": "牛角",
    "answer": "ごかく,ぎゅうかく",
    "meaning": "equal (in ability), even, evenly matched, well-matched, on par (with), horn (of a cow)"
  },
  {
    "question": "重水",
    "answer": "じゅうすい",
    "meaning": "heavy water"
  },
  {
    "question": "花菱",
    "answer": "はなびし",
    "meaning": "flower-shaped family crest"
  },
  {
    "question": "外層",
    "answer": "がいそう",
    "meaning": "outer layers"
  },
  {
    "question": "梨園",
    "answer": "りえん",
    "meaning": "theatrical world"
  },
  {
    "question": "少輔",
    "answer": "しょう,しょうゆう,すないすけ",
    "meaning": "assistant vice-minister (ritsuryo system, early Meiji period)"
  },
  {
    "question": "襯衣",
    "answer": "しんい",
    "meaning": "underwear"
  },
  {
    "question": "金神",
    "answer": "こんじん",
    "meaning": "Konjin, God of (unlucky) directions"
  },
  {
    "question": "秋草",
    "answer": "あきくさ",
    "meaning": "plants which flower in autumn (fall)"
  },
  {
    "question": "毬藻",
    "answer": "まりも",
    "meaning": "marimo (variety of algae, Cladophora aegagropila), round green algae, Cladophora ball, lake ball, mo"
  },
  {
    "question": "馬頭琴",
    "answer": "ばとうきん",
    "meaning": "morin khuur (stringed musical instrument of Mongolian origin), matouqin"
  },
  {
    "question": "成都",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "蹴球",
    "answer": "しゅうきゅう",
    "meaning": "football (incl. soccer, rugby, American football, etc.; esp. used for soccer)"
  },
  {
    "question": "播州",
    "answer": "ばんしゅう",
    "meaning": "old name for part of Hyogo prefecture"
  },
  {
    "question": "恵方巻き",
    "answer": "えほうまき",
    "meaning": "ehōmaki, uncut sushi roll eaten during setsubun"
  },
  {
    "question": "裏垢",
    "answer": "うらあか",
    "meaning": "secret account, hidden account (e.g. online service)"
  },
  {
    "question": "古川",
    "answer": "ふるかわ",
    "meaning": "old river"
  },
  {
    "question": "侯国",
    "answer": "こうこく",
    "meaning": "marquisate, marquessate, principality"
  },
  {
    "question": "城址",
    "answer": "しろあと,じょうし",
    "meaning": "castle site, ruins of a castle"
  },
  {
    "question": "陪審",
    "answer": "ばいしん",
    "meaning": "jury"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼び子",
    "answer": "よびこ",
    "meaning": "whistle"
  },
  {
    "question": "電探",
    "answer": "でんたん",
    "meaning": "radar"
  },
  {
    "question": "刳い",
    "answer": "えぐい",
    "meaning": "harsh (taste, feeling, etc.), acrid, pungent, astringent, sharp (language, question, etc.), biting,"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎮魂祭",
    "answer": "ちんこんさい,たましずめのまつり",
    "meaning": "ceremony for the repose of a soul, ceremony to pray for the long life of the emperor, empress, crown"
  },
  {
    "question": "咳く",
    "answer": "しわぶく,せく",
    "meaning": "to cough"
  },
  {
    "question": "蔽う",
    "answer": "おおう",
    "meaning": "to cover, to hide, to conceal, to wrap, to disguise"
  },
  {
    "question": "威徳",
    "answer": "いとく",
    "meaning": "virtue and influence, virtue and authority"
  },
  {
    "question": "葛根湯",
    "answer": "かっこんとう",
    "meaning": "infusion of kudzu, cinnamon, etc., used as an antifebrile, for hangovers, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "妻女",
    "answer": "さいじょ",
    "meaning": "one's wife, one's wife and daughter or daughters"
  },
  {
    "question": "大天狗",
    "answer": "だいてんぐ",
    "meaning": "large tengu, powerful tengu, big braggart, blowhard"
  },
  {
    "question": "追儺",
    "answer": "ついな",
    "meaning": "(ceremony of) driving out evil spirits"
  },
  {
    "question": "建設大臣",
    "answer": "けんせつだいじん",
    "meaning": "Minister of Construction"
  },
  {
    "question": "謀将",
    "answer": "ぼうしょう",
    "meaning": "military general skilled at strategy"
  },
  {
    "question": "堅パン",
    "answer": "かたパン",
    "meaning": "hard biscuits, hardtack"
  },
  {
    "question": "御坊",
    "answer": "おんぼう,ごぼう",
    "meaning": "cemetery guard, crematorium worker, temple, monk's quarters, monk"
  },
  {
    "question": "開明",
    "answer": "かいめい",
    "meaning": "civilization, civilisation, enlightenment"
  },
  {
    "question": "白化",
    "answer": "はっか,はくか",
    "meaning": "bleaching, whitening, chlorosis, albinism"
  },
  {
    "question": "信用取引",
    "answer": "しんようとりひき",
    "meaning": "credit transaction, dealings on credit, margin transaction, margin trading"
  },
  {
    "question": "常考",
    "answer": "じょうこう",
    "meaning": "isn't it obvious?, that's common sense"
  },
  {
    "question": "征討",
    "answer": "せいとう",
    "meaning": "subjugation, conquest"
  },
  {
    "question": "悍馬",
    "answer": "かんば",
    "meaning": "unruly horse, unmanageable horse, unbroken horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "阿鼻",
    "answer": "あび",
    "meaning": "Avici (lowest level of hell)"
  },
  {
    "question": "レンズ豆",
    "answer": "レンズまめ",
    "meaning": "lentil (Lens culinaris)"
  },
  {
    "question": "石敷",
    "answer": "いしじき",
    "meaning": "stone paving, stone paved area"
  },
  {
    "question": "筑前",
    "answer": "ちくぜん",
    "meaning": "Chikuzen (former province located in the west of present-day Fukuoka Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "高炉",
    "answer": "こうろ",
    "meaning": "blast furnace"
  },
  {
    "question": "合縁奇縁",
    "answer": "あいえんきえん",
    "meaning": "a couple strangely but happily united, uncanny relationship formed by a quirk of fate"
  },
  {
    "question": "放射冷却",
    "answer": "ほうしゃれいきゃく",
    "meaning": "radiative cooling, radiational cooling"
  },
  {
    "question": "廃寺",
    "answer": "はいじ",
    "meaning": "ruined temple, abandoned temple, temple ruins, closing a temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "操車",
    "answer": "そうしゃ",
    "meaning": "operation (of trains)"
  },
  {
    "question": "英和辞典",
    "answer": "えいわじてん",
    "meaning": "English-Japanese dictionary"
  },
  {
    "question": "辻堂",
    "answer": "つじどう",
    "meaning": "wayside shrine"
  },
  {
    "question": "木魂",
    "answer": "こだま",
    "meaning": "echo, reverberation, spirit of a tree, tree spirit"
  },
  {
    "question": "開局",
    "answer": "かいきょく",
    "meaning": "opening (of a broadcasting station, post office, bureau, etc.), establishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "上古",
    "answer": "じょうこ",
    "meaning": "ancient times"
  },
  {
    "question": "妊活",
    "answer": "にんかつ",
    "meaning": "trying to conceive, attempting to get pregnant (through various means)"
  },
  {
    "question": "薇",
    "answer": "ぜんまい",
    "meaning": "royal fern (Osmunda japonica), flowering fern, osmund, fiddlehead fern"
  },
  {
    "question": "集合知",
    "answer": "しゅうごうち",
    "meaning": "wisdom of crowds"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹垣",
    "answer": "たけがき",
    "meaning": "bamboo fence (hedge)"
  },
  {
    "question": "刷",
    "answer": "すり,さつ",
    "meaning": "printing, impression, issue"
  },
  {
    "question": "真弓",
    "answer": "まゆみ",
    "meaning": "Japanese spindle tree (Euonymus sieboldianus)"
  },
  {
    "question": "燻煙",
    "answer": "くんえん",
    "meaning": "smoking (esp. as a means of preserving food)"
  },
  {
    "question": "鮨",
    "answer": "すし",
    "meaning": "sushi, anything made with vinegared rice (may also contain vegetables, spices, fish, or other delica"
  },
  {
    "question": "庶出",
    "answer": "しょしゅつ",
    "meaning": "illegitimate birth"
  },
  {
    "question": "法曹",
    "answer": "ほうそう",
    "meaning": "legal profession, judicial officer, lawyer, attorney"
  },
  {
    "question": "高潮",
    "answer": "こうちょう,たかしお",
    "meaning": "high tide, high water, climax, high point, storm surge"
  },
  {
    "question": "横っちょ",
    "answer": "よこっちょ",
    "meaning": "sideways"
  },
  {
    "question": "夕顔",
    "answer": "ゆうがお",
    "meaning": "bottle gourd (Lagenaria siceraria, esp. Lagenaria siceraria var. hispida), moonflower (Ipomoea alba)"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤帽",
    "answer": "あかぼう",
    "meaning": "red cap, (railway) porter, redcap"
  },
  {
    "question": "朝日新聞",
    "answer": "あさひしんぶん",
    "meaning": "Asahi Shimbun (newspaper)"
  },
  {
    "question": "精管",
    "answer": "せいかん",
    "meaning": "seminal duct"
  },
  {
    "question": "妓",
    "answer": "ぎ",
    "meaning": "geisha"
  },
  {
    "question": "輻射",
    "answer": "ふくしゃ",
    "meaning": "radiation"
  },
  {
    "question": "天下国家",
    "answer": "てんかこっか",
    "meaning": "the world and the nation, the state of the world, high affairs of state"
  },
  {
    "question": "端座",
    "answer": "たんざ",
    "meaning": "sitting upright (properly)"
  },
  {
    "question": "側背",
    "answer": "そくはい",
    "meaning": "flank"
  },
  {
    "question": "気胸",
    "answer": "ききょう",
    "meaning": "pneumothorax"
  },
  {
    "question": "狂する",
    "answer": "きょうする",
    "meaning": "to go mad (over something), to be crazy (about something)"
  },
  {
    "question": "英和",
    "answer": "えいわ",
    "meaning": "English-Japanese, English-Japanese dictionary"
  },
  {
    "question": "投票率",
    "answer": "とうひょうりつ",
    "meaning": "voter turnout, (polling) turnout"
  },
  {
    "question": "随喜",
    "answer": "ずいき",
    "meaning": "deep gratitude, overwhelming joy, great happiness"
  },
  {
    "question": "不得要領",
    "answer": "ふとくようりょう",
    "meaning": "vague, ambiguous, noncommittal, off-point"
  },
  {
    "question": "縁台",
    "answer": "えんだい",
    "meaning": "bench"
  },
  {
    "question": "約数",
    "answer": "やくすう",
    "meaning": "divisor, factor, measure"
  },
  {
    "question": "麦粉",
    "answer": "むぎこ",
    "meaning": "wheat flour"
  },
  {
    "question": "医療過誤",
    "answer": "いりょうかご",
    "meaning": "medical malpractice"
  },
  {
    "question": "根切り",
    "answer": "ねぎり,ねきり",
    "meaning": "excavation (as preparation for construction), cutting roots, extermination, rooting out"
  },
  {
    "question": "儀仗",
    "answer": "ぎじょう",
    "meaning": "cortege, guard"
  },
  {
    "question": "万葉",
    "answer": "まんよう,まんにょう",
    "meaning": "Man'yōshū (8th century anthology of Japanese poetry), thousands of leaves, thousands of years, all a"
  },
  {
    "question": "治安出動",
    "answer": "ちあんしゅつどう",
    "meaning": "public security operation"
  },
  {
    "question": "町立",
    "answer": "ちょうりつ",
    "meaning": "established by the town"
  },
  {
    "question": "八双",
    "answer": "はっそう",
    "meaning": "style of sword fighting"
  },
  {
    "question": "怪事",
    "answer": "かいじ",
    "meaning": "mystery, strange event, mysterious affair"
  },
  {
    "question": "社食",
    "answer": "しゃしょく",
    "meaning": "staff canteen"
  },
  {
    "question": "空荷",
    "answer": "からに",
    "meaning": "lacking cargo, in ballast"
  },
  {
    "question": "仰山",
    "answer": "ぎょうさん",
    "meaning": "a lot, plenty, abundant, great many, exaggerated, grandiose"
  },
  {
    "question": "身頃",
    "answer": "みごろ",
    "meaning": "body of a garment, bodice"
  },
  {
    "question": "幣",
    "answer": "へい,ぬさ,まい",
    "meaning": "staff with plaited paper streamers, reward, present, gift, offering to the gods"
  },
  {
    "question": "縄張",
    "answer": "なわばり",
    "meaning": "stretching a rope around, roping off, cordoning off, demarcation, one's turf, domain, territory, jur"
  },
  {
    "question": "墜死",
    "answer": "ついし",
    "meaning": "falling to one's death"
  },
  {
    "question": "植毛",
    "answer": "しょくもう",
    "meaning": "hair transplantation"
  },
  {
    "question": "内儀",
    "answer": "ないぎ,おかみ",
    "meaning": "your wife, his wife, secret meeting, secrecy"
  },
  {
    "question": "乳色",
    "answer": "にゅうしょく,ちちいろ",
    "meaning": "milk white, opaque white"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱臭",
    "answer": "だっしゅう",
    "meaning": "deodorization, deodorisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "輪形",
    "answer": "りんけい",
    "meaning": "ring-shaped, circular"
  },
  {
    "question": "神火",
    "answer": "しんか",
    "meaning": "sacred flame"
  },
  {
    "question": "体当り",
    "answer": "たいあたり",
    "meaning": "ramming attack, hurling oneself (at), throwing oneself into (e.g. a role), going all out"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶対主義",
    "answer": "ぜったいしゅぎ",
    "meaning": "absolutism"
  },
  {
    "question": "成人の日",
    "answer": "せいじんのひ",
    "meaning": "Coming of Age Day (national holiday; second Monday in January), Adult's Day"
  },
  {
    "question": "遵法",
    "answer": "じゅんぽう",
    "meaning": "law observance, obeying the law"
  },
  {
    "question": "核実験",
    "answer": "かくじっけん",
    "meaning": "nuclear (bomb) test"
  },
  {
    "question": "離縁状",
    "answer": "りえんじょう",
    "meaning": "letter of divorce"
  },
  {
    "question": "水塊",
    "answer": "すいかい",
    "meaning": "water mass"
  },
  {
    "question": "核分裂",
    "answer": "かくぶんれつ",
    "meaning": "nuclear fission, karyokinesis (division of a cell nucleus during mitosis or meiosis)"
  },
  {
    "question": "敏感肌",
    "answer": "びんかんはだ",
    "meaning": "sensitive skin"
  },
  {
    "question": "錯視",
    "answer": "さくし",
    "meaning": "optical illusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "緑葉",
    "answer": "りょくよう",
    "meaning": "green leaves"
  },
  {
    "question": "車中泊",
    "answer": "しゃちゅうはく",
    "meaning": "spending the night in a car, train, bus, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "復仇",
    "answer": "ふっきゅう,ふくきゅう",
    "meaning": "reprisal, revenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "手切れ",
    "answer": "てぎれ",
    "meaning": "severing of connections or relations"
  },
  {
    "question": "掌紋",
    "answer": "しょうもん",
    "meaning": "palm print"
  },
  {
    "question": "展覧",
    "answer": "てんらん",
    "meaning": "exhibition, show"
  },
  {
    "question": "南面",
    "answer": "なんめん",
    "meaning": "south face, south side, the south, facing the south, ascending the throne, ruling"
  },
  {
    "question": "胸腔",
    "answer": "きょうこう,きょうくう",
    "meaning": "thorax, thoracic cavity"
  },
  {
    "question": "断髪",
    "answer": "だんぱつ",
    "meaning": "cutting of hair (to a short length), haircutting, bobbed hair, bob"
  },
  {
    "question": "泥濘む",
    "answer": "ぬかるむ",
    "meaning": "to be muddy, to be slushy"
  },
  {
    "question": "紙上",
    "answer": "しじょう",
    "meaning": "on paper, in the newspapers, in a letter"
  },
  {
    "question": "足留め",
    "answer": "あしどめ",
    "meaning": "preventing (someone) from leaving, confinement, keeping indoors, inducement to stay, being stranded,"
  },
  {
    "question": "大蔵",
    "answer": "おおくら",
    "meaning": "Ministry of Finance"
  },
  {
    "question": "吸い飲み",
    "answer": "すいのみ",
    "meaning": "feeding cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "入神",
    "answer": "にゅうしん",
    "meaning": "inspiration, genius, super-human skill"
  },
  {
    "question": "証す",
    "answer": "あかす,しょうす",
    "meaning": "to prove, to verify, to guarantee, to promise"
  },
  {
    "question": "医師会",
    "answer": "いしかい",
    "meaning": "medical association"
  },
  {
    "question": "度する",
    "answer": "どする",
    "meaning": "to redeem (from sin), to save"
  },
  {
    "question": "宿六",
    "answer": "やどろく",
    "meaning": "husband"
  },
  {
    "question": "民族性",
    "answer": "みんぞくせい",
    "meaning": "racial or national characteristics"
  },
  {
    "question": "六種",
    "answer": "ろくしゅ",
    "meaning": "six kinds"
  },
  {
    "question": "人工芝",
    "answer": "じんこうしば",
    "meaning": "artificial grass (lawn)"
  },
  {
    "question": "噴霧器",
    "answer": "ふんむき",
    "meaning": "sprayer, vaporizer, vaporiser, atomizer, atomiser"
  },
  {
    "question": "在留",
    "answer": "ざいりゅう",
    "meaning": "residing (esp. abroad), staying, living"
  },
  {
    "question": "後塵",
    "answer": "こうじん",
    "meaning": "trailing dust, dust left by someone running ahead"
  },
  {
    "question": "打ち掛け",
    "answer": "うちかけ",
    "meaning": "women's bridal robe with trailing skirts worn over a kimono, ending play for the day, leaving a game"
  },
  {
    "question": "土石",
    "answer": "どせき",
    "meaning": "earth and stones"
  },
  {
    "question": "トタン板",
    "answer": "トタンいた",
    "meaning": "galvanized sheet iron, galvanised sheet iron"
  },
  {
    "question": "訳有り",
    "answer": "わけあり",
    "meaning": "having special circumstances (e.g. problems, issues, advantages, flaws, defects, etc.), imperfect (m"
  },
  {
    "question": "航空燃料",
    "answer": "こうくうねんりょう",
    "meaning": "aviation fuel"
  },
  {
    "question": "白砂糖",
    "answer": "しろざとう",
    "meaning": "white sugar"
  },
  {
    "question": "麗々しい",
    "answer": "れいれいしい",
    "meaning": "ostentatious, gaudy, showy"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶筅",
    "answer": "ちゃせん",
    "meaning": "tea whisk, bamboo whisk for making Japanese tea, hair style where the hair is tied up in a bundle on"
  },
  {
    "question": "煮凝り",
    "answer": "にこごり",
    "meaning": "jellied fish or meat broth"
  },
  {
    "question": "見離す",
    "answer": "みはなす",
    "meaning": "to abandon, to give up on, to desert"
  },
  {
    "question": "上申書",
    "answer": "じょうしんしょ",
    "meaning": "written report"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷や奴",
    "answer": "ひややっこ",
    "meaning": "cold tofu"
  },
  {
    "question": "決定版",
    "answer": "けっていはん,けっていばん",
    "meaning": "definitive piece, definitive (authoritative) edition, last word"
  },
  {
    "question": "獣皮",
    "answer": "じゅうひ",
    "meaning": "hide, pelt, animal skin"
  },
  {
    "question": "塑像",
    "answer": "そぞう",
    "meaning": "plaster image, clay figure"
  },
  {
    "question": "メガ盛り",
    "answer": "メガもり",
    "meaning": "mega-sized portion, mega-sized serving, mega meal"
  },
  {
    "question": "奸賊",
    "answer": "かんぞく",
    "meaning": "villain"
  },
  {
    "question": "断わり",
    "answer": "ことわり",
    "meaning": "notice, notification, warning, permission, consent, rejection, refusal, nonacceptance, declination,"
  },
  {
    "question": "脳内出血",
    "answer": "のうないしゅっけつ",
    "meaning": "brain hemorrhage, brain haemorrhage"
  },
  {
    "question": "熱処理",
    "answer": "ねつしょり",
    "meaning": "heat treatment"
  },
  {
    "question": "強打者",
    "answer": "きょうだしゃ",
    "meaning": "slugger, heavy hitter"
  },
  {
    "question": "船首像",
    "answer": "せんしゅぞう",
    "meaning": "figurehead (on a ship)"
  },
  {
    "question": "懐旧",
    "answer": "かいきゅう",
    "meaning": "reminiscence, nostalgia, thinking fondly of the past, recalling the old days"
  },
  {
    "question": "欠品",
    "answer": "けっぴん",
    "meaning": "stockout, out of stock"
  },
  {
    "question": "腿肉",
    "answer": "ももにく",
    "meaning": "leg (meat), round, ham"
  },
  {
    "question": "硬水",
    "answer": "こうすい",
    "meaning": "hard water"
  },
  {
    "question": "国民投票",
    "answer": "こくみんとうひょう",
    "meaning": "national referendum"
  },
  {
    "question": "神経組織",
    "answer": "しんけいそしき",
    "meaning": "nerve tissue"
  },
  {
    "question": "素裸",
    "answer": "すっぱだか,すはだか",
    "meaning": "nudity, stark naked, in one's bare skin, penniless"
  },
  {
    "question": "逆徒",
    "answer": "ぎゃくと",
    "meaning": "rebel, traitor"
  },
  {
    "question": "永続性",
    "answer": "えいぞくせい",
    "meaning": "persistent, permanence"
  },
  {
    "question": "空威張り",
    "answer": "からいばり",
    "meaning": "bluffing, bluster, bravado"
  },
  {
    "question": "英邁",
    "answer": "えいまい",
    "meaning": "wise and great"
  },
  {
    "question": "惚け",
    "answer": "ぼけ,とぼけ",
    "meaning": "fool, idiot, dotage, senility, dementia, touched in the head (from), out of it (from), feeling slugg"
  },
  {
    "question": "女所帯",
    "answer": "おんなじょたい",
    "meaning": "female household, household consisting wholly of women"
  },
  {
    "question": "情夫",
    "answer": "じょうふ,いろ",
    "meaning": "lover (male)"
  },
  {
    "question": "寡占",
    "answer": "かせん",
    "meaning": "oligopoly"
  },
  {
    "question": "上す",
    "answer": "のぼす",
    "meaning": "to raise, to record, to bring up (a matter), to serve (food), to send someone out"
  },
  {
    "question": "遠赤外線",
    "answer": "えんせきがいせん",
    "meaning": "far-infrared rays, far-infrared radiation, FIR"
  },
  {
    "question": "寸足らず",
    "answer": "すんたらず",
    "meaning": "a little too short, slightly worse, a bit inferior"
  },
  {
    "question": "目的物",
    "answer": "もくてきぶつ",
    "meaning": "object, objective, aim"
  },
  {
    "question": "永久歯",
    "answer": "えいきゅうし",
    "meaning": "permanent tooth"
  },
  {
    "question": "廃刊",
    "answer": "はいかん",
    "meaning": "ceasing to publish, discontinuance of publication"
  },
  {
    "question": "肘当て",
    "answer": "ひじあて",
    "meaning": "(detachable) elbow rest, arm rest, elbow pad, elbow strike (karate)"
  },
  {
    "question": "取捨",
    "answer": "しゅしゃ",
    "meaning": "adoption or rejection, selection, choice, option"
  },
  {
    "question": "薄寒い",
    "answer": "うすさむい,うすざむい",
    "meaning": "somewhat cold, a bit chilly"
  },
  {
    "question": "紡錘形",
    "answer": "ぼうすいけい",
    "meaning": "spindle-shaped"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨中",
    "answer": "うちゅう",
    "meaning": "in the rain"
  },
  {
    "question": "原人",
    "answer": "げんじん",
    "meaning": "primitive man"
  },
  {
    "question": "遡及",
    "answer": "そきゅう,さっきゅう",
    "meaning": "tracing back, retroactivity"
  },
  {
    "question": "酢酸",
    "answer": "さくさん",
    "meaning": "acetic acid"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉱業",
    "answer": "こうぎょう",
    "meaning": "mining industry"
  },
  {
    "question": "行政権",
    "answer": "ぎょうせいけん",
    "meaning": "executive power, authority"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍制",
    "answer": "ぐんせい",
    "meaning": "military system, military organization, military organisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "市民運動",
    "answer": "しみんうんどう",
    "meaning": "citizens' campaign, citizens' group"
  },
  {
    "question": "後略",
    "answer": "こうりゃく",
    "meaning": "omitting the rest"
  },
  {
    "question": "式辞",
    "answer": "しきじ",
    "meaning": "ceremonial address"
  },
  {
    "question": "至上命令",
    "answer": "しじょうめいれい",
    "meaning": "categorical imperative, overriding necessity"
  },
  {
    "question": "貞潔",
    "answer": "ていけつ",
    "meaning": "chastity, purity"
  },
  {
    "question": "泥縄",
    "answer": "どろなわ",
    "meaning": "measure taken too late, measure taken in haste"
  },
  {
    "question": "冗長性",
    "answer": "じょうちょうせい",
    "meaning": "redundancy"
  },
  {
    "question": "色水",
    "answer": "いろみず",
    "meaning": "colored water"
  },
  {
    "question": "退寮",
    "answer": "たいりょう",
    "meaning": "moving out of a dormitory"
  },
  {
    "question": "動物界",
    "answer": "どうぶつかい",
    "meaning": "animal kingdom, Animalia"
  },
  {
    "question": "室内犬",
    "answer": "しつないけん",
    "meaning": "indoor dog, dog kept indoors, house dog"
  },
  {
    "question": "轟轟",
    "answer": "ごうごう,とどろとどろ",
    "meaning": "thunderous, rumbling, thunderously, rumblingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "私腹",
    "answer": "しふく",
    "meaning": "one's own profits, one's own pockets"
  },
  {
    "question": "駿足",
    "answer": "しゅんそく",
    "meaning": "swiftness of foot, fast runner, swift horse, fleet steed"
  },
  {
    "question": "慣わす",
    "answer": "ならわす",
    "meaning": "to make (someone) learn, to be accustomed to ..., to be used to ..., to always ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "下等動物",
    "answer": "かとうどうぶつ",
    "meaning": "lower animals"
  },
  {
    "question": "煮付ける",
    "answer": "につける",
    "meaning": "to cook hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "激白",
    "answer": "げきはく",
    "meaning": "candidly revealing (secrets), revelation, disclosure, confession"
  },
  {
    "question": "心密かに",
    "answer": "こころひそかに",
    "meaning": "inwardly, secretly"
  },
  {
    "question": "炭素繊維",
    "answer": "たんそせんい",
    "meaning": "carbon fiber, carbon fibre"
  },
  {
    "question": "付け髭",
    "answer": "つけひげ",
    "meaning": "false moustache"
  },
  {
    "question": "臭覚",
    "answer": "しゅうかく",
    "meaning": "the sense of smell"
  },
  {
    "question": "二重顎",
    "answer": "にじゅうあご,ふたえあご",
    "meaning": "double chin"
  },
  {
    "question": "単元",
    "answer": "たんげん",
    "meaning": "teaching unit"
  },
  {
    "question": "馬脚",
    "answer": "ばきゃく",
    "meaning": "horse's legs, stage actor who plays the role of a horse's legs"
  },
  {
    "question": "漁業権",
    "answer": "ぎょぎょうけん",
    "meaning": "fishing rights"
  },
  {
    "question": "伴走",
    "answer": "ばんそう",
    "meaning": "running alongside, pacesetting, accompanying"
  },
  {
    "question": "短期記憶",
    "answer": "たんききおく",
    "meaning": "short-term memory"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛煙家",
    "answer": "あいえんか",
    "meaning": "heavy smoker, habitual smoker, person who loves smoking, tobacco lover"
  },
  {
    "question": "玉の肌",
    "answer": "たまのはだ",
    "meaning": "skin as beautiful as a gem, beautiful skin"
  },
  {
    "question": "内服薬",
    "answer": "ないふくやく",
    "meaning": "medicine taken internally"
  },
  {
    "question": "俎板",
    "answer": "まないた",
    "meaning": "chopping board, cutting board"
  },
  {
    "question": "修整",
    "answer": "しゅうせい",
    "meaning": "adjustment, retouching (in photography)"
  },
  {
    "question": "一筆書き",
    "answer": "ひとふでがき,いっぴつがき",
    "meaning": "one-stroke sketch, unicursal"
  },
  {
    "question": "域外",
    "answer": "いきがい",
    "meaning": "outside the area"
  },
  {
    "question": "自裁",
    "answer": "じさい",
    "meaning": "taking one's own life, suicide"
  },
  {
    "question": "以西",
    "answer": "いせい",
    "meaning": "... and westward, west of"
  },
  {
    "question": "乗算",
    "answer": "じょうざん",
    "meaning": "multiplication"
  },
  {
    "question": "銭勘定",
    "answer": "ぜにかんじょう",
    "meaning": "counting the revenues and expenditures, counting the gains and losses"
  },
  {
    "question": "局部的",
    "answer": "きょくぶてき",
    "meaning": "localized (pain, rainfall, etc.), local"
  },
  {
    "question": "波を切る",
    "answer": "なみをきる",
    "meaning": "to cut one's way through the waves"
  },
  {
    "question": "萌え出る",
    "answer": "もえでる",
    "meaning": "to sprout, to bud"
  },
  {
    "question": "献杯",
    "answer": "けんぱい",
    "meaning": "offering a drink"
  },
  {
    "question": "歌曲",
    "answer": "かきょく",
    "meaning": "melody, tune, song"
  },
  {
    "question": "躙り寄る",
    "answer": "にじりよる",
    "meaning": "to sidle up to"
  },
  {
    "question": "発火点",
    "answer": "はっかてん",
    "meaning": "point of ignition, flash point"
  },
  {
    "question": "地デジ",
    "answer": "ちデジ",
    "meaning": "terrestrial digital broadcasting"
  },
  {
    "question": "五徳",
    "answer": "ごとく",
    "meaning": "the five virtues, tripod, three or four-legged kettle stand, family crest in the shape of such an ob"
  },
  {
    "question": "行き道",
    "answer": "ゆきみち",
    "meaning": "route (when going somewhere), way (to get somewhere)"
  },
  {
    "question": "詩文",
    "answer": "しぶん",
    "meaning": "poetry and prose, literary works"
  },
  {
    "question": "賜り物",
    "answer": "たまわりもの",
    "meaning": "boon, gift"
  },
  {
    "question": "立体交差",
    "answer": "りったいこうさ",
    "meaning": "multi-level crossing"
  },
  {
    "question": "三十六計",
    "answer": "さんじゅうろっけい",
    "meaning": "the 36 (ancient Chinese military) strategies (of which the last resort was said to be beating a retr"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀粉",
    "answer": "ぎんぷん",
    "meaning": "silver powder, powdered silver"
  },
  {
    "question": "波線",
    "answer": "はせん,なみせん",
    "meaning": "wavy line"
  },
  {
    "question": "摺り",
    "answer": "すり",
    "meaning": "printing"
  },
  {
    "question": "大衆小説",
    "answer": "たいしゅうしょうせつ",
    "meaning": "novel for the masses, popular fiction, pulp"
  },
  {
    "question": "相通ずる",
    "answer": "あいつうずる",
    "meaning": "to be in common, to have in common, to be in mutually understood, to be mutually connected, to have"
  },
  {
    "question": "鈍麻",
    "answer": "どんま",
    "meaning": "torpor"
  },
  {
    "question": "小売",
    "answer": "こうり",
    "meaning": "retail"
  },
  {
    "question": "姓名判断",
    "answer": "せいめいはんだん",
    "meaning": "fortunetelling based on writing or pronunciation of one's name"
  },
  {
    "question": "手柄話",
    "answer": "てがらばなし",
    "meaning": "boastful story, big talk"
  },
  {
    "question": "教職課程",
    "answer": "きょうしょくかてい",
    "meaning": "teacher-training curriculum"
  },
  {
    "question": "立ち居",
    "answer": "たちい",
    "meaning": "movements, sitting and standing"
  },
  {
    "question": "嚆矢",
    "answer": "こうし",
    "meaning": "whistling arrow used to signal the start of battle, start (e.g. of a movement), beginning, dawn"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄み",
    "answer": "きみ",
    "meaning": "yellow, yellowish"
  },
  {
    "question": "実況見分",
    "answer": "じっきょうけんぶん",
    "meaning": "on-the-spot investigation"
  },
  {
    "question": "難曲",
    "answer": "なんきょく",
    "meaning": "difficult musical piece"
  },
  {
    "question": "生鮮",
    "answer": "せいせん",
    "meaning": "fresh"
  },
  {
    "question": "燃え滓",
    "answer": "もえかす",
    "meaning": "cinders"
  },
  {
    "question": "投ずる",
    "answer": "とうずる",
    "meaning": "to throw, to cast (e.g. vote, light, shadow), to devote oneself (e.g. to a cause), to invest, to put"
  },
  {
    "question": "女盛り",
    "answer": "おんなざかり",
    "meaning": "prime of womanhood"
  },
  {
    "question": "総合職",
    "answer": "そうごうしょく",
    "meaning": "regular position, position with a prospect of promotion"
  },
  {
    "question": "上意下達",
    "answer": "じょういかたつ,じょういげだつ",
    "meaning": "conveying the will of the governing to the governed, top-down (system)"
  },
  {
    "question": "超過勤務",
    "answer": "ちょうかきんむ",
    "meaning": "overtime (work)"
  },
  {
    "question": "折り詰め",
    "answer": "おりづめ",
    "meaning": "food packed in a wooden box"
  },
  {
    "question": "系統的",
    "answer": "けいとうてき",
    "meaning": "systematic"
  },
  {
    "question": "巧拙",
    "answer": "こうせつ",
    "meaning": "skill, workmanship, dexterity, quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "ムー大陸",
    "answer": "ムーたいりく",
    "meaning": "Mu (legendary lost continent)"
  },
  {
    "question": "誘い水",
    "answer": "さそいみず",
    "meaning": "pump priming, cause, impetus, spark, trigger, stimulus, incentive"
  },
  {
    "question": "根っ子",
    "answer": "ねっこ",
    "meaning": "root (of a plant), stump (of a tree), root (of a problem, etc.), base, foundation, origin, source"
  },
  {
    "question": "焚き付け",
    "answer": "たきつけ",
    "meaning": "kindling, firelighter"
  },
  {
    "question": "受け狙い",
    "answer": "うけねらい",
    "meaning": "aiming for laughs, trying to make people laugh, playing to the crowd, crowd-pleaser"
  },
  {
    "question": "六感",
    "answer": "ろっかん",
    "meaning": "the six senses"
  },
  {
    "question": "化合",
    "answer": "かごう",
    "meaning": "chemical combination"
  },
  {
    "question": "幾夜",
    "answer": "いくよ",
    "meaning": "number of nights"
  },
  {
    "question": "点と線",
    "answer": "てんとせん",
    "meaning": "points and lines"
  },
  {
    "question": "偽証罪",
    "answer": "ぎしょうざい",
    "meaning": "crime of perjury"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪玉",
    "answer": "あくだま,あくたま",
    "meaning": "bad character, bad person, villain, baddie"
  },
  {
    "question": "虫ピン",
    "answer": "むしピン",
    "meaning": "pin (esp. for mounting insects), setting pin"
  },
  {
    "question": "僧籍",
    "answer": "そうせき",
    "meaning": "priesthood"
  },
  {
    "question": "左巻き",
    "answer": "ひだりまき",
    "meaning": "counterclockwise, anti-clockwise, eccentric, abnormal"
  },
  {
    "question": "脳溢血",
    "answer": "のういっけつ",
    "meaning": "cerebral apoplexy"
  },
  {
    "question": "封建的",
    "answer": "ほうけんてき",
    "meaning": "feudal, feudalistic"
  },
  {
    "question": "誘因",
    "answer": "ゆういん",
    "meaning": "contributing cause, exciting cause, incentive, motive"
  },
  {
    "question": "押し倒し",
    "answer": "おしたおし",
    "meaning": "oshitaoshi, (frontal) push-down, (win by) knocking down opponent by pushing him with hand(s) rested"
  },
  {
    "question": "各駅",
    "answer": "かくえき",
    "meaning": "every station, local train, train that stops at every station"
  },
  {
    "question": "熱膨張",
    "answer": "ねつぼうちょう",
    "meaning": "thermal expansion"
  },
  {
    "question": "結晶構造",
    "answer": "けっしょうこうぞう",
    "meaning": "crystal structure, crystalline structure"
  },
  {
    "question": "伝染性",
    "answer": "でんせんせい",
    "meaning": "contagiousness"
  },
  {
    "question": "原題",
    "answer": "げんだい",
    "meaning": "original title"
  },
  {
    "question": "物臭い",
    "answer": "ものぐさい",
    "meaning": "troublesome, bothersome, burdensome"
  },
  {
    "question": "内耳",
    "answer": "ないじ",
    "meaning": "inner ear"
  },
  {
    "question": "マル暴",
    "answer": "マルぼう",
    "meaning": "yakuza group"
  },
  {
    "question": "引っ被る",
    "answer": "ひっかぶる",
    "meaning": "to take upon oneself, to pull (a thing) over one's head"
  },
  {
    "question": "鶏がら",
    "answer": "とりがら",
    "meaning": "chicken bones, chicken carcass"
  },
  {
    "question": "町名",
    "answer": "ちょうめい",
    "meaning": "name of a town or street"
  },
  {
    "question": "新味",
    "answer": "しんみ",
    "meaning": "fresh taste, novelty, originality, freshness"
  },
  {
    "question": "大岡裁き",
    "answer": "おおおかさばき",
    "meaning": "judicial decision made with human kindness and warmth in a fair manner (from the decisions of Ōoka T"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱ぎ着",
    "answer": "ぬぎき",
    "meaning": "undressing and dressing, taking off and putting on (clothes)"
  },
  {
    "question": "乱読",
    "answer": "らんどく",
    "meaning": "indiscriminate reading, unsystematic reading, desultory reading, reading at random"
  },
  {
    "question": "全曲",
    "answer": "ぜんきょく",
    "meaning": "all compositions, the entire composition"
  },
  {
    "question": "挙行",
    "answer": "きょこう",
    "meaning": "celebration (of ceremony), solemnization (e.g. of a marriage), solemnisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "回送",
    "answer": "かいそう",
    "meaning": "forwarding, sending on, redirecting (e.g. mail), deadheading (e.g. train)"
  },
  {
    "question": "末広がり",
    "answer": "すえひろがり",
    "meaning": "spreading out like an open fan, becoming prosperous, folding fan, ceremonial folding fan"
  },
  {
    "question": "騙し打ち",
    "answer": "だましうち",
    "meaning": "surprise attack, sneak attack, foul play"
  },
  {
    "question": "静止画像",
    "answer": "せいしがぞう",
    "meaning": "background image, static image"
  },
  {
    "question": "法る",
    "answer": "のっとる",
    "meaning": "to conform to, to be in accordance with, to follow (rule, tradition, example, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "間の手",
    "answer": "あいのて",
    "meaning": "interlude (in traditional Japanese music), chanting or clapping along (during a song or dance), inte"
  },
  {
    "question": "半ば過ぎ",
    "answer": "なかばすぎ",
    "meaning": "beyond the middle"
  },
  {
    "question": "三春",
    "answer": "さんしゅん",
    "meaning": "three spring months"
  },
  {
    "question": "下屋",
    "answer": "したや,げや,しもや",
    "meaning": "small attached annex, lean-to"
  },
  {
    "question": "引数",
    "answer": "ひきすう",
    "meaning": "argument (e.g. function, program, programme)"
  },
  {
    "question": "石蕗",
    "answer": "つわぶき",
    "meaning": "Japanese silverleaf (Farfugium japonicum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "中敷",
    "answer": "なかじき",
    "meaning": "insole, (shoe) insert, intermediate layer, rug, carpet"
  },
  {
    "question": "寨",
    "answer": "とりで",
    "meaning": "fort, fortress, stronghold, fortification"
  },
  {
    "question": "冬芽",
    "answer": "とうが",
    "meaning": "winter buds, winter sprouts"
  },
  {
    "question": "天柱",
    "answer": "てんちゅう,てんじ",
    "meaning": "pillars supporting heaven, tuning peg (on a biwa or shamisen)"
  },
  {
    "question": "御嶽",
    "answer": "うたき,みたけ",
    "meaning": "(Okinawa) sacred site, sacred grove, large, high mountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "清白",
    "answer": "すずしろ",
    "meaning": "daikon (variety of large white Oriental radish, Raphanus sativus var. longipinnatus) (primarily used"
  },
  {
    "question": "毘沙門",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "天網",
    "answer": "てんもう",
    "meaning": "heaven's vengeance, heaven's net"
  },
  {
    "question": "原虫",
    "answer": "げんちゅう",
    "meaning": "protozoan"
  },
  {
    "question": "愧死",
    "answer": "きし",
    "meaning": "dying of shame, being so ashamed one wants to die"
  },
  {
    "question": "六歌仙",
    "answer": "ろっかせん",
    "meaning": "six immortals of poetry, six notable Japanese poets whose poems were included in the anthology Kokin"
  },
  {
    "question": "浅見",
    "answer": "せんけん",
    "meaning": "shallow view, superficial idea"
  },
  {
    "question": "聚楽",
    "answer": "じゅらく",
    "meaning": "grey wall covering material (gray)"
  },
  {
    "question": "懐胎",
    "answer": "かいたい",
    "meaning": "conception, becoming pregnant, pregnancy"
  },
  {
    "question": "妖姫",
    "answer": "ようき",
    "meaning": "ghostly, beautiful woman, ghost of a beautiful woman"
  },
  {
    "question": "花水木",
    "answer": "はなみずき",
    "meaning": "flowering dogwood (Cornus florida)"
  },
  {
    "question": "大典",
    "answer": "たいてん",
    "meaning": "grand ceremony, state ceremony, important law, legal canon"
  },
  {
    "question": "飼主",
    "answer": "かいぬし",
    "meaning": "(pet) owner, keeper"
  },
  {
    "question": "全角",
    "answer": "ぜんかく",
    "meaning": "em, em quad (printing), full-width character"
  },
  {
    "question": "査閲",
    "answer": "さえつ",
    "meaning": "inspection, examination"
  },
  {
    "question": "法印",
    "answer": "ほういん",
    "meaning": "highest rank among priests, mountain ascetic monk, signs that distinguish Buddhist teachings from ot"
  },
  {
    "question": "秋水",
    "answer": "しゅうすい",
    "meaning": "clear autumn water, clear fall water"
  },
  {
    "question": "木管",
    "answer": "もっかん",
    "meaning": "wooden pipe, wooden bobbin, woodwind instrument"
  },
  {
    "question": "落穂",
    "answer": "おちぼ",
    "meaning": "fallen ears (of grain), gleanings"
  },
  {
    "question": "糀",
    "answer": "こうじ",
    "meaning": "kōji, malted rice, malt, malt-like material from growing mold on rice, barley, beans, etc. (used as"
  },
  {
    "question": "杜若",
    "answer": "かきつばた",
    "meaning": "rabbitear iris (Iris laevigata)"
  },
  {
    "question": "北洋",
    "answer": "ほくよう",
    "meaning": "northern waters"
  },
  {
    "question": "進士",
    "answer": "しんし,しんじ,しじ",
    "meaning": "palace examination (national Chinese civil servant examination based largely on classic literature),"
  },
  {
    "question": "全日制",
    "answer": "ぜんにちせい",
    "meaning": "the full-day (school system)"
  },
  {
    "question": "地侍",
    "answer": "じざむらい",
    "meaning": "provincial samurai in the middle ages, who engaged in agriculture in peacetime"
  },
  {
    "question": "回春",
    "answer": "かいしゅん",
    "meaning": "return of spring, rejuvenation"
  },
  {
    "question": "女工",
    "answer": "じょこう",
    "meaning": "female factory worker"
  },
  {
    "question": "淡青",
    "answer": "うすあお,たんせい",
    "meaning": "light blue, pale blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "屋敷町",
    "answer": "やしきまち",
    "meaning": "residential area"
  },
  {
    "question": "天成",
    "answer": "てんせい",
    "meaning": "(product of) nature, born (musician)"
  },
  {
    "question": "座頭",
    "answer": "ざがしら,ざとう",
    "meaning": "leader of a troupe, blind man, masseur (usu. blind)"
  },
  {
    "question": "書き味",
    "answer": "かきあじ",
    "meaning": "the feel or performance of a pen"
  },
  {
    "question": "受信料",
    "answer": "じゅしんりょう",
    "meaning": "(radio, TV) license fee, licence fee"
  },
  {
    "question": "兎の毛",
    "answer": "うのけ",
    "meaning": "just a hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "岩清水",
    "answer": "いわしみず",
    "meaning": "water trickling from rocks"
  },
  {
    "question": "折鶴",
    "answer": "おりづる",
    "meaning": "folded paper crane"
  },
  {
    "question": "帝国議会",
    "answer": "ていこくぎかい",
    "meaning": "Imperial Diet, legislative assembly of Japan (1889-1947), legislative assembly of the Holy Roman Emp"
  },
  {
    "question": "娼妓",
    "answer": "しょうぎ",
    "meaning": "prostitute, harlot"
  },
  {
    "question": "渡月橋",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "凡て",
    "answer": "すべて",
    "meaning": "everything, all, the whole, entirely, completely, wholly"
  },
  {
    "question": "鄭重",
    "answer": "ていちょう",
    "meaning": "polite, courteous, hospitable"
  },
  {
    "question": "神経科",
    "answer": "しんけいか",
    "meaning": "neurology"
  },
  {
    "question": "庫裏",
    "answer": "くり",
    "meaning": "temple kitchen, monastery kitchen, quarters of a head priest (and his family)"
  },
  {
    "question": "蹠",
    "answer": "あしうら,あなうら",
    "meaning": "sole of the foot"
  },
  {
    "question": "短篇",
    "answer": "たんぺん",
    "meaning": "short (e.g. story, film)"
  },
  {
    "question": "相場師",
    "answer": "そうばし",
    "meaning": "speculator"
  },
  {
    "question": "白地図",
    "answer": "はくちず",
    "meaning": "outline map, blank map, base map"
  },
  {
    "question": "日清戦争",
    "answer": "にっしんせんそう",
    "meaning": "First Sino-Japanese war (1894-1895)"
  },
  {
    "question": "獄吏",
    "answer": "ごくり",
    "meaning": "jailer, gaoler"
  },
  {
    "question": "標す",
    "answer": "しるす",
    "meaning": "to leave (a mark, trace, etc.), to print, to stamp, to be a sign of, to be an omen for"
  },
  {
    "question": "噺家",
    "answer": "はなしか",
    "meaning": "professional comic (rakugo) storyteller"
  },
  {
    "question": "地下足袋",
    "answer": "じかたび",
    "meaning": "work tabi, split-toed heavy cloth shoes with rubber soles"
  },
  {
    "question": "鷹匠",
    "answer": "たかじょう",
    "meaning": "falconer, hawker"
  },
  {
    "question": "楽人",
    "answer": "がくじん,うたまいのひと,らくじん",
    "meaning": "musician (esp. Gagaku), carefree person, person living at his ease"
  },
  {
    "question": "間話",
    "answer": "かんわ",
    "meaning": "quiet conversation, gossiping, idle talk"
  },
  {
    "question": "貧農",
    "answer": "ひんのう",
    "meaning": "poor farmer, needy peasant"
  },
  {
    "question": "民生委員",
    "answer": "みんせいいいん",
    "meaning": "district welfare officer"
  },
  {
    "question": "子袋",
    "answer": "こぶくろ",
    "meaning": "womb, uterus, pork or beef uterus, eaten grilled or raw"
  },
  {
    "question": "石窟",
    "answer": "せっくつ",
    "meaning": "cavern, grotto, rock cave"
  },
  {
    "question": "穹窿",
    "answer": "きゅうりゅう",
    "meaning": "vault of heaven, vaulted sky, dome, vault, arch"
  },
  {
    "question": "北限",
    "answer": "ほくげん",
    "meaning": "northern limit"
  },
  {
    "question": "月報",
    "answer": "げっぽう",
    "meaning": "monthly report"
  },
  {
    "question": "助教",
    "answer": "じょきょう",
    "meaning": "assistant professor"
  },
  {
    "question": "知行",
    "answer": "ちぎょう,ちこう",
    "meaning": "carrying out one's duties, ruling a fief, ruling a territory given by one's liege, territory given b"
  },
  {
    "question": "幔幕",
    "answer": "まんまく",
    "meaning": "curtain, drapery"
  },
  {
    "question": "泊地",
    "answer": "はくち",
    "meaning": "anchorage, berth"
  },
  {
    "question": "圧搾機",
    "answer": "あっさくき",
    "meaning": "compressor, press"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄粉",
    "answer": "てっぷん",
    "meaning": "iron powder"
  },
  {
    "question": "無反動砲",
    "answer": "むはんどうほう",
    "meaning": "recoilless rifle, recoilless gun"
  },
  {
    "question": "リンパ球",
    "answer": "リンパきゅう",
    "meaning": "lymphocyte"
  },
  {
    "question": "岩床",
    "answer": "がんしょう",
    "meaning": "bedrock"
  },
  {
    "question": "坑内",
    "answer": "こうない",
    "meaning": "within a pit or (mine) shaft"
  },
  {
    "question": "揺曳",
    "answer": "ようえい",
    "meaning": "flutter, linger"
  },
  {
    "question": "財務諸表",
    "answer": "ざいむしょひょう",
    "meaning": "financial statements"
  },
  {
    "question": "善がる",
    "answer": "よがる",
    "meaning": "to satisfy oneself, to feel satisfied, to be proud"
  },
  {
    "question": "煎り豆",
    "answer": "いりまめ",
    "meaning": "parched or roasted beans (or soybeans)"
  },
  {
    "question": "下降気流",
    "answer": "かこうきりゅう",
    "meaning": "downward air current"
  },
  {
    "question": "雨ガッパ",
    "answer": "あまガッパ",
    "meaning": "raincoat, oilcoat"
  },
  {
    "question": "干草",
    "answer": "ほしくさ,ほしぐさ",
    "meaning": "hay, dry grass"
  },
  {
    "question": "五平餅",
    "answer": "ごへいもち",
    "meaning": "skewered sweet rice cakes served with soy sauce and miso"
  },
  {
    "question": "身幅",
    "answer": "みはば",
    "meaning": "width of a garment"
  },
  {
    "question": "舞手",
    "answer": "まいて",
    "meaning": "dancer"
  },
  {
    "question": "一元",
    "answer": "いちげん",
    "meaning": "unitary"
  },
  {
    "question": "石見",
    "answer": "いわみ",
    "meaning": "Iwami (former province located in the west of present-day Shimane Prefecture)"
  },
  {
    "question": "決め球",
    "answer": "きめだま",
    "meaning": "winning pitch"
  },
  {
    "question": "六合",
    "answer": "りくごう",
    "meaning": "the universe, the cosmos"
  },
  {
    "question": "新道",
    "answer": "しんどう",
    "meaning": "new road"
  },
  {
    "question": "虚名",
    "answer": "きょめい",
    "meaning": "false reputation, empty title, empty name"
  },
  {
    "question": "漁民",
    "answer": "ぎょみん",
    "meaning": "fishermen"
  },
  {
    "question": "勢威",
    "answer": "せいい",
    "meaning": "force, power, influence"
  },
  {
    "question": "八面",
    "answer": "はちめん",
    "meaning": "eight faces, all sides"
  },
  {
    "question": "元禄",
    "answer": "げんろく",
    "meaning": "Genroku era (1688.9.30-1704.3.13)"
  },
  {
    "question": "焜炉",
    "answer": "こんろ",
    "meaning": "cooking stove, burner (gas, electric, etc.), range, cooktop, hob"
  },
  {
    "question": "上梓",
    "answer": "じょうし",
    "meaning": "publication, wood-block printing"
  },
  {
    "question": "河馬",
    "answer": "かば,かわうま",
    "meaning": "hippopotamus (Hippopotamus amphibius)"
  },
  {
    "question": "海山",
    "answer": "うみやま",
    "meaning": "sea and mountains"
  },
  {
    "question": "集光",
    "answer": "しゅうこう",
    "meaning": "concentration (of light, e.g. with lens or mirror), condensation, condensing"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹籠",
    "answer": "たけかご",
    "meaning": "bamboo basket"
  },
  {
    "question": "首班",
    "answer": "しゅはん",
    "meaning": "head, leader, prime minister"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷却剤",
    "answer": "れいきゃくざい",
    "meaning": "coolant, refrigerant"
  },
  {
    "question": "側頭葉",
    "answer": "そくとうよう",
    "meaning": "temporal lobe"
  },
  {
    "question": "閻魔帳",
    "answer": "えんまちょう",
    "meaning": "teacher's mark or grade book"
  },
  {
    "question": "大伯母",
    "answer": "おおおば",
    "meaning": "grandaunt, great-aunt"
  },
  {
    "question": "自切",
    "answer": "じせつ",
    "meaning": "autotomy, self amputation, act of cutting off a part of one's own body in order to escape a predator"
  },
  {
    "question": "嬌態",
    "answer": "きょうたい",
    "meaning": "coquetry"
  },
  {
    "question": "宣教",
    "answer": "せんきょう",
    "meaning": "religious mission, religious proclamation"
  },
  {
    "question": "千両",
    "answer": "せんりょう",
    "meaning": "Sarcandra glabra (species of flowering shrub in the family Chloranthaceae), 1000 ryō (an old Japanes"
  },
  {
    "question": "剛体",
    "answer": "ごうたい",
    "meaning": "rigid body"
  },
  {
    "question": "湯の花",
    "answer": "ゆのはな",
    "meaning": "hot-springs mineral deposits (resembling flowers), flowers of sulphur, geyserite"
  },
  {
    "question": "有情",
    "answer": "うじょう",
    "meaning": "sentient beings, humaneness, compassion"
  },
  {
    "question": "今次",
    "answer": "こんじ",
    "meaning": "the present time, new, recent"
  },
  {
    "question": "邪馬台国",
    "answer": "やまたいこく,やばたいこく",
    "meaning": "Yamataikoku, historical Japanese state thought to have existed during the late Yayoi period"
  },
  {
    "question": "高札",
    "answer": "こうさつ,たかふだ",
    "meaning": "official bulletin board (esp. Edo period), highest bid, highest tender, your letter"
  },
  {
    "question": "苗代",
    "answer": "なわしろ,なえしろ",
    "meaning": "rice nursery, bed for rice seedlings"
  },
  {
    "question": "粉飾決算",
    "answer": "ふんしょくけっさん",
    "meaning": "fraudulent accounting, window-dressing settlement of accounts, creative accounting"
  },
  {
    "question": "無差別級",
    "answer": "むさべつきゅう",
    "meaning": "open-weight (unclassified) division (category)"
  },
  {
    "question": "矩",
    "answer": "く,かね",
    "meaning": "quadrature, carpenter's square, perpendicularity, straightness, model, standard"
  },
  {
    "question": "高分子",
    "answer": "こうぶんし",
    "meaning": "macromolecule, high polymer"
  },
  {
    "question": "矢倉",
    "answer": "やぐら",
    "meaning": "turret, watchtower, high wooden stage, scaffolding, wooden frame (of a kotatsu), yagura, fortress, w"
  },
  {
    "question": "内服",
    "answer": "ないふく",
    "meaning": "internal use"
  },
  {
    "question": "豪毅",
    "answer": "ごうき",
    "meaning": "fortitude, firmness of character, hardihood, manliness"
  },
  {
    "question": "病原",
    "answer": "びょうげん",
    "meaning": "origin of an illness, cause of a disease, pathogenesis, etiology"
  },
  {
    "question": "支那",
    "answer": "しな",
    "meaning": "China"
  },
  {
    "question": "死海",
    "answer": "しかい",
    "meaning": "Dead Sea"
  },
  {
    "question": "臨界状態",
    "answer": "りんかいじょうたい",
    "meaning": "critical state"
  },
  {
    "question": "島嶼",
    "answer": "とうしょ",
    "meaning": "islands"
  },
  {
    "question": "不帰",
    "answer": "ふき",
    "meaning": "returning no more (usu. of a person who has died), dying"
  },
  {
    "question": "閉山",
    "answer": "へいざん",
    "meaning": "ending the climbing season, closure of a mountain to climbers, closing a mine, discontinuation of mi"
  },
  {
    "question": "桃源",
    "answer": "とうげん",
    "meaning": "earthly paradise, Shangri-la"
  },
  {
    "question": "抜錨",
    "answer": "ばつびょう",
    "meaning": "weighing anchor, setting sail"
  },
  {
    "question": "艦型",
    "answer": "かんけい",
    "meaning": "type of warship, model warship"
  },
  {
    "question": "大足",
    "answer": "おおあし",
    "meaning": "big feet, long stride"
  },
  {
    "question": "泡盛",
    "answer": "あわもり",
    "meaning": "awamori, strong Okinawan liquor distilled from rice or millet"
  },
  {
    "question": "背恰好",
    "answer": "せいかっこう,せかっこう",
    "meaning": "stature, height, size, physique"
  },
  {
    "question": "刃傷",
    "answer": "にんじょう",
    "meaning": "bloodshed"
  },
  {
    "question": "大日本",
    "answer": "おおやまと,だいにっぽん,だいにほん",
    "meaning": "Japan, Yamato (former province located in present-day Nara Prefecture), Great Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "婚外子",
    "answer": "こんがいし",
    "meaning": "child born out of wedlock, illegitimate child, love child"
  },
  {
    "question": "トルコ石",
    "answer": "トルコいし",
    "meaning": "turquoise"
  },
  {
    "question": "寸時",
    "answer": "すんじ",
    "meaning": "moment, very short time"
  },
  {
    "question": "炊爨",
    "answer": "すいさん",
    "meaning": "cooking (rice, grains)"
  },
  {
    "question": "癇癪玉",
    "answer": "かんしゃくだま",
    "meaning": "fit of anger, temper, rage, firecracker"
  },
  {
    "question": "無位無官",
    "answer": "むいむかん",
    "meaning": "having no special rank or title"
  },
  {
    "question": "親政",
    "answer": "しんせい",
    "meaning": "direct Imperial rule"
  },
  {
    "question": "方眼",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "人畜",
    "answer": "じんちく",
    "meaning": "men and animals"
  },
  {
    "question": "名城",
    "answer": "めいじょう",
    "meaning": "fine castle, famous castle"
  },
  {
    "question": "本所",
    "answer": "ほんしょ",
    "meaning": "main office, this office"
  },
  {
    "question": "下司",
    "answer": "げす",
    "meaning": "low-life, sleazebag, boor, person of humble rank, humble person, peasant, menial, churl, petty offic"
  },
  {
    "question": "機織",
    "answer": "はたおり",
    "meaning": "weaving, weaver"
  },
  {
    "question": "府内",
    "answer": "ふない",
    "meaning": "within the prefecture (of Kyoto or Osaka), within the town limits of Edo"
  },
  {
    "question": "拝観",
    "answer": "はいかん",
    "meaning": "see, inspect, visit"
  },
  {
    "question": "試聴",
    "answer": "しちょう",
    "meaning": "trial listening (e.g. to a record before buying), audition"
  },
  {
    "question": "延べる",
    "answer": "のべる",
    "meaning": "to lay out (a futon), to make (bed), to spread out, to stretch, to widen, to postpone, to extend"
  },
  {
    "question": "未見",
    "answer": "みけん",
    "meaning": "not yet seen, unseen, unacquainted, unknown"
  },
  {
    "question": "灯火管制",
    "answer": "とうかかんせい",
    "meaning": "blackout (to prevent being seen by enemy aircraft during a nighttime air raid)"
  },
  {
    "question": "急便",
    "answer": "きゅうびん",
    "meaning": "express dispatch, urgent correspondence"
  },
  {
    "question": "学用品",
    "answer": "がくようひん",
    "meaning": "school supplies"
  },
  {
    "question": "今上陛下",
    "answer": "きんじょうへいか",
    "meaning": "His Majesty the Emperor, the present emperor, the reigning emperor"
  },
  {
    "question": "抄",
    "answer": "しょう",
    "meaning": "excerpt, extract, annotation, shō (unit of volume, approx. 1.8 ml)"
  },
  {
    "question": "斎場",
    "answer": "さいじょう",
    "meaning": "funeral hall, ceremony site"
  },
  {
    "question": "斑紋",
    "answer": "はんもん",
    "meaning": "speckles, spotted pattern"
  },
  {
    "question": "世を渡る",
    "answer": "よをわたる",
    "meaning": "to make one's way in the world, to earn one's living, to live"
  },
  {
    "question": "流感",
    "answer": "りゅうかん",
    "meaning": "influenza, flu, cold"
  },
  {
    "question": "奔馬",
    "answer": "ほんば",
    "meaning": "runaway horse, galloping horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "客体",
    "answer": "きゃくたい,かくたい",
    "meaning": "object (philosophical)"
  },
  {
    "question": "手引き書",
    "answer": "てびきしょ",
    "meaning": "handbook, manual, guide, primer"
  },
  {
    "question": "挺身",
    "answer": "ていしん",
    "meaning": "volunteer, volunteering"
  },
  {
    "question": "大関",
    "answer": "おおぜき",
    "meaning": "ōzeki (second highest rank in sumo)"
  },
  {
    "question": "浄財",
    "answer": "じょうざい",
    "meaning": "monetary offering, donation"
  },
  {
    "question": "図示",
    "answer": "ずし",
    "meaning": "showing by a diagram, illustrating, representing graphically"
  },
  {
    "question": "日銀",
    "answer": "にちぎん",
    "meaning": "Bank of Japan, BOJ, BoJ"
  },
  {
    "question": "市民階級",
    "answer": "しみんかいきゅう",
    "meaning": "middle class, bourgeoisie"
  },
  {
    "question": "酬う",
    "answer": "むくう",
    "meaning": "to reward, to recompense, to repay, to retaliate, to get revenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "縛する",
    "answer": "ばくする",
    "meaning": "to bind, to restrain"
  },
  {
    "question": "主格",
    "answer": "しゅかく",
    "meaning": "nominative case"
  },
  {
    "question": "意を酌む",
    "answer": "いをくむ",
    "meaning": "to enter into a person's feelings, to guess what somebody feels (using one's intuition)"
  },
  {
    "question": "無警告",
    "answer": "むけいこく",
    "meaning": "without warning or notice"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀盤",
    "answer": "ぎんばん",
    "meaning": "skating rink, ice surface, silver plate"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄疸",
    "answer": "おうだん",
    "meaning": "jaundice, icterus"
  },
  {
    "question": "作劇",
    "answer": "さくげき",
    "meaning": "playwriting"
  },
  {
    "question": "大外",
    "answer": "おおそと",
    "meaning": "far out wide (horse racing), far outside"
  },
  {
    "question": "縺れ合う",
    "answer": "もつれあう",
    "meaning": "to get entangled (with each other), to get muddled together"
  },
  {
    "question": "血痰",
    "answer": "けったん",
    "meaning": "bloody phlegm"
  },
  {
    "question": "執行役員",
    "answer": "しっこうやくいん",
    "meaning": "operating officer, company executive"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤旗",
    "answer": "あかはた",
    "meaning": "red flag, Red Flag (Communist Party newspaper)"
  },
  {
    "question": "背水",
    "answer": "はいすい",
    "meaning": "backwater, standing with one's back to water (river, lake, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "内証",
    "answer": "ないしょ,ないしょう",
    "meaning": "secrecy, confidentiality, privacy, secret, one's circumstances (esp. fiscal), inner realization, per"
  },
  {
    "question": "餌付く",
    "answer": "えづく",
    "meaning": "to begin to eat or feed"
  },
  {
    "question": "生石灰",
    "answer": "せいせっかい",
    "meaning": "quick lime"
  },
  {
    "question": "補聴器",
    "answer": "ほちょうき",
    "meaning": "hearing aid"
  },
  {
    "question": "尊敬語",
    "answer": "そんけいご",
    "meaning": "honorific language"
  },
  {
    "question": "休館",
    "answer": "きゅうかん",
    "meaning": "closure (of a library, museum, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "娘子",
    "answer": "じょうし,むすめご",
    "meaning": "girl, young (unmarried) woman, (grown) woman, lady, (someone else's) wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "白熱電球",
    "answer": "はくねつでんきゅう",
    "meaning": "light bulb, incandescent light bulb"
  },
  {
    "question": "神権",
    "answer": "しんけん",
    "meaning": "divine right (e.g. of kings)"
  },
  {
    "question": "城郭都市",
    "answer": "じょうかくとし",
    "meaning": "fortified city, walled city"
  },
  {
    "question": "焼売",
    "answer": "しゅうまい",
    "meaning": "shumai, shaomai, steamed meat dumpling (Chinese-style)"
  },
  {
    "question": "相伝",
    "answer": "そうでん",
    "meaning": "inheritance"
  },
  {
    "question": "大学芋",
    "answer": "だいがくいも",
    "meaning": "candied sweet potato"
  },
  {
    "question": "涼をとる",
    "answer": "りょうをとる",
    "meaning": "to enjoy the cool breeze"
  },
  {
    "question": "梯子段",
    "answer": "はしごだん",
    "meaning": "step, stair, staircase"
  },
  {
    "question": "輸送量",
    "answer": "ゆそうりょう",
    "meaning": "traffic, volume or quantity of goods transported"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜の女",
    "answer": "よるのおんな",
    "meaning": "street prostitute, streetwalker, lady of the night"
  },
  {
    "question": "忘れん坊",
    "answer": "わすれんぼう",
    "meaning": "forgetful person"
  },
  {
    "question": "貴家",
    "answer": "きか",
    "meaning": "your home"
  },
  {
    "question": "六面体",
    "answer": "ろくめんたい",
    "meaning": "hexahedron"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛸の足",
    "answer": "たこのあし",
    "meaning": "Penthorum chinensis (species of saxifrage)"
  },
  {
    "question": "春巻",
    "answer": "はるまき",
    "meaning": "spring roll"
  },
  {
    "question": "脱法",
    "answer": "だっぽう",
    "meaning": "evasion of the law, circumvention of the law"
  },
  {
    "question": "脊",
    "answer": "せい,せ",
    "meaning": "height, stature, back, spine, reverse, rear side, ridge (of a mountain)"
  },
  {
    "question": "搔い摘む",
    "answer": "かいつまむ",
    "meaning": "to sum up, to summarize, to summarise"
  },
  {
    "question": "蛇頭",
    "answer": "じゃとう",
    "meaning": "snakeheads, Chinese criminal gangs, esp. for smuggling Chinese immigrants"
  },
  {
    "question": "柱石",
    "answer": "ちゅうせき",
    "meaning": "pillar, cornerstone"
  },
  {
    "question": "時の鐘",
    "answer": "ときのかね",
    "meaning": "hour bell"
  },
  {
    "question": "苦杯",
    "answer": "くはい",
    "meaning": "bitter experience (ordeal)"
  },
  {
    "question": "三冠王",
    "answer": "さんかんおう",
    "meaning": "winner of triple crown"
  },
  {
    "question": "鯰",
    "answer": "なまず",
    "meaning": "catfish (esp. the Amur catfish, Silurus asotus), earthquake"
  },
  {
    "question": "御神輿",
    "answer": "おみこし",
    "meaning": "portable shrine (carried in festivals), buttocks, lower back, waist, hips"
  },
  {
    "question": "滅茶滅茶",
    "answer": "めちゃめちゃ",
    "meaning": "disorderly, messy, ruined, absurd, unreasonable, excessive, rash, very, extremely"
  },
  {
    "question": "生糸",
    "answer": "きいと",
    "meaning": "raw silk thread"
  },
  {
    "question": "偽薬",
    "answer": "ぎやく",
    "meaning": "inactive placebo, placebo"
  },
  {
    "question": "包含",
    "answer": "ほうがん",
    "meaning": "inclusion, comprehension, implication, containing, covering"
  },
  {
    "question": "運指",
    "answer": "うんし",
    "meaning": "fingering (of a musical instrument)"
  },
  {
    "question": "一飛び",
    "answer": "ひととび",
    "meaning": "one jump, one flight, (at) once, (in) one stroke"
  },
  {
    "question": "箒星",
    "answer": "ほうきぼし",
    "meaning": "comet"
  },
  {
    "question": "呉服",
    "answer": "ごふく",
    "meaning": "cloth (for Japanese clothes), kimono fabrics, textile, drapery, dry goods, piece goods, silk fabrics"
  },
  {
    "question": "胸裏",
    "answer": "きょうり",
    "meaning": "one's heart, one's mind (feelings, bosom)"
  },
  {
    "question": "定位",
    "answer": "ていい",
    "meaning": "position, orientation"
  },
  {
    "question": "聴講生",
    "answer": "ちょうこうせい",
    "meaning": "auditor, auditing student"
  },
  {
    "question": "酎ハイ",
    "answer": "ちゅうハイ",
    "meaning": "shōchū highball, cocktail of shōchū with tonic water"
  },
  {
    "question": "電送",
    "answer": "でんそう",
    "meaning": "electronic transmission (of data)"
  },
  {
    "question": "懐炉",
    "answer": "かいろ",
    "meaning": "pocket heater, hand warmer, heater pack"
  },
  {
    "question": "狷介",
    "answer": "けんかい",
    "meaning": "obstinate, stubborn, headstrong, self-centred, self-centered"
  },
  {
    "question": "安逸",
    "answer": "あんいつ",
    "meaning": "(idle) ease, idleness, leisureliness"
  },
  {
    "question": "ゴム風船",
    "answer": "ゴムふうせん",
    "meaning": "rubber balloon"
  },
  {
    "question": "装画",
    "answer": "そうが",
    "meaning": "book-cover design, picture on the cover of a book"
  },
  {
    "question": "回転翼",
    "answer": "かいてんよく",
    "meaning": "rotary wing (aircraft), rotor"
  },
  {
    "question": "学界",
    "answer": "がっかい",
    "meaning": "academic world, academia, academic circles, scientific world, learned circles"
  },
  {
    "question": "減算",
    "answer": "げんざん",
    "meaning": "subtraction"
  },
  {
    "question": "逆玉の輿",
    "answer": "ぎゃくたまのこし",
    "meaning": "man marrying into wealth and power"
  },
  {
    "question": "液面",
    "answer": "えきめん",
    "meaning": "liquid surface"
  },
  {
    "question": "皮目",
    "answer": "ひもく,かわめ",
    "meaning": "lenticel, skin-side (of a fillet of fish)"
  },
  {
    "question": "重囲",
    "answer": "じゅうい,ちょうい",
    "meaning": "close siege"
  },
  {
    "question": "造血",
    "answer": "ぞうけつ",
    "meaning": "blood formation, blood making, hemopoiesis (haemopoiesis), hematosis (haematosis), hematopoiesis (ha"
  },
  {
    "question": "町家",
    "answer": "まちや,ちょうか",
    "meaning": "townhouse (i.e. house in the middle of a town), traditional townhouse, tradesman's house (esp. a hom"
  },
  {
    "question": "胚",
    "answer": "はい",
    "meaning": "embryo, germ (e.g. wheat germ)"
  },
  {
    "question": "私有財産",
    "answer": "しゆうざいさん",
    "meaning": "private property"
  },
  {
    "question": "二重瞼",
    "answer": "ふたえまぶた",
    "meaning": "double-edged eyelid"
  },
  {
    "question": "切込み",
    "answer": "きりこみ",
    "meaning": "cut, notch, raid, attack"
  },
  {
    "question": "和製英語",
    "answer": "わせいえいご",
    "meaning": "Japanese word constructed of elements from one or more English terms, pseudo-English word or phrase"
  },
  {
    "question": "模糊",
    "answer": "もこ",
    "meaning": "dim, vague, indistinct, faint, obscure"
  },
  {
    "question": "致傷",
    "answer": "ちしょう",
    "meaning": "inflicting injury (criminally)"
  },
  {
    "question": "細密画",
    "answer": "さいみつが",
    "meaning": "miniature"
  },
  {
    "question": "文民",
    "answer": "ぶんみん",
    "meaning": "civilian"
  },
  {
    "question": "熟視",
    "answer": "じゅくし",
    "meaning": "staring at, scrutinizing, scrutinising"
  },
  {
    "question": "水際立つ",
    "answer": "みずぎわだつ",
    "meaning": "to be splendid, to be superb"
  },
  {
    "question": "号する",
    "answer": "ごうする",
    "meaning": "to name, to take a second name or alias, to announce, to boast, to declare"
  },
  {
    "question": "欠席裁判",
    "answer": "けっせきさいばん",
    "meaning": "trial in absentia, judgment by default (judgement)"
  },
  {
    "question": "衆愚政治",
    "answer": "しゅうぐせいじ,しゅぐせいじ",
    "meaning": "mobocracy, mob rule, ochlocracy"
  },
  {
    "question": "一髪",
    "answer": "いっぱつ",
    "meaning": "hair, hair's breadth"
  },
  {
    "question": "上腕骨",
    "answer": "じょうわんこつ",
    "meaning": "humerus (upper bone in arm)"
  },
  {
    "question": "退色",
    "answer": "たいしょく",
    "meaning": "fading, faded colour, faded color"
  },
  {
    "question": "変態性欲",
    "answer": "へんたいせいよく",
    "meaning": "abnormal sexuality, sexual perversion"
  },
  {
    "question": "門派",
    "answer": "もんぱ",
    "meaning": "division of a religious sect, branch of a school"
  },
  {
    "question": "大腿筋",
    "answer": "だいたいきん",
    "meaning": "femoral muscle, thigh muscle"
  },
  {
    "question": "頭角",
    "answer": "とうかく",
    "meaning": "top of the head"
  },
  {
    "question": "職域",
    "answer": "しょくいき",
    "meaning": "range of one's work (occupation)"
  },
  {
    "question": "女形",
    "answer": "おんながた,おやま",
    "meaning": "onnagata, male actor in female kabuki roles"
  },
  {
    "question": "新装",
    "answer": "しんそう",
    "meaning": "redecoration, remodelling, remodeling, refurbishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛惜",
    "answer": "あいせき,あいじゃく",
    "meaning": "missing someone, loathing to part"
  },
  {
    "question": "演繹",
    "answer": "えんえき",
    "meaning": "deductive reasoning, deduction"
  },
  {
    "question": "騒乱罪",
    "answer": "そうらんざい",
    "meaning": "crime of rioting"
  },
  {
    "question": "被せ",
    "answer": "きせ",
    "meaning": "not folding on a stitch but placing the fold (2mm) deeper past the stitch, folding the excess back t"
  },
  {
    "question": "唐草",
    "answer": "からくさ",
    "meaning": "arabesque pattern, toothed medick (Medicago polymorpha)"
  },
  {
    "question": "公共放送",
    "answer": "こうきょうほうそう",
    "meaning": "public broadcasting (e.g. NHK, BBC)"
  },
  {
    "question": "共産",
    "answer": "きょうさん",
    "meaning": "communism, Communist Party"
  },
  {
    "question": "有効期間",
    "answer": "ゆうこうきかん",
    "meaning": "term of validity, period for which something is valid (e.g. ticket)"
  },
  {
    "question": "血豆",
    "answer": "ちまめ",
    "meaning": "blood blister"
  },
  {
    "question": "春季",
    "answer": "しゅんき",
    "meaning": "spring season"
  },
  {
    "question": "腰掛",
    "answer": "こしかけ",
    "meaning": "seat, bench, temporary job while looking for a better job or until one marries"
  },
  {
    "question": "推計",
    "answer": "すいけい",
    "meaning": "estimate, estimation"
  },
  {
    "question": "絵皿",
    "answer": "えざら",
    "meaning": "decorative plate, palette, pallet"
  },
  {
    "question": "囃",
    "answer": "はやし",
    "meaning": "accompaniment for traditional performances (noh, kabuki, etc.), orchestra, band"
  },
  {
    "question": "我意",
    "answer": "がい",
    "meaning": "self-will, obstinacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "分力",
    "answer": "ぶんりょく",
    "meaning": "component of force"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶巾",
    "answer": "ちゃきん",
    "meaning": "tea cloth, tea napkin"
  },
  {
    "question": "講話",
    "answer": "こうわ",
    "meaning": "lecture, discourse"
  },
  {
    "question": "抗生剤",
    "answer": "こうせいざい",
    "meaning": "antibiotic"
  },
  {
    "question": "手間隙",
    "answer": "てまひま",
    "meaning": "time and effort, trouble"
  },
  {
    "question": "男声",
    "answer": "だんせい",
    "meaning": "male voice"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇観",
    "answer": "きかん",
    "meaning": "wonderful sight"
  },
  {
    "question": "型押し",
    "answer": "かたおし",
    "meaning": "stamping, embossing, tooling (e.g. leather), sigillation"
  },
  {
    "question": "周章狼狽",
    "answer": "しゅうしょうろうばい",
    "meaning": "consternation, falling into a panic, fluster, confusion, dismay, discomfiture"
  },
  {
    "question": "土建",
    "answer": "どけん",
    "meaning": "civil engineering and construction, public works and construction"
  },
  {
    "question": "錦糸卵",
    "answer": "きんしたまご",
    "meaning": "thin omelette cut into strips"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹馬の友",
    "answer": "ちくばのとも",
    "meaning": "childhood friend, old playmate"
  },
  {
    "question": "滑降",
    "answer": "かっこう",
    "meaning": "descent (esp. in skiing), sliding down, downhill (skiing race)"
  },
  {
    "question": "旧作",
    "answer": "きゅうさく",
    "meaning": "old work, existing work"
  },
  {
    "question": "踏み石",
    "answer": "ふみいし",
    "meaning": "stepping stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "内部監査",
    "answer": "ないぶかんさ",
    "meaning": "internal audit"
  },
  {
    "question": "常飲",
    "answer": "じょういん",
    "meaning": "regular drinking, habitual drinking"
  },
  {
    "question": "所管",
    "answer": "しょかん",
    "meaning": "jurisdiction"
  },
  {
    "question": "郵便番号",
    "answer": "ゆうびんばんごう",
    "meaning": "postal code"
  },
  {
    "question": "傷病兵",
    "answer": "しょうびょうへい",
    "meaning": "sick and wounded soldiers"
  },
  {
    "question": "篤志家",
    "answer": "とくしか",
    "meaning": "charitable person, philanthropist, volunteer, supporter"
  },
  {
    "question": "父性愛",
    "answer": "ふせいあい",
    "meaning": "paternal love"
  },
  {
    "question": "吸水",
    "answer": "きゅうすい",
    "meaning": "water absorption"
  },
  {
    "question": "皮膚科",
    "answer": "ひふか",
    "meaning": "dermatology"
  },
  {
    "question": "嗅ぎ出す",
    "answer": "かぎだす",
    "meaning": "to scent out, to detect"
  },
  {
    "question": "捉まる",
    "answer": "つかまる",
    "meaning": "to be caught, to be arrested, to hold on to, to grasp, to find (e.g. proof), to get (e.g. a taxi), t"
  },
  {
    "question": "入れ子",
    "answer": "いれこ",
    "meaning": "nest (of boxes), nesting, concealed information, adopting a child after one's own has died, child ad"
  },
  {
    "question": "左官",
    "answer": "さかん,しゃかん",
    "meaning": "plasterer"
  },
  {
    "question": "後ろ前",
    "answer": "うしろまえ",
    "meaning": "backwards"
  },
  {
    "question": "清爽",
    "answer": "せいそう,かわらか",
    "meaning": "refreshing, neat, tidy, trim"
  },
  {
    "question": "三親等",
    "answer": "さんしんとう",
    "meaning": "kinsman of the third degree (of consanguinity)"
  },
  {
    "question": "言い切り",
    "answer": "いいきり",
    "meaning": "affirmation, declaration, assertion, end of sentence"
  },
  {
    "question": "痴呆症",
    "answer": "ちほうしょう",
    "meaning": "dementia"
  },
  {
    "question": "今カノ",
    "answer": "いまカノ",
    "meaning": "current girlfriend"
  },
  {
    "question": "絞首",
    "answer": "こうしゅ",
    "meaning": "hanging, strangling to death"
  },
  {
    "question": "楽天",
    "answer": "らくてん",
    "meaning": "optimism"
  },
  {
    "question": "カスピ海",
    "answer": "カスピかい",
    "meaning": "Caspian Sea"
  },
  {
    "question": "胆汁",
    "answer": "たんじゅう",
    "meaning": "bile, gall"
  },
  {
    "question": "地獄絵",
    "answer": "じごくえ",
    "meaning": "picture of Hell, painting representing Hell"
  },
  {
    "question": "扇情",
    "answer": "せんじょう",
    "meaning": "suggestiveness, sensationalism, stirring up strong emotions"
  },
  {
    "question": "漆器",
    "answer": "しっき",
    "meaning": "lacquer ware, lacquerware, lacquer work, lacquerwork"
  },
  {
    "question": "無精者",
    "answer": "ぶしょうもの",
    "meaning": "slouch, lazybones"
  },
  {
    "question": "起毛",
    "answer": "きもう",
    "meaning": "nap raising"
  },
  {
    "question": "羊皮",
    "answer": "ようひ",
    "meaning": "sheep skin, fleece, parchment"
  },
  {
    "question": "四角柱",
    "answer": "しかくちゅう",
    "meaning": "quadrangular prism"
  },
  {
    "question": "断交",
    "answer": "だんこう",
    "meaning": "breaking off relations (esp. between countries)"
  },
  {
    "question": "業態",
    "answer": "ぎょうたい",
    "meaning": "business conditions, business category, line of business"
  },
  {
    "question": "巨大地震",
    "answer": "きょだいじしん",
    "meaning": "massive earthquake, megaquake"
  },
  {
    "question": "内回り",
    "answer": "うちまわり",
    "meaning": "inner tracks or lanes, going around an inner circle, indoors"
  },
  {
    "question": "夏日",
    "answer": "かじつ,なつび",
    "meaning": "summer day, hot summer day, day on which the temperature reaches at least 25 degrees Celsius"
  },
  {
    "question": "捩じ切る",
    "answer": "ねじきる",
    "meaning": "to twist off"
  },
  {
    "question": "健康保険",
    "answer": "けんこうほけん",
    "meaning": "health insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "誤飲",
    "answer": "ごいん",
    "meaning": "accidental ingestion, swallowing something by mistake"
  },
  {
    "question": "世紀末的",
    "answer": "せいきまつてき",
    "meaning": "fin-de-siècle, decadent"
  },
  {
    "question": "遊撃手",
    "answer": "ゆうげきしゅ",
    "meaning": "shortstop, short"
  },
  {
    "question": "道交法",
    "answer": "どうこうほう",
    "meaning": "Road Traffic Act"
  },
  {
    "question": "膝の皿",
    "answer": "ひざのさら",
    "meaning": "kneecap"
  },
  {
    "question": "忘恩",
    "answer": "ぼうおん",
    "meaning": "ingratitude, thanklessness"
  },
  {
    "question": "さ行",
    "answer": "さぎょう",
    "meaning": "the 'sa' column of the Japanese syllabary table (sa, shi, su, se, so)"
  },
  {
    "question": "独擅場",
    "answer": "どくせんじょう",
    "meaning": "field in which one acts unchallenged, unrivaled sphere of activity (unrivalled), one's monopoly"
  },
  {
    "question": "三面記事",
    "answer": "さんめんきじ",
    "meaning": "human-interest article, page-three news, police news"
  },
  {
    "question": "篤実",
    "answer": "とくじつ",
    "meaning": "sincerity, faithfulness"
  },
  {
    "question": "理容師",
    "answer": "りようし",
    "meaning": "barber, hairdresser"
  },
  {
    "question": "立会",
    "answer": "たちあい",
    "meaning": "presence (e.g. of an observer), observation, observer, witness, trading session (at an exchange)"
  },
  {
    "question": "地場",
    "answer": "じば",
    "meaning": "locality, local area, local stock exchange, local dealer"
  },
  {
    "question": "灰緑色",
    "answer": "かいりょくしょく",
    "meaning": "greenish gray, greenish grey"
  },
  {
    "question": "身丈",
    "answer": "みたけ",
    "meaning": "length (of clothing)"
  },
  {
    "question": "朝な夕な",
    "answer": "あさなゆうな",
    "meaning": "morning and evening"
  },
  {
    "question": "合成繊維",
    "answer": "ごうせいせんい",
    "meaning": "synthetic fibre, synthetic fiber"
  },
  {
    "question": "明明後日",
    "answer": "しあさって,みょうみょうごにち",
    "meaning": "in three days' time, two days after tomorrow"
  },
  {
    "question": "献じる",
    "answer": "けんじる",
    "meaning": "to present, to offer, to dedicate"
  },
  {
    "question": "畏",
    "answer": "かしこ,かしく",
    "meaning": "yours sincerely, respectfully yours"
  },
  {
    "question": "車内灯",
    "answer": "しゃないとう",
    "meaning": "interior light (train, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "懇談",
    "answer": "こんだん",
    "meaning": "informal talk"
  },
  {
    "question": "絶え間",
    "answer": "たえま",
    "meaning": "interval, break, pause, intermission, gap (e.g. in the clouds), rift, cleft"
  },
  {
    "question": "住い",
    "answer": "すまい",
    "meaning": "dwelling, house, residence, address, living, life"
  },
  {
    "question": "通暁",
    "answer": "つうぎょう",
    "meaning": "well versed, thorough knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "仰向き",
    "answer": "あおむき",
    "meaning": "facing upward"
  },
  {
    "question": "恍ける",
    "answer": "とぼける",
    "meaning": "to play dumb, to feign ignorance, to play innocent, to have a blank facial expression, to play the f"
  },
  {
    "question": "拝察",
    "answer": "はいさつ",
    "meaning": "surmise, guess, inference"
  },
  {
    "question": "思慮分別",
    "answer": "しりょふんべつ",
    "meaning": "discreet and well-advised judgment, wise and mature judgment, making judgment with prudence"
  },
  {
    "question": "読み流す",
    "answer": "よみながす",
    "meaning": "to read smoothly, to skim"
  },
  {
    "question": "酒色",
    "answer": "しゅしょく",
    "meaning": "wine and women, sensual pleasures, dissipation"
  },
  {
    "question": "引き切る",
    "answer": "ひききる",
    "meaning": "to saw off, to interrupt, to suspend, to discontinue"
  },
  {
    "question": "食い溜め",
    "answer": "くいだめ",
    "meaning": "stuffing oneself with food, eating enough to go without food for some time"
  },
  {
    "question": "無沙汰",
    "answer": "ぶさた",
    "meaning": "not writing or contacting for a while, neglecting to write (call, visit, etc.), failing to write (ca"
  },
  {
    "question": "人受け",
    "answer": "ひとうけ",
    "meaning": "popularity"
  },
  {
    "question": "一足違い",
    "answer": "ひとあしちがい",
    "meaning": "barely miss (meeting someone, catching a train, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "空即是色",
    "answer": "くうそくぜしき",
    "meaning": "emptiness is form, illusion of the reality of matter"
  },
  {
    "question": "発祥地",
    "answer": "はっしょうち",
    "meaning": "cradle (of civilisation, civilization, etc.), birthplace"
  },
  {
    "question": "温帯",
    "answer": "おんたい",
    "meaning": "temperate zone"
  },
  {
    "question": "大意",
    "answer": "たいい",
    "meaning": "synopsis, precis, summary, gist, outline"
  },
  {
    "question": "不随",
    "answer": "ふずい",
    "meaning": "paralysis, palsy"
  },
  {
    "question": "憎憎しい",
    "answer": "にくにくしい",
    "meaning": "hateful, detestable, loathsome"
  },
  {
    "question": "水垢",
    "answer": "みずあか",
    "meaning": "(mineralogical) fur"
  },
  {
    "question": "性体験",
    "answer": "せいたいけん",
    "meaning": "sexual experience"
  },
  {
    "question": "背比べ",
    "answer": "せいくらべ,せくらべ",
    "meaning": "comparing heights, comparison of statures"
  },
  {
    "question": "胚芽",
    "answer": "はいが",
    "meaning": "germ (of a cereal, e.g. wheat, rice), embryo bud"
  },
  {
    "question": "居抜き",
    "answer": "いぬき",
    "meaning": "going concern, stocks and all, goods and furniture included"
  },
  {
    "question": "不束",
    "answer": "ふつつか",
    "meaning": "rude, inexperienced, stupid, incompetent"
  },
  {
    "question": "出世魚",
    "answer": "しゅっせうお",
    "meaning": "fish that are called by different names as they grow larger"
  },
  {
    "question": "小利口",
    "answer": "こりこう",
    "meaning": "clever, smart"
  },
  {
    "question": "手控える",
    "answer": "てびかえる",
    "meaning": "to hang (hold) back, to hold off, to refrain, to reduce or cut back on, to jot down a note"
  },
  {
    "question": "追い越し",
    "answer": "おいこし",
    "meaning": "passing, overtaking"
  },
  {
    "question": "音響効果",
    "answer": "おんきょうこうか",
    "meaning": "sound effects, acoustics"
  },
  {
    "question": "快便",
    "answer": "かいべん",
    "meaning": "(pleasantly smooth) defecation"
  },
  {
    "question": "小馬鹿",
    "answer": "こばか",
    "meaning": "fool, someone beneath one's contempt"
  },
  {
    "question": "旧交",
    "answer": "きゅうこう",
    "meaning": "old friendship"
  },
  {
    "question": "悪逆無道",
    "answer": "あくぎゃくむどう,あくぎゃくぶとう,あくぎゃくぶどう",
    "meaning": "treacherous, heinous, treasonous, atrocious"
  },
  {
    "question": "春眠",
    "answer": "しゅんみん",
    "meaning": "deep sleep, sleep soundly"
  },
  {
    "question": "一口乗る",
    "answer": "ひとくちのる",
    "meaning": "to join in, to have a share in, to get in on the act"
  },
  {
    "question": "魚の目",
    "answer": "うおのめ",
    "meaning": "corn (on one's foot)"
  },
  {
    "question": "下辺",
    "answer": "かへん",
    "meaning": "lower side (go, chess, othello board)"
  },
  {
    "question": "美技",
    "answer": "びぎ",
    "meaning": "excellent performance, fine play"
  },
  {
    "question": "納付",
    "answer": "のうふ",
    "meaning": "payment, supply"
  },
  {
    "question": "取り直し",
    "answer": "とりなおし",
    "meaning": "rematch (e.g. in sumo when the match is too close to decide)"
  },
  {
    "question": "曲がり道",
    "answer": "まがりみち",
    "meaning": "roundabout road, curving road"
  },
  {
    "question": "日割り",
    "answer": "ひわり",
    "meaning": "daily rate, (day-by-day) schedule, program"
  },
  {
    "question": "蓋開け",
    "answer": "ふたあけ",
    "meaning": "opening, beginning, commencement"
  },
  {
    "question": "講ずる",
    "answer": "こうずる",
    "meaning": "to take measures, to work out a plan, to lecture, to read aloud, to confer"
  },
  {
    "question": "焦げ付き",
    "answer": "こげつき",
    "meaning": "a bad debt"
  },
  {
    "question": "生年",
    "answer": "せいねん,しょうねん",
    "meaning": "year of a person's birth, number of years since one's birth, age"
  },
  {
    "question": "包容",
    "answer": "ほうよう",
    "meaning": "toleration, magnanimity, comprehension"
  },
  {
    "question": "気っ風",
    "answer": "きっぷ",
    "meaning": "character, disposition, spirit, temperament"
  },
  {
    "question": "流行り物",
    "answer": "はやりもの",
    "meaning": "fashionable thing, popular thing, craze"
  },
  {
    "question": "力合わせ",
    "answer": "ちからあわせ",
    "meaning": "test of strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "土となる",
    "answer": "つちとなる",
    "meaning": "to die, to become earth"
  },
  {
    "question": "猿知恵",
    "answer": "さるぢえ,さるじえ",
    "meaning": "shallow cunning, shallow cleverness"
  },
  {
    "question": "羽子",
    "answer": "はご",
    "meaning": "shuttlecock (in hanetsuki)"
  },
  {
    "question": "切絵",
    "answer": "きりえ",
    "meaning": "cutout, cutout picture, papercut art"
  },
  {
    "question": "副葬",
    "answer": "ふくそう",
    "meaning": "burying a dead person's personal belongings with the body"
  },
  {
    "question": "詩神",
    "answer": "ししん",
    "meaning": "the Muses, great poet"
  },
  {
    "question": "水船",
    "answer": "みずぶね",
    "meaning": "water trough, track pan, cistern, water tank, boat transporting water (esp. drinking water), water b"
  },
  {
    "question": "迦陵頻伽",
    "answer": "かりょうびんが",
    "meaning": "kalavinka, imaginary bird in paradise that sings sweet notes"
  },
  {
    "question": "青星",
    "answer": "あおぼし",
    "meaning": "Sirius (star in the constellation Canis Major), Alpha Canis Majoris, the Dog Star"
  },
  {
    "question": "石綿",
    "answer": "いしわた,せきめん",
    "meaning": "asbestos"
  },
  {
    "question": "一類",
    "answer": "いちるい",
    "meaning": "same kind, accomplices, companions"
  },
  {
    "question": "笹藪",
    "answer": "ささやぶ",
    "meaning": "thicket of bamboo grass"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄巾の乱",
    "answer": "こうきんのらん",
    "meaning": "Yellow Turban Rebellion (China, 184 CE)"
  },
  {
    "question": "綱手",
    "answer": "つなで",
    "meaning": "mooring rope"
  },
  {
    "question": "監査委員",
    "answer": "かんさいいん",
    "meaning": "supervisory auditor, member of inspection committee"
  },
  {
    "question": "本ちゃん",
    "answer": "ほんちゃん",
    "meaning": "performance, take, going before an audience or on-air, game, season, crucial moment, actual sexual i"
  },
  {
    "question": "駒鳥",
    "answer": "こまどり",
    "meaning": "Japanese robin (Erithacus akahige)"
  },
  {
    "question": "姥",
    "answer": "うば",
    "meaning": "elderly woman, noh mask of an old woman"
  },
  {
    "question": "毒麦",
    "answer": "どくむぎ",
    "meaning": "darnel (Lolium temulentum)"
  },
  {
    "question": "愚僧",
    "answer": "ぐそう",
    "meaning": "silly monk, foolish monk, I, me"
  },
  {
    "question": "佐々成政",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "会所",
    "answer": "かいしょ",
    "meaning": "meeting place, club"
  },
  {
    "question": "御璽",
    "answer": "ぎょじ",
    "meaning": "imperial seal, privy seal"
  },
  {
    "question": "愛子",
    "answer": "いとしご,まなご",
    "meaning": "beloved child, dear child"
  },
  {
    "question": "内府",
    "answer": "ないふ,だいふ",
    "meaning": "Minister of the Interior (669-1868 CE), Lord Keeper of the Privy Seal (1885-1945 CE)"
  },
  {
    "question": "天理",
    "answer": "てんり",
    "meaning": "natural laws, rule of heaven"
  },
  {
    "question": "仕着せ",
    "answer": "しきせ",
    "meaning": "livery, servant's clothes provided by employers"
  },
  {
    "question": "聖油",
    "answer": "せいゆ",
    "meaning": "holy oil"
  },
  {
    "question": "軻遇突智",
    "answer": "かぐつち",
    "meaning": "Kagutsuchi, fire deity who burned to death his mother Izanami during childbirth (and was therefore b"
  },
  {
    "question": "スレ主",
    "answer": "スレぬし",
    "meaning": "original poster (of a web-forum thread), OP, thread starter"
  },
  {
    "question": "鑓",
    "answer": "やり",
    "meaning": "spear, lance, javelin, jeering"
  },
  {
    "question": "司法官",
    "answer": "しほうかん",
    "meaning": "officer of the court"
  },
  {
    "question": "秣",
    "answer": "まぐさ,うまくさ",
    "meaning": "fodder"
  },
  {
    "question": "野砲",
    "answer": "やほう",
    "meaning": "field gun, field artillery"
  },
  {
    "question": "沿海州",
    "answer": "えんかいしゅう",
    "meaning": "(Russian) maritime provinces"
  },
  {
    "question": "永世中立",
    "answer": "えいせいちゅうりつ",
    "meaning": "permanent neutrality"
  },
  {
    "question": "笹原",
    "answer": "ささはら,ささわら",
    "meaning": "field of bamboo grass"
  },
  {
    "question": "原口",
    "answer": "げんこう",
    "meaning": "blastopore"
  },
  {
    "question": "同学",
    "answer": "どうがく",
    "meaning": "the same school"
  },
  {
    "question": "疽",
    "answer": "そ",
    "meaning": "type of carbuncle"
  },
  {
    "question": "人工血液",
    "answer": "じんこうけつえき",
    "meaning": "artificial blood"
  },
  {
    "question": "白虹",
    "answer": "はっこう",
    "meaning": "white rainbow"
  },
  {
    "question": "縦陣",
    "answer": "じゅうじん",
    "meaning": "column"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍票",
    "answer": "ぐんぴょう",
    "meaning": "military scrip"
  },
  {
    "question": "三宮",
    "answer": "さんぐう",
    "meaning": "Grand Empress Dowager, the Empress Dowager and the Empress Consort"
  },
  {
    "question": "鎗",
    "answer": "やり",
    "meaning": "spear, lance, javelin, jeering"
  },
  {
    "question": "国電",
    "answer": "こくでん",
    "meaning": "city electric train service operated by (former) Japanese National Railways"
  },
  {
    "question": "放射光",
    "answer": "ほうしゃこう",
    "meaning": "synchrotron radiation"
  },
  {
    "question": "高段",
    "answer": "こうだん",
    "meaning": "highly ranked"
  },
  {
    "question": "大法廷",
    "answer": "だいほうてい",
    "meaning": "full court, grand bench of the supreme court"
  },
  {
    "question": "金柑",
    "answer": "きんかん",
    "meaning": "kumquat (Fortunella spp.), cumquat"
  },
  {
    "question": "阿頼耶識",
    "answer": "あらやしき",
    "meaning": "alaya-vijnana (store consciousness, consciousness forming the base of all human existence)"
  },
  {
    "question": "長征",
    "answer": "ちょうせい",
    "meaning": "lengthy military expedition, the Long March (China, 1934-1936), Long March (series of Chinese launch"
  },
  {
    "question": "擂り鉢",
    "answer": "すりばち",
    "meaning": "(earthenware) mortar (for grinding)"
  },
  {
    "question": "灯籠流し",
    "answer": "とうろうながし",
    "meaning": "ceremony in which paper lanterns are floated down a river"
  },
  {
    "question": "州法",
    "answer": "しゅうほう",
    "meaning": "state law, state statute"
  },
  {
    "question": "独尊",
    "answer": "どくそん",
    "meaning": "self-conceit, vainglory"
  },
  {
    "question": "縦走",
    "answer": "じゅうそう",
    "meaning": "traversing, walking along the ridge of a mountain range, longitudinal"
  },
  {
    "question": "公営住宅",
    "answer": "こうえいじゅうたく",
    "meaning": "public housing"
  },
  {
    "question": "詭計",
    "answer": "きけい",
    "meaning": "tricks, wiles"
  },
  {
    "question": "鉄面",
    "answer": "かなめん,てつめん",
    "meaning": "iron mask (worn by samurai)"
  },
  {
    "question": "奥伝",
    "answer": "おくでん",
    "meaning": "esoteric"
  },
  {
    "question": "大徳",
    "answer": "だいとく,たいとく,だいとこ",
    "meaning": "great virtue, virtuous priest, priest, rich person"
  },
  {
    "question": "石切り場",
    "answer": "いしきりば",
    "meaning": "quarry, stone pit"
  },
  {
    "question": "村道",
    "answer": "そんどう",
    "meaning": "village road"
  },
  {
    "question": "国民学校",
    "answer": "こくみんがっこう",
    "meaning": "elementary school (in an educational system operated in Japan between 1941 and 1947)"
  },
  {
    "question": "財テク",
    "answer": "ざいテク",
    "meaning": "money management technique, zaitech"
  },
  {
    "question": "廃道",
    "answer": "はいどう",
    "meaning": "disused road, abandoned road"
  },
  {
    "question": "歩度",
    "answer": "ほど",
    "meaning": "one's walking pace"
  },
  {
    "question": "大同",
    "answer": "だいどう",
    "meaning": "largely the same, Daidō era (806.5.18-810.9.19)"
  },
  {
    "question": "腐朽",
    "answer": "ふきゅう",
    "meaning": "deterioration, rot"
  },
  {
    "question": "炒り豆",
    "answer": "いりまめ",
    "meaning": "parched or roasted beans (or soybeans)"
  },
  {
    "question": "颯と",
    "answer": "さっと",
    "meaning": "quickly (esp. actions), suddenly (esp. wind, rain, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "飯綱",
    "answer": "いづな,いいずな,いいづな",
    "meaning": "a type of fox spirit, least weasel (Mustela nivalis)"
  },
  {
    "question": "画帳",
    "answer": "がちょう",
    "meaning": "picture album"
  },
  {
    "question": "御前様",
    "answer": "おまえさま,ごぜんさま",
    "meaning": "you, person of high rank, nobleman, wife of a nobleman"
  },
  {
    "question": "営舎",
    "answer": "えいしゃ",
    "meaning": "barracks"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀輪",
    "answer": "ぎんりん",
    "meaning": "silver ring, bicycle wheel, bicycle"
  },
  {
    "question": "校旗",
    "answer": "こうき",
    "meaning": "school flag"
  },
  {
    "question": "寝屋",
    "answer": "ねや",
    "meaning": "bedroom (esp. one used by a married couple), sleeping quarters, inner room, room at the back of the"
  },
  {
    "question": "鑷子",
    "answer": "せっし,ちょうし,ぢょうし",
    "meaning": "tweezers (esp. in a medical or laboratory setting), forceps"
  },
  {
    "question": "心性",
    "answer": "しんせい",
    "meaning": "mind, disposition, nature"
  },
  {
    "question": "列聖",
    "answer": "れっせい",
    "meaning": "canonization, establishment of sainthood"
  },
  {
    "question": "血液製剤",
    "answer": "けつえきせいざい",
    "meaning": "blood products"
  },
  {
    "question": "陰キャラ",
    "answer": "いんキャラ",
    "meaning": "gloomy person"
  },
  {
    "question": "落研",
    "answer": "おちけん,らっけん",
    "meaning": "rakugo research society, rakugo research club"
  },
  {
    "question": "増資",
    "answer": "ぞうし",
    "meaning": "increase of capital"
  },
  {
    "question": "下総",
    "answer": "しもうさ",
    "meaning": "Shimōsa (former province located in parts of present-day Chiba, Ibaraki, Saitama and Tokyo prefectur"
  },
  {
    "question": "副編",
    "answer": "ふくへん",
    "meaning": "associate editor, deputy editor"
  },
  {
    "question": "修習",
    "answer": "しゅうしゅう",
    "meaning": "apprenticeship"
  },
  {
    "question": "秋桜",
    "answer": "あきざくら",
    "meaning": "common cosmos (Cosmos bipinnatus)"
  },
  {
    "question": "指人形",
    "answer": "ゆびにんぎょう",
    "meaning": "hand puppet, glove puppet"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀雪",
    "answer": "ぎんせつ",
    "meaning": "silver-glittering snow"
  },
  {
    "question": "銘刀",
    "answer": "めいとう",
    "meaning": "sword inscribed with the name of the swordsmith"
  },
  {
    "question": "演義",
    "answer": "えんぎ",
    "meaning": "popularization, simplification, explaining in simple language, adaptation of history for popular rea"
  },
  {
    "question": "博物誌",
    "answer": "はくぶつし",
    "meaning": "natural history"
  },
  {
    "question": "都電",
    "answer": "とでん",
    "meaning": "metropolitan tramway, tram operated by the metropolitan government (esp. Tokyo)"
  },
  {
    "question": "変速機",
    "answer": "へんそくき",
    "meaning": "transmission"
  },
  {
    "question": "石女",
    "answer": "うまずめ,せきじょ,しゃくにょ",
    "meaning": "barren woman, sterile woman, stone statue of a woman"
  },
  {
    "question": "海上封鎖",
    "answer": "かいじょうふうさ",
    "meaning": "sea blockade"
  },
  {
    "question": "建付け",
    "answer": "たてつけ",
    "meaning": "fitting (e.g. door, window), fit"
  },
  {
    "question": "奇祭",
    "answer": "きさい",
    "meaning": "strange festival, odd festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "文物",
    "answer": "ぶんぶつ",
    "meaning": "(the products of) culture or civilization (civilisation)"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷光",
    "answer": "れいこう",
    "meaning": "cold light, luminescence"
  },
  {
    "question": "鼻ピアス",
    "answer": "はなピアス",
    "meaning": "nose piercing, nose ring"
  },
  {
    "question": "貝合わせ",
    "answer": "かいあわせ",
    "meaning": "kai-awase, Heian period shell-matching game, Heian period shell comparison game, tribadism, tribbing"
  },
  {
    "question": "毒腺",
    "answer": "どくせん",
    "meaning": "venom gland, poison gland"
  },
  {
    "question": "夜想曲",
    "answer": "やそうきょく",
    "meaning": "nocturne"
  },
  {
    "question": "冷却器",
    "answer": "れいきゃくき",
    "meaning": "refrigerator, cooler, freezer, radiator (of a car)"
  },
  {
    "question": "組み討ち",
    "answer": "くみうち",
    "meaning": "grapple, scuffle, fight, defeating one's enemy on the battlefield"
  },
  {
    "question": "分速",
    "answer": "ふんそく",
    "meaning": "speed per minute"
  },
  {
    "question": "敗亡",
    "answer": "はいぼう",
    "meaning": "defeat (in battle)"
  },
  {
    "question": "新店",
    "answer": "しんみせ,しんてん",
    "meaning": "new store, newly-opened store"
  },
  {
    "question": "伴天連",
    "answer": "バテレン",
    "meaning": "padre, title for Portuguese Jesuits (in Japan in the 16th century), Christianity, Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "膣前庭",
    "answer": "ちつぜんてい",
    "meaning": "vaginal vestibule, vulvar vestibule"
  },
  {
    "question": "巻き藁",
    "answer": "まきわら",
    "meaning": "straw post for training sword strikes, karate punches and arrow hits"
  },
  {
    "question": "籤引き",
    "answer": "くじびき",
    "meaning": "lottery, drawn lot"
  },
  {
    "question": "中原",
    "answer": "ちゅうげん",
    "meaning": "middle of a field, middle of a country, field of contest"
  },
  {
    "question": "先物",
    "answer": "さきもの",
    "meaning": "futures"
  },
  {
    "question": "点前",
    "answer": "てまえ,たてまえ",
    "meaning": "tea-ceremony procedures"
  },
  {
    "question": "茶坊主",
    "answer": "ちゃぼうず",
    "meaning": "tea-server, flatterer, sycophant"
  },
  {
    "question": "須磨",
    "answer": "",
    "meaning": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "意想外",
    "answer": "いそうがい",
    "meaning": "unexpected, unsuspected"
  },
  {
    "question": "土人",
    "answer": "どじん",
    "meaning": "native, aboriginal"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤潮",
    "answer": "あかしお",
    "meaning": "red tide"
  },
  {
    "question": "大君",
    "answer": "たいくん,おおきみ,おおぎみ",
    "meaning": "liege lord, shogunate, emperor, king, prince"
  },
  {
    "question": "枢機",
    "answer": "すうき",
    "meaning": "important point, essential part, vital point, important state matters"
  },
  {
    "question": "球界",
    "answer": "きゅうかい",
    "meaning": "the baseball world"
  },
  {
    "question": "然し",
    "answer": "しかし",
    "meaning": "however, but"
  },
  {
    "question": "等等",
    "answer": "とうとう",
    "meaning": "etc., et cetera, and so on"
  },
  {
    "question": "雲梯",
    "answer": "うんてい",
    "meaning": "overhead ladder, horizontal ladder, monkey bars, yunti (scaling ladder used for escalade in ancient"
  },
  {
    "question": "燐火",
    "answer": "りんか",
    "meaning": "phosphorous light, ignis fatuus, will-o'-the-wisp"
  },
  {
    "question": "嘔気",
    "answer": "おうき",
    "meaning": "nausea"
  },
  {
    "question": "適職",
    "answer": "てきしょく",
    "meaning": "suitable occupation"
  },
  {
    "question": "氷床",
    "answer": "ひょうしょう",
    "meaning": "ice sheet"
  },
  {
    "question": "播種",
    "answer": "はしゅ",
    "meaning": "sowing, seeding, planting"
  },
  {
    "question": "銀砂",
    "answer": "ぎんしゃ,ぎんさ",
    "meaning": "silver powder, white sand"
  },
  {
    "question": "木賃宿",
    "answer": "きちんやど",
    "meaning": "cheap lodging house"
  },
  {
    "question": "経済封鎖",
    "answer": "けいざいふうさ",
    "meaning": "economic blockade, embargo"
  },
  {
    "question": "物性",
    "answer": "ぶっせい",
    "meaning": "physical properties, properties of matter, physicality"
  },
  {
    "question": "野猿",
    "answer": "やえん",
    "meaning": "wild monkey"
  },
  {
    "question": "総当り",
    "answer": "そうあたり",
    "meaning": "round robin, having no losing tickets (of a lottery), brute force (in cryptography), using all combi"
  },
  {
    "question": "仏法",
    "answer": "ぶっぽう,ふつほう",
    "meaning": "Buddhist teachings, Buddhism, French law"
  },
  {
    "question": "雛祭り",
    "answer": "ひなまつり",
    "meaning": "Hinamatsuri (March 3), Girls' Festival, Dolls' Festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "塵埃",
    "answer": "じんあい,ちりほこり",
    "meaning": "dust, dirt, dreary world, petty affairs of everyday life"
  },
  {
    "question": "哺乳",
    "answer": "ほにゅう",
    "meaning": "lactation, suckling, mammal"
  },
  {
    "question": "和毛",
    "answer": "にこげ",
    "meaning": "downy hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "主力艦",
    "answer": "しゅりょくかん",
    "meaning": "capital ship"
  },
  {
    "question": "軍備拡張",
    "answer": "ぐんびかくちょう",
    "meaning": "expansion of armaments"
  },
  {
    "question": "土壌汚染",
    "answer": "どじょうおせん",
    "meaning": "soil pollution"
  },
  {
    "question": "力戦",
    "answer": "りきせん",
    "meaning": "hard fighting"
  },
  {
    "question": "邦訳",
    "answer": "ほうやく",
    "meaning": "translation into Japanese"
  },
  {
    "question": "智者",
    "answer": "ちしゃ,ちさ",
    "meaning": "sage, wise man, wise person, man of wisdom, buddha, bodhisattva, enlightened priest"
  },
  {
    "question": "オタ芸",
    "answer": "オタげい",
    "meaning": "type of dancing and shouting performed by fans at concerts (usu. idol concerts)"
  },
  {
    "question": "卵生",
    "answer": "らんせい",
    "meaning": "oviparity, produced from eggs"
  },
  {
    "question": "鑑別",
    "answer": "かんべつ",
    "meaning": "discrimination, judgement, judgment, separation, sorting"
  },
  {
    "question": "上意",
    "answer": "じょうい",
    "meaning": "will or decree (esp. of shogun), emperor's wishes"
  },
  {
    "question": "部屋住み",
    "answer": "へやずみ",
    "meaning": "an adult-age eldest son who has yet to come into his inheritance, (a young adult still) living at ho"
  },
  {
    "question": "野良着",
    "answer": "のらぎ",
    "meaning": "clothes for doing farm work or working in fields"
  },
  {
    "question": "減り込む",
    "answer": "めりこむ",
    "meaning": "to sink (into), to cave in, to get stuck in"
  },
  {
    "question": "四辺形",
    "answer": "しへんけい",
    "meaning": "quadrilateral, quadrangle, tetragon"
  },
  {
    "question": "串刺",
    "answer": "くしざし",
    "meaning": "skewer, spit, skewering, impalement, running through (e.g. with spear), stabbing"
  },
  {
    "question": "撥条",
    "answer": "ばね,ぜんまい,はつじょう",
    "meaning": "spring (e.g. coil, leaf), mainspring, power spring"
  },
  {
    "question": "狭小",
    "answer": "きょうしょう",
    "meaning": "narrow, cramped, small-sized"
  },
  {
    "question": "皇統",
    "answer": "こうとう",
    "meaning": "the imperial line"
  },
  {
    "question": "養親",
    "answer": "ようしん",
    "meaning": "adopter, adopting parent or parents, adoptive parent or parents, foster parent or parents"
  },
  {
    "question": "三遊間",
    "answer": "さんゆうかん",
    "meaning": "the hole (between third and short), area between the third baseman and shortstop"
  },
  {
    "question": "逍遥",
    "answer": "しょうよう",
    "meaning": "ramble, saunter, walk, wander, stroll"
  },
  {
    "question": "木蔭",
    "answer": "こかげ",
    "meaning": "shade of tree, bower"
  },
  {
    "question": "宛ら",
    "answer": "さながら",
    "meaning": "just like"
  },
  {
    "question": "台場",
    "answer": "だいば",
    "meaning": "fort, battery"
  },
  {
    "question": "無声映画",
    "answer": "むせいえいが",
    "meaning": "silent movie"
  },
  {
    "question": "町角",
    "answer": "まちかど",
    "meaning": "street corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "革細工",
    "answer": "かわざいく",
    "meaning": "leathercraft, leatherwork"
  },
  {
    "question": "進行係",
    "answer": "しんこうがかり",
    "meaning": "program director, programme director, facilitator, steering committee (chair)"
  },
  {
    "question": "後裔",
    "answer": "こうえい",
    "meaning": "descendant, scion"
  },
  {
    "question": "無声",
    "answer": "むせい",
    "meaning": "voiceless, unvoiced, silent, noiseless"
  },
  {
    "question": "良港",
    "answer": "りょうこう",
    "meaning": "good harbor (harbour), fine harbor"
  },
  {
    "question": "朦々",
    "answer": "もうもう",
    "meaning": "dense (e.g. fog, dust, etc.), thick, vague (as in being unable to think clearly), dim"
  },
  {
    "question": "寄せ手",
    "answer": "よせて",
    "meaning": "attacking army"
  },
  {
    "question": "擬す",
    "answer": "ぎす",
    "meaning": "to imitate, to copy, to mimic, to enter someone as a candidate, to press (e.g. a weapon against some"
  },
  {
    "question": "茗荷",
    "answer": "みょうが",
    "meaning": "Japanese ginger (Zingiber mioga)"
  },
  {
    "question": "捻転",
    "answer": "ねんてん",
    "meaning": "twisting, torsion"
  },
  {
    "question": "浮動票",
    "answer": "ふどうひょう",
    "meaning": "swing vote"
  },
  {
    "question": "烏骨鶏",
    "answer": "うこっけい,うこつけい",
    "meaning": "silky fowl, silky"
  },
  {
    "question": "優先席",
    "answer": "ゆうせんせき",
    "meaning": "priority seat, courtesy seat, seat provided in trains, buses, etc. for the use of the disabled, youn"
  },
  {
    "question": "連取",
    "answer": "れんしゅ",
    "meaning": "scoring in succession (points, sets, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "酷烈",
    "answer": "こくれつ",
    "meaning": "severity"
  }
]}